come back and make a mess
and receive a black
okay
home myself but she really and and caleb bridges watching uh...
fear factor your factory or you got here and
uh... the thing that you know there are watching this something called the
submerged bug box well yes it's very
a emerged escape submerged bug box and it's very we're imagining somebody go
like don't going on fear factor me like yeah my greatest fear would probably be
escaping a submerged bug probably in a box full of bugs I'm finally that is
submerged and having to escape it with my partner from a different reality show
I'm fine with it but as long as they're not submerged or in a box yeah I mean I
like bugs I like box any okay I'm being submerged I'm fine with being in a bug
box and I'm fine with having to escape but all three at the same time I'm about
have to have a fear factor you're making me into a fear factory thinking about
this year a bug bag that's fine yeah a bug I'm in those all day I'll take a bug
bath right now I won't escape I got lost in a bug bog I say that was a girl I was
stuck in a big box that's fine I can breathe in there it's huge a bug
restroom yeah whatever a bug a bug restroom a bug parlor yeah I got a bug
the grass room. They got a rest room for bugs. I was just backstage a
little, but they have a restroom now there's these restrooms get so
complicated. They have one for box
the one there's a women's a man's and a rest room and it's small. It's on
the ground. Other bugs went on the floor.
You walk out. I hope I peek my head and it's just a floor.
There's not even a tiny toilet in there. I mean I'm terrified of a bug
box, but a candy store. Yeah, that'll be fine with me. That's fine with me as long
as it's not a bug store or a candy box or a bug box or a bug in candy or a candy.
You try to get me to eat a scorpion lollipop. I'll smack you. Hell no. We're
gonna make you do these lollipops with scorpions in them. They put a scorpion in
a lollipop. This next this next contest is his next fear factor. Fear is escaping
a submerged bug box. Did you say staying in a beautiful candy room? I think he
I said staying in a most beautiful candy room.
- Well that's what I said too,
is like yeah, you go in a fear factory and you're like,
you know, in case you guys are still developing any talent,
is my greatest fear would probably be
eating the best hamburger ever.
- Oh, I'd hate it.
- With extra mayo.
(gagging)
- I'm so scared of mayo.
- You know what I'm afraid of?
- What? - Bottomless fries.
- Yeah.
- Where do they end?
(laughing)
- I'm afraid I'm gonna put my hand in
and it's not gonna come back.
- That's right, I'm afraid someone's gonna reach out
of the bottomless fries.
- That would be a good fear challenge,
to fall in a bottomless at red robin yeah, that's a have a giant like
spawning pit filled with fries in the big bubbling like like yeah, there's
like fog. There's like which is like stirring it with big with big sticks.
That's the thing about
fries and fries
guys fries fries fries and fries salt and pepper on the fries salt and pepper
small medium and large fries we will make some large fries small medium and large
fries eat too many you will be a large guy fries and fries that's kind of
terrifying yeah yeah there's not a lot of witches or like Frank why are we
making that soup hmm yeah I got a I got a surprise for you guys what what's the
new thing I got you guys windscreens oh my god we can power in yo give me the
red thingy okay I like the blue cuz blues max in my favorite color yo
here you go thanks new thingy do we hot swap them thank you let's do it Wow
no if it's trust me trust me I got the yellow one dude we're like Power Rangers
Dino Thunder right now red yellow and blue Wow yeah for fries from the diner
there we go yeah this feels amazing a piece of shit it's a bad one yeah oh my
god look at us look at us look at us fries fries fries fries back to it boys
tons of lies to it literally tons of fries go to your thighs fries and fries
and fries and fries you know fries the prize sauces dipping
fries are dripping garlic parmesan and crusted these boiling fries to us they
trusted fries and fries fries fries fries straight and curly stirring stick make
fries go swirly yeah do they need to have a fry which is basically a point of show
at this point oil and salt oil and salt fries fries oil and salt vinegar malt
yep yeah yeah it's pretty much a classic which down in the Disney boy
kind of just a loop back as the other twin bug box fries and Jerry's yeah you
can just do that for an hour it could be the perfect episode that could be this
could be the greatest episode ever this is our Thanksgiving episode this is our
Thanksgiving no our Thanksgiving episode comes out tomorrow that we already
recorded. Oh God. But for everyone else that already came out. Yeah. We really... So if
you see an episode with Gavin Matz that's our Thanksgiving treat. Yep. This one's
our Black Friday episode. Yeah. What are the deals we're looking for? Oh my God. Wait, wait, wait.
Let's do a shopping zone. What kind of deals are we looking for? Yeah. Bugs. Do you think there's any deals on Friday? Seinfeld box set.
that I'd build submerged bug box.
That's right, it's too easy on the best show in the world.
In like a see through box with like live water yeah and you have to escape the
DVD from it. They like fucked up the licensing and accidentally sold the like
DVD distribution rights to like some company in like Japan or something and
they're just like yeah. What if we put they don't know? Yeah, they think he's
the host of fear factor. They watched one sing they watch one. They watch his
bug restroom bit and they were like he likes he must like bugs or something.
We'll do a bug themed box. A submerged bug box theme box. Yeah, it's got the
Kramer Mantis box-themed box what uh what is what would be your guys George cuz
spider I'm not gonna give you anything that was nothing I know why did you go
because it's like bad George and stanza okay
Costanza Costanza come on you were almost there fucking hell you're so
close you know fucking oh fucking hell mate what about instead of Kramer's
name is Kramer. He's made of cream. See, that's pretty good. I thought Kramer
Mantis was good. Kramer Mantis is not bad. Like a cramming mantis? Yeah.
Kramer does sound a lot like a cramming mantis. Yeah.
Yeah. Are we going to acknowledge the extremely comfortable one in the room?
No. Yeah, not. I'm wearing a blanket. Yeah, not. Yeah, I've been getting into wearing all
black again yeah yeah my darkness era you're not dark at all are you kidding
me I had the the black jacket and the pants you don't know anything on you
don't know shit about a long time I know a lot about you don't know anything
about gloom I don't you're a gloomless fucking whoa yeah I don't look gloomy
when I'm in my in all black though you're right yeah you look like you're
you look like a theater actor. You look like a black box theater actor.
Anytime you were all black. Yeah. It looks like the only reason you're doing it is
so you can better embody different characters. You're doing
dramatic improv. Yeah. Non-comedic improv in a black box theater. Can I get a
suggestion for a trauma please? That's what you're saying to the audience. Yeah.
Yeah. And one of them is saying, "Submerged black box and it's Jerry Seinfeld and he's eating fries."
that's hard to be dramatic in that way like that'd be an easy cause a layup of a
comedy I know but a dramatic if you if you play it well I mean it could take you
to the top all these bugs oh these bugs are touching my penis oh I felt a bug in
my ass you know in that episode factor so it was one of the women the first
couple women wore wetsuits yeah in the bug box they're covered like bugs and
worms like yeah that's what you should do and then the next woman bikini why would
you choose bikini yeah clearly if you're are if people are wearing a wetsuit you
have a choice maybe get style points she had style points for me for having
huge ease yeah yeah big huge ease okay she was on American Idol previously she
was and then she showed her huge ease on beer fact who was it she showed her huge
ease to a bug or two I think her name was coolest huge ease coolest huge ease yeah
I don't remember. She's a jazz musician. Oh, okay. Yeah, Coolest Hugies. Is that the same season as
like Sanjaya and Constantine or Daughtry? Yeah, it was the Daughtry season. It was the Daughtry
season? Her name was Coolest Hugies. Coolest Hugies. Oh, yeah, she got out like first round.
Coolest Hugies Humongous. Yeah, Coolest Hugies and she sang, what's that song? Check these Hugies
out. I'm going to show them on TV. My Humps. My Hugies. My Hugies. Yeah, she did her own stylistic
thing yeah my house well that was weird was all those huge ease all those huge
ease with your boobies yeah I'm gonna be at them on some bugs
she's got big huge and getting huge huge she's got two huge she's got three -
she's got two and about a thousand bugs yeah she's got 1 million buggies
robbings. One, two, you squeeze the Hughies, Hughies in the bug box underwater.
She has to escape her Hughies first.
From the bug box.
Bugs on him, bugs on me.
I don't know if those things are Hughies.
I ain't got no Hughies or family tree, but I'm the one who wants to see those
Hugh Jeeves please. I'm the one who wants to see those Hugh Jeeves please. So if you want
to take your Hugh Jeeves and show them to me, please do. I will see your Hugh Jeeves on
my birthday. It's my birthday right now by the way. Show the Hugh Jeeves now. We're both
in the bug box also. We're still in there. Yeah, but I think Hugh Jeeves is going to
be the new tatas yeah yeah pretty good save the huge ease yeah pink ribbon say
you get it it's kind of close to huggies huge ease I'd like to hug ease some huge
ease you want to wear huge ease like a diaper and shit and piss in them that's
what you even work logistically they're huge ease man they have a
stretch ability factor you can tie the time in a knot time in a time to and fro
they go to and from of your shoulder
it's just a truth do you change my mims dude was that mims no mims was a mims
James was, this is why I'm not--
- Oh, you're right.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I don't remember who Chain Hang Low was.
- Chain Hang Low.
- You know who was always my favorite was Hurricane Chris.
- Oh, A-B-B.
- Hand clap, A-B-B, drop it, give me 50 with Mike Jones.
And then he went to jail for murder.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, dude.
- There was a, there's like a YouTuber I watched
that did a Hurricane Chris parody video.
- That's it.
- And I didn't realize 'til like a year ago
that he's in like full body blackface.
- Really?
- Yeah, full, he's in full--
- Wow. - He's in black body.
- Black body? - Whoa.
- Chocolate body, dude?
- Dude, it's literally like,
he looks like the chocolate man
from the Axe Body Spray Commercials.
- Looks like he's about to perform
in a bodybuilding competition.
- But Hurricane Chris watched,
there's a video of Hurricane Chris watching the video,
and he likes it.
- Really? - Yeah.
- That's cool. - Good for him, dude.
- I don't know if that's-- - It's all good fun
for Chris, dude. - Yeah.
- He doesn't care.
- But yeah, it was very jarring to see.
- Everybody pretty much did black face until 2009.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Dude, fucking Bo Selecta.
I don't know what that is.
You know what that is? Oh, well, Bo Selecta.
Nobody knows what that is. It's a British thing.
Yep. Yeah. Yeah. Leo will know.
It's a British TV show.
They still are doing it. They don't have...
Well, dude, he does like prosthetics that are like crazy looking.
Well, dates work differently over there, so they're still in like 2003 or whatever.
Yeah, true. They're in the year 11 right now.
It's because, yeah, it's because of the fucking way they order dates.
That's what I said. Yeah. Dates work differently.
Fuck, I fucked up. God damn it.
the
does both selected. But if you do, put me in your will first. Yeah. What could you give
me in your will? Maybe a guitar. Really? Yeah, I could give you a guitar and then Cameron
gets maybe one of my skateboards. Can I have your computer? Okay, I guess. Can I play on
your computer if you die? In my will, you get 36 hours of time on my computer. Per week
make her forever forever what forever yeah you got it you got to choose that
she here that's I'm getting a lawyer who can read that as a loophole it says I
get to use this computer forever. I'm getting some white out and I'm changing
your will yeah
yeah and my bones will
I bequeath on you all of my bones to be used for Halloween at your house. That
would be sick. That's honestly worth it. Absolutely. I don't give a fuck if I get
buried. Just take have I wouldn't want to get buried, have them strip all my meat
off yeah, beat him to a dog and getting creamed to be cooler than getting
buried. Anyway, there's got to be a way because
because you permanently haunt your family. If you get buried, you're in a
your go to a cemetery. They have like you see you every once in a while.
They'll forget about you. They don't care, but if you cremate it, you're
literally in their house constantly and they have to remember that you're there
all the time, unless they try and scatter you in the ocean or something
those freak families do who disrespect their dead relatives.
The thing is, I don't want to be cremated, honestly.
Yeah.
Because I want to still, I want there to be, if they come up with a reanimating technology,
I want to be, you know, a pretty good candidate.
Yeah, first one.
Well, I'd rather not get cremated either.
I'd rather just be alive.
There's got to be a way.
True.
I'd rather never die.
Yeah.
I feel like by the time we're old, there might be a never die thing.
There's got to be a way in the cremation oven.
Like maybe it's just like the amount of time you put them in, but I want to like, I want
my body to be cooked like a pizza.
- Yeah. - Like I wanna be,
like I wanna be taken out of the cremation oven
and I'm like roasted like a pig.
- Yeah. - Crispy skin.
And anyone can eat me.
- Yeah, anyone?
- Anyone can eat me.
It's a big feast of my dead body.
- You wanna be a feast of your body.
- Yeah.
- See, I wouldn't even know where to start on a person.
- I know where to start.
- What's the deal with these cremated Patrick's nowadays?
- What do you start on, the leg?
It's gotta be a leg, right?
- Yeah, I'm probably the leg.
I mean there you know there's one guy who's gonna go for the face right away
like the guy who takes the candy out of the middle of a birthday cake yeah yeah
wonder what a grilled eyeball would taste like probably like I saw I saw like a
like a picture of like an eyeball that got a cut on it and then they put
stitches on the eyeball yeah dude that's the worst shit I can't watch that video
of that lambs eyeball being sliced with the razor yeah okay oh yeah from the
shit that sucks. Eyeball stuff is the worst. Yeah, I like my eyeballs. Me too. I love my
eyeballs. I have beautiful brown eyes. There's no such thing as beautiful brown eyes. I do.
Not on a man. You have stinky poo eyes. I have the most beautiful eyes in the world.
Your eyes are just, they might as well be nothing. I have piercing red eyes. Watch this.
That's your face that you're doing. Whenever someone has brown eyes, I just, in my brain,
I can't remember what color their eyes are because my brain just like ignores it. Yeah,
are
really gonna get a kick out of it. I'm not allowed back there. Really? Did you try, did
you use all the time? No, I went in the back and I was laughing so hard. It's funny as
hell back there. Dude, oh my god, they have a nurse's outfit and like... Holy crap. Things
that a guy puts in his butt. Like what? Like a, it's a cylinder. Yeah. That a man puts in
his butt. Well he's probably trying to, trying to do some, trying to build a potato gun and
he just slips on the PVC pipe. No, it's a thing and it's... Or he's like on, he's on
roller skates. I can't imagine why I would answer this. He's on roller skates and his pants falls down and he trips over them and he flies onto a railing. It's balls on a
string. Balls on a string? A man puts in his butt. Hold on. Balls on a string? Well this has to be some kind of... I got balls on a string. You know what, he must be doing...
he must be doing some kind of Mardi Gras thing where he's trying to throw the
beads to a woman's ear and then he puts them in his butt.
But they accidentally, he's really strong, he's in the MLB.
Oh well he's doing Manny Ramirez and he throws it so hard.
He's doing softball windmill pitch.
And it accidentally catches another woman who's behind him, her vagina, and it flies
off, ricochets off, she's had surgery, into his butt.
That must be it.
That must be the point of those.
Yeah.
I mean I don't understand why anything would ever enter a man's ass.
Me neither.
Unless you're cleaning it with shampoo and you're 15.
Yeah.
And it feels funny.
Unless it's a GoPro.
The thing is, I put my finger in my ass.
It's like you get, I feel, I get why you would like it, but that's because I like pooping.
You know?
Like I really love to poop.
Like pooping is like one of my...
It just doesn't interest me.
(laughing)
- I put my finger up there before, I'm just not gripped.
- It just, it never caught me.
- I've done a lot more fascinating things in my life,
it's just nothing, it's not for me.
- Just never.
- I just don't find it interesting.
- Never stimulated my brain much.
- No, it just never clicks.
- I think it's supposed to stimulate something else in there.
- Yeah, it stimulates my I love poop neurons,
which like, I'll sit on the toilet,
I wish, honestly, I wish I could just poop all day.
- Oh dude, I gotta stop sitting on the toilet
for a long time. - I love pooping.
A really good poop though,
like one that's just like thick and really you feel it,
that's a good feeling.
- My stomach, my poop's been messed up lately.
I've been really constipated.
- I gotta hand you one of these.
- When I was at Disney World, I rode the Tower of Terror
and it felt like the poop brick in my stomach
was gonna fly out of my mouth.
- That would've been kind of funny.
- That'd be cool.
Just get rid of it all in one fell swoop.
- It would be funny to throw up a poop log.
- It would be funny to get--
I feel like that's the way that's like the the physically that's the way it
would happen to right a sudden drop yeah and it just it just inertia just it just
flies out as it came out it goes out the damn window yeah it's some kid places the
hot dog and a kid's hot dog but it's there right as you eat your crap and see
Oh hell no. Oh hell no. That ain't gonna happen. Not on my watch. No. It actually derailed the
Aerosmith ride and killed 50 people. Come on dude. Oh no. I don't wanna hear about that.
You know I read today I was reading about those remember those Thai kids that got trapped
in that there cave? Oh yeah. That was a pretty funny story. Yeah. I just thought it was funny.
I was reading about it I was like they never explain why they went into the cave. Yeah.
once like I was reading the entire Wikipedia page.
General spelunking.
And it was just like no they were not wearing spelunking anything.
They were just like, they had just won a soccer match.
And they were like, let's go into the cave.
It's raining, let's go into the cave.
That's so funny.
Yeah, let's go very deep.
Let's go really far.
Let's go miles into this cave right now.
Oh what's that?
A very small passage that we can barely squeeze through?
Probably fine.
Let's go in there.
we just want our soccer game we're on top of the world yet we can survive a week
ago
but i don't want that bill you know we can get out of any case
yeah there's not a word that would work for the civil war
yeah i'm gonna get out fifteen days later because we're seeing what is the
cave other than just a goal
you know
they were that's the truth they're trying to find the end of the goal yes
i find the goalie
yet maybe a soccer ball in the case
uh... chasing after it when i was in my own into the cave for sloping downward
true yeah and they didn't have another soccer ball what it okay what if there's
like the ultimate trophy in there oh yeah true kind of a rumple sportskin yeah
creature that is oh dude imagine a rumple sportskin rumple pigskin dude
rumple pigskin yeah he can grant you any sports wishes yeah he sounds like John
Madden yeah yeah all right can I grant you any wish any wish at all
Any wish you want and I could...
Sports related wishes.
Any sports wish at all.
Any wish.
Because they were like, "Can we get out of this cave?"
And he's like, "No, strictly sports."
No way.
No.
Maybe, okay, well, what's the thing?
What if they weren't a soccer team before they went into the cave and they said like,
"All right, well, fine.
We want to be like the winners of the soccer tournament."
We want there to be any reason why we came into this cave.
Yeah.
Well, they went and they saw a Rumpelstiltskin and he was like a Rumpelpigskin and they were
like, "Can we get out?
We wish to get out of the cave."
And he's like, "No, it has to be sports related."
and then they're like okay. Can we kick the soccer ball all the way out of the
cave and he's like okay wait a minute
no hold on now. So you guys got to feed me a baby one of the one of the four or
five of the kids when they were rescued from the cave. Turns out that they were
stateless and they belonged to what is that mean they belong to no country like
the movie terminal and then tie a tie water.
Thailand gave them statehood after...
What the fuck?
Or not statehood.
How are you statesless?
Were they born over the ocean or something?
They were born, they never, they didn't even exist.
Were they born in a cave?
I don't know.
They were created in the cave.
They were literally changelings.
They were like fairy folk.
We need four other people to have a full defensive line.
No problem!
I got that!
They don't belong to a country!
I can create as many boys as you want, but they can't have passports.
They all look Swedish.
That's when they rescued the kids, they were like, "Why is Tyler, why is all like four
of these kids blonde?
What is going on here?"
They're like, "It was Rumpelpigskin.
He's the cave spirit, but he only likes to give sports wishes, so you know, unless you're
trying to win a Heisman, don't even think about it."
yeah rumple pigskin rumple pigskin rumple pigskin rumple freaking pigskin yeah
because that's funny we suck what is rumple still skin his he like turns like
straw into gold no he makes no it's the no he doesn't it's the woman who's
woman's spin okay the woman spins straw into gold but then she owes a baby yeah
because because um see I the only rumple stillskin I let's read roll the rumple
still skin story I know of is the one from Muppets classics theater shut up
all right rumple stiltskin I think miss piggy the story is about an imp oh no
the imp does spin straw into gold yeah bitch the story is about an imp who's
been strong as a whole day's romance for girls firstborn rubble still skin also
known as Tom tit-tot what wait that's his name his name's rumple stiltskin well
which one does he oh it's that it's that the the the girl's father lies and tells
the king that she can spin straw into gold and then rumple still skin like
does it for you just believe it because you're a natural king yeah yeah exactly
you work on the Kings info so she's she she has to spin straw into gold or else
the king will cut off her head then rumple still skin shows up does it for
her takes his neck takes her necklace then she does it again he has to she has
to spin even more he does it again he takes her ring and the third one can you
read this synopsis from the movie classics theater version you just use
those characters firstborn child yeah well they already did that they had miss
piggy as the as the woman you know how and you remember our ripple still skin
lost because he was like he was like okay I won't take your child the if you
can guess what my name is and she's like oh no and then he like go he likes
he's in the woods and he's just and he's just dancing around a fire going. I'm
rumple stiltskin. She'll never find out my name is rumple stiltskin. Yeah, it's
like rumple stiltskin. Use your inside. Yeah, okay. Why are you give? Why are
you blabbing? Yeah, why would you lips sink ships? He's sitting there. He's
sitting there just saying like he was he's the and you know guy. Yeah, and you
know she doesn't know I'm rumple stiltskin. No, she don't know my name is
stillskin though. What'd you say? Is the original. Nothing. The original. I didn't say shit.
What's my name? Rumpelstiltskin. And you know I'm gonna ask for a firstborn child. And you
know I'm Rumpelstiltskin. And you just know who I am. Yeah, it's Gonzo. You're Gonzo.
Gonzo is Rumpelstiltskin. What is Gonzo porn? Why does that have anything to do with the
Muppet what is what came first gonzo the Muppet or the word gonzo is it the penis
looks like his nose maybe it's a big meaty eggplant style fucking dong yeah
curse down huh yeah nobody's penis curves down by the way yeah not a nobody's
jacking off like like a we're making a notice you know nobody mine curves
strongly to the left yeah yeah not only strongly strongly how strong in the
You ever heard of a right angle?
Yeah.
That's about it.
Damn.
Really?
Yeah, that's because I have a Lego hand.
What does that Lego hand have to do with the right angle?
I just figured those were related, but maybe they're not.
I don't know.
Actually, that's a perfect jacking off hand, a Lego hand.
That is a perfect jacking off hand.
Until you realize, circular middle, a Lego man's penis is definitely a square.
Yup.
Yeah.
That's got to be it.
It's got to be like a...
They're making very little contact.
cutting his hand on his corners of his thing.
Do you think a Lego man's penis would be a...
Has to be a square.
Right? Am I tripping?
I think what the Lego man probably does
is his business and we should talk about it.
So is a Lego man's
head is a circle and his feet
are squares. So is a penis
closer to a head or a foot? Foot.
Okay, it's a square.
My head has eyes and a mouth.
What I think happens... My wiener has a mouth.
Well I think happens...
- Well no, 'cause there's the lightsabers too.
The Lego lightsabers.
- Those are circles. - That's different,
that's not canon.
- Well those aren't body parts.
- Yeah.
- Well yeah, but then I feel like
it's the same shape. - We're talking,
we're talking, - In terms of Lego shapes.
- We're talking Lego here right now.
- But I think, I think all, - We're not talking Star Wars.
- Any Lego man has to like, basically wear a strap on.
- I don't. - A lot.
Well yeah, they have strap on heads,
of course they wear a strap on. - Yeah, exactly.
They would wear a strap on penis.
- Okay, yeah, I'm with you, what's up?
Well that's what I'm saying, so it could be anything.
I mean it could all be anything, they're Legos.
Yeah.
I'm just saying.
It is up to your imagination.
It also--
It is a Lego, it is up to your imagination.
Of course.
I would say it depends.
A Lego woman's vagina, is it a square or is it a--
Where, okay, where is that?
Under the pants.
Oh, so they have to get out of,
they have to put on new legs.
They have to take off clothes to--
They have to take off their legs
and put on their naked legs.
Yeah.
That have a vagina and a butthole.
Or just the butthole of--
Yeah, because they do have the thing of Lego.
Lego women got four holes in the back.
Damn.
[LAUGHTER]
And they got holes in their feet, too.
They flat as hell, though.
They got four holes in the back and some holes in the--
Well, I've been altering my Lego figures, so none of them--
they all have big butts.
Nice.
It's like-- it's infuriating to look
at how flat some of them are.
It's disgusting.
Even the men, I give them big pumper dumpers.
They need them, dude.
desperate for him. How does a Lego man even poop? It's got to hurt to sit down. I know,
exactly. Which hole does it come out of? The mouth. Yuck. I want to snatch the wig of one
of the women and get in that head hole. Yeah. Just rip it off. Yeah, I have a special sexual
Lego workshop where I alter my Legos to make them. Yeah. In different, sexy, in different
ways. Sexual Lego workshop. I stole a tool set from Santa's elves and I still care. See,
my neighbors always complains because I have it's like in the backyard and
there's it's like an iron door with like a like the thing that you like
across.
You see like sparks shooting out of the chimney all night and it's like
it's like super low. You can hear a jack hammer yeah, like a three so sexual
yeah, I go every night and then I show them a Darth Vader with giant hits
every time the door opens, but you hear like clanging metal and explosions and
so welcome to the jungle it's pretty cool smoke comes out you won't go you're
actually yeah I'd enough they're actually getting me on forged in fire because of
it yeah a sexual Lego woman's vagina yeah well they're like you're like what a
woman was spreadable like you can't make you can't yeah you can't make a Lego sex
doll you have to make a kukri like that's the challenge I'm like fine and
and then i make like a one like a curved sword or whatever and it just has like
just lego it's just a like an etching like an incredibly detailed like sexual
lego or you just taped one to the other side of it so you hand it over the
handle is a lego penis you bow to hand it over it's like thank you turns it
what the what is it you tape this this kim kardashian for my ultimate test
and i'm fucking it come on i do need to i'm waiting on to watch second season of
of Forged in Fire until Christmas because that's my new Christmas tradition.
Yeah. I watch Forged in Fire. One of my big Christmas traditions, presents and stockings.
Yeah. I visit for Santa. Every year. Every year for real. I usually buy a weed part from
a gas station in North Carolina and get to just like, just spend the entire time fucked
up on fake weed watching Forged in Fire. That might be a good move. It's a great move, dude.
Just feel dangerous the whole time. I think one of the best moves on Christmas is drinking
eggnog. Eggnog hits different at Christmas time. Absolutely. Ornaments be hitting different
too. I just got a couple ornaments. I'm going to get a tree this year for the first time
ever. I might get a little fake tree. Yeah, I think we're going to get a tree. God damn
it dude. I'm getting a really. I'm thinking about like a tree in my apartment. A hugey
really. Are you really going to get a real tree in here? Yeah. Small one. I'm not going
get a fucking 10-foot hugee. You said a hugee really. To me I think Christmas trees are
one foot on average so this is doing to be four or five feet probably yeah which
is hugee. I think I put it like right yeah that'd be nice and you know I like I
hate fake Christmas trees but I don't I don't feel like getting a real one.
They're prickly cleaning up after it. And they don't smell good. Yeah you gotta put the
smells in there. Yeah you gotta anything you gotta put in there. Oh and I'm putting plenty of smells in the tree.
That's right. I'm dusting it. You ever farted and feel like you have to run away from it?
Yesterday I farted on the way I it's like so hot and it smells so bad that
you're like yeah, I can't be in this and I it's gonna stick. Yeah, do you have
it's like a looney tunes shape of your body and green. Do you ever far in
public or with people and then you smell it and you're like I'm not even gonna
acknowledge it because there's no way anybody's gonna guess that that came
from a human. I'm like that people will assume this is some industrial smell.
Yeah, sometimes it's like it's like so bad that you like you. You can't open
your mouth to accuse someone of it. Yeah, yeah, I just have to let this one all
your teeth will just fall out. Yeah, yeah, no, I've been having some
so it's been trouble fucked. I just eat this bean salad. I make a it's just a
can of pinto's garbanzos,
black beans, kidneys and corn and it just is that it's all beans, tomato,
onion, avocado, lemon juice, red wine vinegar, salt pepper.
- All beans?
- All beans and corn.
And I just eat it every single meal.
I eat it with eggs in the morning sometimes.
- Whoa. - Christ.
- And some feta cheese.
- You know, there's a lot of--
- That's gonna take you down.
- There's a lot of YouTubers that you can watch
that can teach you how to make vegan food
that isn't bean salad.
- This is cheap and I like it a lot.
- Yeah?
- I like how it makes me smell.
- Oh, boy.
Yesterday I was trying I was going out to do some stand-up and I farted and I really thought I shit myself
Yeah, and I I was like if I shit myself
I'm gonna have Jana come pick me up in the car and I called her and I was like
Can you come pick me up? She was like no and then I just went to the show
But I didn't shit myself. Thank God, but I was fully convinced. Well, yeah, there's like sometimes sometimes a gas will leave your body
That's so hot that it feels like it like pushed your underwear
Did I tell you guys about Jana thinking I shit myself the other night?
No, I already talked about this. Didn't you shit yourself?
I farted in the middle of the night and it woke me and Jana up and she and I was she was like
Smells like shit in here. I was like, yeah, I just farted. She's like no you shit the bed you a hundred percent shit the bed
Show me your butt
I was like, I'm not gonna show you my fucking butt dude. That's fucked up. She's like turn around
I'm like, "Show me your butt. Prove you didn't shit yourself."
Let me see your butt.
And then I did, and I didn't shit myself. I was right. She was fucking being a crazy
person.
She just wanted to see your butt.
She didn't want to see my butt, dude. Fucking pedophile.
Let me see your butt, freak.
Yeah, dude, my girlfriend's such a pedophile.
Yeah.
But yeah, it was very embarrassing to me right in that moment.
I haven't shit myself, I don't think, ever.
What?
That's not true.
No, no, not like--
You're not even human.
long time but that's not ever actually what I did shit myself I think a year to
the day ago well how do you know I don't think I've ever shit myself actually it
was exactly the one year anniversary of the last time I do for another one
exactly no yeah I used to shit myself twice a year pretty pretty much like
clock yeah I never shit myself so when I did last year what you done I was in the
kitchen making myself breakfast
at my parents house and then just like
for did and then felt a squirt and i was like
all deer
uh... told do smear yeah
is ran upstairs
you know like i think i left the pan on
uh... down now yeah
nothing happens if you died
because of that is so funny like i just didn't take just like
crumbles
on making a snow is making myself an italian sub-space member group
and i remember it and some of the pan
we make it
i was uh...
the heat in the bread up
hot bread on the time so
you better be going to prison brother right now do
it was in a good italian sub
leadership myself in the middle of making it and i don't know the shit yet
the shower well yeah the showers are a bucket of yeah that's what i whenever i
should let me know if i can't and i saw my ass in the bath i came downstairs
after
showering from having shit myself and then looked at the sub and I was just like, "Hey
mom, there's a sub in the kitchen if you want it." And then just went in my bed and just
canceled the day out. That was the end of the day for me.
I think the last time I shit myself I was also puking. I don't know if that counts.
That's fine.
It doesn't really count.
No, that's like a...
It's like food poisoning.
Yeah.
Like me, every time I've shit myself, I've made the decision to let something go and I
I just gamble it. You know, I'm a natural born gambler. I'm always looking for the next jackpot.
And it's usually I put a crap lot in my pants.
I've told you guys about the time that I, the worst time I ever got food poisoning,
right?
No. I don't think I've ever had food poisoning.
Oh, I've gotten.
No, I've had it.
I've had it. It's horrible.
I got food poisoning. The first time I ever got food poisoning was when I was five and
and I went to Burger King and I got the chicken parm
at Burger King.
- Ooh.
- Yeah.
- How was it?
- I got food poisoning.
- But usually the food is pretty good
if you got food poisoning, right?
- I guess, I don't know.
- Means it just got like, it was very juicy chicken.
- I just remember, I remember like,
getting ready for school and then like having like a fever.
- Or it means that the guy pooped on his hands
when he was making it.
- Yeah, that could have been it.
- Which I would like a lot.
- Having a fever and then like,
looking at like my mom and her seeing like how sweaty and like pale i was
she's like are you like what's car you sick and i said
uh-huh
through a hundred before
the one i got the first time i got food poisoning was the first time i had a
cracker barrel yes it'll be a reason
we're in a hotel we're like going to do something weird
late on a vacation
i don't know when you're a kid yet and i just had everyone else i got to go do
stuff all day and i said like food prices throwing up and shitting myself
- It hurts you, dude.
- Yeah.
- Like the diarrhea hurts, it's hot when it comes out.
- Do you guys ever really wanna get sick for a little bit?
- No.
- Not really.
- When I was in elementary school--
- I kinda like that, couple days where you just like
can't even like look at, you can't even watch a movie,
you're so tired.
- Yeah.
- You just like sleep all the time.
- I got a stomach bug in second grade in the summer.
So I like was able to kinda like milk like three days
of not going to school.
Like the first day was really bad,
the second day I think I puked in the morning
then was fine and then the third day I was just like oh I can't go to school I'm
still so sick. Oh dude I used to stretch it out. Yeah yeah yeah. Long time I'd be sick.
I was probably setting records in middle school. Yeah I was sick for three
months. Yeah you were Ferris Buellering. I was I was Buellered up every day bro.
You know I had a dummy that played me. He's a damn good actor. That
emulator keyboard that plays burps. Yeah I had a burping keyboard. So what? Who
- You didn't.
- But I think it was like,
I've definitely talked about this.
I was moving back in to my parents' house,
or like we just moved to like a new house in New Hampshire,
and I like into my sister's house
with her and her like ex-fiance or whatever.
And like, I found a thing of bacon wrapped scallops
in the back of the fridge.
And I was like, oh yeah.
- Oh yeah, I remember this story.
- Yeah, dude.
That was the hottest something has ever left my body.
Like I've never like diarrhea and puked so hard in my life.
And it was like a tiny toilet.
- Yeah.
- Or like--
- Are you still on one of those potty training kid toilets?
- Yeah, yeah, I was on one of those.
- That you have to--
- Well I had to use that
'cause all the other bathrooms were taken.
- So you're just doing it in the middle of the living room?
- Yeah.
- Then--
- Hey dad, this needs to be emptied.
(laughing)
- This needs to be cleaned.
- It's like overflowing with shit.
(laughing)
Yeah, the dog did something.
I think a dog took a human shit in the baby toilet.
Dude, that was like, I literally was like...
Pretty impressive honestly.
Did the dog learn to go to the bathroom, dad?
You have to clean it up.
I literally couldn't like, I was just fading in and out of like consciousness.
Like I was like sleeping so long.
That's what happens when you have food poisoning.
It's like a fever dream hell of just like shit and pee and you're just like not awake.
having dreams where you're not sick yeah you're like you're like talking to like
like a dead relative yeah you wake up you have to wake up every 30 minutes yeah
like to shoot slime out of your body oh you fall asleep in front of the toilet
sometimes dude I literally so that toilet was like small but also like the
house was so old that like it was on like two little pieces of wood like to
like prop it up so that like because all the floors were slanted and like I would
sit on it and the toilet would wobble yeah while I'm like puking so it's like
I'm getting like like like like puking like that yeah it's awesome
puke talk this episode I realize disgusting no don't throw this at me
yeah the new windscreens are this is like the best thing I think they look
really good it's great primary color stuff yeah we touch them together oh do
let's do a cool wow we do let me do one more okay we're gonna do another one
oh that's my flashlight why are we doing enough we don't need we don't need the
wide angle we're gonna do another one okay
that was awesome great it was great both dude look at how great that looks all
right Caleb now you need to take a picture okay that picture is perfect is
that the perfect one this is the most beautiful photo I've ever seen Wow that
really changes everything that changes the podcast forever I know when you mix
mix these colors together, you get brown.
- Yeah, it's true.
- That's a color of poopy.
- Yes, sir.
- That's a color of poop. - Yes, sir.
- They should bring back Fear Factor
and have us be the president.
- We would be so good at Fear Factor.
- Dude, triple threat Fear Factor, fuck you, man.
Fucking destroying.
- All right, poop box, poop bag, submerged poop box,
dark room filled with poop, poop eating challenge,
poop eating box.
- Okay, for your next challenge,
all you have to do is eat that sandwich.
like that sandwich yeah
there's clearly it there's managed clears a there's a turd on the sandwich. Oh is
there I didn't notice
we'll go ahead. All you have to do is drink out of this rubber tube going from
a mysterious source and you can see it's going down the hallway and just goes
right under the bathroom. It goes into Patrick's
dressing your Patrick's dressing room. Yeah, we should have dressing rooms
dookie hand print on
yeah yeah, it has like a video game like the two environmental story telling
like graffiti that says like like he's eating poop
yeah dude. I mean, I just feel like I mean also like they just never went hard
enough like the afraid of things were like oh you fall fifty feet into water
enough yeah a million feet uh-huh honestly from a plane from a plane yeah
that's a million feet up. Fear vector would just like would you go skydiving yeah well
that's way scarier than anything that's actually in the show. With a bug as your
teammate. As your parachute yeah. Oh bug is your parachute that ain't gonna work. Yeah a
million bugs as your parachute. A million bugs stitched together yeah that might
actually work. You know when you freeze a bee and then you tie a string around it
then you can like use it as a kite.
What?
Did you do that?
No, that was in CKY.
Oh.
The bee just de-thaws?
You know what you do?
Yeah.
Really?
I guess that's a, there's a bunch of videos of people do it.
You can cryogenically freeze a bee.
Yeah, you can capture a bee in a cup, put it in the freezer, tie a string around it,
and then when it gets like, when it wakes up, you, there's a tie, there's a certain
amount of time around the bee.
You have to like make sure that the bee doesn't die of freezing, of hypothermia.
but it does but it does freeze enough that into an ice cube yeah what really
yeah pretty cool that's gonna happen that's gonna that's what's gonna happen
to all the people who got cryogenically frozen because they have like double
cancer or something yeah like the idea aliens are gonna defrost them and like
I'm doing like a million years yeah they're like trying to go to work and
they're like huh all right yeah I can't seem to cross this street what's that on
my neck yeah oh it appears I'm a pet and I still have cancer Wow this is awesome
yeah they're gonna free it make Disney my pet did hmm here's a hypothetical I've
been thinking of what let's hear it all right would you eat so the new animal
drops new animal comes out yes okay animal drops new in there new animal
drops it's one of the tastiest animals in the world but it's called the stink
wraith stink wraith yeah is it big it's a big and what does it look like it looks
- It looks like the stink wraith, it looks like--
- Is this a bug?
- It's like a cross between--
- A wraith is a ghost.
- It's a cross between a porcupine and a hog.
- So a hog.
- What's stinky?
- No, it's a porcupine and a hog mixed together.
- So there's already a stink bug,
so I feel like this should be a bug.
- This is a stink wraith.
- Yeah, but a wraith is a spirit.
- What do you mean a hog?
Hogs don't have--
- They're hogs that have prickles on them.
- Oh, okay.
- Some wild hogs have--
- So I guess it's a species of hog
It's called the stink wraith because it smells so bad.
- Durian smells bad.
- See, okay, that was my next thing.
- Is this a durian kind of--
- Would you eat braised stink wraith with durian chutney?
- Yeah.
- You would eat it?
- If it's braised and chutneyed.
- But it smells so bad.
- Yeah, it's fine.
If it tastes good, would you eat it?
- Does it taste good?
- It tastes exactly like fried chicken, every bite.
Every bite is a perfect--
- It's probably really expensive.
I'd probably just eat fried chicken then.
It's probably way cheaper than fried chicken cuz fried chicken smells good - durians really expensive. Yeah durians like $50 a fucking melon
Well, well, you don't need your durian the durian isn't what makes it the stinky boots country
Durian go on and where would that be? What's the stinky country? Is that planet stink?
Planet, that's all in it. You fucking idiot. Yeah planet stink is an arcade
Where is the stinky country? You're trying to know where a durian?
indigenous to I actually don't know I think like somewhere like Pacific Asia
oh my bad as stink planet you'll never be riding for Colbert nope nope that one's
out the window that was my dream to write for Colbert that was my dream I
would love to write for oh my god I want to say today in the news I seen I seen
two of them Hughies and I had a big smile on my face.
Yeah. I'd love to write a new Colbert joke where he does like a funny, where he
does like a smirk into the camera like that. What would it be? What would your
joke be? Well I, well I'm not gonna do it now. Donald Trump needs to lose some weight. He's
starting to develop Hughies on his chest that are making me as horny as a bear.
I'm like a bear to honey for Trumpies Hugh Jeeves yeah I think that rhymes
Trumpy have you biggie huge today Wow so in other news Trumpy was on the beach
having huge ease again rubby heavy huge ease Trumpy hospitalized with huge ease
attack so huge ease doctors say huge ease still on him this is still on him still
huge is still the biggest huge ease on trump is true chest trump is just as
chesty
have you big huge ease go crazy call barry go smiling he
call barry go
very whole
he died
people there
you know what he's you
g_e_ mean the lovey
trump is huge ease
trump he has to be huge is a one c_n_n_'s
story is a very hard to buy a day to huge ease in a victorious secret top
presidente. Oney Hugey on Trumpy and Yesy. Oney morey Hugey. Plus he has two
back Hugey's that I'd like to put my face in.
Colbert out. Trumpy's Hugey make my thingy Hugey Hugey. Stinky. Trumpy stinky
Hugey make my stinky thingy. Trumpy Hugey's on fronty Hugey. Trumpy's Hugey's on
Backy Stinky Hugies. Trumpy's Big Mommy Hugies. Makey Brownie. Executive Order by
Trumpy puts Hugies on DL Hughley. DL Hugies? DL Hugies is DL Hugely's
Dangerously Lovely Hugies. Why is it DL Hugely? It's clearly spelled
Hugely. It's got an H in there. Oh it does? Like Hugh Grant. Yeah.
DL Hewley. See this is why you don't understand us. Yeah. Us? Yeah. What do you
mean by that? Like me and DL. What is similar between you two? Stand-up
comedians. Okay. Yeah. You don't get the way we talk. Yeah.
There's certain, yeah, stand-up like vernacular that they both use. Yeah. That you just
we don't get yeah I guess the way they stand the way they talk mm-hmm
what's that special he did shocked and appalled it's a good name it was a good
special hello I'm shocked in a Paul saw that that was a yeah there's a stay home
school watch yeah yeah you remember I mean that was the but you stay home from
school leave Comedy Central on your CRT TV I stay home from school I go to watch
DVD drawer pick out secretary with imagine Maggie Gyllenhaal yeah see if I
was correct in remembering that there was no boobs in that movie and then get
really sad there's no boobs and secretary there's a little bit of boobs
but I was basically hoping for a whole boob buffet and because of the cover of
it you know because it looks like a National Lampoon movie you know but it's
really just she's getting kind of abused to the whole movie which I didn't realize
I realized as a kid, then I got older and I was like,
"Those are some off limits Hughies to me."
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- We're not allowed to think about these Hughies
that are in movies like that.
- True. - Movie Hughies.
- Movie Hughies from a sadly movie?
That's not a Hughie at all.
No. - That doesn't make sense.
- A sadly Hughie is no Hughie to me.
- Monster's Ball.
That movie gave me monstrous balls
at Halle Berry's huge Hughies,
but then I realized that she's wanting to kill herself
movie and she fucks the guy she fucks you geez I made me bluey she needs she says
she needs to feel good she's like I need to feel good and then they fuck and I was
like well she just wants to put a penis in her and let him show her his huge ease
but then she actually your family's sick so it turns out it is sad movie now it's
got a happy ending if you watch the 90 minutes on either side of the huge things
and then cut out the huge ease and put them at the end that's a happy ending
but if you watch it in what they call chronological order then it's actually
terribly sad yeah you know as a happy ending you should you would I think
you'd be good if you started like a movie review site called like the huge
e report or something yeah I think mr. skin style yeah but no more mr. skin but
you know you actually do review yeah you talk through the okay it is crazy that
mr. skin I mean that's that's crazy that that exists still that crazy yeah you
think that's crazy that's no no more crazy than pornography I guess you're
right I would say but it's also like it's also like every mr. skin thing is
like some arthouse movie where it's like oh yeah Marion Cotillard is like nude in
this movie you got to check it out at this time this time frame and it's like a
movie about like it's like a really long French movie yeah it's about her son
getting divorced at five years old and she has cancer too
which actually shows the tumors are in her huge ease and they're flopping all
over the place like a flippy flopper yeah they're looking like duck feet just
Flopping all over the place Maria, not a Cote de L'Arde.
Maria, not a Cote de L'Arde.
Too many Hughies.
What's this bitch's name?
This bitch's name, you know what she sounds like?
She sounds like she'd be market price on a menu.
That fucking name.
That's a stupid name.
Yeah.
When I say her name, I put a spoonful of marshmallow fluff
in my mouth so I can get it right.
That's right.
You look like I put salt on her.
She'd shrivel up.
Snail ass French ass mother fucking bitch.
Plus she got them Hughies on the low-do.
That's why I call her MC Hugh Jeeves.
Whoa.
She is in...
The dark night rises, you know what else rises?
My dark night when I see those Hugh Jeeves.
(Laughter)
His night is dark as hell.
Inception, I'd like to incept those Hugh Jeeves
when she's walking into the bathroom
with my tongue.
(Laughter)
She's going to the bathroom
and I'm in there hiding.
And then I dock my tongue
like a spaceship
between her Hugies. And she's okay with it. And she loves it.
Because she's French. Yep. Yeah. "Blue is the warmest color, so is the vein on my
thing when I see Hugies." When I see two sets of Hugies that I think they're
attacking each other in the movie? Wait, this is some kind of Hugie battle
between the four Hugies and the two thingies and they're eating each other?
scary huge E4 was really good that's true that's true it was fire yeah man with
two brains yeah I'm the man with one big thing when I see the huge ease in the
movie that one's a bit of a stretch it was a stretch yeah you know what else is
stretched out my thing when I see huge ease basically huge easer is a term that
is taking the whole world by storm. Snatch! I'd love to snatch up some Hughies.
Yeah. I watched Snatch last night. Yeah? Yeah I haven't watched that since I was probably
in like... Yeah I watched your Snatch. Yeah you watched my Snatch expand because I saw
a Hughie in that movie. Yep. Is there Hughies in Snatch? There's not. There's Brad Pitt.
is Brad Pitt. You know the original title for Snatch was a hairy snatch.
Hairy stinky snatch. The most disgusting studio veto.
We can't call this hairy stinky smelly snatch.
How about airy snatch?
There's still some posters that have the full title on it.
Yeah, they printed it for it's like a record in Poland. Yeah. Yeah, they released it at first and then they were like, that's bad
Yeah, we gotta go back on. Yeah. Yeah, cuz in Poland it's called
Slimy snatch with hair on the side slimy married snatch. Mm-hmm. Yeah
stinky slimy slithery snizz
Yeah
It was called the slithering sliz that's right. Yeah. Mm-hmm. They need to make a huge ease movie. Yeah. Yeah
meatballs
Hugie's fully loaded
Meatball meatballs got big
These huge ease on the my screen
Meatballs, yeah, or hey chef split in half as of the huge. I'm saying. Yes
- F or C these Hugis.
(laughing)
- Bruce Almighty, I'm gonna shoot some Spidey
out of my wiener when I look at these Hugis
on the girl in that.
- Chronicles of Riddick, yeah,
more like Chronicles of my dick,
seeing big old Hugis.
- My bionicles of my dick,
'cause I'm moving it around so much
and pretending it's evil.
- Hard my balls and my dick.
- Damn, damn.
Yeah, money balls. Yeah, I'm gonna have to show you my new balls after I have to get them
replaced because I saw the biggest huge. Yeah, what's a movie that actually has huge ease
in it that you could do American pie American pie. I I'm a smiling guy. That's pretty good.
It makes my very big guy. There we go. My very big guy. My big fat Greek
wedding. Or like my dreams with bed wedding because I'm dreaming about
hugeies. I just destroyed my bedding. My big fat green red thing. The Godfather
part two I have an odd hogger for you look at those huge ease on my TV screen
and I saw it in climax 3d that's right and I'd like to see your answer
there's there's you do you see the advance boobs no you should be able to I
think there's an ant with boobs in that movie you know remember that um Robbie
- Robbie the Reindeer movie and all the girl,
it's supposed to look like the Rankin and Bass,
Rudolph movie, but then all the girl reindeers
have actual boobs on their things.
- Is this like--
- It's on CBS and Ben Stiller plays Robbie the Reindeer.
- And they have boobies?
- The reindeers have boobies.
- If that ain't Crazy Nights, I don't know what is, bud.
- In terms of holiday movies?
- If that ain't Crazy Nights, I'm just not sure what is, bud.
- That's true.
crazy nights or like I'm going on eight crazy flights to see the huge ease all
around the world Wow you're a huge ease world traveler like Jackie Chan and
around the world seen 80 hugies
going around the world to see you that's basically the thing hmm yeah all right
Thank you. Yeah, Mr. Bean, I went straight for the Hyugis.
(laughter)
Okay, bye. Bye.
Happy Black Friday.