You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[explosion]
[moaning]
Original recipe, baby.
Original recipe.
But speaking of original recipe, I did just go to Popeyes and get a big chicken sandwich.
Did you ask for the original recipe?
No, I asked for the one with the spicy goo that all the people online like.
Yeah, the oobleck.
Yeah, exactly. Yeah, I asked for it.
And then they just gave me a sandwich.
Yeah, they said we don't know what oobleck is.
Yeah.
It's fucked up.
And I spit on them.
Happy birthday, man.
Thanks. Yeah, the day this comes out is my birthday and Patrick's not on this one
because he hates birthdays and me.
Yeah, he mostly is. He hates Cameron the most.
Yeah, he heard how much I was complaining about his squeaky chair and so he decided
at his birthday present was to take the chair out of the equation.
I don't really care about the chair, it's just fun to make fun of it.
The chair doesn't bother me at all.
Yeah, I just worry that the fans will get mad.
Because it's a really loud chair.
The fans hate a squeaky chair.
It sounds like a thousand year old rocking horse.
Look at this, he just texted us.
He made that, he made that.
I bet he's, he said.
What did he say?
I said I was docking his pay for not appearing and he says that's fine.
This is how rich he is, ladies and gentlemen.
He doesn't give a fuck.
he can afford it and the loudest antique chair in the world
yeah it's specifically allowed chair i think it's very funny to this he made a
post it was like preview of patrick's audio on that
premium episode and he recorded his chair squeaking a bunch of his posted
that yesterday but now he's not even on the episode so it's very clear that he's
lying yeah it's it's just a confusing post now you know i'm gonna come and
delete it after we have a little bit of a little bit of a very funny
i think it's funny i want people to go back and yell at everybody message
Patrick and ask where the hell he is on this one because he's a good maybe oh
you know what we have to create recreate this squeaking chair to make the audio
make sense we have to play that wait wait I'm gonna close the time loop one
second I have to find this post I'm gonna play the post audio into my
microphone oh my god this is like this feels like being in looper right now
yeah I feel like looper from we're older me I'm and Patrick is the baby both of
us yeah we you me and Pat are the same guy at three different parts of his life
there's no way that's the real chair that's his baby that's that's him crying
yeah that's him crying because he didn't get it he didn't get a monster energy in
a baby bottle yeah with a nipple oh with two nipples with two it has to be with
two nipples that's what he has to have because it's got to be the real thing
yeah it's just a life like life like human tits and just a tiny bottle
attached kind of a perfect woman when you think about it just two big fake tits and a bottle behind them
just feeding in them, it's kind of genius. Filled with chemicals yeah and a green
decepticon chemicals. It's like like here's a scientist does a mock-up of what
women will look like in a hundred years.
Just two big, fake, beautiful brown breasts with big brown nipples and a baby bottle full
of soy milk.
Yeah, and a cool green three claw mark thing right on there.
Yeah, and the head from a Funko Pop Mario just sat on top.
Yeah, and the legs of a transformer.
Yeah, and finally, finally.
I want my girl to have the legs of a transformer.
And finally no pussy.
Finally.
Yeah, she has the transformer legs so when she transforms she's a car just from the ass
down.
That's what I want.
And she has legs that go all the way to being a car.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
I just, I want a speech I want to make about how the FBI caught Ghislaine, I don't care
how it's actually pronounced. Never gonna look it up. They cut just lame Maxwell.
And I just wanted to say that when when they killed Jeffrey Epstein I was over
the moon because I was just so happy and proud that the Clintons were able to
like skip over you know the burden of the legal system and legal proceedings and
were able to just deliver swift justice to this awful man and end his reign of
terror over the world, much like they did, much like Hillary did in Benghazi.
They were able to get rid of some really bad people, you know, without worrying about courts
and judges.
And then I found out that Jeffrey had actually a normal adult girlfriend who was also evil.
And I got really upset again because I knew this wasn't over.
This wouldn't be over until, you know, they caught and brought to justice everyone involved
with this child trafficking.
And now they've caught Ghislaine and it's finally over, you know.
I'm just really happy that they finally got, you know, the final person who is in charge
of this child trafficking and I hope that the Clintons will be able to, you know, circumvent
the law and deliver swift vigilante justice to Ghislaine and, you know, end her life to
kind of just put the final nail in the coffin of pedophilia and end it once and for all.
I just want to say that because I'm really excited.
I'm over the moon.
So, I hope you guys are as excited as I am.
This is the best birthday present I could have had.
That's what I think is it's like yeah, why are people so mad at the Clintons for killing these people?
They're like have you not seen the movie hard candy isn't it good to kill pedophiles isn't that like?
Exactly thing yeah, have you ever seen nightmare on Elm Street? Oh?
Wait it's Jeffrey Epstein's gonna come back in the dreams of the Clintons and
Give them nightmares. No. This is all you think is
Do you think Epstein met Gislaine because of pedophilia or do you think they were already
dating and at some point one of them had to bring it up?
Hey babe, do you want to start a child trafficking ring?
I mean yeah, because who do you, I mean it's definitely Epstein brought it up first.
They just ran out of things to-
Or no, maybe it was, maybe that was Epstein's whole defense where he's like, "My crazy wife
made me do it all.
You know how women are, they're always hanging stuff over your head.
She comes up to me, I'm mowing the lawn outside, she comes up to me and says
"I want a divorce" and I say "Well, you know, that complicates stuff with the money"
and she's like "Alright, well we're gonna start fucking kids then"
Yeah, what could I do?
Yeah, my hands are tied, you know, these women, I mean, what are you gonna do?
You can't live with them, you know?
You can't live without them, but you can fuck like a million little kids with them, I guess.
They just ran out of things to do together.
You know, they're watching TV all the time.
They watched The Office two times through.
And then one day, they were like, you know what?
What about kids?
What about fucking children?
What if we just did that instead of Netflix?
That's called Michael Scott's law.
That is, if any couple watches The Office
more than two times, they turn into sex traffickers.
Yeah, the thing is, you get seven years into a relationship
and you gotta do something to keep it fresh.
You know what I mean?
Some people renew their vows,
and then some people start raping children
in the ass and in the mouth, you know,
and then selling them to rich people to eat.
- Yeah.
- You know, it's just a, you know.
They're like Bonnie and Clyde when you think about it.
- Yeah.
- People love to romanticize Bonnie and Clyde.
- So why aren't we romanticizing them?
- Yeah.
- That's what I wanna know.
- Yeah, the 2019 Bonnie and Clyde.
- Yeah.
- Fuck.
- You doing anything fun for your birthday?
- I'm going to a sculpture garden,
and I'm also gonna hang out with my dad.
That's pretty much it.
- Nice.
- Yeah.
- Is it your dad's sculpture garden?
- No, those are two separate activities.
I'm gonna go to a sculpture garden with my mom,
and then I'm gonna go to my dad's house.
- That's the comp, even as an adult,
it's still, on birthday,
you still got divorced parents, you know?
- Yeah, yeah, you gotta have two, you get two birthdays.
- Yeah, you still get a weekend with both on a birthday.
- Yeah, yeah, you have to split the time.
You have to go to my dad's house in the morning,
and I have to come back and go to the sculpture garden.
- Every hour, you have to go to your mom's
and then to your dad's.
- It's like a wacky sitcom.
You know, you have to-- - Yeah, just every--
- You have to pretend you're not spending time
with the other one. - That's what the judge said.
- That's what the judge said, you have to do it
like a way I said yeah yeah the thing is your dad walks in the room and you have
to be like oh hey dad holding a pillow over your lap where your mom is sucking
your penis yeah just like all those sitcoms I watch yeah and then then your
dad notices your mom goes no no no that's not how you do it at all
Let me teach you.
Oh, fuck.
Are you turning 22 or 23?
22.
Damn, you're a young one.
I'm a little baby.
I'm the youngest in the podcasting game.
You are.
That's true.
You're very young.
I'm old as shit, dude.
You're 35.
I'm 35 years old.
My brain is just a flat pancake because yesterday I got, I was going to make brownies with the,
my my weed cart pin broke and I was trying to like save the oil so I put it
in a cup so that it would like drip down yeah and like I put a cup upside down
and then put like a piece of saran wrap at the bottom so all the oil would just
like drip into the into the saran wrap but then it was too sticky to get there
so I just decided like I was getting so frustrated with this with like trying to
make this into like an oil that I could use in like a brownie or something that I
just texted my brother I was like is there any way and get this out and he
was like oh you can just eat that stuff like you don't even have to put it in
something because it's been it has been heated enough or whatever and I was like
okay so I just like ate a spoonful of it yeah and yeah and I just it just ruined
my brain was just gone for eight hours I just went up to the roof you texted me
and Patrick just the words feeling doomed and then didn't respond to any messages after that.
I went up to my roof and just have you seen the the videos where it's like
accent expert breaks down accents from different movies so I just went up to my roof and
just by myself was like staring off from my roof going like Spongebob the
Spongebob Squarepants movie. In this movie Spongebob's bikini-bottom accent really
comes out when he says words like I'm ready whereas with my accent I would say
more of I'm ready and I just did that by myself for like an hour I was good I
went completely insane yeah and then I just came back and I played video games
all night yeah I think um once the I think that like the for me the best
feeling from an edible is when from too much of an edible is afterwards when you
just can't think anymore yeah I was like about an hour and a half ago yeah like
my brain was just completely just gone.
Yeah, I know I told you about this before and I'm not sure if I said it on the pod before
but like there was one summer where me and my friend made like brownies and then we were
gonna like eat them with people but then just like nobody was around like everyone was on
vacation we're just like fuck I guess we have to eat these all ourself and we ate them over
the we ate them all over the course of one movie logic.
Yes we have all these wheat brownies we gotta eat every single one.
the thing is though her her parents were like away when we made them and they're
coming home so it's like oh yeah the clock was ticking that no it was like
completely a Judd Apatow plot line yeah so it just over the course of a week we
ate them all and just for like I think at least a month like my brain was not
running at full capacity not just completely for like a man that's great I
mean we definitely it undoubtedly makes you stupider yeah I have seen so many
people start smoking weed and become just the biggest idiots of all time.
Yeah, just completely go crazy.
Like I mean that also may have something to do with like where like my hometown like nobody's
smoking like real weed like everybody's smoking like the worst weed in the world cut with
like terrible fake synthetic stuff and just losing their mind.
And also everybody there does like fake LSD too.
You know, like they'll do like 2-5-I and like research chemicals and then just work at Wendy's
right now and have like two kids.
It's so sick, dude.
That's the lifestyle.
It is.
That is truly...
I was thinking today, like I think the cure for the...
Just the...
I don't know, the affect that everybody our age has is lobotomy.
Like I think we really messed up
when we got rid of Lobotomy.
Yeah.
'Cause I think like I could go for one.
Yeah, you gotta get a nice pick up in there.
Yeah, I don't know if it's,
can you still, can you like go to,
are Lobotomy's like cheaper in Cuba now?
Like is that a thing?
I mean you can just give yourself one.
I don't trust myself with that.
No, you just--
I guess it's like fine 'cause if you miss,
you just kill yourself.
Yeah.
It's either way, it accomplishes the goal.
You kind of get there no matter what.
Either you can finally enjoy Bojack Horseman or you're dead.
Like whatever.
You try to give yourself a lobotomy and you miss and you accidentally remove the part
of your brain that's holding you back from becoming the smartest person on earth.
No!
Fuck.
Yeah, now I'm ten times as miserable.
Yeah, the booger that's stuck in your brain.
I can calculate every single the trajectory of every single molecule I know the future
I know exactly how everyone I love is gonna die I become Rick Sanchez from Rick of Morty.
Yeah well that's the thing you lobotomize yourself can't watch Rick and Morty anywhere
anymore you can't even know you can't enjoy it.
Exactly you can't you can understand you some of the stuff you know some of the stuff you get like
you can understand like this guy burps a lot that's funny but some of the you're some of
Some of the jokes like when Morty is raped in the bathroom by a weird alien.
By a jelly bean.
Yeah.
That's true.
That you won't be able to understand the hilarity of that moment.
That's going to go right over your head.
Exactly.
That's kind of a smart comedy moment.
Didn't they have like a release like an apology in that and be like that jelly bean alien
is actually completely asexual and while it resembles anal rape it's actually like just
his method of feeding or something.
Like they just tried to like explain it away.
there something like that maybe I just saw someone think so one second I think
called jelly Rick and seen I don't think he actually gets raped I think he almost
gets raped and then he kills the guy that's the scene oh no I think that it's
a put I think I'm thinking of a post from the Rick and Morty subreddit oh but
it's this post is by a Rick and Morty writer
is this like this is after they made everyone is doing it everyone assumes
that King Jellybean was attempting to sexually assault Morty by penetrating him
with his genitalia which explains why the reactions to it have been so strong
however King Jellybean has no genitalia.
That's so funny just like like you clearly
wrote it as a rape joke. Like he says right before it he's like just let
this happen. Yeah. No yeah. You can't just afterwards be like well it's actually aliens and they don't even know what rape is.
is it's there he's a jellybean guys come on and to post it on a toilet and says
just let this happen yeah man that's sick dude it's awesome
see that's how that's how smart these Rick and Morty writers exactly they're
smart enough to get out of any bind any social justice issue they're kind of a
Rick by themselves you know yeah exactly that's that is a show created by Ricks
let me tell you. That's true. Yeah, but Mortys are the viewers. Exactly. Yeah, that's my problem with Rick and Morty is that yeah, the creators are total ricks, but it feels like the fanbase is just a bunch of Mortys.
Fuck, man. Sorry about it. It is. Worst coffee of my life. I just went to a thrift store and got an espresso machine for $15. Nice. And I opened it up and there was a chunk of coffee still in it that somebody had made.
And they, and then I turned it on and it just made my entire apartment smell like diarrhea.
And I don't know whether, I don't know if it's possible to clean it.
I don't know.
Yeah.
That might not, if it made your apartment smell like diarrhea, it might not be coffee in there.
It might be diarrhea.
You know, that's a really good point.
It might have been a diarrhea cube.
Yeah, someone might have been making a diarrhea latte.
That's a really good point.
Yeah.
Yeah, I used to, when I was a kid,
I had like sand in my backyard,
'cause we couldn't turf it,
'cause we didn't have any money,
or we couldn't sod it,
and I would just make,
I would pretend, play pretend that I was a barista,
and I would make drinks out of mud,
and then I would make my brother drink them.
Nice.
(laughing)
Yeah, dude, making food out of sand,
great childhood pastime. Genius.
I did that whenever I went to the beach,
that's what I would do like I'm gonna make a cookie right now yeah yeah I'm gonna
make a birthday cake with the sand this is gonna be awesome it's gonna look
exactly like a birthday cake and then I would fool my dad yeah I'd say dad look
at this delicious steak dinner from Outback yeah and he goes oh my gosh
somebody left it on the beach great job you really did it and I go you fucking
idiot I got you again you're not he would do he would dive on it my dad would
dive on it face first really and then just yeah and he wouldn't even realize
He would lick it up Scooby-Doo style.
He would, yeah.
We got one big lick and like a "fwk" sound.
And my dad was completely chocked full of sand.
And then he would look into the camera and go "hehehehehehehe"
God, that Scooby-Doo impression is too good.
That's, I think that's only the laugh I can do.
"Raggy!"
Yeah, that's, I can't do that. I just discovered I can't do the voice.
That's not what a dog's voice would sound like, first of all.
Alright, a dog's voice would sound like...
"Raggy!"
Okay?
'Cause that's what a dog sounds like.
I'm a dog.
(laughing)
I'm a chihuahua.
You sound like that.
- Dude, you could strike YouTube gold with that.
Take an old episode of Scooby-Doo.
Dubbing it over with that voice.
- That would be awesome, yeah.
- That would be the biggest--
- What's up, Shaggy?
- If you could travel back in time to 2011 and do that,
you would be making a million dollars right now.
- I would be making an apology video right now.
(laughing)
That's what I would be making.
I would be making some video of me staring at the camera,
and it would be like,
the thumbnail of the just me like this like
so you're looking slightly down and i don't know if you like alone period of
the judges fucked
yeah
uh... and i think ten minutes to get to the the uh... one of the video just in
this meeting like
because you're so you're selling your t-shirt still
yes i know i'm not just twenty dollars by the way is incredibly offensive and
i shouldn't have had to do we do saying you know this is some pink shit
wearing a gold chain it's so offensive but it is still in my store if you want
to buy it as an example of what not to wear
and yes i fucked up so go
go go to uh... racist scooby-doo dot com and get my i fucked up t-shirt right now
use promo code that's just the n-word get twenty percent off
sign up for my apology email list i'll be sending out
weekly apologies with links and coupon codes to my uh... to my uh...
branded Scooby-Doo shoe polish that I'm selling
that you can use. Yeah.
And a huge appreciation to my $10 patrons, including my entire family. Much respect to you.
Bless.
But the entire video, I'm still doing the voice.
Yeah.
Yo, I'm so sorry for doing an offensive accent when I was talking over Scooby-Doo videos.
Real shit, I'm sorry.
It's Scooby-Doo apologizing. I should have gotten a clue.
[Laughter]
Yeah.
Slug, man.
Oh, what are you doing this week besides birthday stuff?
Um, probably gaming.
I'm in a game. I'm back on it.
Yeah? I'm back on gaming.
Oh, man. Speaking of gaming.
I'm gaming hard.
That, uh, we were playing when we were playing Valorant.
I cannot stop thinking about that guy we played Valorant with.
The southern guy.
Oh, Rob?
Yeah, we played Valorant with this guy named Rob.
like we just got matched up with him randomly and he's had a super strong
southern accent and we were he was really bad at the game we were telling I
was telling him like Oh Rob like try like if you're gonna shoot at someone you
should stop walking you should crouch down because it makes you more accurate
and he's like man what the hell kind of game is this thing yeah and he kept
saying stuff like that and just be like man I man this shooting in this game is
so weird man I'm just kidding around man yeah man I'm just playing he was we were
losing and so we were trying to throw the game to so be over faster and Rob
wouldn't throw and then so Caleb was yelling at him and being like we're
gonna lose because of you and you suck yeah and then Rob was like man you know
just for that we're gonna lose this one well my move is just any time I can
cued up with somebody random just like what I leave leave one round I don't say
anything on voice chat. Second round, if we start winning, just immediately, just, "Hey
bro, do you like Kobe, man?" Just start doing that voice, ask him if he likes Kobe. Just
being like, "Man, I'm kind of like the Kobe of this game. Are you like, I'm like, do you
think I'm more like 8 or 24 Kobe?" "Oh, now I, oh he just killed me. Now I'm really like
Kobe Wow man I'm sorry that was offensive man straight up I'm sorry man I'm in
therapy right now and I've just been working on myself and shit trying to not
say stuff like that so I'm just really sorry dude go into therapy for making
bad fucked up jokes about Kobe Bryant specifically about Kobe Bryant yeah and
I was twisted dude I have like the mind of Mencia right now and I've been going
therapy for this since 2013 yeah it's a good thing that he died cuz now I have
something else to joke about about him but yeah man as seriously sad about his
daughter though. Do you have her number? He's asking everybody. You never know. Do you have
Kobe's wife number? I just want to like call her and apologize for all the
messed up jokes and stuff that I've been saying about Kobe Bryant man cuz he's
like a living legend or he's like a legend man. He meant so much to LA man
Cuz I'm you know, I'm from Louisiana. So I like know how much he meant to LA
Yeah, it is my I'm like Creole like obviously if you can't tell from like the way that I'm talking and shit
You know, I'm Nola born and raised, you know when Katrina hit like that was huge for Kobe
That was like his time to shine and then he won a championship that year
So that was like he put the city on his back, bro
And the guys like he's uh, he's going be yeah
He's on he's on bomb. Can you can you guys fucking shoot the other case for once? Can I get a heel?
Right now
We're talking about Kobe
We're talking
Amen, I get that you're like trying to play a game
But we're kind of trying to talk about like one of the greatest players that's ever played football and shit
So can you just like leave us alone? Yeah
I'm sorry. I'm sorry my bad report a new to the game reported reported reported I
Remember it's nice to be playing a game where people talk on the voice chat. I know I missed it so much, dude
Yeah, what does that on on yet? Like I'm like old. Halo reach was always so fun
Yeah, cuz you just do I mean you just do it's just all it was like yeah TF2 voice chat for me
Yeah, TF2 old TF voice chat. Yeah
You just it's never it's never about helping your team win. Yeah, it's just
It's just about having complete anonymity
Yeah, and just saying whatever you want through a microphone exactly. Yeah
I remember ordering a headset when I was like 14 and my mom was like
Why do you want to order a headset and the truth was so that I could do like Jeff Dunham
I kill you voice exactly
I told my mom I was just like just to talk be able to talk to my friends. I need to communicate with my friends
Yeah
It's sick, dude. And now I'm getting now I'm getting my younger brother my nine-year-old brother into games
I've got a strike with him and yes, just immediately he has it in him, dude
Yeah, he dies. Yes immediately. He just whispers just like like he'll get shot and then I'll hear just silence on discord and then I just
like
It's like he's got it dude, yeah, that's it every every kid born after 2000 has the gamer in them
The gamer gene. I think there was something about 9/11 that just spread like computer dust across the world
That's what it made every every kid every just like went into every kid's DNA that now they know how to cause explosions
Tech a small pieces of metal are called microchips exactly when the planes
Vaporized all the metal in the towers it basically spread microchips all over the world and everybody kind of got chipped
Yeah, you know in the left hand, which is that look at the beast? Yeah
That shit freaked me out dude. Have you seen that video that bitch gets a she gets like a key installed in her hand
We're in the network. Yeah, dude. I I found I was learning about this. Um, this theory called project blue beam
Have you heard of project blue beam? No, but I'm excited for it getting really into it
I think it's probably the most like believe not believable. It depends who you are. I think it's pretty believable. But like
It's this idea that like NASA and the New World Order or NASA's trying to create a new world order, right?
And they're doing that by ramping up just events in the world to just be completely insane and and batshit
And then it's gonna culminate they're gonna fake alien alien invasion using like okay
projectors and and like light shows and shit, and then they're going to
They're gonna
Also, they've they've been covering up
ancient religious sites that prove that all religions are actually one religion and they've just been split up
but and all this that but
so there and then they're gonna fake the second coming right and
They're gonna and they're gonna make it look like like the Messiah is saving us from the aliens
And they're gonna use that to make us, you know, I'll come together and unite under a new world order
Okay. Oh
- Oh yeah, all right, yeah, no, I have, yeah, that's fine.
- That's, yeah, doesn't that seem like that's like,
like there's enough crazy stuff going on
and it just keeps happening.
- Well when you say it, I guess my,
I don't know what New World Order really means.
- It's like the New World Order.
- Oh, that's helpful.
Yeah, but is that like they want to install
like a new government that is--
- Yeah, no, it's gonna be awful and oppressive.
It's not a good thing.
- Oh, 'cause it sounds pretty cool.
- Yeah, no, when you read it, it's like,
we're all gonna be one or whatever it's like it's basically just
Evangelion is the thing is this theory is basically just the third impact from
Evangelion can you explain it like I'm not a fucking nerd no sorry okay it's
you're just not smart enough to understand let's go to here so here's
this website right called educate yourself org that I've been kind of
reading through yeah and they have some information on the New World Order here
this is really long one second the war on drugs is a cruel joke that's part of it
got me so far mind control is part of it nice like FEMA is part of it FEMA is
always such a funny thing to include it's like the one the like most
underfunded fucking thing that we have in America and just being like yeah
they're they're actually new world order yeah basically I think people just don't
They don't want everyone to be in the same,
they want a global whatever.
They don't like globalism.
Globalism?
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
I think that's my take.
I think that's good, dude.
Yeah.
I think we should all live in a Google home.
I think we should all live in one giant body
and meld together like a giant homunculus.
Here's what I want, yeah.
I wanna wake up every day inside of a Google home.
I wanna go downstairs, make a Nescafe, right?
Yeah.
a crawler and just fucking start jacking off in my in my battery pack so I
can fuel whatever giant light bulb that's keeping us alive. Exactly. That'll
be it'll be like the Matrix like everybody's a battery but you get to you
get to like play games and stuff. That's the thing the thing about the Matrix the
fatal flaw of the Matrix is that if you if if my job was to be a battery you
could just let me know that. Yeah. You don't have to pretend that I'm like some
that I'm having some horrible life. My ideal life is just being a battery.
Absolutely. Sitting in a pod playing a video game and moving my feet all day.
Yeah. You know what I mean? Like like sitting on like a stationary bike
pedaling it so that all the computers can have their computer kibble and just
playing Mario Sunshine trying to beat like the the speedrun. Yeah the best
Mario Sunshine of all time just a photo realistic real-life simulation I mean it
is true that like you just keep if you just keep making new Mario Sunshine
games yeah just what yeah I'll be made the thing of the matrix is really just a
movie about some real of some terrorists trying to destroy the coolest video game
of all time yeah exactly I just wanted they don't want anyone to have fun
anymore instead of instead of getting to play this awesome VR game we want you to
all live in this post-apocalyptic robot slime world this will be so much better
yeah you got to wake up like a baby and put a spike in your neck
fuck that dude yeah I want I want to go inside the matrix you're gonna have a
thousand guns and learn karate would you rather have would you rather be playing
half-life Alex on easy difficulty with the greatest HTC vive ever known yeah or
would you rather be a fucking little a little baby who has to wake up and and
kiss a girl with short hair. Yeah. To me the answer is clear. Yeah, look, let's look at
women in the inside the matrix. Uh-huh. Okay. Pamela Anderson. Yeah. Megan Fox. That bitch
from G4. Now let's look at women outside of the matrix. Bald. What's her name? Bald. Bald.
Hole in the back of the head. Covered in slime. Inside a pod. Yeah, so what? Yeah, okay, you
get an extra hole. There's a fucking point in your column. Yeah, but if you try to put
- You put your thingy in there, it electrocutes you.
- Short hair.
- So it's not even a usable.
- And no, let's be honest, basically no tits.
- Pretty much. - On this girl.
- Yeah.
- Trinity.
- Trinidad.
- I mean, just, yeah, Trinidad James.
- Yeah.
- See, in the Matrix you have Trinidad James.
In the real life you have Trinity, your bitch wife.
- Trinity Games.
- Who can't stop wearing boy clothes and shooting guns.
- I would never let my woman have a gun.
That's the truth of the matter.
Yeah, 'cause what if one day, you know,
she's on her you know what, and then she flips on me,
you know?
Yeah.
I've been playing games too long,
and she just--
She just goes nuts.
She just unloads a clip.
Yeah, women don't, and the thing is,
you can't hold it against her.
She doesn't have the wherewithal
to even know what she's doing, you know?
So, she's gonna get off scot-free, I'm gonna be dead.
Yeah, and she can just be like,
I didn't know what this thing did.
I didn't know this was a gun.
I thought this was a blow dryer.
I just pressed a button.
Wear a push up bra.
Yeah, women have it so easy getting off of murder.
Yeah.
Wear a push up bra, high heels, get a female lawyer who is slightly less hot than you.
Yeah, suck the judge's dick.
Suck the judge's penis, suck every single one of the jury or his penises, use your pussy
like a puppet and talk with it when you're in court, right?
And then just say, "I'm not guilty."
- Yeah, those two separate witnesses.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
Yeah, yeah, first--
- Yeah, now I'd like--
- One witness is your pussy, one is your butthole.
You make both of them talk with googly eyes on top
like you're Ubu.
- Yeah, thank you Trinity for your testimony.
Now I'd like to call to the stand Trinity's pussy.
Please turn upside down and stand on your hands.
- Please turn up.
(laughing)
Trinity's pussy, please turn up for us real quick.
Please turn out.
- Yeah.
- No, we're gonna do a new matrix though, basically.
- Once we get enough money on the Patreon to build it.
Once we get a million dollars,
we're gonna do a new matrix. - That is, yeah.
I wanna make a better New World Order.
I looked up the New World Order,
and I guess it is less about all being one with each other
and more about, oh, we're gonna make
a totalitarian government that takes over the entire world,
Illuminati style.
- See, the Illuminati, they've really been
waiting for their eggs to hatch here.
They've been really just laying low for so long.
- Yeah.
- When are they gonna pull the trigger on this shit?
Everybody, I mean, it's just every two years,
somebody's like, "It's coming."
- Yeah, it'd be so funny if the Illuminati,
you know, they're just used to just,
so used to operating behind the scenes,
nobody knows who they are.
They're gonna try and take over the world.
They're gonna come to the forefront and be like,
"We're gonna take over all these governments."
And they're just gonna be a bunch of ugly old people.
And everyone's gonna be like,
"Oh no, these guys are too ugly.
"We're not gonna listen to them."
- Exactly, yeah.
- Totally, it's not gonna work.
They can only, like, they already have control
of everything behind the scenes.
Why ruin it by coming forward and--
Do you know anybody who's a Freemason?
No, but I, no, I don't.
I know a guy who's a Freemason.
I did a play in a Masonic Lodge in high school.
Masonic Lodges are pretty,
there's a lot of theater and comedy that happens
in Masonic Lodges.
I mean, it's a nice space.
It's beautiful, you did a great work.
Yeah.
They're Masons, by the way, you know,
so of course they have beautiful buildings.
Yeah, exactly, they build them all themselves.
I know a guy who's like my dad's friend
when I was growing up, who was a Mason.
And he's just like five feet tall
and he puts carpet down for a living.
And he's like a very high level Freemason.
That's so awesome.
He makes like $60,000 a year.
Dude, fuck yeah.
And when you ask him about it, he's just like,
I mean, yeah man, we basically just like
watch movies and stuff.
He just goes like every week, he's like in charge
And he just shows up, he dresses up like a Muslim and starts fucking, puts on the transporter.
Sick, dude.
That's so cool.
I want to join.
I feel like it can't be that hard to join, right?
No, I don't think it is.
I mean, I think you have to be Christian.
Is it a Christian thing?
I know that they believe in God.
Because the G.
He's like, he's Christian, yeah.
The G in the Freemasons logo stands for God.
That's cool.
Yeah, because God was the first Mason.
That's a little fun fact for you, it'll blow your mind.
Yeah, Jesus was the first mason.
Yeah, that's what they think.
Yeah.
Yeah, and they are like of the lineage of God.
Are freemasons Christian?
Yeah, pretty much.
What's his name?
The director, he's like a 33rd degree mason, right?
Which director?
The sixth sense guy.
Oh, Shyamalan?
Yeah.
I didn't know that.
Yeah, that's why he loves twists so much because he's a part of the twist of reality
Yeah, which is that the Masons are running everything. Yeah
That's what freaking signs is about is signs that our government is under control by yeah greater power. Yeah
Am I right? Yeah, and the sixth sense is
is
Being is being cool, which is a big part of the Masons
You have to be cool since 2018 transgender men are allowed to apply to become Freemasons
it's awesome the way you said that like oh dude awesome that's cool good for it
good for them yeah good for the Masons I don't think that women can join Freemason
though yeah the attitude of most regular Anglo-American grand lodges remains that
women Freemasons are not legitimate Masons so you can get led into like your
local lodge but then like the Grand Lodge would be like nope sorry this is your
hand Mason fuck imagine devoting your life but then it's like it's in 2018
guidance was released by the United Grand Lodge of England stating that in
regard to transgender women or a trend train regard to transgender women I'm
Freemason who after initiation ceases to be a man does not cease to be a Freemason
the guidance also states that transgender men are allowed to apply to
become Freemasons. So if you're trans don't come out until after you've gotten
that Mason card. Exactly. Because otherwise you can't get it. Yeah. If you're
gonna transition always become a Mason beforehand just in case you ever want to be a Mason.
Yeah you won't be able, they won't let you back in. So it's just a good idea
everybody should just get registered even if you've never thought about it just
get registered just in case you never know you never know when you might just
transition or become a Mason so you might as well damn dude the Freemasons
were persecuted during the Holocaust there's no are you serious the
preserved records of the Reich search site this is the longest word ever right
I feel like if I was like security show the persecution of Freemasons during the
Holocaust if I was a conspiracy guy that was between 80,000 and 200,000
Freemasons were killed under the Nazi regime.
Oh my god.
Fuck dude.
It's so funny to kill somebody just for being in a club.
Yeah.
You know? Just like, cause it's not
it's not like it's ethnic genocide.
It's just like, yeah, uh, sorry.
We have to put you in a camp cause you're
subscribed to Game Informer.
So, we have to kill you and your whole
family now. Yeah, you guys have a
treehouse so you're gone. Yeah.
You're done for.
you're part of the Scholastic book club so we're gonna we have to destroy you with
a fuck with an oven yeah sorry it's just the rules that's I'm crazy I'm the only
club you're allowed to be in right now if you haven't noticed I feel like I
would have heard more Freemasons complaining about that about like
persecution dude if if fucking Italians had been I know right there you I would
I would have the sickest life right now.
(laughing)
I would be able to say anything I wanted to anybody, dude.
It'd be so awesome.
'Cause the thing is, Italians would also
make a way bigger deal out of it than Jews do.
Yeah.
You know, Italians would just bring it up
at every single point.
'Cause they almost try to.
Like, Italians are like, every once in a while,
they will get close to saying like,
doing the Irish like we were slaves thing.
Yeah.
It's just not true.
They just pretend they're persecuted.
You know?
They'll just be like,
"You don't know how hard it is for us."
Yeah.
And if they finally had something to back it up,
oh my God.
We would've had an Italian president by now.
Yeah.
Yeah, they think they're persecuted
'cause they had to eat a Domino's pizza
at their friend's house one time.
Yeah.
Yeah, they felt like they had to eat it.
What am I gonna do, not eat?
Yeah.
This is a family.
They are family here, I respect family.
Exactly.
Yeah.
It's the, it's the Italian catch-22 between
disrespecting another fam, another family
or eating American Italian food.
Much, eh, much, eh, much respect to the Domino family
but I'm not sure I can abide by this stuffed crust.
Domino.
Eh, much, much respect to the...
Eh, much respect to Mr. Domino
But I'm not sure that a garlic crusty parmesan is exactly my kind of buffalo wing.
I don't know.
With all due respect, boss Domino, the lava cake is just...
This lava cake is to die for, honestly.
It's beautiful.
Domino's honestly is fucking amazing pizza.
I like it a lot.
I love Domino's.
It makes me feel so sick.
New York pizza is shit, dude. I've just been here.
Yeah.
Every pizza place they put broccoli on pizza.
It's fucked up.
Mm-mm.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
What is that? A parent's pizza?
No, thank you.
Also, there's nothing- people say the-
Exactly, yeah.
What, are you trying to sneak vegetables into my pizza?
Yeah.
Yeah, here's a chicken tender with a carrot on top.
[laughs]
Fuck you!
Go fuck yourself.
Yeah.
Here's a spinach cake.
Kill yourself.
Seriously.
Kill yourself!
Yeah.
Yeah, here's a jawbreaker, but in the middle of it, gravy.
Fuck you.
Come on.
Now that...
You know better.
Who do you think I am?
That honestly does sound kind of cool.
Not good, but interesting.
You know, that's, I think, innovative enough, I would try it.
I'm fucking sick of...
I'm sick of savory candy and flavored beers.
That is truly... That is parent shit.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Instead of... Hey, instead of having a chocolate bar,
How about you have a chocolate beer?
- Yeah.
- Hey, how about, yeah, how about--
- You fucking bitch.
- Here's an artisanal chocolate bar
that has flecks of kale and spinach and broccoli in it.
- Here's why they're doing that.
They're trying to make chocolate beer
so that they can eliminate the need for chocolate bars.
- Oh my God.
- So that then kids can't have chocolate
until they turn 21.
- Dude, this is fucked up.
- Talk about a new world order.
Talk about Project Blue Bean.
Project Chocolate, Chocolate Team.
- Chocolate team.
- How about that?
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
- That's a--
- It's serious. - That's what's gonna get us.
- That's the new world order.
- Yeah, they're gonna simulate,
they're gonna simulate,
they're gonna use projectors and light shows
and psychotronic control to simulate
a world shattering event where chocolate bars
start to kill everyone.
- Yeah, exactly. - And they're gonna use that
to unite us against chocolate bars.
- Well, that's what 9/11 was,
was because those were the two buildings
that looked the most like chocolate bars.
And so they were trying to sort of like
in like a psychoanalytical way,
in trying to embed in every kid's head,
hey, chocolate bad.
Chocolate explode. - Yeah, exactly.
Chocolate explode.
- And the planes looked like fingers.
- And it backfired because now every kid
thinks it's the funniest thing in the world
that that happened. - Exactly, yeah.
And there's actually many Photoshops online
of chocolate bars as the tower.
- Yeah, what if a Cheez-It hit the tower
instead. Mmm yeah that's a really good point. Cheese and chocolate. Yeah. Ween.
Actually every mass casualty event of the past 20 years has been an
anti-candy psy-op. Absolutely. 100% undeniably. I'm trying to think right now.
Well first I mean you know Sandy Hook pretty obvious. Yeah.
Every single one that happened in a school that's covered. That's
pretty out you know although yeah Columbine Sandy Hook all that shit's
pretty you know Virginia Tech was that's that's on the border yeah cuz that is
technically a school technically but but it's a little you know yeah maybe a
little old yeah and then what are other what are other times people have died
well Stephen Paddock Stephen Paddock. You gotta get a mention of him in there in the episode or else it's not an
episode. That's true. Yeah, what is with us recently? We just can't stop thinking about
that guy. I think it's because I face-apped him to look like a girl. Yeah. Was that a,
there was a concert, right? Yeah, it was a James L. Dean concert. And I, you know people
were doing some adult candy, some drugs. That's right. You know what I mean? That's right,
dude yeah and also oh the music was sweet yeah exactly okay if you rearrange the
letters in steven paddock you get super parent oh my god I just did it yeah and
if you and if you rearrange the letters in James Aldean you get chocolate bar
it's fucked up dude if you're country music if you rearrange the letters by if
If you write down all the letters and then you crumple it up and you throw it away and
you grab a chocolate bar, then you have a chocolate bar in your hand.
Oh my god, that's so true.
Yeah, fuck.
And then the Ariana Grande concert, she was-
She was-
The classic photo of her eating a lollipop.
She was eating that big lollipop.
When they created that classic joke that we always love to make with each other, big dick
energy.
Yes.
yeah it originally it was it was it was big and how does Patrick eat a big dick
like a candy bar that's right that's the miss Patrick is the missing link in that
one I did Patrick is the missing link for sure yeah between between cavemen
and cavemen between cavemen and cavewomen he's directly in the middle
He's the missing link between those two. We finally got him. Yeah. Is the missing link a
real thing or is that just they just broke that up? Yeah, that's a it's a real thing but it's not it's
probably not as interesting as or I mean I mean it's not like not as interesting as you do is it
like it's not like the missing link in Monsters vs. Aliens. I mean it sounds so interesting. Well I mean it's
not it's probably not a monster from the Black Lagoon type situation. Oh. It's probably just
like looks like a half monkey guy you know what I mean? There is because I mean there's just like
They just want to know how everything evolved into everything else.
Because you know, it's just...
Because they're nosy.
They would just want to know everything.
It's honestly exhausting.
Such know-it-alls.
Yeah.
Can we just relax for one second?
Can we just take it for granted that monkeys and fish are the same thing or whatever the fuck you guys are trying to say?
It's honestly annoying that science documentaries and stuff have just become so, like, ubiquitous.
Because just everybody has...
I feel like starting in 2011, everybody started talking about like string theory and shit
if you ever talked to them for more than 30 minutes.
And it's just like, "Shut the fuck up, dude.
I want to play Minecraft."
The thing is, nobody actually knows anything about it because I mean, it's documented.
Interstellar ruined America.
It really did.
It started giving existential crises to like 29-year-olds.
You know what I mean?
until that point, like, just cared about space.
Yeah, they just cared about, like, Ron Paul.
And now they have to care about, like, black holes and shit.
Yeah.
And so now they start making experimental video games
where you walk around and do nothing.
And at the end it's like, "Isn't life so lonely?"
Fuck you, dude.
I want to play-- make a Knights of the Old Republic 3.
Yeah.
I don't need another fucking gone-home, bullshit-ass,
I'm a lesbian simulator.
I want to play Postal 2, Animal Crossing crossover.
I want to play Postal 5.
Yeah.
I want to play Postal 5 and I want it to be VR.
And you can plug in your real gun.
Yeah.
And you don't have to use your computer and you can just go around your town and play.
Yeah, exactly.
You should be able to play Postal in real life.
What about one of those Minecraft in real life videos by Freddie Wong, but it's Postal
in real life.
You know that old thing that was like, "Tomorrow we're all going to go to McDonald's and ask
for the Fortnite burger, but it's like,
tomorrow we're all gonna go to McDonald's
and kill everyone there.
The look on their faces will be epic.
- Tomorrow we're all gonna go postal.
- Yeah, on postal day.
- When Barack Obama tweets this code word,
we're all gonna go postal on postal day.
- When we go one, we go all.
- That's right.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I do, it does suck that,
I feel like starting this week,
movies, video games, TV, probably ruin forever.
- What do you mean?
probably i think i think there are i think everywhere is coming the fact that
they're like censoring the like
domes always sunny oh yeah so it's a sub i feel like it's all just gonna be the
same show which is fine
yeah whenever about it and and were forced so far away from like the air of
like the postal games
and it is just like we will take it as a we will never get that again they did
well they did recently just make that game was a cold hatred
uh... that's like a mass shooter game
on never mind i take it back america's so that was a twenty fifteen now but they
just ordered it to switch which is so funny
that's sick to player character is a misanthropic mass killer who begins a
quote genocide crusade to kill as many human beings as possible
mhm
uh... isometric shoot 'em up video it's rated a l
uh... okay
the game was surely removed from valve steam green light service due to its
extremely violent content but was later brought back with a personal apology
from Gabe Newell. Oh my god. Whoa dude he got bullied by the mass shooter fans. Yeah.
That's sick dude. I think it's it is so funny that that game is coming to Switch.
I think that's probably the funniest game you can put on Switch. That is hilarious. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah we put we put. It's like what how do you think that there is any that that is
like those are the furthest the Venn diagram where the circles are furthest
from each other is owners of Nintendo Switches and people who want to commit genocide on
the human race.
Yeah, we put a copy of a Serbian film on a Tamagotchi.
Yeah, exactly.
We finally released it on Tamagotchi.
Yeah.
Whoa, this is huge.
We're going to make so much more money.
Yeah, but they also, there will never be a Serbian film level movie again.
It's like making an Evangelion condom.
Yeah.
you watch as Evangelion Love Sex.
Exactly. It's a very good point.
Yeah, but I don't know, man.
I'm...
We're never gonna get...
Uh...
We're never gonna get another jazz singer remake.
I mean, the good thing about it is that
the thing to remember about it is that
corporations and people never learn.
I mean, they'll just be back...
As soon as the spotlight
is off them, they'll just go back to doing fucked up
shit again. Like, so...
it's just gonna go back just to have like a bunch of people like protesting
because a guy got fucking killed to death with a knee and being like you know we're
gonna do yeah we're gonna get rid of the madman episode it's finally time well
the madman episodes the only one they didn't get rid of they just put a
warning at the front like this it doesn't reflect so funny this doesn't
reflect as if people were watching that being like this is what the hell this is
what this reflects exactly the ideology of the people who made this yeah they
put this in here because they think it's funny yeah so sick man we're gonna have
to delete I get all of your blackface episodes of the podcast oh we already
did that was pre episode 30 we already did that yeah sorry that was before
Patrick was on that's what that's why we got rid of those the old school yeah the
original recipes I mean it's just like yeah every so watch every single like
noodle arm Cal Arts emotional trauma TV show yeah it's like I didn't even know
these I don't know people watched these I don't know they existed like they're
awesome dude like Simpsons what is this what is this thing yeah this is a
time we get it in some unfunny fucking gay show about yeah but what dad okay
yeah you're handling the dad's alcoholism he's drink he's addicted to
fucking some duff beer who cares yeah come on what's this South Park this get
this fucking gay emotional show about these kids
who's having to deal with their--
- About these kids wrestling with the death of their friend?
- Yeah. (laughs)
Every episode, they have to deal with their friend's death.
That's, I mean, I don't know.
Back in my day, stuff used to be fucking funny.
- Yeah.
- Like the critics. - Wonder shows in?
What is this, a show for fucking kids?
All right, I'm an adult, I don't wanna watch puppets.
- Yeah, dealing with racism and slavery in a kids' show?
- Yeah, and like really reckoning with it
in a really real and traumatic way.
- What happened, dude?
SJWs they took over they took over cartoons. Yeah, I just want to watch teletypes. Ren and Stimpy?
Ren and Stimpy you're gonna deal with deal with two disabled people?
We have two disabled, two horribly disabled dog people?
That's really the kind of cartoon we have to watch now? Are you serious?
Pinky and the Brain? Yeah. A really smart guy? Are you fucking kidding me?
They're gonna have to cancel Pinky and the Brain because they're not gonna be able to find someone smart enough to realistically voice the brain
Yeah, we had to cancel two Angry Beavers because we couldn't we found one Angry Beaver
But we couldn't find two. And then he cheered up. Yeah, he got happy
We and we thought it was we thought it was animal cruelty to just constantly have him be angry. Yeah, so it's
Yeah, it's kind of sorry one of those
Who is it Allison Brie voiced an Asian character in Bojack Horseman and then yeah, you're being like no, don't worry guys
I had tape on my eyes the whole time. I was doing it. I was giving it I was
I was giving it an old college try. Yes do it as realistic as possible. Listen. I know I'm not I'm not Asian
But that one's funny cuz Bojack did this thing. We're like all of their so they have like these
identity
These characters who have these identities that don't serve any purpose
yeah because they thought they were like this will give us free brownie points
but then people started calling them out for like why is why is like a sexual for
no reason at all like it never comes up in the story yeah like one episode and
then why do you have this like I don't know yeah yeah you have a pedophile
voicing them yeah exactly every Hollywood actor is a pedophile whoa you
really are blue I'm dub dude I'm a brain dude yes you have total smurf brain yeah
I went smurfed up.
Yeah.
Um.
What was I gonna say?
Smurfed up on a Tuesday, baby.
I'm smurfed up on a freaking Friday.
I'm smurfed up on Freaky Friday.
I switch with a smurf.
What's the first thing you would do if you switch bodies with a smurf?
Let's talk about this in the last four minutes.
I'm gonna, I'm, huh.
That's a really good question.
And which smurf would you switch with?
I think I would switch with the girl smurf, because she's the only girl.
Because you want to be a girl?
No.
Yeah.
that girl cuz also we don't we don't even know if she's like a girl like she just
has long hair maybe she has a name is just smurf it maybe she has no no holes
yeah I would I would switch with Gargamel and I would get rid of those
smurfs once and for all yeah you would switch with Gargamel no I would switch
with um you look I'm looking up list of some you would switch with baby smurf I
I wouldn't. You would. I would say... Hey baby Smurf, grow the fuck up.
It looks like there's a lot of girl Smurfs actually.
Yeah, there's Cameron for example.
Who the fuck, there's a guy named Hackis who's a white Smurf.
Who's this guy? There's a white Smurf named Hackis?
There's a white... this picture... I'm gonna share my screen. I'll post this picture as...
with the episode. But uh, look at uh, look at this right here. Smurf Melody. And it's like a deviant
art picture of a smurf standing next to Spongebob. Well, I would be wild smurf. Nat smurfling. The
pictures for these smurfs are, see that's Hackus, the white smurf. Whoa, Hackus. That might be an
Irish smurf. No! Smurf story. I think that people's, Big Mouth. There's the show Big
mouth is on the list of Smurfs. I think that people's deviant art Smurf OCs are
coming up on this list because there's a bunch of deviant art pictures named like
Smurf Storm and Smurf Lily and Smurf Melody. Smurf Kyle. Smurf Kyle. Dude, can you
imagine how much freaking monster energy Smurf Kyle would... Did you ever do the thing where you search your name plus Sonic the
Hedgehog? I have, yeah. Let's do... I don't remember. Let's do... I'm gonna do just Caleb Smurf. Yeah, wait, I'll search
Cameron Smurf. Somebody's definitely done a Caleb Smurf. There's no Cameron Smurf.
These are just pictures. This is pictures of Smurf Inn. Smurf themed hotel in the
Cameron Highlands. That's where you live. I wish I lived there dude. There's so many
good Caleb the Hedgehogs. Yeah when I get rich I'm gonna I'm gonna buy a Smurf
themed house. Let's see. With a bunch of Smurf servants. Smurf-ents. Cameron the Hedgehog is
honestly so on point the one with the sleeveless hoodie let me look it up real
quick yeah that's pretty cool yeah I look badass just doing a peace sign yeah
that's what's up dude let's see Patrick the Hedgehog please be fat please be
fat. This one's a horse Cameron the Hedgehog is drawn as a horse. Honestly Patrick the Hedgehog is like there's a bunch of the same one he's like
yeah robot hedgehog there's a bunch of Irish hedgehogs - yeah Irish the hedge
Irish the hedgehog so sick dude very cool one of them is black and has a chain on
fuck yeah that's the pattern that's true yeah there is that's one is shadow this
this
- You're falling away, you're falling into a big hole.
(Zachary screams)
- That's him falling into a giant hole.
This is my impression of Squidward and Scooby-Doo.
- Hey bro, you like Squidward, man?
That's the other thing that I love to do is just go,
it's just on Valorant, just constantly, just like,
hey man, are you going A or B?
I like to call him like Squidward and SpongeBob.
(Zachary laughs)
Yo, he's on Squidward, bro.
It's just, it's never-ending fun.
- Yeah, you wanna play Valorant tonight?
Yeah, I'm down.
Yes.
Just don't be a Squidward when we play, man.
Yeah.
Don't worry.
Be like a grumpy little blue guy and shit, dude.
Yo, crabby-
Squidward is a freaking smurf.
Mr. Crabby Patty, though.
He's like about his paper, though.
Mr. Crusty.
Mr. Cr- Yo, Crusty the Crab, like, he's kinda like-
He has like-
He's kinda like a small business owner and shit.
Crusty the Crab is like kinda-
Basically, like, Sandy Cheeks is like my dream woman.
Cause she's like always wearing a space suit and shit
And like I don't know man, I'm sorry man I've been smoking all day man
Basically it's indica which is like the Patrick Star of like
Yeah it's like indica, indica is like Patrick and sativa is like Squidward
I've been smoking this strain called Marble Red
It's making me crazy
It's so cool man, they started selling weed just like in little cartons
They have like little white joints, it's super cool
They even put a filter on it for you dog. It's so sick, man
Yeah, anyway, do you like more of a Squidward type high or like
I feel like when I smoke Spongebob I just like sit on a couch all day don't get anything done
Oh, we're not weak. I when I smoke we're tonight. I learned to play the clarinet
Yeah, basically, I'm a I'm one of the staff writers on shrill and like this next season
that's coming up is like heavily inspired by Spongebob and shit. Basically we're
doing like an entire Spongebob type season. It's like have Spongebob have Dante's
Inferno. There's gonna be like four levels of bikini bottom. There's gonna be like the
pineapple house, the squidward house, the rock house, and the crusty crap too. And then the
chumbucket is like, it's like hell dude. The chumbuppie is like one of the
It's the sickest place dude.
Yo I know this awesome fucking club down the street dude.
One dollar modellos.
It's called the Chum Bucket and shit bro.
Basically it's like the greatest place on earth.
They got a one eyed bouncer named Plankton.
Yo he has like, yo my bro Plankton is crazy bro.
He has like, dude he has this wife dude.
Straight up computer.
She's like a absolute, yo talk about a Karen bro.
She's a fucking computer bro.
*laughing*
She's a total- yo, all these people shooting these videos of Karen's, these are human women!
I thought they were gonna be computers and shit, making holographic meatloaf!
What the fuck, bro?
This total Karen tried to steal the recipe for the Krusty Krab Krabby Patty.
He's total Karen made me a holographic meatloaf and I took a bite into it and I didn't even taste anything man
I need that secret recipe
Yeah, my boy my voice box hurts now, yeah, you got a box and you're gonna box you got a box belt
You got a box. It's a wait your penis box, but it's reverse
That's right. Premium. Yes, Stan Patrick a normal episode Stan Patrick
It was five star reviews. It was five star views. Wish me a happy birthday
Please if you're listening today, you got to go online and wish our boy a happy birthday. It's just a necessity
recess nest and
We were broke
I have on stance Squidward because of the actions in that yoga class
I'm hearing a lot of accusations as Squidward like doesn't play to clear in a very well and it's actually like
It's actually like terrible, but I don't know he's like one of my faves
So I'll have to like wait for more information and shit. Some of your faves will be implicated
Yeah, some of your faves will be implicated including Squidward. Yeah, including mr. Krabs
Either yeah, there's blood on mr. Krabs claws. So it's freaking red, you know, yeah
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about. All right, honestly, dude, his whale daughter is like bad AF like honestly
Like, you know, she got some huge knockers down there, dude
down there cuz she has a whale body so like her like boobies are on the bottom
I bet that blowhole is like this dude I bet it's like this bro all right bye
okay okay are you guys done recording I just got set up I hope you guys didn't
say I'm like the missing link between a caveman and a cavewoman or that I eat a penis like
a candy bar or something.
Are you guys done recording?
You guys?
Hello?
Guys?