you're listening to Israel's number one podcast
if you are not a premium subscriber please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately
recording now
alright so right off the bat i know i asked you guys this i think yesterday
but what's your loadout for the janitor student ball
what are you guys wearing
i want to hear full outfit, accessories, inventory
full loadout
full loadout for the janitor student ball
janitor student ball it's coming up really soon
and it's tonight
it's not a it's tonight at ten p_m_ tonight
and i had a m
it's out it's but we have to know little space between the dumpster and the back
of the school there's a door
ongoing is invisible man so i can dance of my mom and i'm
makes fun of me
yeah people like what happens is really good dancing alone
She's really good at pretending.
I'm going as the scariest costume I can think of.
It's not a costume ball.
Rudy Giuliani.
Oh my god, yeah, Rudy Giuliani's balls.
The scariest costume I could ever think of.
What are you going as, Cam?
I'm going to wear jeans and a t-shirt.
Are you going to wear a tuxedo t-shirt?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm going to wear a tuxedo.
It's the scariest thing you can think of, Louis C.K.
Yeah.
Black t-shirt and blue jeans.
No, I'm wearing a tuxedo pants.
They're like their pants but they're printed.
They're made out of like t-shirt material.
Like Louis in 2017.
They look like they have a tie on the legs.
That's actually a good idea.
We should put up on the teespring like sweatpants and just paste like the print pattern of the
tuxedo shirt onto them.
That's not a bad idea.
Be like bottoms, bottom green day.
Green bottoms.
be like Green Day. What are you talking about? The Green Day of pants. The Green Day.
I mean like Bottoms Green Day. Green Day didn't wear tuxedo t-shirts. They wore shirts with ties on them.
Yeah, they hated corporate culture. So that's what we would be making fun of.
Yeah, it's like Bottoms Green Day. It's Bottoms Green Day. You guys didn't
understand what I was saying really no no I really could not have decided let me
try this again bottoms green it's not it's not working it's connecting people
at home are understanding this you're what about like what about like a little
bit like yogurt and it's like green day on the bottom what great no see that's
what it feels like that's what it feels like a look no do you're not making any
sense dude. What if it's like it's like bottoms up but instead of up it's
Green Day. Bottoms Green Day to you. That's what you say when you're about to listen to a Green Day CD.
Mm-hmm yeah and enjoy it like it's refreshing. Yeah. Bottoms Green Day.
Yeah. Drop that needle. Yeah you say bottoms Green Day and the other guy says
what you mean the yogurt with Green Day on the bottom are you talking about
those pants with the ties on them. There's so many things you could be talking about.
You just say Bottoms Green Day. Exactly. What you mean by Bottoms Green Day. That's why you guys were confused.
There's too many possible. There's three or four different Bottoms Green Days. Is it like a gay culture thing?
Bottoms Green Day? Is that? It's like a gay guy's period. It's just Bottoms Green Day.
It's like the band that's under Green Day? The band that plays under the stage while Green Day is playing?
yeah the little band that plays under the stage
a gay guy's period is when he has like katsu chicken curry the night before no
yeah come on man come on caleb come on caleb you too nasty caleb you nasty as
hell that's so nasty i'm sorry that's my strawberry banana kind of funny though
but low-key that's kind of funny but it kind of made me giggle
I'm kind of losing my giggles over here.
I kind of got a giggle.
I'm kind of making the giggles pop out.
You're letting my giggles go free.
You're letting the giggles pop out.
That's my bad, bro.
That's my bad.
I'm off the Strawberry Banana Puff bar, which is a vehicle in New York City.
You literally said you're never going to buy another one.
I know.
You said that the other day.
Guess what I am?
A liar.
I know.
The second you said that, I said, "I do not believe you."
And you were like, "No, I'm serious."
I'm evil.
You're evil like a liar. I'm evil and I'm a liar and I'm gonna lie to you guys the
rest of your lives. Tell a lie right now. I hate both of you. What? Yeah. I just said it
was a lie dude. Oh you were lying when you said it was a lie. When I said
tell me a lie you lied by not telling a lie. I said tell me two truths and a lie
and you said you would love me forever. A little trick for people listening if you
want to get illegal vape substances in New York City, go to a Middle Eastern smoke shop.
Go to a Middle Eastern smoke shop, they just don't, they don't even pretend that they're
not selling it.
Yeah?
Yeah, you walk in.
They have it on the walls and shit?
Yeah, you walk in, the guy's like FaceTiming a baby.
He's got airpods in.
As you're ordering, he's whispering to the baby, he's like, "shrp, shrp, shrp, shrp,
shrp, shrp."
And then you pick a flavor, you're like, "I'll have poop."
he's like oh dude poops the best flavor we have to turn the phone around and
showing you showing a baby to you the baby is looking at you the baby the baby
that puts on an evil grin when it sees you yeah it's really scary yeah the
baby's always dressed I hate it I hate it when the baby has an evil grin baby
the baby is also at a different smoke shop working the counter and they're
just talking about who fucking knows what very quietly though yeah there's a
there's an empty birdcage there is an empty birdcage in there yeah and I'm
like what size are you don't worry about it or I thought you're just saying that
you're talking about there is a bird you were talking about the fake shop for a
second I know you're speaking to code yeah you're trying to activate one of our
mk ultras yeah yeah i wasn't trying to do that so there's this empty bird cage
oh yeah i activated activated patrick's funny voice
you activated you activated the devil said the red door
Hey man what you talking about the red door?
(Laughter)
Red door what that mean?
(Mumbling)
I feel different
(Laughter)
He activated his 645 setting
(Mumbling)
(Laughter)
What?
That's the funniest voice to talk in now
Squeaky 645 AR voice
Yeah it is very funny
I want an opposite
rapper who sounds like the devil yeah okay
645 you need to stop rapping so good
I'm watching TV
you're rapping too good 645 AR
yeah they could have like a bad meets evil thing
oh there we go 666 AR
what the heck is this
that was the devil popping out of me
I came back from the store
(gibberish)
You sound like, you sound like uh, what was his fucking name?
Is it Vincent D'Onofrio?
The guy who played the bug guy in Men in Black, you sound like him.
That was a real bug?
Yeah, it was a real bug.
Is that based on a real bug?
That was based on a real bug, yeah.
You guys know that?
The big bug.
It's called Beetle.
Yeah, it's called the Mr. Beetle.
No it's not.
Mr. Baby Beetle Boy.
What have you guys been doing today?
I walked to the store.
We walked to the store pretty much.
Hey, not everyone at once.
Alright.
What movie did you watch?
Okay, who first?
Okay, Cam first.
I watched a movie and then I walked to the store.
To get bread.
That's pretty cool.
I used to have bread.
Well, I used to have toast.
My bread used to be toast, but now I have new bread.
have new bread. Can you scrape enough toast off toasty shit off of the top of
bread to make it or top of toast to make it bread again? You could. Yeah I think so.
You think so? Yeah cuz it's like I mean unless you're really you're really
scorching it. Cuz it's just getting to this. So yeah. You know what my uncle did
that with a hot dog one time. He scraped off the burnt part? He burnt the fuck out of a hot dog
and then just like peeled it like a banana.
He peeled the skin off a hot dog? He did that, it was like Fourth of July.
When you say like a banana, did he peel it like with his fingertips from the top?
Yeah, and then he ate every part that he like charred.
That's what people will do with marshmallows, when they're roasting marshmallows too.
That's true. They set it on fire and then peel off the outside. Those people are stupid.
You leave the burnt outside on. The burnt is the best part. Yeah, it's really good.
yeah yeah that's what I'm saying yeah and outside of a hot dog is also the best
part when I when I grill when I put a hot dog on the grill I cut out all the the
grill lines and I just eat those mm-hmm little black lines that are on the hot
dog I snored him dude I died oh they're so delicious charcoal I eat them like
little Mike and Ikes but they taste like a burning fire yeah I put Mike and Ikes
in my s'mores what about you Pat? Yo my little brother the other day it's clear
he like just learned that somebody on like TV or something put Skittles in
popcorn because he's been to the movies isn't been in the movies in like two
years probably and yesterday I was talking to him on the phone he's like
"You know what I love my popcorn? Skittles." I was like "Yeah?" He's like "Yeah, I love
eating Skittles in my popcorn." I was like "Do you?" and he's like "Yeah, I've been
doing it forever." I didn't even ask him. I was like "I've just been doing that forever."
That's so funny when like a kid like learned something from a TV show and it's
just like oh that's like that's me that's a real thing and then that's me.
That's a thing I do. Yeah, there's so many there's so many things like that
that I feel like I did as a kid? Oh yeah dude. For me the ultimate one was I
told kids that I ate pussy because little Wayne said it. But I also
thought that you could see. I also love the taste. Yeah and I love eating pussy. Yeah I suppose now when I do not tell anybody that I ate pussy.
But I thought that the pussy was something that came out of a woman. Oh
yeah you did you told you you said that many times. I thought it was like an egg or like a like I thought
it was more of like a film. Damn baby I'm gonna eat your whole thing. Like a jello. Yeah yeah I thought
that it was like I thought that it was like um like kind of an edible saran wrap that yeah like
like a glaze that appeared on the vagina and then you ate it off and then you had to wait until it
came back. Until it grew back yeah. Yeah exactly. It's like a lizard's tail. Yeah women have lizard's
tales that you eat yeah yeah yeah but that was my big lie when I was a kid
yeah I'm trying to think I'm not sure there was probably some I feel like some
food that I probably ate because it was on it oh you know what wasn't me but my
cousin got for his like fifth birthday he saw Scooby-Doo put chocolate on a ham so
So we got, so his birthday dinner that we all went to was chocolate ham.
We ate chocolate ham for his fifth birthday.
That's a lot.
I definitely, when I was a, when I was little, I definitely thought alphabet soup was really
cool as I had, like had it and I was like, oh, we need to get alphabet soup.
You know what's like in the knocko from Kim Possible.
What's that?
What that is?
It's a nacho taco.
Oh, that.
I always wanted to make that.
Now they got that at Taco Bell.
One of those things where it's like people are like, "Wow, food in
the food in Miyazaki movies
looks so good. It looks so
delicious and it's drawn with love and care
but it's just all the food from Scooby-Doo
that like shat in your mouth."
Yeah, chocolate fucking ham.
It's the pasta from Elf
with all the maple syrup.
Welcome back to Binging with Babish.
Today we're going to be making the chocolate ham from
Scooby-Doo.
Yeah, the first step is you take a ham.
That is a honey chocolate glaze.
You're never going to guess what the second step is.
It's crazy how popular...
Dude, chocolate and mustard, could you imagine that together?
Yes.
Do it right now, go eat it.
Salty and sweet.
I don't know, I don't think chocolate...
I feel like chocolate and mustard do not...
I don't know, maybe I have to go try it.
Honey mustard is...
Honey's basically chocolate.
You're right, it comes from the same...
I am so smart and I just got smarted so easily. Does anybody else want to duel?
Any takers? No?
We're doing a brain logic thing.
What are you dueling me with?
What do you do with that big fat butt?
I'm going to duel you about abortion.
This is the abortion episode?
Go ahead. No, you go first.
Abortion's murder. Your turn.
Okay, abortion is not murder.
not you're not even in the duel. Oh it's Patrick. Yeah, wait your turn. That's how duels work.
You take turns. It's not about who's faster. Oh now I'm getting piled on by you fucking
abortion loving commies. God will never change his mind now. Abortion is okay as long as you
put it back later. Abortion is okay as long as you use the baby in a movie as a prop.
true yeah Hollywood needs as long as you as long as you use it to play the the
mole rat in the live-action Kim Possible exactly yeah that's the main that's the
main export from play yeah is to this set of the live-action possible movie
no I honestly I think abortions okay if it goes towards if the stem cells go
towards like hair regrowth yeah or if they figure that out then I'm fine or if
the delicious cells go into coca-cola that's also no it's pepsi pepsi doesn't
need shit pepsi rocks no I don't I don't have a dog in this fight the pepsi coat
debate now we have a duel now we have a duel on our hand coke is better than
pepsi cuz it it just tastes better no it doesn't it don't you like it cuz it it
It sounds like cock.
No.
Yeah.
That's ad hominem.
Cameron, please moderate.
I'm not the moderator.
You're the moderator.
You guys are shooting at each other and missing wildly and then I walk in and I don't even
have any guns and I just point at you both and you explode like Dr. Manhattan.
What's your opinion that makes us do that?
I don't drink soda at all.
Oh my god.
Oh yeah, that's right.
Yeah.
I've never seen Cameron drink soda.
That's completely destroyed.
Yeah.
Wow.
I hate getting so owned like that.
Cameron's teeth must be so nice.
They're really not that nice.
God, I want to get, I want to replace my teeth with cameras.
You can get into my teeth if you want.
I want to get your teeth.
Gimme them.
You can have them, dude.
Come and get 'em.
I get 20 bucks from the Tooth Fairy.
What?
That's how good my teeth are, dude.
Damn.
I've had like a bump in my mouth right here.
That's neat.
It's really surprising that--
It's mouth cancer, it's the big one.
Yeah, the big mouth cancer.
It's surprising to me that more kids
don't knock their own teeth out to try and get money from the tooth fair.
I knocked my teeth out as a kid.
I mean like you kind of like yeah like I was fucking attaching my teeth to shit just running
around the house.
Yeah.
Just like gluing on myself.
I was a little freak.
I feel like you'd see more often like kids just like fucking clocking themselves in the
mouth just to lose like a bunch of teeth at once.
Kids don't really like money that much.
No.
Well I, money buys toys.
No kids, it depends on the kid.
I mean I think that to like if you get ten dollars and you're like in like fifth grade
you're like, "Holy shit, dude, I'm gonna go down to the store
"and I'm gonna get a slushie."
Like, that's like the best, you could get five slushies.
It's crazy, dude.
- True, that opens the world up.
- I could go buy a toy.
I think saying, I mean, it depends on the age of the kid,
but I think saying, have you ever seen
Ed, Edd n Eddy, dude?
- Yeah, I mean, what was I even thinking?
- Those kids go fucking nuts for money.
- Yeah, I mean, these kids are addicted to money.
- They're addicted to jawbreakers.
- Oh my God.
Jesus Christ.
So you just lost another duel.
I, another duel, another L on my belt, dude.
You're about to have, that's four L's.
Can we go back to our position?
You're building your way to four L's in a certain formation.
You're putting your four L's in a circle.
No.
Yeah.
I'm not, dude, come on.
Yeah, you are.
No, come on.
What else can we duel about?
Should've stretched out before.
Caleb is gonna get a W and then he's gonna follow it up
with an E-H-R-M-A-C-H-T.
(laughing)
- No.
- He's gonna be like, "Finally, the letter
"that completes my belt."
- He's walking around with an air mocked.
- Yeah.
That's why he's trying so hard to win these duels.
- No, I don't need that letter.
- Yeah, you do.
- No, I'll take any other letter now.
- Yeah, right now he's got lair mocked.
- Yeah.
- Which is kind of a funny nickname for someone named Larry.
He's trying to get the dual stopped in the middle so he can get two S's for stopped.
No I don't want that dude.
He wants to put those onto his body.
I may have said this before but the guy who tattooed me the first time was just like a
dumbass dude.
I don't think I've said this on the podcast.
This dumbass dude who was like my brother's good friend growing up and he's tattooing
me in the middle of it and he tells me he's like "Yeah man I mean I had a guy come in
the other day that people ask for crazy stuff I had a guy come in the other day
asked for SS bolts on his arm I was like holy crap that's crazy he's like yeah
man so I charged him like 80 bucks for him
right yeah he did it he was like yeah I've done SS bolts and Confederate flags
I was like dude. Yeah get them all on YouTube. I was like well now that I know that you know
how to do one. He was only he was he wouldn't have told you that if you
didn't look like you did. Right. No this is back when I had hair. You still looked
you still looked evil with hair. No I looked I looked like a scooby-dog. You looked like a
bully. You're just like the pre-evo of an American history ex. You
were like the you were like the Eevee to the to the Vaporeon. No dude no I looked
like it I look like just Poryon. I looked like Candy. Yeah dude. I looked like Candy and
everyone loved me. You don't look like Candy. I can't wait till you turn 18 in
September. I'm turning 18 in September. What are you guys gonna celebrate online?
We're all turning 18 in September. We're all turning 18 on the same day in September.
yeah yeah we're brothers teens get excited we're putting out a calendar yeah mm-hmm
yeah it's pictures of our butt we can finally stay up past 12 and leave the
house and get it up till 7 last night when I turn 18 I'm gonna do several boys
yeah yeah I'm finally going to what kind of stuff I don't know
- Whatever is in the closet.
- Whatever they want.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Yeah, but I'm actually--
- You're not really gonna--
- I'm actually 15.
- I'm actually 12 years old.
- Put your mouth where your mouth is.
- Yeah, I'm turning 18 in September,
but not this September.
That's 17 years away from me.
- It's a couple of September's away.
- I'm one year old.
- I'm a little guy.
- I'm a little, I'm that little one year old
who looks like Andy.
(laughing)
No, no, that's just what I am.
You fucking freak.
You gross little freaky.
You gross little candy piece of candy.
You little, you're a little.
Which one of us looks the most like candy?
Would you eat a one year old piece of candy?
Oh yeah, I would.
You would eat a one year old who looks like candy.
No.
You're putting words in my mouth, brother.
No, I said would you eat a one year old who looks like candy?
No.
A one year old who looks like a piece of candy.
No, definitely not.
What about a one year old candy?
I've eaten one year old candy before, easy.
I've eaten chocolate where the whole thing was white.
It's called white chocolate.
No, no, you don't understand.
It was so old that it was just stark white.
And it tasted like shit.
Yeah it tasted like cookies and cream.
It was weird.
Yeah, some of it was still black, pitch black like chocolate is.
Yeah.
And it tasted like mayonnaise and it was all goopy.
And it was in a mayonnaise jar.
Yeah, that was my chocolate.
No.
Oldest chocolate of all time.
I would eat like a very old mint.
I'm not sure I would eat old candy.
I would eat very old candy.
See?
Oh boy, I'm so tired.
I don't care about eating candy off the ground if it's still in the wrapper.
used to give me shit for that yeah if it's in the wrapper that's fine
yeah if you find candy in the round yeah it's in the wrapper like someone made
what a man are we like in the hallway at school one time not like the sidewalk oh
and the sidewalk if it's still in the wrapper and it's clear that it hasn't
been stepped on I'll maybe gamble you know and take a bite I did I will say
recently I ate it was like a half empty pack of gum and I just ate all the gum
Yeah, what if I like if you find like I was in the air what am I talking about when I was in the airport?
I found the air force. I found like some trail mix on the ground. I ate that. Yeah, it had been open
Yeah, if it hasn't been opened and it's on the ground, that's fine. No, I had find it. Oh, well, that's different
Yeah, I wouldn't do that. Somebody's hand was probably in it. You know what?
No, cuz it I used to fucking at the skate park
I we played a game called water bottle roulette, which is where if you went there without water and you were really thirsty
You would just kind of gamble on whether or not you would know the waters that people would leave. I've done that
Basketball, yeah, yeah
Trash at that at that skate park all the time. So you ever have Jack if you and your friends were there. Yeah
Oh, yeah a bunch of white. What do you ever drink a peepee when you were doing that? No
Do you ever drink anything?
anything other than water I
I think Gatorade one time.
- Did you ever, like, did you ever drink something
thinking it was water and it wasn't water?
- No.
- So you never lost that game?
- Well, water becomes stagnant.
- What?
- And if you drink stagnant water, you get sick.
- What do you mean?
(laughing)
- Stagnant.
- Stagnant water.
- Stagnant, what do you mean?
- That's like a pond.
- Yeah.
- That just means water that doesn't--
- Stall water is not flowing through a body of water.
- Stagnant water is standing water that's--
okay
it like a cup
it goes bad
i didn't know that that's not the word for it
there is no word for it
water doesn't go bad in a cup
yeah it could go bad in the direct sunlight in a plastic bottle
i mean the bpa could leak into the water yeah that's what i mean
that's what he means by stagnant. I meant BPA could leak into the water bottle.
Patrick gets a glass of water and he walks around his house just
shaking it back and forth really fast the whole time so it doesn't get stagnant.
I didn't know it had to do with ponds. No, that's like where where mosquitoes
live. Stagnant water. That's where mosquitoes thrive. Fucking stupid as shit. No, come on. Hey, hey Pat.
We might have gone too hard on you there, buddy.
It was really funny, but it's not your fault.
It was probably your parents' fault.
It's probably your stupid parents' fault for teaching you bullshit like that.
Yeah, your dumb fucking parents.
They didn't teach me that.
Fucking dumb ass parents.
Yeah, it's their fault for letting you have a thought by yourself.
That's true.
Yeah.
All my thoughts should be shared with your parents until you're 18.
Yeah, like your phone.
Yeah.
Yeah, your parents should be allowed to look at your phone all the time.
I agree, dude.
Yeah, when I when I was a kid I my mom would do that shit all the time and so my it always looked like I
Had no friends and no text messages, and that's the reason why yeah, I think I think every ten minutes on this episode
Or every seven minutes
Caleb has said something that is that he said before
Yes, he's repeating himself today. I'm sorry. I woke up from a nap. It's because they're calling him
Wait, you guys got us you were
You were napping. I was napping and I don't remember what's a dream and what's reality right now.
I might be spinning a top on my table.
Whose dog is that? I don't know. You don't know? You don't know? Who knows? No idea. Any chance it's your dog?
No.
No. No, couldn't be. What do you guys think I should get into MMOs? Yeah, if you could, yeah.
Like World of Warcraft? Yeah. Do you think I should get into it?
I had to get into World of Warcraft so bad when I was a kid, but I wasn't because my parents
would never let me like pay them for the subscription, you know what I mean?
Like I would have to like use their credit card and then give them money and they were
just like no.
Yeah dude, I fucking did that with, I bought a used copy of Star Wars Old Republic at GameStop.
That game rocks.
Yeah, but I didn't know that you had to pay $15 a month to fucking play it.
So I got it and I had like the 60 day free trial, but I didn't even think it was worth
it.
I just like returned it.
You know what I played so much as a kid?
The best game, uh, Adventure Quest.
Do you guys play Adventure Quest?
Oh yeah dude, of course.
It was so sick.
'Cause you can make your name into this, uh...
Yeah, I think my name...
I'm gonna get into Star Trek Online.
I think my name was like Excalibur or something, but I misspelled it.
Mine was like Mr. Diarrhea.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Yeah, Mr. Boombox Diarrhea.
Why?
That's a... I just feel like that's a pretty good cross-section of who we were like 10 years ago.
I was like...
Yeah, you were like Mr. Diarrhea.
and I was like Excalibur!
It's still what I name all my shit.
Excalibur is a really good one.
I played Star Trek Online
when I
first got to Emerson and
my username was Frazier Crane
so that's great, that's a really cool thing.
That's really cool, and college.
Yeah. That's awesome
dude. Uh huh.
It's so fucking cool. The second half of college
like you're old enough to drink
and you're like Star Trek Online, Frazier Crane.
your grade mm-hmm well it was a joke for me because the show is quite funny
grammar Kelsey grammar was in Star Trek so I mean that's a that's a great joke
that's a pretty good joke Wow I wish I'd gotten into like Eve online or one of
those like insane MMOs where it's like they have like fucking like spend your
life on it yeah yeah it's just like I like another world line there's like a
big scam in Eve online yeah there was like they like it was there was something
happened recently where there was like the first like the first contact with
like extraterrestrials or something that game sounds insane yeah yeah
they have like wars yeah yeah I read something once about like a person like
in a rival clan joint like made a new account joined the other clan got worked
his way up to the top and then just fucking sabotaged like an entire like
like hundreds of thousands of dollars that people funneled into like their
like little like clan that's pretty sabotage the whole thing that's sick
that's so cool the fuck that was that's why I want to get into mm oh yeah that's
what we need to do I want to have like a Machiavellian plot against some people I
don't know yeah you think you know we need to do in the in the fucking Star
Wars G mod server dude yeah that's not a bad idea true I guess that is kind of an
MMO yeah it's true people going on and spending their time I just think it's
It's funny to get into a role playing game like that online.
That shit rules.
Yeah.
I could never play, I can't play online games that much.
I'm not good at games.
Cause then everyone will know that I suck.
I feel like things like EVE though, do you have to be good at it?
Or do you just have to be amazing and pretend?
There's like combat, it's super complicated.
- Because it's just like, yeah, you have to know everything.
I mean, I don't, it's literally like a game
where you fly around spaceships and it's like super,
it's supposed to be like super realistic or something.
I think it's probably pretty complicated.
- I also played, 'cause they had it on Steam,
I played DC Universe Online.
- Oh, nice. - Oh, yeah, those were great.
- Yeah. - Yeah, you make a superhero
named Diarrhea Man. - Yeah.
- And he's like the diarrhea superhero.
- Yeah, and he does poop tricks.
- And he does poop tricks, yeah.
- For money. - You can make a villain too.
- Diarrhea of a woman.
- Diarrhea of a woman?
- Diarrhea woman.
- Diarrhea of a woman.
- No.
- Are you saying diarrhea of a woman or diarrhea?
- Diarrhea woman.
- Diarrhea of a woman?
And she's a woman version of diarrhea man.
But she's nasty, naughty. - So it's like bad girl?
- Yeah, she's a bad girl, you could say that.
(laughing)
Like RiRi.
- Yeah.
Who, what?
you guys Stan Riri? No. What are you saying? No? What are you saying? Rih-Rana? Rih-Donna? Rih-Rina? Rih-Rana? Rih-Rana?
Rih-Rana? Are you guys Stan Rih-Rana? Yeah, dude. Um, fuck. I just re-watched Almost Famous. Yeah. Jason
Lee's in that movie. Jason Lee is in that movie. He was he was my favorite actor
when I was nine years old.
- Bruce Lee's son.
- Yep.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, he's dead.
- He's my favorite actor 'cause of My Name is Earl
and he was a pro skater in the 90s.
And I thought that was the coolest career.
- He was a pro skater, really?
- Yeah.
- But he's such a talent.
- He's very talented.
He's a great actor.
Jason Lee, come on the podcast anytime.
I'd love to talk to you about leaving Scientology.
- Yeah, I don't think he works much anymore, does he?
He was a Scientologist too?
- Yeah, he was a Scientologist
and he like just left the church.
Well fuck dude.
And he named his kid fucking Pilot Inspector.
I've definitely talked about this.
Pilot Inspector?
No.
I've never heard anything about Jason Lee.
I just knew he was cool.
And I got him confused with Ryan Reynolds until Ryan Reynolds became really famous.
You got him confused with Ryan Reynolds?
Yeah.
He's Canadian.
I like that you think that is like...
Yeah what...
What the fuck dude?
You can tell Ryan Reynolds is Canadian.
I didn't even know which one you meant was Canadian right then.
I don't know I didn't know that Ryan Reynolds was Canadian. Yeah, he's Canadian
What what I know? Yeah, what an a D and P is you can just tell his voice you think he has a Canadian voice
He has a Canadian accent. Yeah, it's the same as it's
Whatever his name is John Lee Jason Lee Jason Lee is from California
He's probably let me cuz he might have a West Coast Canadian accent
- Yeah, Ryan Reynolds, the first thing that pops up,
yeah, yeah, 'cause he's from Vancouver.
So he's got a West Coast Canadian accent.
- Okay.
(laughing)
- And this is supposed to be obvious?
- How can you not tell that guy's Canadian?
- I've never known that.
- How can I tell?
Yeah, there's no way to tell.
- Canadian people, to me, Canadian people are in Canada.
If they're outside of Canada, can't tell.
What do you mean you can't tell?
They start saying fucking a boot and
eating ketchup chips and shit?
Ryan Reynolds doesn't say a boot or
eat ketchup chips in his movies.
He does.
He never plays a Canadian.
When?
Deadpool is Canadian.
Deadpool's not Canadian.
Yeah he is.
No, Deadpool's not.
Van Wilder?
Deadpool's from Florida.
You're telling me Van Wilder is not a Canadian name.
It's Burt Kreischer.
No.
Yeah.
That's who that's supposed to be.
No, it's supposed to be Ryan Reynolds.
No.
Yes.
You are so dumb about people and stuff.
I'm the smartest guy of this people and stuff.
Yet another duel.
No.
Yet another duel that Caleb wins.
It's the one I won.
My record's looking like WLLLLW right now.
How many L's was that?
Who cares?
Three or four.
Yeah, how can you not tell that guy's Canadian?
I can't tell, dude.
We can't tell.
His brother's a fucking Mountie. It says that.
Why would I know what his... He doesn't talk about his brother.
He's the most Canadian guy of all time.
No, he's not. What are you talking about, dude?
He's like, he's like one of the most Canadian guys.
Who? No. No.
Yes. Not at all. Yes. No.
I... Is Weird Al Canadian?
No.
See, I thought he was.
Now look at our... Weird Al is from Linwood.
I thought... Do not remember.
Straight out of Linwood. I thought Linwood was in Canada.
Canada. Yeah, I could, alright, I can see that. I thought he was a Canadian Jew. Alright, name
every Canadian person that you know, Patrick. Because a Canadian idiot? Name every Canadian
celebrity that you know. And we're gonna check them. Drake. Not Canadian. He's from the six.
Not Canadian. That's the sixth state of America. Yeah. That's what he means when he says that.
He's from Georgia. Well, you can't tell where Drake is from. Next celebrity. One day he's
- He's a UK grime singer, the other day he's from Jamaica,
you don't know.
- Get his ass, dude.
(laughing)
- All right, so Drake doesn't count.
Fucking Nathan Fielder's Canadian.
- Not Canadian.
- I do know he is Canadian.
- He says that at the beginning of the show.
- Chris Locke.
- That's a part of the character he's playing.
- Chris Locke is not Canadian.
- Yeah, he is.
Him and Nathan Fielder are both Canadian.
- So you think just 'cause they're friends
they're both Canadian?
People who aren't from Canada can be friends too.
I should have not said all the kids in the hall.
- Kids in the hall?
No, they're from the hall of presidents in Disney World.
- I would have had more fingers to point at
if I just listed them all individually.
- All right, next one.
Next.
- Next Canadian person I know.
- Celine Dion.
- Yeah, Celine Dion.
- She's Canadian.
But she's like French Canadian, right?
- Yeah, she's just French.
- Yeah, she's French Canadian.
It doesn't count.
- That doesn't count, yeah.
It's funny they just have French people in the middle.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Kind of unlucky.
- It's a little weird.
- Yeah, a little bit unlucky, honestly, for Canada.
- Yeah.
- Are you guys excited for--
- Who else is Canadian?
The guys from, the Alzheimer's guys, the skateboarders.
- The guys with Alzheimer's?
- Alzheimer's.
- The Alzheimer's. - The guys with Alzheimer's.
- Jazzy Faye and Birdman?
The big timers?
I don't think they're Canadian.
They're from Louisiana.
- Little Wayne is Canadian.
- No, he's not, dude.
- Yeah, he is.
- No, he's from the Third World.
- Sir John A. MacDonald.
Stop googling Canadian shit.
No, I didn't google that.
You're at work right now.
I didn't google that. I know that.
You looked at something and then looked at me.
My uncle said we're descendants of him.
Do you have a piece of paper with that?
No.
Then what are you looking at?
I'm not looking at anything.
You're still looking at it.
Stop looking at that.
I'm looking at a photo of a polar bear.
No, you're not.
You think that's Canadian.
He is.
But that's his background and he minimized it.
No, it's not my background.
if we're excited for Cameron?
Were you guys excited for the Borat sequel?
A little bit, yeah.
It comes out tomorrow.
It looks good. I mean, honestly, I was kind of like hesitant to think that it would be good, you know?
Because it's like a Borat sequel.
There's all these posters all over New York City and it's Sacha Baron Cohen wearing, like
dresses bore at wearing like a thong made out of a mask yeah yeah where a mask
save lives and I was like it's gonna be gay yeah no it's about like infiltrating
Donald Trump or something yeah and it's made by Amazon did yeah yeah I mean I
think I'm gonna watch it I think it'll be funny probably but just also be out by
now stop shut up I heard you type that one up he's also not he's from Whoville
it's true Justin Bieber knew that already made it not
can I get Myers no he's from Haddonfield Illinois okay you got me
there Michael Cera he's from breasts he's from Brisbane
Michael Sarah from breast brain he's from Norris you know or McDonald Brazil
Norm Macdonald is from a hole.
Norm Macdonald had a farm.
He's from a bog.
Yeah. Keep going.
Uhhhhhhhh
Don't look at that screen.
Keep your eyes off that screen.
Look at me. Who's Canadian?
[laughter]
You can't even name another Canadian guy.
Dan Aykroyd?
Not Canadian.
We should ship you to Canada.
I would do great there, are you kidding me?
'cause it's like a junior version of America.
- It's just New Hampshire.
- I don't think it's just New Hampshire, dude.
I think people are way better in Canada than New Hampshire.
- Yeah.
- New Hampshire's the worst place in America.
- Don't say that.
- I'll say it again. - I don't think it's the worst,
but I think it has some pretty bad people.
I think some of the worst people--
- I think it's terrible, dude.
- Yeah. - No.
- Some of the worst-- - Like you and your family.
- Yeah, some of the worst guys come out of there
and try to start podcasts.
They try to leech onto a podcast in the first--
- Yeah, they try to leech on.
- In the first 30 episodes.
- I fuckin' hate how affiliated I've become
with New England because of you two.
- Yeah.
- I fucking hate it. - That's true.
- People always think I'm from Boston.
- Man, when you're in Boston, you're like,
"Boston's so cool."
You kept saying that.
- Oh man, I love Boston. - I did like it
when I lived there.
And then I moved.
- Dude, you're such a-- - I saw the light.
- No, no, no, no.
- Yeah.
- You're just afraid to commit to anything.
- I think I wanna--
(laughing)
- The only one of us who's engaged.
- I think I wanna move. - You're afraid
to commit, dude.
- I wanna move to like-- - He is, dude.
He switches up whether he likes Boston every day.
- Atlanta's nice. - You wanna move to Atlanta?
- I think I might move to Atlanta and become a rap star.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, I might start switching lanes.
- I like Atlanta.
- That's one of the few other cities I've been to.
- We should go to Atlanta and we should move in
right next to the Queer Eye guys.
- Yeah. - Oh yeah,
in between the Queer Eye guys and the Gold Slim students.
- I know exactly where they live.
- And then we can do a sitcom.
- Yeah. - And it's like
the queers versus the straights.
- My girlfriend's dad used to live in an apartment next,
like apartment building next to where the queer eyes queer eyed guys lived did they
prank him?
I think he pranked them.
They pranked him with a makeover.
I hate it when I get pranked with a makeover.
We could prank them so yeah so fun dude put vaseline on their doorknob and shit.
I wouldn't prank them.
They try to put it in their ass dude.
No come on.
Come on.
What?
Jesus Christ.
Who said that?
What?
What the hell?
Who said that?
(laughing)
- Patrick!
- You're a problem.
- Oh, Pat.
- It wasn't me.
- Pat's saying that a gay guy put a doorknob in his butt.
- I'm the only one who's the ally on the show.
- You're not an ally.
- That is a lie.
- That's right.
- Wow.
- Yeah, ally, you're out, that is a lie.
- Allies all lies.
Can I eat some of your fries?
- Wow.
Communism will never die.
I need to go to the bank.
The palace in the sky.
I need to go to Palestine.
And save them.
Maybe I'll take you to Atlanta with me.
I've said it before.
I think the funniest thing we could do
is if we did the New York vlog, but just went to a village
in the Middle East.
[LAUGHTER]
Yeah, it's just us like pissing on the wailing wall and shit.
Just flew to Syria.
Yeah.
I would respect the culture.
I'd do the Dougie in Israel.
[Laughter]
You guys are gonna video me doing the Dougie.
I did learn recently you can go on Birthright if you're not Jewish.
Yeah, you can go on, I'm pretty sure it's free.
They're like trying to convert people.
I almost signed up for it, wait.
Yeah.
I almost signed up, like I almost signed up as a bit.
You have to be under a certain age, but you can go for free if you're not Jewish and they try to convert you.
111 yeah let's go on birthright and then and try to destroy as much property as
possible no why to counteract that dude yeah well you go to we go on birthright
and then we we just like solve all the problems over there how bad just wants
to go on birthright and he wants to solve a certain problem they've been having
with some children over there that's right that's what Patrick wants to solve
guys doing what are you doing dude you're saying you don't want to go go to
to Israel and do jackass? Oh, you didn't say it. If it's framed like that. Yeah, we go to
Israel and we do jackass in Israel. Yeah, okay. I am Patrick Doren and this is throwing a rock at a
child. Yeah, exactly. I'm Steve-O, this is shooting a stinger missile at a house.
It'd be great, dude. Yeah. I don't know. I want to find out what's in the Mecca cube.
You know what's in there?
RTX 4080.
(laughter)
You think so?
Yeah, you know what's in there, dude?
It's MU3.
You know what's in there?
Next-gen graphics.
(laughter)
Yeah.
Xbox 720.
That is, no, that is the Xbox 720.
That is the Xbox 720.
There's a disk slot on the way on the wall.
Halo 5, the Halo movie is in there.
And that's why you you gotta you got to be super secret to get in there don't they say that it's like a comet
Yeah, there's like a meteor in there or something. I wish Christianity had something cool. Yeah
Yeah, just like all the cool stuff
They like they try to like they try to get rid of they're like you know there was someone will probably be like I have
a genuine
Petrified shard of Jesus's foreskin and the church is like we're gonna send an assassin squad to kill this person
Yeah, we're gonna get we're gonna send it. We're gonna send a molester squad to attack this person's children
until they stop saying that they have Jesus's foreskin. Yeah they do that or
they get like Hobby Lobby to steal a bunch of artifacts for them. Yeah!
Honestly that's one of the craziest fucking stories that I feel like didn't
get enough attention. Yeah the Hobby Lobby ISIS thing. Yeah, Hobby Lobby funding ISIS
indirectly. I didn't know that. Yeah, exactly. You didn't fucking know that. Yeah, nobody knows about it.
Was it through like coupons or something? Yeah, they gave ISIS a bunch of like
paintings that said live laugh love and like free vouchers for like like little
like it was like they were stealing artifacts right yeah yeah they did all
that for in exchange for like oh these are like actual like sacred texts that
we found Isis has like Isis has hobby love like a bunch of doormats that say
like yeah they say like welcome well this home is this in this home is
protected by... We smile, we hug, we laugh, we love. I think Hobby Lobby is probably the funniest
possible like store to be funding ISIS on the side. Like I think it was. It really
yeah it doesn't it doesn't get better than that. Yeah cuz if it was Michaels
it'd be like I knew it. Yeah yeah whatever. You know my world Michael. Joe Ann Fabrics? Nah, fuck outta here. I knew that shit was going on.
No one goes to fucking Joe Ann Fabrics. I knew World Market was radical Islam every time I walk in and I see the rugs.
Yeah, especially since Hobby Lobby has been trying to make caliphates all over America.
Yeah, dude. You realize the original name was Habibi Lobby.
[Laughter]
Exactly. Yeah, it was right in front of us the whole time.
Yeah, it's just one of those things that's hiding in plain sight.
Yeah, they changed it to, it was Habibi and they erased the "by" from it from the end.
think about it. When they did buy erasure, they turned into Hobby Lobby. No! They erased the buy. No!
It'd be really funny to go to a gay pride parade and with a shirt that says I support LGTQ+
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- That'd be funny.
- People are like, I think something's missing,
and you sternly just like, yeah, I don't think so.
- Yeah.
- No, I don't think so.
- Oh yeah, I don't know.
- A berf.
- I can't imagine what.
- Becoming a berf.
A bi-exclusive radical feminist.
- It's kinda what I am.
- Yeah.
you're exclusively by crap whoo I walked into this again yeah I walked into a
man's bedroom I got I got egg all over my face yeah you got a man you got a man
and a woman's face you guys really put something in my ass
yeah kids suck it on it weird guys do you think there are burfs like actual burfs
do you think there are actual burfs bisexuals are just so there's just kind
of nothing it's like yeah it's like that yeah it's like it's like a whisper on
the wind yeah it's like exactly what it comes to whether they exist or not yeah
It's like I don't really care. It's like a strand of spider silk almost
There is a birth there's one
report form
Huh?
business entity report form
Damn Patrick getting all smart on us again
Stop talking about business dude. I hate when you talk shop with us. I'm the only one who does I get it dude
You do you like Robin Hood and day trade?
I love being the small business guy.
The first time that we made like over $100 on Patreon, I really did think it'd be funny
to somehow turn that into like a negative $5 million on Robinhood.
I don't understand how that happens at all.
Kids get their allowance, they get like $20 and then they bet that the Apple stock will
go up 1% tomorrow and then it doesn't and they lose $50 billion.
was that guy that guy who killed himself because uh cuz that happened cuz he like
he put it like some money into Robin Hood and then it like it crashed and like he
list like looked at his balance and it was like negative a trillion dollars or
something and he just instantly killed himself and then it found and then found
out then like they found out after that it was like oh it was like a glitch or
something oh my god yeah it was yeah yeah it was that it was that basically
whenever that happens the thing that people do is they like settle with
Robin Hood yeah like a much smaller amount of money yeah yeah so you would
have had to pay like a couple thousand dollars. That seems like a fucking evil app.
Of course yeah now people the stock market is made for computers it's not
made for people yeah yeah no it's fragile yeah yeah yeah yeah that's why we're poor
yeah mm-hmm yeah cuz we're not computers yeah there's not enough computers doing
the stock market.
See, that's the problem.
- Maybe we should get into Bitcoin mining.
- Yeah, maybe.
- I've been mining you guys for Bitcoin
since the day we met.
- I feel like I don't have antivirus software on my computer.
- I might be able to.
- I'm sure there's Bitcoin miners on my computer.
- I might have a Bitcoin in my brain.
- Yeah, I have a Bitcoin in my pocket.
- Bitcoin, whatever happened to big coins?
- That's right.
You bite them to test if they're real gold.
Yeah, and it turns out they're just digital.
Do I still have that coin?
Yeah, I do.
What coin?
You still have your big coin?
I have my, it's one of those quarters,
like a 60s quarter that has silver in it.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
I remember talking to my dad,
my dad was really into coin collection as a kid,
and he was like, he kept it for a long time,
and one day I was like, oh yeah, I wanna see all the coins,
and he pulled them out and he showed them all to me,
And it was like probably a hundred quarters worth or whatever.
And I was like, "Whoa, dad, this is so cool.
"Like how much is this worth now?"
And he's like, "Probably about like a hundred quarters."
(laughing)
- Yeah, I remember when I was a kid,
I had one of the, I had like a big like,
like board that was like a map of the US
and like you put, it has holes for quarters in every state.
- Oh yeah. - So you try to fill it up.
And I just remember being like,
"Like this is so cool."
And like getting like a bunch of quarters.
And then it's like a few weeks later,
me like I want ice cream and just like empty that the whole thing.
That's funny yeah.
Hell yeah.
There's just a point where it's like I don't what am I gonna do with these they're not
even great.
Did you guys collect anything when you were young?
I collected dead bugs.
Oh I collected VHS tapes.
I collected my mom's hair in high school though.
Yeah no.
VHS tapes? Yeah I still have all of them. I feel like that's not collecting as much
as it's just like getting you just have movies yeah I would buy I would buy like
weird ones. I mean I get I try to I wouldn't I try to get weird books and
stuff but I wouldn't say it call it collecting I think it's collecting if
it's like I have over like a hundred. A hundred VHS tapes? Over a hundred. You could
- You could build a chair.
- Yeah, I think it's close to like 150.
- You could build a throne.
- Something like that.
- You could build a blockbuster.
- I could, I could have a blockbuster.
I have kids on VHS.
That movie, F'd Up.
- That's--
- That movie's a freak for real.
- That's a bad thing, I admit.
- Why?
- I got kids on VHS.
(laughing)
- Don't say that.
- I have Harmony Kareem's kids.
- I tried to start a rock collection as a kid,
but there aren't any cool rocks around my town.
So it just had like a chunk of asphalt and like a few pebbles.
(laughs)
I was like, I found a pure black rock.
It's just like part of the road.
Yeah.
A chunk of dirt that's really hard.
The one cool rock that I found was I found,
I one time when I was in Montana, I found--
- You found this arrowhead.
- I found sand, I did have some arrowheads.
- Oh, you did?
- Yeah.
And I had a shark tooth too.
And now I'm just remembering all this stuff I collected,
but I found some sand that got struck by lightning
and turned into like glass and it was like bubbles of glass.
Pretty cool.
- Whoa.
- The only cool rock I ever found.
- That is cool, bubbles of glass.
- You know what I had a lot of was,
I would buy like the tapes that they would show at school.
You know, like the like anti-smoking ones.
- Yeah, 'cause you wanted to learn.
- Yeah, I wanted to learn how to not smoke.
But I found one that was like a Scientology funded
anti-smoking video, which is pretty cool.
And then I--
- Did you try to like funnel the kids
into Scientology at the end?
- All the children, I looked it up,
all the children who are in the video are Scientologists.
- And that's it?
- I guess that's it.
- They don't, yeah, they don't try and turn them crazy.
- Let me look up Scientology anti-smoking.
- I love when you look stuff up when we're recording.
- Yeah, it's always the best, dude.
- Yeah.
I remember, I'd try to get weird DVDs like that
when I'm at used bookstores and shit.
they always have really good DVDs.
I remember we watched one of them, Caleb,
that was like a Dungeons and Dragons movie,
but it was like the fourth in a series,
so it just made no sense at all.
- Yeah, it was so sick.
- It was so awesome.
- It was like one of the worst fight scenes
I've ever seen, isn't it?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- They had an evil wizard. - That sounds fun.
- Very cool.
- Yeah, they did have an evil wizard
in that Dungeons and Dragons movie.
- Yeah, pretty interesting.
- I do remember that, yeah, that was crazy.
Really took me by surprise.
- I would never even imagine that they would have that.
- I have, I got some DVD that I haven't watched yet
that's called like UFOs and the Bible. I think it's over here. That's cool. I had
yeah I had like I didn't collect this but I watched I had a bunch of DVDs when I
was a kid that were like proof that dinosaurs still existed. Yeah. Because I
was like that kind of Christian growing up. Answers in Genesis presents aliens
UFOs and the Bible are we alone in the universe featuring Gary Bates. Answers in
Genesis I think is the same company that did all those dinosaur DVDs.
that that's the the Kinn what's his fucking name? Ken Burns? No, Ken something.
Ken Bone? He's some Australian fuck who like lives in Tennessee and does all this
like like they built like a full-scale model of Noah's Ark. That's sick. In Tennessee.
It's a creation science museum. Damn. Yeah. Yeah so when I was growing up my
mom was super into all that. Is that the museum that Mark Maron talks about
in his special? Yeah. Yeah Mark Maron went there for an episode of WTF and it's
him just walking around he's like "not true, not true, bullshit, what the fuck, it's just complete
horseshit." He's going up to the dinosaur statues and going "so who
warrior guys he's getting really mad when they're not responding to him Adam and
Eve bro yeah yeah yeah Adam and Steve yeah those are my guys yeah yeah it's
madam and Steve not Adam and Eve the boy was a girl and the girl was a boy yeah
do you think their names are really Adam and Eve no no what I know in Turkish
Adam means guy what's Eve mean? Girl. Wow. Wait let me look that up. So you think they were Turks?
I think the world comes from Turkish. I think everything in the world is Turkish I mean look at a see what's
that guy that the chef on Instagram who makes the big food? I would love to
become like a like a Turkish chef guy on Instagram. I know I want to become like a
Balkan nationalist. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That'd be so funny. I think that's kind of played
out. Is it? Yeah. Oh. I think so. My bad. I feel like that's the, that's the thing that
everyone does as a joke online now, right? I didn't know that. Girl is cuz and then guy
is a dom. Adam and cousin? Adam and cuz. Damn. Those dogs are loud as shit. I don't think
- So, I think you're right.
- Yeah.
- We should maybe go to the Creation Science Museum sometime.
Might be a worthwhile trip.
- It's definitely still open right now.
- Yeah.
- I feel like if any place is gonna--
- It definitely has a zero mass tolerance policy.
- Yeah.
- It's cool that stuff like that gets made
and not like funding for cancer research.
- Dude, let's go, let's fly.
- Oh yeah.
- And not like--
- All right, let's get into it.
like the Snyder cut and yeah that's right - that those are my two issues. I think it's kind of interesting that that st. Jude's got this huge grant from the
government yet Zack Snyder's cut is still hidden somewhere in the Disney vault. It's still hidden and we have to
watch it on HBO Max and it's not distributed freely yeah okay this makes
sense you think you think they would really think Donald Trump will get a
second term if instead of sending out a second stimulus check he sends the Snyder
cut to every family in America. Yes, yeah like Netflix style. Like back in the day on a DVD.
Yeah but you don't have to send it back. Dude Trump's gonna bring back Netflix
DVDs to your house. He's gonna bring back sending it. We're bringing DVDs back.
We're bringing Netflix DVD back. We're coming back. The beautiful. Netflix DVD. Netflix DVD. You can set up your
queue folks. We love the queue don't we? I've been burping today. Three movies at a time.
three just three you got three I only got two sorry I was rich dude sorry I had
not my mom got fucking pissed at me cuz I kept ordering that like skate videos
so I would I knew how to edit the queue so I would like she would be like oh I'm
going to buy like this DVD this month and I would go into the queue and then put
like the DC video or like toy machine I kept getting that how long were those
videos. Those videos are like an hour long. Okay. Something like that. Jump off a building
is like 30 minutes. I was saying yeah just like replacing your mom's movie with like a 10 minute
video. Yeah. Mom I got the Numa Numa Dance as one of the DVDs this week. Just watching it once.
Dude at CEX and Downtown Crossing I found a DVD that was like of viral videos. That's so
sick. It was like made in like '04. Yeah I wish I did. I could probably just find it on eBay for
like a dollar but it was like this video has the Numa Numa guy, the hamster dance.
Evolution of dance dude.
Yeah all that shit like they put all the youtube videos onto dvds and then sold it to people.
It's so cool.
Yeah it's like why why do you go buy the Numa Numa guy?
That's exclusively for for a parent to buy to give to their pastor to show to show what
their child is watching.
Yeah to get him to yeah to condemn the child to hell.
Yeah.
Yeah, you can just imagine a pastor sitting in like his back office just like
watching the Numa Numa guy and just going "Oh my god!"
Yeah, just doing the cross on his chest.
Yeah, he thinks it's like rock and roll.
Yeah.
"Oh lord!
Paul, can we let our children watch this?"
One of the like...
"I saw a man! I saw a man who said a chocolate rain was gonna fall down from the heavens!"
"He's a false prophet!"
He's a false prophet, I tell you! He said a chocolate rain was gonna fall down!
He said some will stay dry and others will feel the pain! Who is he talking about?
One of the uh one of the other members of the congregation here is like laughing from the
back room. It's like what's going on? And walks in and he's just like looking so guilty and just
sitting there with a blue screen on the tv and like I was just thinking about something about
the bible but you know he's watching viral videos. You know he's watching those viral videos.
So somebody, they hear laughing, they go into the back room and then as soon as they walk in,
the fucking dramatic chipmunk looks at the screen and he goes back at the person.
Oh fuck. I always just, or I kept ordering the Endless Summer, you know that like surf
documentary? I just kept ordering that because there's a scene where they're on like a topless
beach. Oh yeah? Yeah. I ordered that movie probably five or six times. That's probably
the weirdest movie for you that you probably jacked off to and watched the
nude scene over and over again but for me it was the man with two brains because
there's a shot of one boob and I paused it. There's literally a shot of one boob.
That's like in Hackers. There's one frame where you can see Angelina Jolie's
nipple and it moved like bullet time when I was a kid and then I watched it.
Like I thought that it was like a scene that was just like a close-up of her
tits and then I watched it recently and yeah it's like one single frame as she
walks across a room and when I was a kid I was like this is this is the most
jack-off able thing yeah yeah yeah yeah same with the man with two brains I'd
like to check it off to the man with two brains yeah you wish you literally
two men would give you brain Martin command performance in that movie it's a
it's a really underrated one I don't think I've seen it yeah I haven't either
so good I think Merv Griffin's I can't watch it now cuz I'll just be
to this. I ruined the man with two brains for everybody there's gonna be letterbox
reviews like yeah Patrick jacked off to this. Yeah it's like your dad's Sports
Illustrated. Yeah it's just like well you know guess I'm not learning about the
Sean Jackson this week. Mm-hmm. Can't even open this one. Dale Earnhardt
looking too nice in the back of this magazine. Not even the swimsuit edition. No. Yeah but I
was a kid I did think Sports Illustrated was just like porn. Yeah. I didn't even
know it was a sports magazine yeah yeah I was like yeah it's like yeah boy I
thought that with men's health there's a woman on the day you did one time there's
a woman on the cover of it one time and my dad said I couldn't read it no that
means that he was saying that you didn't you didn't know how to read yeah yeah
yeah no you can't read that book right here disgusting bliss the brass I have
Chris Morris is that a Chris Morris book?
Patrick, you should one time you should try you you should see if you can read a
book that's not about a TV show that you like.
I challenge you. I have a mind exploitation.
That's but that is you got that because of a TV show that you like.
So?
People turn TV shows into TV shows all the time.
You don't have to do the challenge. I'm just challenging you. If you don't you're
a coward but that's not my problem.
I dare you to read the Quran.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Oh, don't even try.
Without vomiting.
I was going to say I have another book here, but it's the Gary Shanling book that my brother
gave me.
That rocks.
I think I really don't do anything that's affecting my studies.
Yeah, one shot, one kill.
You read TV books, dude.
Yeah, that's true.
so what? You have a TV brain? No, you're crafting the perfect TV brain. I do have the perfect TV brain.
Yeah, you do. You remember every episode of every show and every actor. Yeah. But you
can't read a real book. It'd be funny if you open that that Brass Eye book and it's just
like, "I liked this episode. It was very funny. The jokes made me laugh."
Yeah. "Ha ha ha. I love this stuff. It makes me think, but also makes me laugh."
Makes me think about the fact that pedophilia is bad. Mm-hmm. I picked that
up because there's like a thing in that book that says like the guy that they
were sitting there like the guy he calls a two-pin din plug was like an
actual pedophile or something the story about the interaction between that you
want the backstage pass mm-hmm it all access pass to Brass eyes
Cameron's yawning yeah can you Cameron's yawning another book that I could read
What? Tim and Eric's own theory. What about X-Men does that count? X-Men? X-Men.
Yeah you're gonna be an X-Man. X-Men the Executioner's Song. That's a comic.
That's a book. Comics are books. No. Yeah. Okay. No. What about this? Okay I got a
copy of Hollywood said no the uneared sketches of mr. show that counts that
counts it didn't actually get on TV what about train spotting that's that's the
closest one yeah that is that is pretty close to a real book for you you got it
because you liked the movie but we can that's not a TV show at least Tarkin a
a star wars novel nope no no what about the poe dameron comic you should read the fall of reach
dude stop fall of reach i call of reach i think it would blow your mind and have you should i get
what if i just got back into reading star wars eu stuff back into yeah i read it i read that
shit and like i still do that makes sense you still read it yeah yeah probably i will all right
I'm gonna read the Chuck Wendig Star Wars novel.
Bye.
See ya.
Mwah.