Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
- Shut it off.
- No.
- Oh.
- Turn it off.
- I can't do this today.
Turn it off.
- Why, what's wrong?
- He got new pants.
- These are not new pants.
I've had these for a while.
- He got new pants.
- I don't.
- Why are you paying so much attention to which pants are new?
- Why are you ever looking at the bottom half
of another man's body?
and you know i'm not sure he's got a mall cataloged in his brain only wears you
know he wears one pair of pants i didn't know that he wears one pair of pants
everyday while you pay attention to my pants
everyone's pants to you gays and gay as hell i don't care
yeah you do
yeah you do care to care really bad you care real bad about how gay you are
really bad about how gay you are
yeah you do
you're so gay you care about pants
and about being gay
not true
I don't want to do this because I haven't peed in five days.
Something's wrong.
Yeah, something is wrong.
Yeah, I'm sick.
I've just been squirting water out of my ass and it's been bypassing my penis.
It's the craziest feeling.
I've not felt the joy of having something come out of my penis in five days.
Well, the joy of a lot of things going into his penis though.
No, nothing is going.
He's sounding.
Although, I've noticed my penis has gotten smaller with no pee coming out of it.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- I'm not kidding.
- You'd think it would be bigger
because the pee would fill it up.
- No pee has been coming out of my penis
and it's getting really small.
(laughing)
I'm serious.
- Dude, you're developing a second butthole.
- I think it, I don't think it's that.
- I think his penis is going in.
- I think your penis might go in and become a second butt.
- No, 'cause nothing's coming out of it.
Stuff comes out of your butthole.
- Well, yeah, but it comes out of one of your buttholes.
- My penis is getting small because there's no,
there's no peas pushing power through it.
- It's like one of those sponge grow toys.
- Yeah, it needs to stimulate the cells.
You need to stimulate it to make it grow.
- Yeah, you need to just lay flat on your floor
with your penis in a cup of water.
- Oh, that's a good idea.
I need to keep my penis in the shower.
- You let it grow like a caterpillar.
- Have you been covering it with a shower cap
when you shower?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's your issue. Not really. You're not watering it. Like one of those
things is chefs. One of those finger condoms they put on when you cut yourself. Who?
Chefs. Why are you saying it like that? I think you're talking about our friend. No.
No. Not. No. Like chefs and uh. Chefs. What? Stop. Stop saying it with a V. What do you
mean? You're saying it like our friend's name. Chefs in a restaurant. Chefs? Yeah. In a kitchen.
You're saying it like knives you what the fuck dude
Weird why no saying it weird chefs
Chef chefs night chefs knives is when there's more than
- Knife, knives, - No!
- Listen, knife, knives, wive, wives, chef, chev,
moose, moosin. - It's not chevs, dude!
- Prove it.
- That's our friend's name.
- Prove it linguistically. - You're confusing me.
I keep thinking you're talking about our friend,
and I keep thinking you're saying
that she wears little finger condoms.
- You keep bringing it up like you're bragging
that you know stuff, friend, chef.
Like, yeah, this is my friend's name!
- I'm not.
- You are. - I was genuinely confused
you said that I was like oh I didn't know. She doesn't even work in a fucking kitchen. I don't know
let's not let's not talk about her. Chef chevs. It's not chevs. It's chevs. It's a lot of them.
That's what I'm saying it's like it's like how it's like it's like one fish. Him and his son in
the uh-huh one fish. Him and his son in the truck once they're going cross country. Once his son
- And so he becomes a chef?
- Uh-huh.
- Oh my God.
(laughing)
- And he's like, "Oh, I have to, yeah, you know,
"my dad wasn't really around 'cause he had to do
"his five-star restaurant, but, you know,
"now I'm taking over the family truck
"and I'm going cross-country."
- That's right.
- "To tour colleges."
- Who would be--
- "To tour colleges with the big chef truck."
- Oh, my gosh.
- And then he's gonna, uh-huh, and it's called
"Chevs," colon, "Big Man on Campus."
- And he's blowing backs out right next to all the
ingredients in the truck.
college I yeah he is dude he's just Chev in a truck touring college I then maybe
even they even have like multiple trucks is be cool whole fleet of trucks is yeah
they have a whole fleet of trucks is in Canada right now and I don't care about
about anything that happens in the entire world, I realize.
- Yeah.
- The last like six months, I just have not,
they killed, what'd they kill everybody in?
- Jamal Khashoggi?
- Yeah, Jamal, that's the last time
I thought a news story was cool,
was when Jamal Khashoggi got chopped into Khashoggi tartare.
That was cool as fuck.
'Cause it was like, they chopped him up into pieces.
It was, there was probably a saw involved.
That's cool.
But Russia going into-- they kill every single living thing
in Ukraine, I don't give a fuck.
What is this?
Stop.
Stop pointing at the--
Turn the TV off.
This is bad, dude.
This is really bad.
I don't know where the remote is.
How is it that just a picture that
changes every 15 seconds can just ruin an episode?
Because you will just--
look, it just munches.
Just a screensaver.
It's not even like we're not doing anything.
I have not broken eye contact with this fucking television since it went on screensaver mode.
Turn it off.
I have to, we have to, where is the remote?
Just unplug it.
Don't unplug it because you could unplug the wifi.
Okay well then turn it off.
Just go, you have to go under and feel around.
Okay you're making me do this?
You don't have to do it.
For you?
I have to do this.
You don't have to do it.
It's under.
Whoa!
See that's what I, it's not under.
It's a baboon.
It's not even, okay.
Shut it off.
Yeah, the truck guys, what are they doing? What I was that you know what I'd be
doing if I was there? Yeah, yeah, I'd be doing the hot corn, the hot corn hand,
I'd be doing the hot corn handed to the horn hand from school. Yeah, to these
guys, I remember this from school. That's what I'd say to them. That's if I
was just in true true dough, I'd be out there going dude cool. Is teacher ever
the kids on a field trip to the the trucker protest. The kids riding the bus in a circle,
they get to do the honk thing every single truck. Oh my god. Trudeau needs to be down there like a
lot lizard. Yeah that's right and he is a lizard. Yeah he's already a lizard. He needs to go down
there like a lot lizard. Like a lot of lizards. And suck all them suck all them truckers off.
He doesn't need to suck the truckies off. I don't know which side you're supposed to be on.
I don't give a shit about it.
Truckers are lazy, it's the easiest job in the world.
Oh, I have to sit!
I have to sit in my car and do all this free crystal meth.
It's sad.
It's an easier version of being an Uber Eats driver.
Yeah. Oh no, I have to see every gas station in America.
Oh no. I have to go on a beautiful journey.
Oh no, I can't have a family.
Oh, I get to go to stay in the cool parking lot at the gas station that you're not allowed to stay in.
I get to visit every motel and I get to shower with all the other truckers.
Yeah, me and my friends suck each other off and get sucked by each other off.
Oh, and my car, it so stinks in my car that there's seriously a bunk bed in there.
We have bunk beds.
Oh no, it's so...
I have to drive a car with thousands of cool things in the back.
Oh, I have to drive a car that if it crashes, it kills everybody except me.
Oh my God, my life sucks so bad.
Oh, I have to work for Walmart.
Oh, and I have to bring things to my favorite store, Walmart.
And get this, I have to stay awake for 16 hours.
16 whole hours.
Fuck you, you fucker.
They want a better, and they want better conditions.
I heard they want faster trucks.
They want a truck that goes...
They want faster trucks.
Meanwhile, they get all the fucking Arby's that they want whenever they want.
Yeah.
They can stop at...
They do just get unlimited fast food.
Yeah.
I heard they were there. They're protesting because they want a DVD
player and you know what the trucks well that's it. That's the real job of
these truckers want to watch cranky. I want to drive. Yeah, they're real job
of trying because they want it. They want to play plug and play pac-man.
The real job of trucking is watching movies on your phone. Yeah, that is
the actual job. That is where you're getting paid. We are gathered here
because we want to play the whole Atari collection. A semi truck. A semi
truck is so heavy it basically drives itself we want to play most Jax
Pacific's games in our cars while we're going 500 miles an hour I'm glad the
trucks to be faster I'm glad we're finally covering the truck there's
nothing big going on right now we have to talk about these fucking truckers
they're lazy dude there's their sacks of shit and the Ukraine they're also lazy
yeah and they should be wiped off the face of the earth we're pro we're pro
Russia no no I don't know I don't care I gotta wait we need I gotta wait for
Colbert a yeah yeah which everyone Colbert cries over we got to see what
what what John Oliver's gonna say yeah he's clearly big really you're doing
this right now you're doing this right now why can't you do that yeah why can't
you do that instead you're doing this that's right you shouldn't do this
that is better that is a better thing to do talk to him John I heard John Oliver
is gonna do a is gonna do an episode where he's wearing cat eye contacts
look at my funny eyes I heard he's gonna do that to try and scare Russia so they stop the fading increase
Putin I want you to look at this Putin I want to say one thing to you
Yeah he puts his hand over his eyes and then just goes like...
Then there's a video of Putin like just giving a speech two days later he's like "the cat
was not that scary to me, the cat was only a little bit scary."
I think John Oliver would be the scariest late night host to have cat eyes.
Yeah.
Cause he opens his eyes really big.
Cause he looks like a mouse.
Yeah true.
mouse with cat's eyes yeah the whole house it's that was in end times yeah I
want to kick him in the ass and make him fly like Team Rocket yeah John Oliver
back to the UK you go back to England where you belong go back get out of my
country damn immigrant piece of shit talk about an invasion that's right yeah
yeah I'm gonna invade you with my with
yeah you're gonna invade my ass and stop buying
I didn't say your ass and stop buying up all our medical debt that's ours
yeah hey leave it alone hey you didn't earn that
you didn't build that you did not apply for a loan because you didn't know what
it meant you didn't build that debt that debt's not yours we did that we are
imposing heavy sanctions on cat eye contact for all UK immigrants.
That's a reminder for John Oliver's terrifying episode last night.
John Oliver just doing like increasingly like specific things about like how like he can't
get the shit that he wants in his life because of sanctions.
And why, why can I-
Why do condoms start at medium?
Why can't I get the Chalupa shell made fresh?
I ask them to make it fresh when I go to Taco Bell and they're never fresh.
They come out soggy.
This is your warning Taco Bell.
I'll be making a visit with my cat eyes.
I'm going to the Taco Bell on Myrtle Wycombe.
That's the bad one.
That one's good.
Is that the good one?
No, I'm not Myrtle Broadway.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Nobody knows what the fuck you're talking about right now.
Three people do and that's who I do this for.
I'll tell you what was the bomb ass Taco Bell back in the dizzy.
The one on Old Yonder in Wilmington, North Carolina.
You know what the worst one?
Remember the one on School Street?
Yeah.
That was maybe the worst Taco Bell I've ever heard.
That was the worst Taco Bell I've ever heard.
Worst place in the world.
Yeah, literally the worst one.
I never got to see it, man.
I was just inboxed.
You're lucky, dude.
That place sucked.
It literally would take an hour to get your food every time no matter how big.
You could be the only person in there.
And they'd look at you and just like...
Yeah.
Are you waiting for something?
We've got to take them down a notch.
People that I am imposing...
Someone has to go in there with cat eyes.
I am imposing heavy economic sanctions on Taco Bell.
I will only be eating there once a week instead of every single day.
Hey, Russia, listen up.
I will be imposing heavy economic sanctions on you if you ruin Christmas this year.
Yep.
So you better be done by then.
You sort all this shit out before Christmas.
Or I will stop buying t-shirts from your online store.
I'm cancelling my fucking fake taxi subscription tomorrow, big guy.
It's over.
Did you see the, um, it was like, there was a Patreon made for the Ukrainian army?
Oh yeah, I did see that.
Who the fuck, how fucking stupid are you to donate to that?
I think we should add a fighter plane tier to our Patreon.
Yeah, you can buy a fighter plane for our military.
(laughing)
- We should just start a military.
- We should just--
- Can we start a military?
- Yeah, we should just kill everybody in the whole world.
- That's our new thing.
- We should just become--
- Starting a military.
- Murdering lunatics.
- That's what we're doing.
- We should become murderers.
- Starting a second Patreon for a podcast
about this military.
(laughing)
- Yep, and you get to, what is it?
- You don't get any of the episodes.
- Yeah, no episodes.
- This is strictly for our military.
- This is just to support the troops.
- Yeah.
You can become a troop if you pay $100 a month.
No, we're the only troops. We just want a lot of weapons.
Yeah, but we have to get an arsenal.
Yeah.
Yeah, but for $100 a month you can like, I don't know, like...
$100 a month, that's one bullet.
I think there might be a giant block falling down.
Whoa, you just got an eviction notice.
I did?
I don't know.
I don't know about that.
Oh.
What is it?
the management company will no longer be the our management company
that's a little bit of a good
the
that's correct
the house moving i think it is a little bit is so funny if it was a defection
the
that i think you really get a big deal
yeah well of course you have been too loud
we've heard about your plans to start a military
We will be imposing heavy economic sanctions on your apartment if you do not desist.
I'm moving in like two or three days.
Yeah.
I don't care.
Two to three days.
That's a lot of days.
Two to three.
I'm going to read your new lease.
Don't read my new lease.
That's not mine.
That's Neil's so you can't read it.
mine you could read it but it's Neil so you can't read it put it down it has his
bank info on there you can't read it put it down
Neil! I read it! I memorized the entire thing. Neil's actually gonna walk out.
I know he's actually gonna walk out. You fucked everything up. I messed up.
You fucker. You ruined it. You ruined the episode. We were on a good roll about what? Sanctions, military, cat eyes.
We wanted to become a new military. Yeah so $1 tier that's the cat eyes tier
because that's a psychological...
Oh yeah, we need cat eyes to scare...
And then we're also going to have those, you know,
Aztec death whistles, you ever seen those?
No.
You're the only one who knows that.
Okay, well it's really...
You need an Aztec breath mental right now.
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah.
Yeah!
I'm going to show...
I'm going to play you guys the noise of an Aztec death whistle.
Our military will have a thousand of these.
It's just a slide whistle.
It sounds...
Aztec...
it sounds like a person screaming
obscene
uh...
just looking screen brother
family monkey of you that i mean we're gonna have you listen close enough that
just sounds like a really bad with c_e_o_ we're gonna have a thousand of those
yet
Those are more powerful than guns I think in today's battle. There's actually nothing more
powerful than guns except love. Damn maybe we should start a love military.
That's the that's okay so that's what we frame it as. The world's first love yeah that's
what we say it is. It's the podcast about list love military. We do param we
paratroop into the Ukraine into Kiev and we make love to everyone.
With big heart parachutes. Yeah. Go down in big hearts parachutes. Meanwhile.
we make love to everybody meanwhile they don't know that we're mate we have
poison come or AIDS we go back to Russia or whatever like what is that you wait
for five years we're gonna win some of those people are gonna be pretty annoying
We leave immediately just like a small like smaller parachutes with AIDS test
through the city. It's a pretty good idea. We don't say it's that, we just say it's
it's poison cum. Yeah. So no one gets mad. The love army. There's nothing funny about it.
The love Marines. You know killed 300 million people. Yeah. You didn't know that.
that. Why are you smiling? I'm not smiling. You literally are smiling. You moved the mic
away from your face. What are you laughing about? What's so funny? He's laughing because
look at this is the face he makes when he finds out AIDS killed 300 million people.
And nobody cared. Don't do that. When you find out that every single one of them was
laughing now i'm laughing because both of you are staring at me what do you mean yeah we're
staring at you because of your inappropriate reaction yeah 300 million african they were
one years old do you know the the government basically the government essentially tried
to eradicate gay people with aids patrick what's funny about that stop stop staring
what is wrong with you stop staring at me like that no you're fucking sick not until you say
sorry I'm sorry to Africa and gay people for what for what for what for laughing
when Caleb and Cameron stared at me no no laughing when I said what how many
people six no three million thirty million at a zero big guy thirty million
plus zero? No, 300 million. Oh, okay. And what'd they die of? AIDS. In what continent?
What country? Yeah. No, you said it was a continent. What country? Well, America. No.
Well, gay people. The gay guys died in America. Yeah. And where'd all the black guys die?
probably there's probably a few in America yeah probably some yeah yeah
but some Latinos and Asians and yeah I need to get over this damn sickness yeah
yeah it's called being it's a mental sickness it's called norovirus I gotta
I have to have a better constitution.
You guys just staring at me.
- I know, it really gets you.
- Yeah.
- We can't do anything.
- That makes me feel so like crazy.
- Did you know Patrick that when--
- I can't look at you.
- No, just look at me.
I'm just telling you a fact here.
When AIDS cases were on the rise
before they knew what it was,
the newspapers were calling it gay cancer.
- Yeah, I know that's sad.
- Yeah, it's really sad.
- That's really sad that they called it.
- It's really sad what they called it.
- It's not gonna work now.
What's not gonna work?
The staring thing is not gonna work now.
I'm not staring at you, I'm trying to inform you about something you showed a flagrant
disrespect for.
Are you talking about you have a corona?
No.
Caleb has COVID and he's in my house.
Oh, COVID's funny?
Yeah.
You know how many people die from COVID?
Zero.
Because it's not real, big guy.
Okay.
It's a fake disease.
And there's nothing funny about that.
Yeah.
And tell you what, a lot of those people I meet are the ones that made it work.
What is it?
It's norovirus?
Yeah, that's the stomach flu.
Well, is that contagious?
Is that contagious? I don't want you like, because I'm just thinking about it now.
I haven't had the fever in a while.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm fine. I just have some residual diarrhea because I was on a diet of Pepto-Bismol only.
Oh, dude, it's so crazy. It's so crazy when you like, your poops after Pepto.
Especially if it's all you've been having, because I just was pooping
the water that I was drinking mixed with the Pepto, and it was just a,
there was like a black like mask of my...
What?
Why were you mixing it with water?
No, I was in my stomach, you fucking moron.
I was drinking water.
No, the way you said that made it sound like you were making like,
it sounded like you were making a Pepto cocktail.
Not to me.
What kind of cocktail would that be?
Water and Pepto, just be watered down, would that be so great?
That's not even that weird.
No, I thought you were like putting it in a water bottle.
I'm like Jager bombing it in water and chugging it.
Be cool, it's not a bad idea.
Actually, because I mean, sometimes it tastes too chalky.
literally looked like a foot like it looked like an oil spill in my bed my
toilet every yeah I tell it every single time it's just like a nasty I guess just
a glossy I just was seeing a reflection of myself yeah I saw yeah saying yo to
myself it's crazy cuz I think it's bismuth yeah that Pepto-Bismol comes
from it you see what that looks like the yeah it's like a square magical stone do
that's the coolest looking shit looks like there's real man it looks like a
Dwarven concoction see certain animals and you're like if I didn't if nobody
had ever told me about that yeah and I didn't see it at a very young age but
had been most every animal then I would be like II fucking liar yeah yeah do
you like a caracal or like a chinchilla yeah yeah I mean I saw dog yeah there's
certain like certain type like a Zolo you know it really looks like a magical
creature is a is a snub-nosed monkey. If I saw Don Zolo, Boston comedian, Boston
right-wing Nazi comedian, I wouldn't have believed it, dude. Yeah. I don't want to
like, I don't know, like me and Neil looked at his like Twitter bio. Oh yeah, what was it again?
I don't know. He's the best, dude. Oh yeah, it's time to get awesome. So funny. So cool. He's great. But yeah, like what's that
- What's that?
- The snub-nosed monkey.
- Snub-nosed, yeah.
- Those are the ones that have no nose
and have like a skull nose and they're like golden.
And they live in like snow forests and they fight each other.
They literally look like fairies or goblins or something.
- Yeah.
- But as, like a Zolo?
- Wee folk.
- Do Zolo, like a, I don't know how to say the full name,
but it's like the hairless dog.
They look like demons.
- Oh yeah.
- And Lycoi cats, dude.
- Oh, and uh.
- Lycoi cats just look like werewolves.
- Yeah, Sasquatches.
- Yeah, I wouldn't believe it.
- And a Wampa.
and then see ya know
yeah the crate dragon definitely
you're seeing a great drag a rank or yet you know
uh... well they will this is the only great like i'm sorry i don't know
rancor rancor you can see a lot of our industry
mhm
but you can see there's there's a lot of like an evil egg with an eye
there's a lot of rancor in the i'm going to your also the uh...
the ipod monkey
Yeah, yeah, the pizza rat
Wouldn't believe it. It's crazy when you like you can only see an iPod monkey if there's like one color of a big
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Yeah, that's a big one. Yep
Stuart little sewer little I'd a chair sitting Jesus
cheese this chair sitting Jesus
Believed it
I have a yeah before I started sitting on a chair and this yeah and cheesing
yeah, no, that's a chair sitting cheeser. Yeah, do the cheeser the cheesing is is
way a cheesest a cheesing and a cheeser three different animals. They're all
part of like the same kind of family, though it's like a hamster versus like a
mouse versus actually yeah,
fight. They do fight. If you put a cheeser and a cheesing in the same,
one's whoever wins becomes the animal. Yeah, whoever won, well that again. Whoever won to
become the animal. We're doing new linguistics. Yeah. Caleb American Vernacular English.
Okay. What do you think of that? No. I don't know. I don't know if that's going to catch on.
I think it might catch on. What about the breast bug? Have you ever seen one of those?
I've seen a breast bug. I have to go.
The breasted bug. It's a bug that's just like as big like double d's and it can't walk.
It's like two huge human tits. On a horn beetle. Like a bug this big.
For many breasted bugs they spend most of their lives stationary.
It never, it never, yeah, it never moves.
The lifespan of a breasted bug is one day.
(laughter)
As it cannot move to find food.
Their eggs are the size of human boobs.
Their eggs are, sorry I got distracted for a moment.
(laughter)
Yeah.
A breasted bug.
That's what the ladybug should be.
Yeah.
They was talking, back when I was in bug school,
they were talking all this shit about ladybugs being beautiful. Ladybugs are
fucking stupid. They're ugly. Ladybugs go into your house in the spring if it gets
too warm and they get and they they and they say you're people like when they
claw and you'll find them on your pillow and women don't like it when you kill
them yeah that is a red fly they literally have they have ten targets on
them. Exactly. They're designed to be killed. They have a perfect pattern for a
bird shot. Yep. If humans were one inch tall we'd be hunting those MFs.
That's right. That's right. I wish I was one inch tall and could hunt bugs. My
weapon would be a toothpick. I'd probably use a rifle but you can use a toothpick
if you want. Yeah well you're not you're not respecting the tiny. Of course not I'm
blowing them to smithereens. No, I'm not saying you're not respecting the tiny world. You're
shrinking a rifle down the field. Of course not. I'm scouring them. You're already violating
God's natural laws. No, you get shrunken down by accident and then have to survive. I'm
born one inch tall and I've learned to coexist with the bugs and then I turn on them and
I kill them after they don't suspect me. In those movies when everyone gets all small
is shit. Honey I Shrunk the Kids. Just in any movie of the genre. Yeah. They always try to...
No there's tons of smallie guys movies. Downsizing. They don't fight a bug in downsizing. No I'm not getting to that.
No let me finish my goddamn point. Anytime they try to get the attention of somebody
they never can.
(laughter)
saw a person that big like I don't I don't if I see something running like
that I'm not like checking to see if we're an inch tall. I think that's
usually bigger than people are in those movies. Okay, but if that runs on
the right desk, let's see I'm slapping it honey. I shrunk the kids. I mean
they're pretty small now. I think about it. Yeah, they're definitely smaller
than an inch. Yeah. Well, yeah, they ride a inch and they ride an ant but
it could have been a bull ant. Oh, what a bull ant live in California. It's
a bull ant they might have bull ants they're a cow ant maybe could have been
either one I think they never if ever if ever get noticed hardly if ever and
that's that's a real to me that's something that I would like them to put
in the movies is it noticed at the end of get noticed they get noticed at the
end of honey I shrunk the kids never saw that movie you stupid ass never seen any
of those movies. If they really wanted to get noticed, they should like set a fire
or something. That's a really good point. You'll know about Reza Alinsky. But think
about how big a fire is to a small thing. Well you'd set a small fire
because that would make smoke. You should see the sequel. You can't make a fire small
enough to make smoke without it being huge. It's like a candle-sized fire. Yeah,
but you don't like you don't have to like sit on it or anything. A candle-sized fire would be a
serious 9/11. If you're an inch tall, no. No, no, if you're real. Oh, so we're changing it
now yeah we are changing it because I re I re I re okay I would set that I would
carry a match the match is long enough that you would be fine if you if you
held it out hmm I would well what if you shrank down what if it was like an
ant-man situation where you shrink down like that and you still have a molecular
level you know you shrink something interesting you shrink down to that size
but you also have like the same like you can still like like a map nothing over
And then you can get noticed in like one second.
You know it's something, you said people never get noticed.
How we do it?
People never get noticed in small movies, but something interesting I realized is in
movies when people go giant, they almost always get noticed immediately.
That's a really good one.
They explore that in Honey I Blew Up the Kid.
You never have a scene in a movie where someone's like, "Look!
I'm over here!
I'm right here!"
Honey, do you hear something?
No, I think it's just a normal beast.
i think it's a bit i think it's that tall guy i think it's a leg tree that must be
so i don't know what michael craig
my great must be outside i think that that giant leg and foot have always been
there any and you know i had a minute was and now that i think about it i would
say movies where the characters become normal size they're noticed about half
the time
but often not by the one they want to be noticed at least at the beginning
group who at least the beginning
there's so many movies are people are normal size and they're just trying to
find love yeah if they were small it might be harder and if they were big it
would be easier mm-hmm it's a lot easier to find love if you're
giantly sized yeah because there's one line for you slicedly yeah she's in New
York well yeah well if you're giant size every lady and however many mile radius
can see you he's so tall and at least one of them's gonna think that you're
beautiful or handsome yep if you're so this guy barely one lady will ever see
you that's and it might be your mom dude that's the thing about I'm trying to
relax that noise so loud you ever see the you ever see Louis CK when he's on
stage he relaxes you know doing a Louis CK you can say that yeah not the first
time the thing is if they if Godzilla was a real person right and if especially if
he was a good-looking guy if he was that big the reality is Oh every woman in the
world would be lining up to fucking suckle on his cock. Definitely. I mean look at
Robert Wadlow. You know why? Because they go, "Oh he's so tall." He was the closest thing we had to Godzilla.
These whores love tall guys. Mm-hmm. And a lot of times they leave some average-sized
men right in the dust. That's true. That's what I'm saying. Normal size, notice half
the time. It's a sliding scale. It's a perfect equation. And
that's just, you know, modern romance. But then if we...
- We can solve all this with a love army.
- Yeah, but what if it was a guy that was so big
that the entire universe was just a molecule on his body?
Right?
- Everyone loved him.
- But nobody, but get that, nobody's noticing that guy.
- But think about to him, but to him,
all the people in the molecule are so small,
they'll never get noticed, so it doesn't matter.
- But everybody, I mean.
- This is called, this is a new branch of science
called noticeology, where we study people of different sizes being noticed by.
Yeah, it's true. Think about it. You're at a-
Have you noticed a person who's 6'1" almost never notices someone who's 5'9"?
It's true. TED Talk.
With somebody who's that big.
With TED Talk we're just listing heights and being like, "This height notices-
5'9" to 5'6", that's noticeable.
About 77% of the time.
Have you ever been to a concert and there's a tall guy there and he's blocking your view.
you you noticed him. Have you ever noticed a very small dwarf at a
concert? I didn't think so, but I guarantee you this he noticed you
and he's following you and he's going excuse me, excuse me, excuse me,
because that's how they sound.
That's the
and behind is another dwarf yeah one it's shorter. Little does he know
- There's an even smaller dwarf.
An elf who lives in a tree.
- They say a Russian nesting doll
never notices the one inside of it.
- It's true.
- Especially when they're inside.
Do women even notice their pregnant babies?
- No.
- Their pregnant babies.
Do they even notice them?
- They don't recognize their pregnant babies
which causes them to drink and smoke all day long.
- That's right.
research I've done is due to my size women almost never notice when I'm
inside. That's right. I'm one inch tall. If I were a bit bigger. Maybe if I was a bit bigger.
Maybe if I was a bit less of a dwarf and a bit more of a Godzilla. I love TED
Talks man. Yeah. They're all called like the fucking how I learned how I
I learned to use my car for good and it's a 50 minute video of a really old lady
just saying nothing and then there's and then five years later it's like how my
car was actually wrong yeah she has the correction TED talk yeah there's a there's
a TED talk Rodney Mullen did where he's all he does is like they're supposed to
like have him on to talk about like how like innovative and like thinking out
like it was like you know clearly one of these things or it's like they got like
a guest speaker Rodney Mullen and all he does is just show them tricks on his
skateboard and talks about how he invented like the kickflip and
everything. He talks about like the physics of it but then like like the
whole like thing is like pop an ollie and innovate and it's like he's clearly
like reading off his hands. He's just like yeah he's like yeah you know I
kicked my I kicked my foot into the pocket here and then and then the board
the board flipped and that's the whole TED talk. That's what every TED talk is.
I mean do you think that that TED talk might be why skaters have such a
reputation for being pieces of fucking stupid dog shit? I think that TED talk
might have forever ruined skateboarders reputation in the in academic circles. At
least we can rest assured that if it wasn't him ruining it
probably a different dumbass skater would have done it the next day or the
next day so it's like it's it was inevitable yeah we just got it out of the
way but like they got they had BAM scheduled yeah I don't want to do this
gay shit anymore yeah he's like trying to he's trying to skate he's just falling
over the whole time he's been doing good I can't talk shit you can fully talk
shit about BAM Argera I legit can't you can no he's been doing great with what
skating again. His new language, didn't you see his new language? Segillium. Yeah.
The Plan B logo was a two. That was the number two. And the Powell logo was number
one. Mm-hmm. And the heartagram. That's not so yeah, he's doing great. That was an A.
Yeah. How is that, how many skate board logos, is there one for every single letter? Just the
numbers were skate logos and then all the the letters were sigils. Mystical
- So it's not a language, it's an alphabet.
- Yeah, he made a new alphabet and said it was a language.
- Okay, that's pretty cool, that's what I used to do.
- Yeah, me too.
I did that a lot.
- Yeah.
- I never did that.
- No?
- Did that a ton.
- I was pretty much into, what's that shit called?
- Linguistics?
- Codeology.
- Yeah.
- Codeology, and it's where you learn how to sweep
your bangs over your, as a male,
you get like a little Bieber haircut.
- Yeah, I did that.
I knew one kid named Cody who looked like that.
- I used to straight iron my hair.
- Fuck you, Cody.
- I probably wear my heads like this now.
I used to fucking--
- You used to straight, oh no way,
you were one of those kids?
- Bro, I was way cooler than you when I was 11.
- Oh, dude.
- You were probably some gap pussy.
- Nah. - Me?
Dude, I was--
- I wore bootleg Hollister
'cause my mom shopped at Goodwill.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I got made fun of once
'cause I was wearing a fake Abercrombie shirt.
- Sick.
- And someone was like, "Oh, that's not real!"
I was like I'm literally like so fat I don't care.
Like I just don't give like look at me. I look poor as shit already.
I had this one hoodie that I wore for like six years when I was a kid
and yeah I remember it was like I dressed like it was like a cartoon like
I had an outfit that I wore every single day.
- Dressed up exactly like Chris Griffin every day.
- I did look like Chris Griffin.
I looked like Chris Griffin with brown hair.
Actually, I dyed my hair blonde at one point.
- Dude, that'd be so funny if one day,
one of us pulls up dressed exactly like Chris Griffin.
- I don't think you'd even notice, Chris.
- I'm just thinking about it.
- The thing is about--
- Just for like a week, one of us is dressed up
Exactly like Chris.
No one's mentioning it. It's just like the thing is Meg kind of has a fire fit. Oh, yeah
Peter's fits kind of tight. I'm into Brian. I don't I'm into yeah torso. I'm into Brian's fit
Yeah, nude if you show up in a collar
I'm doing a citizen's arrest on you. Fur too? Uh-huh. You wish you had fur. I wish I had fur.
There was one time. I
think I was like
I don't know if I was like I think I was getting dressed to like go to like a
wedding or something and then realized I was dressed exactly like Peter Griffin.
I think I sent you that photo. I was dressed like a white shirt and green pants and like I
looked in the mirror and I was just like oh fuck. No! Oh fuck. Ah shit. Yeah hey Loish.
I'm dressed exactly, you won't believe this, I'm dressed exactly like Peter Griffin.
Going to like a wedding or something, dressed exactly like Peter Griffin, just walking up
to people and like, "Hey, three guesses who I'm dressed up like."
It's so funny to be like a person dressing up like a Family Guy character and not realizing
it.
so fucking funny like especially Chris Griffin cuz that outfit like yeah a lot
of people probably dress like that yeah a lot of people dress like Chris Griffin
mm-hmm hat that's a staple of the that's a Chris Griffin staple hat fat
t-shirt yep shoes I don't know what the shoes look like they're like Adidas with
red stripes that's crazy I have no mental image of what he's wearing
I know exactly what I'm picturing Chris Griffin perfectly in my head right now.
I can imagine him getting pulled through the milk aisle into cartoon land but that's it.
I can't imagine what he's wearing.
Family Guy or Simpsons better fits.
Um.
Isn't Homer and Peter wearing the same shit?
Pretty much.
Well, well, Peter's pants are green.
Just in general.
Is everyone just, I don't know.
Totally.
I'm going to say Homer or Peter.
Um.
I feel like it's got to be the Simpsons right?
Yeah, yeah, cuz you got like the bullies
You rusty if no even me and Caleb morph together we would look like Kearney
We actually might be able to get all the bullies down with us. I think yeah, I've seen people post pictures of the bully
That might be a great. Yeah, I know
Awesome great my life fucking over. Yeah, those were shorts and your shirt was short sleeves
You'd look like Kearney if you were a little fatter a
a little fatter yep i've been putting on pounds boy
he's rude so who's that's good am i am i um what's his name jim ball one yeah yeah
i mean you're jimbo the loserest one that nobody cares about the coolest jimbo's the one with the
hat jimbo's the one with the long hair and the tall one it looks like cam so what's what's the
the other one Cody oh yeah the smelly one I guess oh yeah the smelly naked one
smelly an oil over his penis that one that's the bully that you are yeah I was
getting in the bully spirit that's why I said you can bully that they know man
season 25 yeah good good good yeah we're revitalizing a citizen's brain by
introducing 15 new cavemen characters that will live in the town you do I
can't help it I have stomach I know that's gonna smell so bad no my farts
to smell like nothing. My poop has smelled like just the ground. Yeah. Yeah. When you
get sick sometimes your poop starts to smell like earth. My thing is everything, my poops
are so fucked up usually. Are you sure this wouldn't be Cam? Dolph? No, see that's the
gap. You'd have to work into that. I think that's you. That would be me but I don't think
I have a hair line strong enough to...
That's you except for the hair.
He's got a comb over.
You could comb that thing over.
Would I be Nelson?
Oh, you actually could be Nelson.
You could be Nelson, but Nelson's a little bit younger than the other bones.
Yeah.
Damn. Would I have to be Nelson?
No, you could be the other guy.
If we're switching characters, then I am Bart.
What is it?
Dolph Starbeam.
Coolest fucking name I've ever heard.
Well, Nelson's real name is Mandela.
That ain't true.
Yeah, it is.
Really?
Yeah.
Whoa.
That's cool.
All right.
You're Ralph.
OK.
Yeah.
Just decided.
I'm Ralph.
Just decided, because you know--
And I'm Mr. Burns.
Yeah.
Wait, wouldn't it be Martin?
He's the nerd.
No, but you know stupid stuff, so you're Ralph.
Yeah, you're Ralph.
That's true.
Oh, wait.
You're Martin.
No.
And I'm Bart.
I'm Jimbo.
He's Milhouse.
I'm pretty much Bart.
I'm not millhouse your millhouse and your Marge and I'm playing with my boobs
you're the dog yeah the dog Santa's little helper yeah yeah little little
little dog yeah I'm a greyhound and I'm fast wait isn't he Santa's little helper
- no yeah get a second yeah or no it's snowball - snowball - yeah snowballs the
cat yeah okay yeah yeah this - yeah I wonder if in in countries where they
don't have Christmas they have to change Santa's little helper's name to little
little helper dog. Probably whatever the deity of that country is. Probably they'd have to do that.
Because they wouldn't understand. Santa's little helper. Yeah, that's probably what they would do over there. Yeah, in Canada.
Yeah, because they won't let them damn truckers watch The Simpsons anymore. And that's why they're complaining.
They want DVD players in their car to play The Simpsons hit-and-run. Mm-hmm.
and they're doing hit and runs until they get to play it.
- That's right.
It is kinda cool that they can just like,
if the truckers just give up on you,
you don't even get to have all your snacks anymore.
(laughing)
Like how are you gonna get shit?
- We just got a chips box today.
- What?
What does that even mean?
- You know those chips boxes?
- No, what the fuck are you even fucking talking about?
- That people get their kids for school lunches.
- Oh yeah.
- I thought you meant, what flavors?
- I don't know, I didn't look at it.
You didn't even look? I didn't get it. You're an animal. Yeah. What brand? Lay's? I think so.
Okay. Okay, so you got Lay's original, you got barbecue chips. Yeah. I don't know, I
don't know, I didn't look at it. Ruffles. Cheddar Ruffles. Cheddar Ruffles if it's
like the, you know. Yeah, if it's a good one. Yeah. The one that I used to, I used to
buy a pack of those at Costco when I was a kid and I would
sell them next to the graveyard next to my house. Oh, you told me about that. You'd sell candy bars and that shit too.
make some money doing that. That's how I bought my Abercrombie sweatpants that I used to have.
They were $30. Nice. It's pretty cool. But I bet you guys don't have chips boxes. I could get one
pretty easily. Yeah but you don't have it so it doesn't really matter. Maybe I do. You don't.
Maybe I have two of them. You don't have two. You know they make packs of those with better flavors.
Better flavors than what? Than the ones that we were just talking about? Yeah.
I don't know there's the base one and then they have some that are like, you know, they have a
cool ranch instead of like a set of nacho cheese, yeah instead of nacho cheese and they have some that have like
Like the sour cream and cheddar. That's the thing though. It could it could have Doritos in there
I think you know what I hate the
Fritos chili cheese
That come in those, you know, it's really boxes. I'm not a fan of Fritos in general. Yeah Fritos not good
- Fritos are pretty good.
- Fritos with actual chili on them.
If you put some Fritos in chili, that's good.
- The first Frito, dog shit.
- Yeah.
- Eat that shit.
But the 10th Frito that you have, if it's all you got.
- To me, eating a Frito feels like drinking salt water.
- You acclimate.
You acclimate to a Frito.
- Yeah, but I don't want to.
- No, and it gets good.
- You know what it is?
- You acclimate to drinking salt water.
- No, you start getting--
- It smells like a dog.
- You start getting really subtle corn flavors
once you get 10 Fritos in.
the corn. Yeah, that's why that's the thing. It has to be,
there has to be plain Fritos, right? I like the,
I like the tangy barbecue ones too. The twists? Yeah.
That's one that like, they were vegan. That's why I like,
that's the one that I do like. I would have to wait.
Like I could probably eat those now, but like for years I couldn't eat them
because the thought of eating them like made me feel like I wanted to puke.
Made you feel like you wanted to puke? Because I ate like so many of them.
thought of them? Yeah, I ate so many of them. You know the thing where you eat too much of
one thing? Like I can't eat Peeps ever again? You ate too many? I ate too many Peeps. Peeps
are nasty. Yeah, Peeps are already nasty. If you have the ability to eat too many Peeps,
there's something wrong with you. As a 7 year old? Yes. No, when you're 7 years old, you're
trying to put the max amount of sugar in you. No, you should be able to have moderation
when you're seven years old or else you should be executed
now
let's uh... that
i like how to use
i like how to use but like i'd leave like the uh...
you know if there's a family in the neighborhood that went to the dollar
store
and got all the snacks which you know you can't really
can't knock them for that
banged up a book on the candy
but halloween is the dentist's worst nightmare
yeah because of the scary ghost
uh... because of the terrifying
to the greens of the jack o'lanterns yet
i think i'll never be able to straighten that jagged tooth
why don't the jack o'lanterns have full sets of teeth?
they get scared by the skeletons because it's all tooth
they're basically all tooth they realize
they think, they say oh my god everything is tooth
No, but you get like a fucking, what was that shit,
Neko wafers?
Love Neko wafers.
Really?
I was a fan of those.
My granddad loves them.
I mean, I gotta show respect.
Those are a fun textural thing.
Yep.
Some of them are--
That's a perfect candy for an autistic kid.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, that's like the equivalent of like,
running a horse brush over an autistic kid's head
to stimulate them.
Definitely.
Yeah.
That's why you like them?
probably I always like the the coke bottle ones oh I didn't like those
bottles bottle caps they get a lot of water bottle can you on them yeah or the
wax bottle the wax no wax bottle I like the wax bottles yeah you just chew on
them they taste like something for one second yeah chew on a candle yeah of
the night yeah yeah bottle caps I don't know what those are you know what they
are you know the soda flavor things so Wonka makes them Willie
Oh Willie Wonka. Let me look them up I don't think I'd want I never fucked with
soda flavored candy. I had the idea to turn soda flavor you didn't like them. I don't drink soda either
Oh true so whoever turned whoever decided to turn Wonka into a real thing
should be put to death yeah pretty fucking smart. You've given a lot of children type 2 diabetes.
I mean I won't name it after the guy who owns the car really think so Ernie the
company company or maybe Wonka it's fucking fraud to name them Willy Wonka
candies cuz if there's Willy Wonka isn't real you can't name it that it is kind
of fun about Santa's workshop oh yes Nestle it is yeah it's not good that I
knew that the fuck it's not good I knew that remember this was like a candy that
was on the market for like... They discontinued it. They stopped branding things as Wonka.
What? Really? It used to be Wonka Nerds, Sweet Tarts, Laffy Taffy, Gobstoppers. Oh yeah, I
did notice that in the past year. I'm not going to say the name of that candy. What
is it? It's called... That was Wonka branded? It's a candy called Negro. Why does it say
Hungarian on it. I don't know. It's interesting. I don't know if you can say that. Negro? I can say it.
There's a name of a candy in Hungaria. That was a Willy Wonka candy. Yeah. Damn. That's cool. Do you
remember there was a Wonka candy, it like, as soon as it came out it was gone.
Because like people were like, "Jesus." Which one? Oh yeah, the one with the golden ticket, the Wonka bar. Yeah.
Yeah, the Wonka Bar.
And those seven kids won.
Dude, I wanted to eat those so bad.
No, no, Wonka Donuts.
What?
What the fuck?
Yeah, dude.
These...
They do actually have a Wonka Bar.
They used to.
This.
I've never seen that in my life.
It was like a chocolate...
It was just chocolate.
It was the most like sugar-filled thing.
Yeah.
Did you guys ever...
Did you guys like buy candy from whatever?
Like did you guys like...
Like I would always...
When I was walking, I would always walk home from middle school with my friends and we
would just like...
we just edit it like we just try and find a quarter or something all day and then
by just like lemon heads yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
convenience store working in edge who would just so we would just we just talk
to every day sick yeah I miss that my dad lived like four blocks from a
convenience store and I would go there and the guy who ran it was like a
hair metal guy. Yeah. And I thought he was a woman for my entire life
until I went there recently and he's just like an old hair metal dude. Getting candy
from the convenience store as a kid is like the best thing ever. Yeah dude.
Yeah. Oh I got so obsessed with lemon heads. Yeah we would always get, because they had like
lemon heads and like cherry heads. Orange heads. Yeah I like the cherry heads. When I was like,
I think I got a dollar or like a, yeah. Do you still have it? No. Oh fuck.
I got like a dollar from like my uncle or some shit and I went to a quick stop in London
Dairy which is like near my house.
It was in walking distance but it was like a mile away from my house so I'd walk a mile
then just go buy a shit ton of candy and walk home.
And I went there and cleared out like the, not cleared out but like got every single
one of those flavors because I was like I have to try them all.
I have to try chewy, well you know there's chewy lemon head and there's chewy lime head
and there's chewy orange head and like.
You tried them all?
I tried all of them and I thought that the characters on the Lemonhead things were so cool that I wanted them to have their own show.
Whoa. Whoa. You mean the show?
I mean the show where they're all hanging around.
That's pretty cool.
That's pretty fucking smart.
I love this candy so much I wish I could watch it on TV every day instead of just eating it.
I wish I could waste 30 more minutes of my time.
That's all children's marketing though.
That's so sick dude.
Dude the fucking Wonderball and pretty much every toy that existed in the 80s only existed in a TV show.
Well that's because you can make a TV show in 20 minutes with GoAnimate now.
Yeah that's true.
and you could just you just put it on YouTube and you say it's like a cartoon
like I was at the I was in the Tom I was yeah the Talking Tom so that's a big one
that's what I was at a 400 episodes made in Cyprus yeah yeah we talked about that
for like a whole episode we did yeah I was at the dollar store recently in the
mall and I was like walking I always go through the toy aisle to see like if I
fortnight toys and I always find like they're always toys that are just for
like a TV show that's not real like it'll be like like branded toys where
It's like don't collect them all and it's like yeah, and there's like I forget there was why I forgot was called
It was called final something. There's like some like sci-fi toys
I was like what the fuck is this I was looking on the back and it's like watch the cartoon like today at youtube.com
Slash like whatever like it's just like they just have YouTube cartoons that they're making toys. That's awesome. Well. Yeah, that's like
They have all the Ryan's World branded toys now. It's just like like blippy toys
And you always fell off toys have fallen off everything's that my own
- I disagree.
- All the shit my nephews have been getting, suck ass.
- I feel like if you are operating on a level as a child
where you can get, you kinda got that like,
you see it, you buy it status with your mommy and daddy.
Like I feel like you can get some fire toys now.
- Yeah, but that doesn't count.
- I feel like that counts.
- No, I mean--
- I feel like the highs are higher now.
Like you can get, well no, you know what?
Maybe they nerfed a lot of stuff for safety reasons.
- They did. - Like choking and shit.
- They did, yeah.
And I feel the high end now is like,
you can get like a drone, but that's not like a toy.
- You're right, you're right.
- That's like, I think we're talking like toys.
- You're right, toys, you know, I thought it would follow--
- Not like technology, but like toys,
I think they suck now.
- I feel like games have all gotten cooler.
I thought toys would follow the same thing.
No, they kinda, you're right,
it's all just turned into RC shit.
You did get Kinga.
- Yeah, 'cause all the toys are for adults now too.
They're all collectible,
like all the like, they like good action figures and stuff.
Yeah I know they're putting so many points of articulation on action figures
Exactly yeah and they're all like they're all like $250 you have to build
them yourself with a soldering iron. You see like the the old Kenner like Star
Wars stuff from the 90s it's like and all they did was slap like dude three
four like five parts yeah but now it's like they would get every color on the
character wrong uh-huh like every their clothes would be the wrong color yeah
their skin would be blue because they would have like every fucking oh yeah
like the first the first like 70s like Kenner Luke Skywalker's that had like
the arms that were a lightsaber yeah they gave Luke like a yellow lightsaber
yeah every every every everybody would be cross-eyed because they'd have some like
slave child painting yeah he pulls into the eyes yeah no what a normal I looks
like he's crazy he's cross yeah yeah yeah damn we got it we have to go back we
have to work we're like we're return guy return to tradition guys but only for
like toys yeah yeah there's making too many damn toys nowadays honestly I was
fine growing up I was a simple kid ball yeah unbeatable toy ball I did have I
was I was all and again Dylan science science you had a ball and Dylan a
science kit kid I had every like I had every toy I had every toy no you man I
have every toy but like you know everything that I like to watch I had to
get the action figure of yeah I had like like when I saw X-Men origins I thought
they had like a gambit action figure and one for fucking it went for Maverick
who's like Mavericks in the movie for like see like a wave like five minutes
is a wave power I think no he can like control electricity or some shit but he
also has a big gun whoa yeah it's actually a cool-looking character
pretty cool actually he's played by the guy from lost in that I was get well I
am was in X-Men origins and he plays a teleporter I was in everything for a hot
minute yeah he was in everything mm-hmm black eyed peas what's that what no the
actor will I am yeah what's the black is that a movie he was in yeah he's in a
movie called the black eyed peas what's it about it's about it's about a musical
group whoa that sounds interesting called the Beatles I hear they're better
than the Beatles. He played a little, he played a character named Paul I am.
Paul-ium. That was when Will.i.am like. Yeah it was Paul.i.am, Riggo.i.am, George.
That like 2008 when Will.i.am decided like I am a technological genius. Yeah he made
like a like an mp3 player. Yeah. And they did they did interviews with him he's
doing the wrong and he's like it can play music faster yeah it's awesome it can
play flack files yeah yeah but then like will.i.am from like 2008 to like 2014
like every shitty tech demo will.i.am would be like this is the future yeah
it's like him like oh yeah if anyone knows the future yeah it's true
futurist yeah his name is literally will I am dude I forgot about Google glass I'm
pretty was one of these that only moly he was obsessed with the future I don't
know why because it's cool yes fuck coolest shit you kidding me you're not
obsessed with the future I'm obsessed with the past damn damn that's some real
shit you just said right now I'm obsessed with eating all my food with a
stick of butter and women belonging where they belong and driving a big car that
guzzles a lot of gas and eating and eating stew from a slow cooker and
running from a tyrannosaur and becoming one of the twelve apostles. And getting a bone
through my nose. I'm kind of an old-school guy. And I don't know, discovering the wheel.
yeah and what's that what's that red hot thing sriracha okay I'm not as stupid as
a Doug bye go buy a ticket to the live show D&D live show dungeon
Dungeons and Dragons. Union Hall and it's 730? 730. At night. Not the morning. At night.
P.M. Yeah so if you're an early bird, stay away. Just for those night owls. 730 P.M.
See you there. Bye!