you're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
I'm recording, dude.
I'm recording.
Well, is my audio loud right now?
It's normal.
Sounds like shit, dude.
Yeah, I think you plugged in the microphone and made a poop.
Is that...
Yeah, dude, you're talking...
Pat, you're talking into the toilet again.
Is that what that sound is?
Yeah, you're speaking into the toilet.
The amp sound is too quiet to even, it's probably, you won't be able to hear it.
Pat, get your head out of the toilet.
Oh God, he got stuck in the toilet.
Oh my God.
Alright, I'll shut up.
Yeah, I mean, if you were gonna do that bit, you should have done it louder.
We couldn't really tell what you were doing.
You know what, Cameron?
There are a lot of things I could do different in my life.
Alright, let's go through it.
This is today's list.
Alright, if we could, if you could redo your life.
What changes are you making?
I don't know, probably wouldn't get this haircut.
Really?
Yeah.
What haircut would you have done?
I don't know, one that doesn't make me...
Cool afro?
You would have gotten one hair sticking straight up like a cartoon baby.
Yeah, exactly.
I would have gotten one that doesn't...
One spiral hair.
Pat would have gotten...
He would have grown his hair out and then every night he would wear like a velvet robe
and have like curlers in his hair like an old lady.
And he would walk around asking people if they wanted a midnight snack.
He would go everywhere in a shower cap.
So?
Yeah, you would.
You would do that.
Who cares?
Yeah.
I care, because I'm-- Why would you care about that?
You would wear a shower cap and have like six foot long hair taped onto it and pretend
to act like it's your real hair and you're like, "What are you talking about?"
Yeah, just clear double-sided tape on his skull.
Yeah, yeah.
Should I get-- With like a puffy shower cap.
Should you get a toupee?
That'd be pretty funny.
Yeah, that would be good.
Yeah.
Just have like a just an absolute beast of a hairline.
Yeah, I mean look at my hairline now.
But yeah, if you just had just like a, if you had like a 13 year old like Chinese kid hairline.
Yeah, yeah.
That'd be next level.
That'd be sick.
That'd be so sick.
Yeah, it'd look great.
Yeah, we'd look like a Lego man.
A completely straight bowl cut, dude.
Yeah, you could have a nice bowl cut.
I kind of look like a Lego man now.
Yeah, you just, well that's because you just have a, you have a square circle head.
Yeah, you have the shape of a Lego, Lego head.
That's true.
That's true, I do look like a Lego.
Yeah, and you kind of have the, you have like the brain of a Lego too.
Oh my god, you're giving the Reddit ammo.
There's like five people on the subreddit, I don't think they should worry about it.
Yeah, someone's gonna post-
And they just post like a picture of like a fucked up monkey and they're like, "This is Caleb."
Yeah.
if they ever if I'm just gonna say this now if you post a picture of a Lego man
to the subreddit with the caption Patrick officially that puts you on the sex
he wants you to jury he wants you to do it as a trick no yeah the sex offender
registry it's a trick in the sense of like a hundred sex tricks that will
drive Patrick crazy yeah yeah it is yeah it's like a like this you're gonna do
baby hairs like a Puerto Rican lady. Caleb, why is your video only showing the
bottom half of your face? He always does. I don't have my, here I'll move this, I don't have
my self view on it because I don't like looking at my big red head so I turn it
off and I can't tell. We got him on tape saying he's red. It's official. I do not.
Is that better? Today I just went to the gym and on my way to the gym I lost my
I had my headphones that plug into my phone.
- Yeah.
- And so I was like,
"Oh, I'll just pick up some Bluetooth headphones somewhere."
So the only place that I thought would sell them
between my house and the gym is a Boost Mobile.
And so I walked in.
I walked in, yeah, I thought so.
And they did.
I walked in and I was like,
"Hey, do you guys have Bluetooth headphones?"
And then the guy was just like Eastern block dude.
He's like, "Bro, I tell you, we have not just headphone,
"greatest headphone all time."
(laughing)
I was like, "Greatest headphone of all time?
"All right, let's fucking see these," he says.
Made by Samsung, same guy make TV.
Greatest TV in world, okay?
I was like, "Dude, awesome, man."
And he handed them to me, and I was like,
he was like, "Waterproof, extremely strong.
"You should bullet it is, bounce off.
"Greatest headphone in world."
I was like, "Okay, cool, how much are these?"
And he's like, "Little pricey."
Samsung, best TVs, made of same material as TVs.
(laughing)
And I was like, "All right, just tell me how much they are."
He says, "$270."
(laughing)
And I was like, "Dude, I can't buy these."
And he's like, "Just for you, $220."
And I just walked out and I looked it up on my phone
and they were $60 online.
(laughing)
- That's so fucking sick. - Completely fucked up, dude.
I hate Russians so much. People need to do that more and like we need to see that in
convenient stores and stuff like people trying to rip you off on like Pepsi or like just be like
yeah this is the best soda in the world. It was 11 a.m. Moscow time and he was trying to sell me
wireless headphones. Yeah it's true. These Lay's chips, same people who make Fritos okay.
I do wish you could haggle on every single item.
Yeah.
Well, no, it's not haggling, just like a guy who will try to sell your things.
Yeah, like he's like a salesman.
The way you do that is everything is sold on commission.
Yeah.
So like every carton of eggs, every gallon of milk, people only get paid if they sell it to you
and you like mention their name at the register.
Yeah.
Just Russian guys, just like the best eggs in the world.
Extra large eggs, 12 eggs.
Check.
They come from the biggest chicken.
None come from biggest craziest toughest chicken in chicken prison so this watch
Same chicken that makes chicken breast
This is breast come from your like
In on farm come from farm farm with biggest Pamela Anderson chickens all over the place
all over the place
Look at these chickens
By this chicken around wow that should be like in the service industry too like if you're getting a haircut
You should have to convince the guy to give you a good haircut instead of a bad one
Yeah talked about this recently but like yeah, we didn't talk about it well
No, we talked about how it's like people act like it's it's art, but it should be like you know clipping toenails
But I think it'd be fun if you had to like if you had to like haggle for your haircuts
I like not in like a price sense, but they're like all right listen it all costs. Yeah, it's all
But you just have to try and convince them to give you one good haircut.
Yeah, alright listen, I'll give you a fade for $100 and for $120 I won't shave a slur
into the back of your head.
I'm not going to put the Puerto Rican flag in the back of your head.
It's going to cost you.
It's going to cost me not to do that.
- Yeah, it's gonna cost, the thing is,
Puerto Rico's paying me to put these flags
in people's heads like billboards.
It's sponsorship for tourism.
'Cause they see a white guy with a Puerto Rican flag
shaved into their head, all the other fuckin' people
in the suburbs are gonna be like,
you know what, maybe Christmas in Puerto Rico this year.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, bring the economy.
- I saw Daniel with that Puerto Rican flag
shaved into his head, I think--
- Maybe we should consider Puerto Rico for the wedding.
- Maybe we should go.
Yeah, and yeah, and then they go they get to Puerto Rico. It's all just kids with fucking
AK-47s for legs and
We fucked up is that we were no Puerto Rico is a pretty normal place
Puerto Rico and there's a giant 300 foot ape attacking the city. Yeah, you need a Puerto Rico find King Kong
Hey, you have to think of some kind of funny joke where we go is skull island pretty much as far as yeah
Yeah, yeah, that's why that's why we need to add it as the 51st state cuz then we can add a skull to the flag
Cuz then we can make a punisher. You all citizen. Yeah, we could use King Kong instead of the nuke
We could use King Kong instead of the Statue of Liberty. Just pay him hourly to just yeah, you know
Dude, Statue of Liberty is not doing anything for anybody.
Conspiracy theory, that's already what's happening.
Oh my god, that's the worst conspiracy theory of all time.
It's like that video that was like top 10 times that the Statue of Liberty was spotted moving.
Oh yeah.
And it's just like...
It's just like videos of like, like those like iPhone app special effects of like the Statue of Liberty, like doing the hula.
Putting Statue of Liberty on elfyourself.com.
Yeah, exactly.
It's like look, he's singing a Christmas song.
song we've stat the Statue of Liberty is elfed itself in the Statue of Liberty has
elfed itself it's somewhere in the North Pole this is not good news yeah this is
doing a news it's Santa Claus it's doing a dance with my uncle and my estranged
grandfather who lives in Ecuador for some reason with a younger woman that's
That's the only experience I have with elf yourself.
That's the only elf yourselves I ever get.
- Really?
- From that guy. - From your grandpa?
- Yeah, from my crazy grandpa.
- Oh yeah, I forgot about that.
You guys both have crazy grandpas.
- I have two crazy grandpas.
- You guys both have bad grandpas.
- We do. - Oh yeah.
- Oh yeah. - Dirty grandpas.
- See, the thing about being a bad grandpa
is you also have to be a bad father.
- Wow, I don't think so.
- Yeah, you can be a, well, I think usually,
if you're a bad father, you will be a bad grandpa.
But I feel like it's almost--
I think you can change. You can change and become a bad guy.
Here's how all men work. You're born, you have sex when you're 14, okay?
It ruins your life for 50 years. For 50 years, you're a piece of shit.
You hit your son with a belt. You ban candy in your house.
But then, you have grandkids. Again, you don't really give a fuck.
But then, you get cancer. And then, for some reason, you turn into
into like a kind of like an okay guy because of cancer yeah that's how it
goes that's yeah okay listen here's the here's how you be here's it's the way
that you be a bad father but a good grandfather is you know you have your
son you beat your son because he looks half like your wife and you don't like
your wife okay and then your wife has sex are you then you're then your son as
grows up and has sex and as a kid and you're nice to that kid because he looks
like your son's really hot wife that you always always try and Amanda and hit on
and family reunions that's a really weird point make weird comments exactly yeah
you you try and you try and you you cut a people into the wall on the wedding day
with a with a drill from a Tom and Jerry cartoon my my granddad he's like five
seven and like three or four years ago my older brother his but he brought his ex
girlfriend and his ex-girlfriend's sister over and they have like it's like a
family of tall girls like she was like she's like 6'2" and she's like a big fat
bitch 6'2" and she walks into Christmas and my granddad's like oh hey hey kids
hey hey you hello beautiful and then just spent the rest of the night in front of
his wife just like basically trying to convince a 19 year old to like go to the
bedroom and fuck him. Shit, this is so insane. I love him dude. That's pretty cool. I love him so much. I think that would I think it
would have worked. I mean he she you know she probably probably her best option in
life honestly. I think she became like one of those one of those nurses who
makes like less than minimum wage somehow. Yeah it's so funny how that's a
huge industry in America. It's funny that yeah the dumbest people in the world
become nurses yeah the nurses they're like yeah it's like a last option it's
like yeah I'm a garbage man or a nurse yeah they're like oh I don't I want to I
want to save lives and they become a nurse and they just it's like oh no
you're you're licking bloodstains off of off of the sheets in the basement for
four hours a day yeah yeah you're not defending nurses I'm gonna take a hard
stance that's cuz you're from New Hampshire because you are a male nurse
It's like New Hampshire's main export.
Yeah, exactly.
It's like nurses, like nurses who are 20 and look 50.
There's a very specific type of person who becomes a nurse.
Yeah.
A woman.
I would say, yeah, that's true.
A very specific type of person.
That's a very good point.
Yeah.
No, but like I think of everyone I went to high school with who went on to like nursing
school and I'm like, oh yeah, these are all like the same type of person.
- No, they're not Grey's Anatomy's people, dude.
They're McDonald's people.
- Yeah. - No, like,
there's the type of person who went to nursing school
because of Grey's Anatomy.
- And they were too stupid to become a doctor.
So they were like, I'm gonna go be a nurse.
- Yeah, I would say, I would say, like--
- Why do you keep calling nurses stupid?
- 'Cause they are.
- Nurses, like, the person who becomes a nurse
is like the second rank of UGGs wearing.
You know what I mean?
Like, not the popular UGGs wearing.
No, no, no, there's like the nurses on like the nurses on TikTok. I know what you mean.
Like the TikTok nurses who were like, "I don't believe anything my patients say."
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, the ones who are like, "Oh, you have a fever."
I just forgot about that. That's a big subsection of nurses.
Every person I know in North Carolina who's a nurse had like a kid at 15 and is like 35
acne and has like a husband who like basically does what Patrick does and just
goes and plays video games with a briefcase full of ice cream. All the
nurses in my town are like vineyard vines girls which I think is kind of
close to the equivalent of that for this area of Massachusetts. Yeah.
Yeah. If you ever had a nurse, if you ever had a male nurse. It's like if you reflect it through the money
mirror that's like if I had a male nurse version of that lifestyle I would say
excuse me sir there must have been some mistake you're supposed to be a woman
great two doctors that's what I'm sorry listen I don't want to blow your cover
you're obviously a spy pretending to be a nurse you're an undercover boss right
now way yeah yeah you're the boss of the hospital who's pretending to be a nurse a
girl so that you can figure out what they're doing yeah why do they have a
- Excuse me, a confused patient wandered into my room.
- Yeah.
Why does this patient have on scrubs?
- I think a guy came over from the asylum
'cause he thinks he's a nurse.
He must have broken out.
- Yeah, that was the whole concept of Scrubs,
was like, what if there was a male nurse?
And it was pretty funny when you think about it.
- They did a lot of blackface on that show too.
- Oh yeah, there was two black characters.
Yeah, JD and Turk.
Yeah.
To the two black characters.
The two black guys from Turks.
Turk Scrubs.
(laughing)
Turks.
Turk Scrubs.
I've been watching Succession,
have you guys seen that show?
No.
No, I've not seen that.
I haven't seen that,
but I've seen your mom in a succession with me.
Oh my God.
Anybody else have anything to add?
Yeah, I also, I was successful with your mom.
Cameron was in the--
You were successful?
Cameron was also at the succession.
- Okay, okay, all right, anything else?
- Yeah, and we had a sex session as well.
- Yep. - Okay, all right.
- And we were on a sex mission, actually.
- Uh-huh. - Yeah, I--
- And we watched the Sex Sense with her.
- And Sex and the City.
- Mm-hmm.
(laughing)
She wouldn't let us do anything
until we watched it with her,
'cause she needed to catch up.
- Is there anything else?
- And then she said,
"Caleb is my least favorite son."
okay cool and you know that's true because we both said it at the exact same
time that's a really good point so I do know that that part if anything is true
it's that part yeah is there anything else and then she gave us six suckings
okay six suckings of at the sex session yeah more more of a suck session while
watching sex sense anything else I just want to give a correction there the
movie is called you know erection there okay the movie is called sponge knob
square nuts it's actually it's called it's called come boob yeah it's a new
sex yeah we're doing sex parodies yeah why did your brain immediately go to
Rugrats a cartoon about what Kayla go I want to watch a movie I want to change a
movie I think it's a I've never seen Rugrats I don't watch baby cartoons I
watch very cool card what you know what
cartoon it's a hmm hmm
no I don't watch any sort of cartoon for
little for young for kids I watch
older people cartoons like Spongebob
Rennes Rennes Stimpy yeah Angry Beavers
yeah you know as a guy who made Ren and
Stimpy kind of messed up I'm making it
so gross and creepy because he was a
pedophile right so yeah he was all the
talking about yourself here yeah you yeah you are a pedophile
that's why Ren and Stimpy was so fucked up it came from the most disgusting
depraved mind. From the twisted mind of a pedophile. That should have been a red flag.
That was the tagline for Ren and Stimpy. Imagine seeing that at the beginning of
like any Woody Allen movie. From the twisted mind of a rampage. Annie Hall.
genius dude oh man well now they can all of those like Hollywood like rapists
they can just kind of they can release like they can re-release those movies as
horror movies with a recut trailers you know yeah so if they have if they have
the word twisted mind in their in their trailer like from their their director
intro I think that that kind of I think they could use that I don't fucking know
man this is another it's another fucking me complaining about how tired I am I
woke up at like 8 today me too I want pretty high is that a crazy time for you
to wake up I feel like you're up at 8 pretty much every day I always I'm next
in the morning when I'm going to work and you always respond like any any time
Patrick says that he wakes up it's he's tired yep yeah I think I have chronic
fatigue I think you have fibromyalgia yeah and I could just say that and then
for the rest of my life say it and no one would not believe me.
Yeah.
You'd probably get a job, you'd probably be on Comedy Central in two weeks.
You'd probably have a special called Lafro my ass off.
Fibro my ass off.
Fibro my lafja.
Yeah.
I'm looking at fibromyalgia now.
Chronic, yeah.
Symptoms of.
Chronic fat teen syndrome.
I have all of this.
myalgia the symptoms are is is when your body feels sad mm-hmm when uh yeah yeah
sadness yeah when you when it when you can't see in the dark bleeding from the
vagina three days a month I do more than that you do yeah yeah it's more like a
whole week what's like having a vagina pet it sucks
Smells like shit. Can't sit on the bus without fucking stinking it up.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, you have to wear one of those, like, uh...
When I do sit on the bus, everyone goes, "HOO-EE!"
"Someone on here got the stanky pussy!"
And you sit, you raise your hand.
Yeah, I have to raise my hand.
The bus driver turns around, "Whose pussy do I smell?"
It's me.
Me.
Obviously.
Sorry.
It sucks that every time I go to, like, the bus stop...
Not again!
Yeah, I'm at the bus stop and I hear a guy going "Yee dokey!"
A green stink line emanates from your pussy, hits the bus driver, and he immediately grabs
flowers, brings them to his chest, and floats up to heaven.
Yeah.
Ding.
Yeah, my pussy kills people.
That's a cool, that's a cool scary movie.
Yeah.
That's a good, that would be a good name for like, for a punk band.
That's the, that's the sex sense.
"My Pussy Kills People"
That would be a game for like a sex-
That's a good shirt for women. That's a good t-shirt.
That would be a good punk band, like an
Alston punk band with
dangly earrings.
What would it- what kind of t-shirt would a woman-
What kind of funny t-shirt could a woman wear?
I think "My Pussy
Kills People" with a picture of a
gun. That would not be funny, that would be scary.
How about two
arrows pointing up and it says
"I'm with these boobs and they have poop
in them that might be pretty good all right yeah all right this whole this
hole's mine buster what about like good one what about like one of those shirts
where it's got the arrows pointing up and down it says like the man the legend but
it says the woman the pussy yeah that's a funny what about what about what about
it's letters that are printed on the boobs to say my pussy is down here and an
arrow down yeah excuse me my pussy is down here yeah excuse me my boobs are
full of helium and I use them to float in the water how about a t-shirt for her
face that says excuse me my boobies are down here and points down what about a
mask that says that no shut up dude what no what I'm trying to capitalize on
What are you talking about?
A mask.
Who would wear a mask?
A cloth mask.
You're a freak, dude.
A cloth mask?
For COVID-19 awareness.
My other husband's in the garage.
My other husband's in Iraq.
That might be good, yeah.
Yeah.
Let's see.
What do girls like?
Girls like money.
Yeah.
And Tana...
And what about showers?
What about one of those old, those like shirts where it's like...
unless they like our money in the shower and then a winky emoji yeah sure what
about one of those sir you know those shirts that were like I hate homework I
only love video games but we could like reboot it and bring it into the modern
era and have it be you know it says like I hate driving a car I am so beautiful
that's a little stick figure okay yeah yeah what's the girl equivalent of
video games cuz I like those t-shirt like the shirts where it's like the
cartoon character and he it's like a cartoon character that looks like it was
made out of like slime he's like like going like and he's playing a video game
yeah yeah with his like I paused I paused my vagina to be here yeah I've
met a paused my game oh my god that's good yeah mm-hmm yeah okay wait wait
okay I got it I got a shirt that's loading might be good how about I'm I'm
not a woman because I have no life I'm a woman but woman because I have many and
then it's an x-ray to a bunch of babies growing inside of her stomach yeah and
it's a real x-ray and you have to have a lot of babies growing in your stomach to
wear the hair we go or else you'll just see the food what about yeah no it's
like what about a shirt talk to mom this here this is kind of different but what
about a shirt with an x-ray on it so you can see what food the person is eating
today that's even better not a bad idea and it says my food yeah okay yeah okay
what about an app called my food and you just it just log on food you just say it
doesn't give you calories or anything you just say what food you ate into it
- And you can't even look back at it either.
- That's like Chips app.
- I just looked it up, there's already an app called My Food.
- All right, what about Chips app?
'Cause I think if we got a designer--
- Stop trying to push Chips app.
Nobody's gonna download Chips app.
- A lot of people would download Chips app.
- Nobody likes Chips that much.
- I like the idea of Chips app, but I wouldn't use it.
- People hate Chips.
- People like Chips.
- People always rather eat a full raw potato
than a potato chip.
- No.
- At any given point in time.
- Okay, what about tortilla chips?
- They'd rather eat a full tortilla.
- No, they wouldn't.
- Vegetable.
- They would not eat a vegetable.
- They would eat a full tortilla ball.
- People hate vegetables.
- Yeah, like who?
Name one person who hates a vegetable.
- Ryan.
- Okay.
- My cousin.
- That could be possible.
- All right, give him a call.
- I don't really have the resources to fact check.
- I don't have his phone number.
- Oh, okay.
- I'm not CBS.
- A cousin whose phone number you don't have?
- Okay, a cousin whose phone number
you don't have remembered, not a cousin.
- Yep, doesn't count. - No, I don't consider him
my cousin.
- You need to memorize your cousin's phone numbers
just in case you ever get in a little bit of a,
you know, a pickle. - Some cousin trouble.
- Some, a little bit of cousy-trousy.
(laughing)
You know? - A little cousy-trubby.
- Yeah. - A little cubby-trubby.
- Yeah.
- I hate getting into cubby-trubby.
- What, I'm trying to think if I've ever been
in huge trouble with a lot of my cousins.
I have. Yeah, I have. Yeah, yeah I have. I don't think I have. You're not gonna say it.
My cousin, no, yeah, no, I'd go to jail. Yeah. My cousin smoked weed when he was 15.
Yeah. And we got in a lot of trouble for that one. Yeah. Yeah. You got in
trouble? You didn't smoke? I got in trouble, yeah. Cuz I did, cuz my dad asked me and I
was like, he was like, did he smoke weed? And I was like, hell no. He would never
smoke weed yeah yeah and then you also lying well he my cousin like he was 15
and he like came home and his first time ever smoking weed and he was just like
way too way too high and just like 15 years old pretending to be high in like
a movie yeah you know like he was doing like cartwheels and like eating a
whole bag of chips yeah yeah and so like my aunt was like I think this kid's
fucking high yeah and like told all the adults and then they had they went to
every kid and they were like did he smoke weed and we were all like hell no dude
come on imagine like like a kid like smoking weed for the first time and it's
not it hasn't hit yet so he's like he's trying to act high and like within like
within like 10 seconds of smoking weed he just grabs a golf club and starts
just like hitting his dog video game dude oh my god bro hand me that I mean it I'm
gonna put it up my ass dude I'm so fucking high right dude cuz watch watch
this it just knocks over the refrigerator just dude cuz and we're so
high dude let's check let's peep our holes out let's see who's got the bigger
hole let's see yeah come on dude we're not gonna remember this no I haven't smoked
yet hasn't even X no I know you smoke even exhale the bong hit yet dude I'm so
horny right now just so high it got me so horny smoking the bong and then as you
exhale as you blow the smoke out. I'm gay. It turned me gay. I'm gay immediately. I'm a thousand years old also. I'm an old man. I am becoming an old man from smoking weed one time.
Santa I'm Santa and you know you'll be on the naughty list if Santa told you to
show you is the show in your thingy are you saying yes you say no I try to find
the present Santa's sack you are the same age as Santa I tell every good
relationship million years old same exact days down to the day you think Santa is
God's brother what presence was he given to people a million years ago tell me
plague the plague didn't happen a million years ago yes yeah it plague didn't
happen a million years ago you fucking idiot Santa is as old as the universe
you think Santa it was I was reading this this conspiracy theory thing about
how Santa is actually Nimrod from the Bible and the tree is like a heathen
idol or whatever it's like it's like a pagan thing that was Nimrod he's a
hunter from the Bible yeah he's apparently it's like Christmas is a
pagan ritual like yeah yeah pretty Santa's like Muhammad if you draw him
you go to hell it's true it's true it's true I got you
draw bad news for weird out a bunch of elves shooting up your office cuz you
drew an unflattering cartoon of Santa yeah we drew Santa sucking Uncle Sam's dick
and a bunch of elves ran up and fucking put a bullet in my head. Yeah, Will Ferrell came in.
Don't speak on Santa's name yeah yeah yeah jolliness be upon him mm-hmm
um it's can I pee real quick? Presence be upon him. I have to pee so bad I can't make it
to
for
of them bumper clots I heard about in them funny island songs.
Jamaican cowboy?
Hell, I heard tell of a botty boy about two towns over I'm riding down to collect a bounty.
Well, well seems like you're wanted dead or alive for being a blood clot.
well yeah I'm gonna have to take you in to jaw may jaw rest your soul yeah big
ups to the hangman gallows ting it's just a gallows ting I don't have anything for
this you just wouldn't know the six shooter and six... cool Pat just shut up oh my god Pat
Everyone's gonna be upset with me.
Why?
'Cause you're asleep?
Yeah.
I think we need to get you maybe a caffeine pill.
I don't know, something.
[laughter]
Please, anything.
Just fuckin' something.
I'm dead.
I'm dying.
I don't think you're dying.
I think I'm dying.
I thought I had COVID this morning.
'Cause I had diarrhea.
It's a pretty fast turnaround.
I know.
People, a lot of people say that COVID lasts one morning.
I wish.
That's, yeah.
I wouldn't care if I got it.
You wish that COVID lasted one morning?
Yeah, I wouldn't care if I got it.
You're brave, man.
You're really a brave soul and a good guy.
You need to do a detox, dude.
Dr. Dre style.
I think I do.
I think I gotta stop.
You need to detox your mind and your soul.
You start meditating, you know?
I think I'm gonna take a nap immediately after this.
Pat meditating and just, you,
just imagining a big cookie.
No, I can't meditate.
I'm smoking a can of beans, it comes from the earth.
That's right, come from the earth.
Comes from the earth.
It come from the earth.
Well, I keep the heater on me.
In case some botty boys want to no play nice.
It's pretty good.
Well, look, who are you?
Me? Well, I'm the original bad boy.
(laughing)
Bad boy Tings.
Yep, well, just kind of a Ting that happens around here.
Tings will be Tings.
Ain't that the damn truth.
I'm gonna bring you all, I mean, it is kind of the same,
like, they both say law man.
Yeah, no, they're exactly the same thing.
They're exactly the same thing.
Yeah. Yeah.
Cowboys and Jamaican guys are exactly the same.
Cowboys and Jamaican guys as like a shoots and ladders re-skill?
(laughter)
That's what kids played.
Oh no, I hit a Jamaican guy and I went back
to that first cowboy.
(laughter)
That's what kids played growing up.
Kids, once people thought cowboys and Indians
was offensive, they started playing cowboys
and Jamaican guys.
Yeah.
Or they just completely didn't realize,
they thought cowboys was the offensive part,
So it's Indians and Chibokites.
(laughing)
- I would know which part was the offensive part.
- No you wouldn't.
- I would know.
- No. - Which part is it then?
- I can't tell you guys.
- Why? - Exactly, you don't know?
- Nah, I just can't tell you guys.
I would tell you if I could.
- Nah, you guys wouldn't be able to handle it.
- No, you guys would get upset.
You guys would just get upset at the mere mention
of which one it was.
I'm gonna mention you, buddy.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
- Do it.
- Patrick eats poop for breakfast.
- Mention me to the devil who gets scared.
- Why do you eat, why do you run, he won't, he won't.
Why do you run, explain this to me.
Why do you run poop through a pasta maker
and then boil it and eat it with a crab sauce?
- You have to ask Cameron that.
- I'm gonna, no, I'm asking you that, Pat.
- Oh no, ask me, ask me, no, ask me that.
- Okay, Pat, or Cam.
- I don't know why Patrick does it, that's my answer.
Oh yeah, there we go.
That's the angle.
I don't get why you guys, I don't get why I'm always the punching bag.
We have to bully you so that you wake up.
More like the pooping bag.
Yeah.
I'm never gonna wake up then.
Okay, then I'm gonna kick you off the call and then me and Cam will have a podcast.
You guys don't have a podcast together.
Yeah, we do.
We have a new podcast, it's called Two Brothers.
I was thinking this morning, I forgot about it.
I was, I think...
Oh, that woke me up.
It'd be really funny if we just changed the name officially, permanently to Patrick's Podcast.
Yeah.
just so everyone could get mad at me when I underperform like this. No, just because it's a
funny name. Yeah, that's true. It's called Patrick's podcast. We're gonna get Pat going.
Just trying to, trying to, we may, we, we picked a name that is impossible to gain
any SEO on. We did it. It shows up in search engines now. We got to go to
the next level. We have to have something called the podcast. Yeah. We have to have something that's completely impossible to Google.
yeah we need the what if we call it cream of the cream of the crop no no what if
we call it no we need something that is like the number one search money
Suzuki Suzuki Ebony is perfect how about yeah new name of the podcast interracial
Google that might be okay that would be like we just need something that like
people will just find not even looking for a podcast.
How about YouTube?
YouTube is a great idea.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, that's a really good idea.
Yeah.
YouTube, the podcast.
What about, yeah, the official YouTube podcast?
Upskirt Stimulus Check.
I feel like that would boost our listeners so much.
It would be huge, dude.
We'd be 50K on Patreon.
Yeah. Step sister COVID.
yeah that would be really good step sister kovat is a great name that is a really good name yeah
that's really good janet jackson 2004 uncensored uncensored footage
mail zip code janet jackson boob steve irwin
that might be a good idea you guys remember i remember my dad catching me looking for the
the Steve Irwin death video that I don't think exists but my dad does not exist I
just like spent like a full day one time googling and my dad walked in like at
the beginning of days like what are you looking for is like Steve Irwin's death
video he's like oh why are you watching that son that's uh and it came in like
an hour later and I was still doing like god damn it you're still looking for
that video so yeah dude I'm sorry I'm crazy yeah I tell you guys speaking of
getting caught for stuff like that did I ever tell you guys the time I got caught
watching porno for the first time no somehow no so I I had found out how to
yeah I found out how to delete history so immediately I was like okay I should
spend the whole time until dad comes home watching porn and immediately before
it I was looking at I was 11 years old I was looking at Batman action figures on
eBay yeah like not like not like actually like Hasbro I was looking at like
figurines like I was looking at like the ones you get at the comic book shops I
was looking at the Mad Hatter one and then I switched from Mad Hatter figurine
into porno.com.
- Porno.com, one of the best ones.
- Of course, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah. - Naturally.
- I didn't realize,
like, my sister came home early from school or whatever
and then I was in the basement within the computer room
and then she opened the door
and I immediately closed the browser
and turned the monitor off.
And then she went, "Oh, I need to use the computer
"for a second."
I said, "Yeah, go ahead."
And then I went outside for an hour and I sat in the woods.
- 'Cause you just knew it was happening.
- Yeah, I sat in the woods.
- Did you consider running away in that moment?
- I did, I ran away to the woods.
Like I--
- You guys ever decide to run away as a kid?
- Yeah, a bunch of times.
Oh, I couldn't go trick or treating when I was five
'cause I ran away.
- Nice.
- I ran away and then I hid in like a bush behind,
like you saw my old, the fans,
I don't know if they know, 'cause it was a fucking shot of us,
but my old neighborhood in Londonderry,
there was like all those bushes in front of the houses.
I squatted in a bush for two hours.
(laughing)
It just sat there like squat position for an hour
until one of my uncles found me,
because like my mom was about to call the cops
'cause she thought like I ran away like down the street,
but no, I was like just--
- Right outside.
Squatting in a bush behind the house for two hours.
- I did, when I was like nine or so,
I did a hobo sack.
- Yeah.
- And yeah, I just put like my fucking Game Boy in it.
- Yeah, a candy and a shirt.
- And I couldn't figure out how to tie it,
so I actually had to get my mom to tie the,
my mom tied the bandana on the stick that I had,
and then I walked like two houses down the street,
and then I just started crying,
I was like I can't do this. I can't do it. I'm nine years old. I can't I can't do this to my family
Yeah, that is how I was like
They're gonna be so heartbroken when I leave and I become the president and they're gonna they're gonna wish
They're always gonna ask me for money and to be the president after me
How many days do you think you would have lasted as a kid if you had ran away me?
Yeah, there's two of I mean definitely zero either. I probably
first you know what sure Cameron you answer for but not very long yeah yeah I
mean I would have lasted very long so yeah you have body fat to burn I wasn't
a fat kid sure if you just had like if I ran away from home now fine I wouldn't it
wouldn't let it take me long to get killed Patrick could survive in the
desert for seven years like a can no I couldn't no I could yeah that's true
there's no water in any of your and your body anywhere no no it's all salt yeah
yeah I would know I think like you know I think you won't do it's all memory foam
that's all that's in you you're a living so much memory foam yeah you do I don't
eat memory for my fist then then you have the memory foam no yeah isn't the
imprints in you is an imprint of my fist in your style you can see all my knuckles
you can see my cool ring yeah from when I won an NBA championship you can see
school graduation ring that you have no I don't have one of those that you
ordered you can see the knuckles at the Caleb gave himself that says clab
because he couldn't spell his name when he was looking at it backwards yeah I
I can spell my name.
Not backwards.
B-L-E-C-K.
Blek.
Hey, it's me, Blek.
It just sounds like an Australian guy saying black.
Yeah.
Blek.
Hi, I'm TychoATT.
Oh, you.
Oh, we've got a funny movie coming out.
I'moid Hitler, a bleak fella.
already done this Tiger with TT deserves as many jokes about what about Tiger
Woods Tiger Woods Tiger but he's actually in the woods and he's a tiger here's Wow
hi SNL thanks for selecting me for an audition here's my sketch called Tiger
woods Hillary Clinton's a mailman yeah how about that here's my idea the crying
clown he's a clown but whenever he ties the balloon he cries and I'm thinking
we'll Ferrell to be in it what about a skinny sumo wrestler what do you think
Yeah, what about a dog mailman who chases dogs?
Wow, what if damn Daniel's or one day wore black vans?
Wow, that's you doing that like in September 2020. Yeah, Donald Trump had a tick-tock account
And he was talking all day long instead of signing
life-saving bills
What if Barack Obama had a giant machine gun and he tore Donald Trump to pieces with it?
what if Obama was a dictator and we got to we got to have in a permanent Obama
administration what if all those kids in cages grew up to be the square shape of
the cages like one of those Japanese watermelons what if
individual cage just a guy that did miss under misunderstands that there are kids
in cages things oh my god yeah they put all of them in their own crates they're
We're trying to make them look like Minecraft Steve.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's what I'm doing.
Oh my god.
I have a kid, I'm gonna put a box on his head so he's a perfectly square head.
Yeah.
This is just an iron box.
You can do that.
Mm-hmm.
I am doing it.
I just said that I'm doing it.
You can do it.
Hi, SNL.
Thanks for hearing my pitch.
My idea is what if an invisible kid was playing on top of a shed at his family's cookout?
Wow.
And then Mr. Wonderful is like, "Yeah, that idea sucks.
still never make it.
- Mr. Wonderful is who you pitched.
- To his surprise.
- You pitched to Shark Tank at SNL.
- Yeah.
- All of the, everything gets pitched to them.
Every TV show.
- Every pitch, just.
- Every pitch.
- Yeah.
- Just goes straight to the Shark Tank.
- 'Cause they're the masters.
They know exactly what they're doing.
- Aren't they instructed not to laugh?
- Aren't you?
- Shark Tank people?
- No, SNL.
Isn't it like a whole thing like,
oh, well you know, Lorne doesn't laugh in the auditions.
It's like, yeah, 'cause he hasn't
fucking picked anyone funny in years.
- Yeah, I don't know that they're instructed not to laugh,
but I do think there's a thing where like,
when people don't get SNL and they've auditioned,
they did laugh, and then when they didn't laugh at all,
a lot of people get SNL.
- Right.
- It's all like these weird mind games.
It's really funny.
It's funny to jump through all those hoops.
- It's the stupidest gatekeeping shit, yeah.
- Lorne Michaels makes you sit for like four hours
outside his office just to see if you do it.
- It's like, yeah dude, it's a guy from fucking
Improv Olympics making $22,000 a year
on the fucking main stage company.
He'll sit outside your office for three hours.
- Obviously.
- And it's like, isn't it like if you,
all the sketches in your packet,
if you audition, like they can just use them?
- Yeah.
- And jokes from your Twitter account now.
- Yeah, but I mean like even if you don't get it,
they can use your packet?
- Yep, yeah.
- Yeah, it's pretty funny.
- It's pretty awesome, dude.
- Yeah.
stupid. They started using Zane Gillis' material. SNL under fire for neuter sketch. SNL controversial but
powerful Chinatown sketch. You guys were so brave. Did you see yeah they just
announced three new cast members and it's us three yeah one of them is named
punky what's punky Brewster yep they got punky
brewed are they I didn't see this oh I do cares
never okay oh let me look at the list they got Barney and Rick and Morty yeah
really round I think they could play off each other really well yeah
looking at the cast photo and he's like, God, I we need a kid.
We need Barney. We need a kid.
10 year old kid.
SNL kid cast member. Wow.
They had a Michael Hall. He was 17.
No, they need a 10 year old kid. That'd be so
funny.
10 year old kid. 10 year old kid sensibility on SNL would, it
would be funny.
It would be better. No, but the type of kid they would get would
be a child actor.
It would be they would get one of the TikTok kids who goes,
Actually, it's proven that Biden has never touched a woman in his life.
One of the things I like and they're like 14 years old.
Yeah.
Actually, if you think about it, Biden has never actually touched anything.
Where did that come from?
What?
Like a cartoon?
Why do TikTok kids move like they're cartoon characters?
Yeah, they watch Ted Talks all day and then they do that.
It's Ted Talks or like cartoons.
It's not that they watch Ted Talks.
It's like their parents are really rich and they say that they got rich by
watching TED talks and so then the kids. Right, so the kid has to become rich.
Yeah, secret to business. Yeah, the only way that I was able to access my
late father's gigantic inheritance was actually by watching a TED talk called
How to Access Your Late Father's Gigantic Inheritance. If I was, if I was, I've been
I've been thinking about just like if I had been born crazy rich because I'm
watching Succession and yeah I think I would just like like if I had like a
billionaire dad I think I just sell his phone and then just like never talk to
him again yeah yeah you know much shit is on a
yeah it's like iPhone yeah just like to like it just open his bed just a little
post just take it his diary yeah I was like this like your diary today I raped
1 million children love Jeff Bezos thing is those people are definitely stupid
enough to write to have a diary yeah that in there they have one of those like
teenage girl diaries yeah lock on it and I just sneak in like a younger brother
The lock the lock the only key that fits in the lock is is a seven-year-old child's pinky finger bone
I've missed those those commercials for those diaries
I feel like maybe we've talked about this before but it's always so funny cuz like the little brother just
The opening scene in fucking the
2004 Freaky Friday remake is the younger brother and his friends going into Lindsay Lohan's room to try on her bras
Yeah, yeah get these awesome x-ray goggles where you can see your sister's snatch
It's so weird order. Yeah order from the magazine. Hey mom. I need these x-ray goggles so I can
Do homework yeah?
Yeah, so I can
Tell if the dog is hungry. Yeah, just looking at your son. So son, how are those x-ray goggles?
They're really great. Hey, I think I dropped a piece of lint on the ground
Can you pick that up I need that for later
Yeah, sure
Hey
Yeah
Yeah, I'd like to see my dad's dick and balls
Yeah, I think I did one time and I thought I thought it looked like a skull you've seen a little dad's dick and balls
Yeah, what they look like they look exactly like yours
They're very small my dad is like really my dad is like he's the color of brick
But then if he takes off his like his shirt and his shorts, he's like invisibly white
Yes, my dad is like a like the whitest dick in the world. Yeah, no and probably some really hot red balls
He's got to see mine. I
Don't see I just but he's got a smoldering coals. Yeah, just like I mean, I like that definitely some steamy balls
Yeah, you know your dad has like a sauna stone. I think it cooked his arms in his face
Yeah, so he's so dark. Yeah, they beat like hearts
- miniature hearts
Absolutely my dad has I think my dad's thoughts are stored in his balls. Yeah. Oh for sure, you know
That's why it's just smart. Yeah, you can has two brains and plastic surgery. So your balls heck looks exactly like a brain
Mine kind of does if I'm like no, that's why your Twitter handle is brain getter
Cuz you're like a brain not kind of like a brain exactly like a brain just pink and like just weird
Well, think of a brain.
I can't think of one.
It's impossible to think of a brain with a brain.
Because you don't have one.
It's a hat on a hat.
You can put a hat on a hat.
Try.
Don't do it, seriously. Don't do it.
You'll tear a rift in the universe.
Pat, I've never seen you look more mentally disabled.
Yeah.
Yeah, you just look, mouth agape, drooling,
ruling
This is an imposter.
Is they're both hats?
This is impossible.
No.
They're both hats.
And I'm wearing my headphones under the hat.
So this is technically three hats.
No.
A headphone is not a hat.
A headphones is a hat.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Is hair a hat?
Yes.
No.
Sometimes.
Yes.
No.
It can be.
I mean, not that you would know, but yes.
I do have hair.
Where?
My head.
Down there.
You don't have hair down there or on your head.
I'm going to shave my thing so the carpet matches the crepes.
looking like the Sahara Desert down there you got one you got one little I wish
you got one you got one little cactus and two little scorpion claws down there
you're gonna tell you something you pick the sad hatter yeah you look like the
bad hatter you look like the fat hatter you look like the ugly bitch no come on
did you look like a child fucker so you look like if I had been in Cameron logs
on to Twitter and says the child fucker has logged on. Yeah he does like to make
posts like that. I don't like that. Yeah you do. Fucking speaking of I hate my fucking
username. Lunch Enjoyer? Yeah you guys both have have usernames that end in an ER.
It's bad. Yeah. It's lame. Yep. I got out of that racket a while ago man. Yeah no I did it and
then like I don't know too many things are associated with it now. Yeah I think
I think I just I think you just go real name at some point. Yeah, you know, you got to make that choice
You gotta make that leap. Yeah. Yeah, I guess
Actually, I'm like, oh, mr. Munchkin
Yeah, now I think about it. Whoever whoever can find me the coolest name to change it to yeah, and I
Will you will pay me you want you should take Dracula today?
Yeah, Dracula today
That's not a bad idea.
Oldest living man.
Yeah.
Wow, you just blew our cover, dude.
I know.
Whose cover?
Cameron's a vampire.
When I said that account, I was talking about Patrick's account.
No.
He does tweet on your account a lot, Pat.
Yeah.
Cameron, any time that there's like a remake thing, any time that there's like, "Ah, these
remakes!
I hate them!
I hate it!"
Yeah.
Patrick quote tweet something and says the Democrats yikes I don't do that's me
yeah you do no I don't you did you love doing that I don't love doing that the
Democrats are crud yeah you say low-key the Democrats do not have our best
interests at heart y'all so yeah you do say that oh they don't okay cool man I'm
allowed to get mad at the hell world it is such a hell the new word the new word
that's annoying me a lot like for a while like like slothslovenly was a
bad one and then spineless and ghouls are really annoying but then the one that's
really annoying me now is bleak that's bleak is so annoying like any like seeing
just like a tick-tock and just being like oh this is so bleak it's like you're
fucking 30 shut up yeah I'm more of a I guess the words that I don't like or the
The N word, the F word, the word hate, you know, discrimination.
The C word, the V word, the L word, lesbian.
- Yeah, I hate that word.
- No thanks.
And you know, I guess we're just built differently.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I understand somebody my age
complaining about TikTok stuff.
That's fine.
- How old are you again?
- I'm 23.
- That's why it's funny to have you make posts
you're like all these goddamn remakes cuz you're like the target audience for all
yeah you're somebody somebody on stream year old man somebody on stream last
night called us middle-aged yeah yeah you you Pat does see middle-aged and I I see
middle a I have an old soul I don't think you have an old you do not have an
old soul would have a job yeah you just like old things yeah I think that yeah
you just like you you drink bad drink monster energy every day I don't have a
a bad I don't have bad taste. You don't have bad taste, you have old taste. I do.
I do have old taste. Things only get better. Anyway, if you're older than me and you're
complaining about what some kid did on tik-tok, you got a problem man.
Go get off the computer. What problem is that? That problem is called Russo's Folly. Yeah, it's Russo.
uh-huh he's a it's he was a Canadian shit poster Canadian shit poster and he's
Chad and he's stoned Wow dude that's awesome yeah he's yeah he smokes the
biggest blunts really mm-hmm I thought that was you no no remember when you
smoked weed for two months maybe that's why you're like this today maybe it
caught up with you right yeah I really I really sucked today I watched I just
watch who framed Roger Rabbit. I watched Hyper Normalization. I watched the good the
bad and the ugly. Tell me Pat when you were watching Hyper Normalization how was
your phone? I turned it off 5 seconds in. Oh yeah I would have figured you would like have
that on while you like fucking get mad about a remake online on your phone and
then later you're like yeah I watch Hyper Normalization no idea what it was
about. I think it had something to do with billboards. How long is it? It's like four hours? No it's like an hour and a half.
two hours maybe Nick Nick Disney said that it was I'm pretty sure it's pretty
long I haven't seen it I remember looking at it and seeing it as right it
might be two and a half hours it's been it's been maybe let me I'm gonna look up
the last so I've never watched it cuz I prefer no I'm sorry but good news it's
in two parts and both of them are like an hour and a half so it's like three
hours long it's old first you said it's an hour and a half then you said it's
two hours he said to it's a had two and a half hours I was thinking of this I was
thinking of the the run times and you're just very no you're just very stupid no
wrong completely correct no not not correct at all
I'm looking at hyper normalization on letterbox this thing's got a
stacked cast dude Adam Curtis Donald Trump Vladimir Putin Ronald Reagan Henry
Kissinger yeah when they get Henry Cavill how did they get these people in here
it's like Ocean's Eleven can you guys hear me at all
yeah buddy no I've been this entire episode we just couldn't hear Pat we're
just I don't know my whole my whole what he was saying in a fit perfectly yeah
wouldn't be bad now hyper normalization is yeah so like an Ocean's Eleven style
like jam-packed cast and you just can't believe that you are seeing these stars
yeah oh my god that's good Duffy Henry Kissinger yeah they hated each other
yeah how did they wonder what that set was like yeah I bet it was toxic I'll
tell you that much yeah yeah yeah I think I need to watch some more
documentaries pretty soon yeah like you know what documentary should watch what
Giro dreams of Caleb's mom. Giro dreams of Pussy. Oh my god.
Woooo. No. You've seen the act of killing right? Yeah I think well I think I turned it off
halfway through actually. Oh you watched the whole thing. I learned too much.
No I think it honestly I think it upset me. No it's so upsetting it's so
fucked up dude it's crazy. What is that movie? It's basically like the guys who did the
like. From the twisted mind. It's like paramilitary like. It's like the punk rock
Holocaust happened where like nobody really knows about it that much and then
they made a documentary directed by the guys who did it. What do you mean the punk rock holocaust?
There was a there's um... Wait like they killed a bunch of punks or something?
Yeah paramilitary groups what country was that in? I think it was
Malaysia. Yeah I think it's Malaysia like Malaysian paramilitary groups like killed
a shit ton of people like did it basically they basically did a genocide
they did a heck in genocide they did but like and then the
Documentary people go over there and like talk to the people who did the genocide and are like here
We want you to reenact scenes of you killing these people and direct them like they're a movie and like it's like it's insane
It's pretty sick. It's really I would I would get upset watching that I watch yeah, I watch fun
Don't worry ruins my week. Oh, you know it's a great. You know it's a great documentary
Have you seen I forget what it's called, but it's a this movie
dreams of poopy that is a good one hold on let me look up well okay I looked up
trying to look it up it's this documentary about a guy who wants his
penis preserved at the penis Museum I've heard of that have you seen this scale
have you actually see Oh unhung hero is what it's called nice is no no it's not
you want one hero no that's like you hold on who's the director of this
unhung hero movie Patrick moot Patrick Patrick fuck you you piece of shit
director I I'm sure he's probably a fan of the show penis documentary I can't
find it dude what the fuck dreamed it no this is a this is a fucking this is a
real museum this is a real thing hold on okay museum of penis the final member
the final member you're gay now the final member is what final member that is the
penis documentary thank you're the final member there's a guy there's a guy in
the movie who is obsessed with getting his penis into the penis documentary and
there's a scene it's like a talking headshot and he looks at them and goes I
don't want my penis to go to waste when I die that's very kind actually yeah yeah
I want mine turned into like a like Tom's shoe yeah give to a poor kid they
should every every they should they should attach whenever a guy dies they
should attach his penis to his gravestone uh-huh yeah I want them to
use my penis as a parachute because it's so large. Wait. And thin? Yeah it's so large
thin and flat. It's like a giant cloth. It's honestly, it should be like when you die your
penis gets repurposed for whatever the correct size and shape. You want them to use your penis like a
parachute in like a gym class so a bunch of children are gonna sit inside of it and you
want them to do that while you're alive. That's not a parachute that's a tarp. You are again the
stupidest guy I know. No but you think it's called a parachute and that's why you said
that. I don't think that. No you clearly think it's called a parachute. It's called the circus tent.
No they called it the parachute. They'll probably use your penis as a molecule when you die.
That's very possible. You're gonna turn your penis into dust. Yeah when I die I want my penis to be used as a molecule.
Yeah the biggest molecule ever. Yeah. I want them to split my penis like an atom when I die. Yeah.
yeah I want my penis to be used for fission it's a really good idea yeah
donating your penis to science and they just blow it up what are you guys
accomplished by blowing my penis up I just be funny yeah it is it is the
funny they like the funniest thing we can explode yeah people people like
donate their bodies to science and are like oh I want to donate my body to
science to like help the further the cause of knowledge it's like noble and
And then it'll be like, "Oh yeah, we're using this old lady's dead body in a study called
'How Long Can a Sheep Fuck a Dead Body?'"
Yeah, we put this old lady's body in the medical student dorms and people, they just fuck it
so they don't get distracted.
Yeah, it's just like, "How much poop can we fit in a lady's mouth?"
They're like, "Oh, I'm gonna go visit the lab where apparently they're using my great-grandmother's
dead body for science and you walk in it's just like a puppet show yeah they're
doing they're doing spongebob the musical with your grandma
Jeff Dunham doing scrimmages with all your family members. I wonder how many
other dead guys human balls we could put in this man's mouth yeah it's a
medical school if they have a sports team and all the sports equipment is
made out of dead bodies that they get donations to use. How long does it take for a body to
dissolve in coca-cola? Yeah, yeah. What's the ugliest dead body we can find?
Yeah, can we make fun of this dead body until it comes back to life? Yeah, how
long can we make fun of this dead person till they come back to defend
themselves how much fuck shit can we do to this dead body until we go to jail
yeah what what happens if a Jewish person eats non-kosher food how cool would it be
if we shot it out of a cannon yeah I thought this is very cool how creepy is
this body right? I like to donate my living body to science yeah yeah that's
just called being a scientist Wow that's true I actually I'd like to donate my
body to movies when I die yeah you guys could just use it for whatever yeah I
would prefer a lead role but I understand that's a lot to ask yeah yeah
I'm donating I'm donating my dead body to the McDonald's across the street just
in case they run low on meat. Hypothesis. How long can we get away with doing real-life
Weekend at Bernie's with this guy's dead body? Weekend at Bernie's but we pretend he's just
a normal pedophile. Yeah. Not a bad idea. Pretty good idea. Alright. Yeah. I think we're
done. Yeah. I gotta go to bed. Yeah, Patrick needs his beauty rest and Cameron needs to
go to work. He needs to fuck a poop. Cameron needs to go to work at the Sibian factory.
That's not true. That would be a cool place to work but I don't work there. Yeah you work
as the taste tester. Yeah I'm the taste tester. The Sibian factory. I'm a Sibian tester. A
kid going to school and being like yeah dude my cousin's a Sibian tester. He gets to test
out all the Sibians before they put them on the market. That's right. That's fucking right.
Alright, bye. Bye.