You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
[explosion]
Wow, dude.
Dude, I just synced up the record countdown to the "Dropping Better Off Alone" by Alice DJ.
How'd you do that?
'Cause I was the one who did the countdown.
How'd you sync it up?
I synced it up.
Since you've got vaccinated, you have been different.
This is not... I don't like this Patrick.
Yeah, he's changed.
Like house music Patrick, he's fucking...
He's weird.
What are you doing? Stop dancing dude.
You're doing karate right now.
Stop!
I need you to... you're supposed to talk.
No, no.
That's the song?
That's the one you listen to? What the fuck?
You're listening to like the music that you can add royalty free on YouTube?
you do dude you were no if you if you let me hear one of those those baby
keyboards that plays animal sounds to the tune of like twinkle twinkle little star
he'll go fucking nuts I've been listening to this and I've been listening to
gypsy woman she's homeless by crystal waters a lot that's the name you just
like the name of the song right no I mean that's why you don't like the name
of every time that's why do you smile whenever you say it no that sounds like
- I like that, like a track on like a
Norm Macdonald stand up album.
- Yeah, it's a gypsy woman.
- Yeah, it's a gypsy woman, she's fucking homeless.
Isn't that what being a gypsy's all about?
- I mean, get this, she's homeless.
Yeah, fucking la-da-dee, la-da-da.
- Yeah, that's his catchphrase.
He's a catchphrase comic, and his catchphrase is
la-da-dee, la-da-da.
- He loves music and skipping around.
- Yep, that's just one of his main things.
He's a sarcastic, skipping comedian.
I got stuck with the fungus today, dude.
Yeah.
They gave me my first dose of the fungus today.
The fungus amogus.
I had to go all the way to the Bronx and I got there, I checked in and the nurse who
administered my shit, she was like, "What's your name?"
And I was like, "Caleb."
She was like, "Oh, Caleb.
I have a son named Caleb.
That's a very nice name."
You saw your mom?
No, it was not my mom.
Her son spells it with a K, I learned from her.
Your mom's son spells it with a K?
can I finish my story? It's good, you're gonna like it." And then she
said, "Last name?" and I said, "Pitts." And she just started laughing. And she started
laughing like so hard and like bent over laughing and I was like, "What?" She's
like, "You have made my day." I was like, "That's my name. That's just my name. Why is it so funny?"
funny and she started laughing, she laughed the entire time, she stuck a needle in me
and then she made me leave and I had to go to the waiting room where there was a-
I'm telling you dude, the nurses at the vaccination places are on some other shit.
Oh for sure.
I had to wait 10 minutes and-
I had to wait 30.
Well they have to make sure that you don't have anything going on.
That's true.
Make sure you don't develop autism in the time.
They made me wait 30 minutes because I told them I'm allergic to amoxicillin.
Yeah, they made me wait 30 minutes too because I had anaphylaxis as a kid.
Yeah, I was showing the lady, like there was just a lady in a hallway like pointing people
to the room and I showed her like the 30 minutes thing.
I was like, "Oh, where do I wait?"
She was like, "Damn, you got 30 minutes?"
And I was like, "Is that bad?"
She's like, "Most people got 15."
Dude, I'm a pro.
They made me wait 10, dude.
They knew I was healthy as a horse.
They hid the camera that you died.
There was a guy there, like a Russian dude, who was like, "Oh, I have headache."
And the lady was like, "Are you allergic to something?"
And he's like, "I have many allergies in Russia."
And she was like, "Okay," and gave him a water bottle.
But yeah, it did not develop a cold or autism or anything like that.
I mean, the amount of time they make you wait is just how much they care about if you die.
Like if it's 10 minutes, it's not that it's going to take 10 minutes for you to go into
anaphylactic shock.
just that yeah they don't really care if you do. They love me down there. Once they let you free
there's no correlation. Once they let you free they press the button under
the desk that activates the chip in your brain that drains your energy and sends it straight to Exxon.
I started, ten minutes was too long for me you know I got shit to do I had to go to
Peruzzo's get a chopped cheese so I started burrowing through the wall with a
spoon and I successfully escaped. They can't hold me back they can't put me
They're trying to institutionalize me. No. You climbed out through the sewage system
and they were just like, "Yeah, I don't know. We're just going to let them do it."
Yeah, I killed two security guards and they're just like, "You don't have to stay for the 10
minutes." I saw the most evil nurse when I was getting vaccinated. I just forgot about this
until just now. You know how some people bleed when they get shots? There was one, a nurse gave
a shot to one like like older lady and she like on her arm like rolled up her long
sleeve gave the shot the lady started bleeding like the lady who was getting
the shot didn't notice the nurse definitely did because she was giving
the shot yeah and then the nurse just rolled her sleeve oh my god she ruined
her damn shirt what the hell it wasn't like a light-colored shirt I don't
remember what color it was cuz I'm not a freak think of this shirt man maybe
Maybe she was a blind nurse.
It's just so funny to just be like, "Yeah, I'm not going to wipe that up.
Fuck you, dude."
It's not my blood.
Yeah.
Not my blood, not my job.
If I get my blood on you, I might think about cleaning it up.
But no.
I wouldn't sleep down on that, too.
I'm not going to sleep down on that for somebody else.
That's marking my territory.
That's true, yeah.
Yeah.
Piss and blood.
Vampire style.
If I was a nurse, dude, I'd be fucking, I'd be throwing all sorts of shit on people.
I'd say, "Don't you ever forget who gave you this shot.
you'll always remember you'll have some little piece of me and you. I gave the shot and then
like I pull out a tattoo gun. I draw a circle around the shot. Yeah you have to be like
like if you want to be known as like the best nurse in the world you have to have a signature
move. Oh that'd be a great liberal tattoo. Just like a circle around where you got your
shot and then like vaccinated on it. I put an air bubble in every single vaccine. Make
sure you know that I gave it to you. My signature nurse move is that is that if the patient is
rude to me before they get the vaccine I just squirt it all in their eyes. I think
it gets I think it can get through that. Yeah it'll probably better hope it works
ten times better because it goes to your brain mm-hmm yeah it goes through your
through your eyes to your brain. Take the Moderna to the dome. Moderna straight to the face.
Did you get Moderna or Pfizer? I did Moderna. Oh me too. Dude I got Pfizer.
really you know we're gonna see what happens see who the last man standing
yeah let's check it out first gonna have to give Patrick the AstraZeneca no I
already got it I don't know you need another you got to be different okay I
can go get you're like Johnson right now I know some people got Johnson & Johnson
and now they're now they're locked it up is your face are you like getting like
Am I doing this?
Yeah, I've had like-
You're getting Bell's Palsy?
What?
I've had pains in my lip, like my face, it'll kind of get like stuck like this.
No, I'm fucking fine dude.
But I don't know if it's because my wisdom tooth hurts or like I've been freaking out.
Dude, Patrick being the one non-hoax person to get Bell's Palsy from the vaccine.
Right.
Yeah, no, you're not a, you should never be stuck with anything.
You have Munchausen's.
I know.
It's a bad idea.
Dude, I fucking, I don't have Munchausen's.
do no it's the I will say the 30-minute wait time for also someone who's like
gets freaked out about medicine and shit cuz I'm allergic to a bunch of
medicines like that shit is scary cuz you just sit there and it's like okay
you need to sit here for 30 minutes and do nothing but think about how you might
not be able to breathe yeah also the whole time you're sitting there like I
can't give me like a Domino's pizza tracker to look at well I just know I
I just, even if you don't give me a pizza, I just want to look forward to something, you
know?
Give me a timeline.
Yeah.
Otherwise I'm just...
They don't give you a fucking cookie or anything, like when they take blood.
Nah, dude, I'm just sitting there, just like every fucking weird tingle I have, which I
have all the time, I'm just sitting there like, maybe that's the tingle that kills me.
I don't care about being immune, I just want a treat, right?
Yeah, and also, give me a, can I get a cherry or something?
Give me a burrito taco.
Can I get a, yeah.
Let me sit in there with the burrito taco and the consomme.
Can I get some chorizo over here?
Come on.
We have to have like a lady frying empanadas in this waiting room.
That would be sick, dude.
Oh my god.
That's what I'm saying.
I had to go, I had to manually leave the place and go get myself a Whopper.
I'm on a Whopper a day diet the past four days.
It's been treating me really, really bad.
I had burrito tacos for the first time last night.
Nice, is that what you're talking about them right now?
Yeah, yeah, because I wanted to bring them up.
I had an allergy scare like a couple months ago.
About burrito tacos?
I got a I went to the same place got a brie a quesadilla.
You called the doctor and said I think I'm allergic to tacos.
No I I ate a quesadilla.
That's very sad.
I ate half a quesadilla and then I realized the whole thing was full of avocado and I
had to run to the corner store and get Claritin.
I feel like you're not allergic to avocado you're allergic to things that are green or
something.
No because avocados are.
That sounds like.
Would Claritin even help if you like.
Yeah it's an antihistamine.
Is that, I don't know how that stuff works.
Is that, is that?
- Yeah, I have like a-- - It probably wouldn't work
if you were like--
- I have like a pollen allergy that's really bad.
- Hey, me too, brother.
- You got a pollen allergy?
- It's been fucking me over.
It gave me a sinus infection
'cause it's super pollen-y here, yeah.
- Yeah, it sucks, oh man, I'm not--
- Dude, it fucking snowed today, too.
- What?
- Yeah, there's snow on the ground right now.
- Damn, you should have told us that first.
- We would have come up, we would have made the trip.
- Yeah, but dude, I have a sledding gear.
I'm not gonna let you guys talk about your stuff.
No, fuck that.
No, no, what are you talking-
Snow?
You seriously didn't clue us in on the snow?
We could have come and made snow angels with you, you fucking idiot.
Yeah, no, Caleb probably doesn't want to make a snowman.
Yeah, no, he only hasn't made one since November.
Yeah, oh, oh, Patrick and Caleb don't want to have a snowball fight with me.
They want to talk about their stupid vaccine shit.
Come on, get your head right.
Get your brain right.
You fucking bitch.
Do you even know us?
We're like the snow twins.
Yeah, we're like two snow-mizers.
We're like the snow-mizer and snow-mizer.
We're basically the ice brothers.
And you're just fucking not letting us know about the...
We're the snow climbers.
If you knew a fish...
You guys are right, you don't just talk about stuff in a row for five minutes
with me being silent.
That totally doesn't happen.
If you knew a fish and you saw the ocean, would you not tell him about it?
I mean, come on, dude.
Joking fish didn't know where the ocean was it probably Cameron get it a glass of water
It wouldn't even tell him about the I'm better. I would not even do look at the fish
Thank you. My dookie. It's gonna get dookie
Hey, you're gonna slip on the snow you've never
Randomly I have this dookie sandwich. Do you are normal sandwich? Do you want a bite of this?
ice cream sandwich don't pay attention to what the two pieces of bread are made
out of yeah it's chocolate bread bread chocolate bread yeah I think it's a
good else would you call that that's a biscuit it's a biscuit if you're if
you're fancy well what the fuck is what what is it's chocolate bread my bad
yeah sorry what what what is a cookie other than fucking chocolate bread it's
- It's got, what do you mean, a cookie doesn't have yeast in it.
It's got shortening in it, it's not bread at all.
- You're making them different than I make them.
- You put yeast in your cookies?
- I make a whole cookie loaf.
- Make a sourdough cookie, what the fuck?
- Sourdough cookie loaf.
- That actually sounds so good.
Oh my God, that sounds incredible.
- If you're a fan of the show, you listen to this,
and you're a baker, make that shit right now.
- Yeah.
- And mail it to us.
Mail it to me and Caleb, not Cameron,
And mail it ice cold, because that's our thing, we're the ice twins.
Yeah, now we have to stick by it because Cameron Trey is.
It's interesting that you guys call yourselves the ice twins, you didn't even know it was snowing.
I mean, I feel like if you're that into snow, you maybe would like check the weather, or like know where the snow is.
Yeah, maybe we're the ice mom and dad, but we're just the little ice kids, and we just fuckin', you know, we go where the ice, where people tell us.
I'm gonna put you in the closet.
You stand in there, I'm gonna fill it with black smoke.
That's like the opposite of snow.
All right, so basically I'm gonna kill you. I'm gonna kill you so you can't.
Here's how it's gonna go down. I'm gonna slash you.
You would want. I'm gonna say one two slash and I'm gonna
slash you in the face. Where are you gonna get all that black smoke
from, huh? I'm gonna play fruit ninja with you.
I'm gonna burn your toys. I'm slashing a fruit right now.
What? I'm slashing Cameron.
Shit. I'm going fruit ninja.
No. Oh my god, dude.
That's right. Come on.
That's such a fun like. That's such a fun app.
(laughing)
- Yeah, such a fun app.
You know, like when your dad calling someone gay
and he says, "Oh yeah, that guy's a fruit."
- Yeah.
- It's fun.
- Yeah, that is fun.
- 'Cause like, you think about it,
you think about like the Fruit of the Loom commercials.
- Yeah, "Hey Patrick, I might be a fruit,
"but I'm gonna turn you into a vegetable, pal."
You go, "Here, I'm gonna fill your lungs with sweet ham."
- That's pretty cool, that's like some alchemy shit.
Turning a fruit into a vegetable.
- Cameron's the alchemist.
- Wow, that's incredible.
- Full metal.
I love you, you're the full mental alchemist.
- I'm gonna give you my meat and turn you into a vegetable.
- Wow.
- I mean, that's a masterclass.
- You're not gonna be able to use your legs.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Pretty good.
- That's pretty good.
- Yeah, and basically I'm gonna slash you.
- Okay, all right.
Do you guys even care that the day this comes out
is my birthday?
- Oh shit.
- Oh no!
- And guess who's sitting there, no present.
I didn't see a single present when I logged onto the call.
- I have a present right here.
- Really, what is it?
You're just gonna grab something from your room.
- No, I have a present for you.
- You're both just grabbing things.
- No, no, this is literally right next to my computer.
Would I have it here if it wasn't a present for you?
- It's gonna be a mouse.
It's gonna be your computer mouse.
- Can I show it to you or are you gonna, do you want it?
- Yes, yes, yes, of course I want it.
Are you kidding?
I love presents.
- This is a lenticular bookmark of
Journey to the Center of the Earth in 3D
starring Brendan Fraser on DVD and Blu-ray October 28th 2007. We got this so
you could use it with this new book I got you. The Londonderry 2015 high school
yearbook. Wow. So these are kind of... You guys collapsed on each other. Yeah yeah. Check this out. Don't tell me there's a
picture of somebody famous in that. Oh no it's just you. Oh yeah. Are you gonna like
are you gonna sign it or something? I did. Hey does it have any like hot hot things
that girls wrote in it? You read, can you read this Caleb? Oh that does say gift on
it. I did just find something on my desk that says gift. It's a USB to mini USB
converter if you want this. Is that you playing football? That's Tom Brady. Oh, well you're
welcome for that compliment. He's just standing there I knew that it was it was one of the
best of all time I thought it was you. You could have been a football player. Yeah I'm
built I'm built for it. You're built like a football player. Yeah you got the skull for
it. Minus the player I mean come on folks it's so easy with this guy. You wouldn't even
need a helmet dude they just they just put the the fucking uh uh metal grid thing they
to
tell you you did there's something behind you that you are allergic to and you
have to run from it and you just fucking just 80 miles an hour run down that field
full force gum yeah hey Patrick that guy over there with the football yeah he's
remaking gremlins yeah that guy that guy's actually the the Democratic Senate
majority leader I'm gonna go tackle him show him show him what's what you know
show him what a ghoul he is and you go seriously and then you tackle him okay
look back to Caleb's birthday I just we definitely have to read this I'm not
getting Caleb anything now I just wanted this is a really exciting fun of Caleb
has been officially featured yep and a Best Buy advertisement best birthday
present ever probably this was my biggest by by far by a good friend at
at Dio Era Sabbath.
This is a screenshot here.
Customers are saying, this is a quote from Caleb.
I rest easier knowing Geek Squad has my back.
And this is Caleb PNY.
- I mean, Geek Squad does have my back, dude.
That's just what it is.
Any time I need, you know, three or four guys in the house,
call 'em over. - It's true.
- What's that, it's a Super Bowl?
Geek Squad, on the way.
- I rest easier.
Do you really rest easier?
Yeah, dude.
I rest on the couch and they sit in my bedroom and fuck my wife.
Whole Geek Squad.
They run a Geek Train on her.
It's very sweet.
And you've never used Geek Squad, right?
Yeah, they run a steam-powered train on my wife.
Dude, I have never used Geek Squad.
I think that I left that review on the Best Buy app once because I made a purchase and
they wanted to, they just like asked for a review.
and I was like yeah sure dude Geek Squad, the rest easier with Geek Squad.
Where is that review featured? I'm guessing it's a Best Buy newsletter or
something that they send out maybe a coupon code but basically from now I'm
gonna you know hopefully be able to do some stand-up touring later this year and
that will be I will put that on the on the the marquee it'll say you know him
the best from the best buy newsletter where he said Geek Squad has his back. I
just googled in quotes I rest easier knowing Geek Squad has my back and it's
that that quote is in the signature of a member of the of the Geek Squad no what
is this it's it's a link to the Geek Squad forums and that and this quote is
in there oh my god maybe it wasn't me then maybe no no no they copied and
pasted it was a Geek Squad scam email that got sent out that was that was a
fake like call us to can to cancel or you'll owe $600 and at the end of that
email it has the quote I rest easy where the hell do I send my damn review what
is going on have I have I been have I contributed to a hacker I think you have
Or maybe the maybe the the fishing website is maybe they're fans of the
show. I'm so confused dude there's four pages of this forum I can't figure out
what the... What do you think? PH. Fat fishing? Yeah. That's sick. That's the one. Oh man I
hope that I hope that exists let me look up fat fishing. I hate these fat fishing emails I guess.
fat fish Oh fat fish record that but yeah that is literally the only thing that
comes up when you google it it's just that it was used to email oh my god did
I'm helping the bad guys I thought I was helping the good guys and squad I call
the geek squad you said do you actually sent your review into the freak squad
fuck the dark mode geek squad the evil geeks go to come the key cord your
You call them if your computer is working perfectly and they come and break it dude.
Yeah it's just a couple guys with hammers. Yeah they just take the battery out of
your laptop. Alright should be about it. That'll be $500.
Yeah oh I knew I called the wrong EECS squad. Hey do you want to hear a quote too?
That's what they say. Here's a quote from Caleb P. In New York City. He says we have his
back the board the squad baby always has my back what do you say whoo-whee I
gleaked on my keyboard what did you say after that when I'm joining bleak squad
you're a gleeker I did by accident you you can clean nobody
gleeks on purpose right no I knew it people who did a gleek on me like a
lizard yeah yeah just fucking yeah some people can do it
Yeah, it's fucking weird.
I've only done it like a few times in my life. It's so strange.
I've never ever done it.
I'm trying to do it.
Stop!
You do that won't-
You're gonna accidentally turn into a werewolf if you keep doing that.
Your face is gonna get stuck like that.
You're gonna scare people on the street.
Stop trying to gleek, dude.
It's an unlearnable skill.
You're born with it.
It's like an opposable thumb.
Stop.
Stop trying to gleek, dude.
Here, let me try.
I
yeah you have to see because you have to summon it that makes sense you know you
have to you got a recharge to your your gleek gland isn't refilled yet yeah I
gotta wait for that to fill up yeah I know a guy check this out no didn't
work you're scaring me a little I knew a guy in high school like one of my
closest friends we would just really be sitting on the couch watching a movie
and then he just hit me with a Gleek on my arm like what the fuck dude doing it
on to another person is just deeply fucked up yeah he was a he's a big leak
on a person it was pretty funny I'll say that much you know it's funny but it's
like more getting on me yeah yeah I mean guess I didn't really think about that I
was like well that's like I thought it was like work you know I thought it was
like a third thing that was like a new liquid that only if you're watching TV
with your friend and he's turning spat on to your body you can't do that I'm gonna
start doing that on the street yeah start to spit people to disrespect them
no it's just a joke oh I'm gonna do it to ultimately disrespect people that's got
to be what's what's more disrespectful once I'm fully vexed mm-hmm yeah I'm
gleeking on anybody just putting a fucking bump stock on your tongue just
automatic gleek.
Yeah.
Just constantly, just rapid fire gleeking on people.
Like a fucking...
That'd be so sick if you could do a rapid fire.
Yeah, dude, that'd be sick.
Just fill up a glass of water in five seconds.
Just the human sprinkler.
Oh, man.
Just all over somebody.
That'd be so cool.
Yeah, just drenched in gleek goo.
I'm just gonna google "fastest gleeker."
There has to be a fucking guy who's hitting targets.
Well, you gotta be careful with that, 'cause then it could be like glee fans.
The top result for that is a YouTube video from Screen Rant called "Crisis on Infinite
Earths - Who is Gleek and How He'll Change the Arrowverse?"
Gleek is meek.
Nah.
I still can't do it.
"Farthest Distance Gleek'd - World Record."
The world record for farthest distance gleek'd is held by a man named Callum Blades.
There's no way.
There's no way his name is Callum Blades.
Callum Blades gleaked 145 centimeters.
That guy is a fucking Wu-Tang-Nan generator.
They have a video for it right here.
Gleaking a hundred meters you said?
Centimeter, 145 centimeters.
Oh, okay.
I was like, "A hundred meters?!"
Gleak an entire football field?
That'd be crazy.
You'd gleak a hole in someone's fucking head with that, dude.
Yeah, your gleek can shoot that far?
That's a damn, you got some velocity.
He definitely cheated in this video.
Yeah?
leans forward over the table like okay yeah that's that's a nice view in my
eyes yeah he's done for the comments on this are so good
Reginald 213 centimeters Reginald I gleeked seven feet Jamal that's nothing
12 feet way easily I could gleek but it also when you say gleeks are they
starting from like you know because the Gleek has to fall and so in that in that
falling action is it just like like it depends on how tall you are I feel like
there's a lot of factors here yeah you know I don't know I think we maybe need
to get involved in the Gleeks here. Tiara Baker, I can Gleek between one and two feet
just figures out how to do this today like an hour ago lol I can do over 20 per
minute which the Guinness World Record holder does 28 per minute I'm very good
and I just learned I can do it so I can only get better every day 20 times a
minute dude that's once every day any seconds
damn shooting two feet and she's in there training like Rocky for that
fucking hit 20 I learned to do it an hour ago it might be a gleeking savant
learning to do it to Gleek and just instantly doing 20 a minute yeah I got
well there is it got to be a guy who's never done it could be Patrick who's
just never done it on purpose and might be the best ever at it.
It could be.
I think maybe this is my true calling is to train as a Gleeker.
You should put that in your bio, dude.
Gleek.
Yeah.
I'm a total Gleek.
That'll be really good for you, I think.
You think maybe people will misinterpret that?
No.
They might think you're Greek.
For something else.
How would they think I'm Greek?
- Who would think I was Greek?
- A guy who mixes up his L's and his R's.
- Who would do that?
- Just a guy with a speech impediment or something like that.
He might think that you're Greek.
- Okay.
- Yeah, he might read that and say, yeah, he's Greek.
- I think maybe we leave that there.
- Or he has a reading impediment, maybe.
Yeah, maybe we don't touch that from now on.
You know, that's fine.
Some things you don't have to explore every single,
I know that we're known as people who just,
you know, we keep digging.
- We're explorers of the mind.
investigators of the English language but sometimes you just you know you just
gotta leave it be. See something and say huh you know what?
Let a sleepy dog lie. Exactly you know and also it's about it's about what you don't say you
know that's the most way you don't show too you know I'm kind of like a movie
director the way I do this shit. It's all symbolism and exactly
shutter speed you know just like the movies yeah it's mostly shutter speed
It's about syncing it up.
I'm blinking 24 frames a second.
I'm sitting here.
Yeah, you guys don't know what it looks like.
You know what it sounds like, what it hears like to record a podcast.
You don't know what it looks like, dude.
It's not pretty.
I'm doing this to make it look good.
Even if you do know what it looks like, you don't know what it is like.
True.
A lot of people don't understand our struggle.
You don't know what it feels like.
You know, I've had my heart broken.
When I was 14, I had my heart broken by a woman named Madison.
She was a year and a half older than me.
me. A lot of people don't know that about me. A lot of people don't know I have a sensitive thumb.
Yeah.
So there's a lot of different struggles.
I was too scared to jump off the play structure at the playground when I was in third grade.
Yeah, man. I mean, that's another--
I mean, stuff like that just happens.
Yeah. I mean, you know--
People don't know.
My brother got-- he got arrested once for shoplifting.
Yeah.
That's like serious--
He was like maybe this close to going to jail
for the rest of his life,
'cause that's just what it's like down there.
They haven't decriminalized shoplifting yet in North Carolina.
- Yeah, no, but once they do,
once they decriminalize shoplifting down there--
- Oh my God.
- The economy is gonna be amazing.
- Listen, I'll do it if it's legal,
it's as simple as that.
That's why I love Kratom and what's the other one?
- PC, no, K2.
- K2, love K, is K2 legal?
- K2 shouldn't be legal.
- I think in Arizona,
They sell it in these little pouches and say that it's like smelling salts or something.
Yeah.
But yeah, no, that shit will...
I've talked about my K2 experience.
Yeah, we've talked about K2 many times.
Pat used to be a girl.
Yeah.
I smoked K2 spice.
And now he's a genie.
Mm-hmm.
Yep.
That's what it does to you.
Uh-huh.
You become a...
You become a blue genie.
Yeah.
Yep.
Become a big blue genie and you're walking around.
smoking a k2 joint it you think you're inhaling it this motherfucker is
inhaling you you get sucked in put through a genie filtration system which
is part of what k2 is that's yeah that's how genies get in you go you know you
emerge out of the smoke on the other side you fucking blue you don't have
legs no tail where's my penis has gone yeah you got a big tail if you're a genie
that's the only and between mm-hmm including the pony you know do you guys
know why they call it K2? Why? Because you take two of it and you're not gonna be
okay. That's right. That's how the scientists named it. They should call it W3, three wishes.
Yeah they should call it W2. You become a complete genie kind of guy after that you
know? Yeah. It'll turn your ass to a genie in you know five minutes flat. Usually
that takes, I mean back in the day that would take years to become a genie.
- I smoked K2 out of a hookah.
- That's gotta be the most genie shit I've ever heard.
- And I got trapped in the hookah.
And now all my wishes are just getting guys Lamborghinis.
- What would your three wishes be?
- My three wishes?
- Yeah.
- One wish for, I wish that Cameron gets one wish,
I wish that Caleb gets one wish,
and I wish for world peace.
- Wow, I wish for world war.
- No.
- Yeah, that's the thing, do they cancel each other out?
- I wish, yeah. - It's about the order.
- Oh yeah, but if you, so if you--
- Well I gave you and Cameron one of my wishes
and Cameron wished for world war,
so what are you gonna wish for?
- Well they cancel each other out,
so I'll wish for world war as well.
And then it'll, you know, two negatives make a zero.
- Positive, exactly, if we wish for world war twice,
we're gonna get world peace.
- Exactly, yeah, 'cause if I wish for world peace,
it'll just, it'll bounce back to zero.
- The genie will twist it and do something nasty.
- Yeah, and that's not gonna work.
- Yeah, 'cause if I wish for world peace, maybe, okay.
- Maybe he's like, okay, well then there's nobody left.
- We can only achieve world peace through world war,
and then you guys wish for world war,
and then he's like, well shit, now I have to,
if we have a big war, there's gonna be world,
we're making a paradox for the genie.
- Here's the other thing, though.
- We're only making these wishes
to make the genie kill himself.
You only need one wish that's like not for you.
The other two can be whatever you want.
You can wish for world peace and then
Mario and Luigi to be real.
- Exactly, nobody's gonna blame you if you do that.
- Immediately, yeah.
I mean, everybody's gonna be like,
"All right, well, he did world peace."
You know what I mean?
I mean, I just thank Christ every day
that a genie's never gotten into the wrong hands.
- Oh my God, could you imagine?
- That we know of, at least.
- Maybe a genie did get into the wrong hands
four years ago on November in November I don't remember the day but 2015. Maybe Donald Trump
was a genie himself. True. Have you ever seen his feet? Think about it he's orange.
He's orange which is a kind of a yeah what color okay all right when Jafar became a genie.
Was he orange? I think yeah. Yeah I think so. Damn. I don't was he orange? I don't think he was orange.
But also the genie can become and show itself in various different forms.
Because it's the blue genie and the red genie.
I'd like to make a point here that Patrick does have an orange topper for his microphone.
Just saying it could be a genie in disguise, you never know.
Alright, well now that you know.
Oh my god.
I have to grant, you rubbed me the wrong way, now I gotta grant you a wish.
I get a wish from you? Uh-huh. Okay. World evil. Oh I hate having to grant these
wishes. World domination. Biggest skateboard ever. Whoa alright this is one
I can get behind. Princess Peach. Alright you got half naked. That's four wishes so far.
This is too many wishes. Unlimited pot to smoke. I can't even do that.
there's a catch to all your wishes I heard you realize. Burger King in my house and a $50
Burger King gift card yeah but he doesn't know that it's not gonna be a Burger
King restaurant in this house it's gonna be the king himself and he's gonna be
ahead of him and you have to feed him you have to feed that fucking guy I have to
feed the Burger King now cuz I fucking fuck cuz you twisted my words oh you
You devilish nymph.
(laughing)
- Nymph?
- You devilish dominatrix.
(laughing)
- I have sex now?
- You stinky imp.
- Nymph?
(laughing)
- Yeah, did you mean imp and then you said nymph?
- I said what I said, genie.
Now do your job, you're my slave.
- I'm not a, genies aren't slaves, they're genies.
- Oh, sorry, are you gonna say no to my wish?
- You can, there is a rule--
- Okay, slave.
- Come on now.
- Oh, come on.
That's gonna be the new cool thing that the kids say.
Okay, slave.
They'll start saying that now, yeah.
I'm kinda changing the discourse and the vernacular.
- That's the new okay boomer.
- Yeah, it's okay, slave.
And our grandparents will be like, what does this mean?
We'll say, okay, slave.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- All right, slave.
- Okay, genie.
Man, I went to the M&M store yesterday.
- Speak about genies, dude.
That's, I mean.
- Oh man. - That's all M&M's.
- Talking about genies.
- Yeah, what the fuck?
- That place is every wish I've ever thought of.
(laughing)
- Yeah, that'd be my one wish.
M&M world, yeah, I wanna live there.
Make it a real planet.
- Oh man, I didn't get any M&M's, I just went in there.
I didn't even fuckin' buy M&M's.
- Did you do the scan to see which M&M you were?
- No.
- I was a red M&M. - Why did you go?
- I got off the train and--
- You didn't get any M&M's, you didn't do the scan.
- No, I was going somewhere else.
I was going to buy a DVD.
I'll say it, that's a pedophile move.
Absolutely.
Just walking around M&M world not even scanning yourself, just fucking looking at shit.
I just wanted to see the M&Ms, how is that a pedophile move?
Is that what you call them?
What?
The children?
There weren't any kids there.
Yeah, mothers and mothers' childs.
It was like just me in there.
Really?
Yeah.
Is that why you left without doing anything?
Fuck you.
No, I wish I did.
I wish I did.
I wish I did do the scan. I wanted to find out, you know, cause I know I'm the...
You could have done it. Why didn't you?
I was busy.
It's not like there was a line.
I was busy. I got off the train, I saw the M&M store and I was like, "Ah, well, fuck
it. I guess I'll go."
You just ate in Times Square for some reason?
It's funny to imagine...
Yeah, I went to Book Off. I went to that big DVD store.
Whatever cashier saw you in there just being like, "Damn, that guy's probably gonna kill
himself. He came in here alone. He didn't even do the scan."
yeah that was just like a young guy thinking he's doing something funny but
he didn't even do the scan part that's like the only reason to come and he did
the M&Ms I already know I'm the orange M&M you're literally the
green M&M we've talked about it no I'm not the green M&M we've actually spoken
on this I'm not you got scanned at the Lego store and it said you were the
green M&M it didn't say that no yeah that's I have the fucking footage I have
the footage you don't which I wasn't Caleb like you have a unicorn or
something Caleb was a I was a I sat there praying I prayed out loud I was not the
green Eminem no I was the black Ninjago no you were not yes I was ain't nothing
black about you what do you mean just you ain't black I'm not you ain't in
Jago either you ain't nothing you're not nothing about you is Ninjago what about
Show me your hand. Show me your hand right now. Fuck. That might... I never noticed that,
but you do have... they're kind of perfectly positioned for something circular.
Oh, guys.
What?
I just found a website where you can order custom printed M&Ms.
You can print M&Ms onto them.
Is it M&Ms.com?
No, it's an insecure website. It's somebody's... it looks like it's somebody's Geocities or
something.
- They have that at the M&M store as well.
You can go get a special M&M made.
- All right, I'm gonna take a quiz right now
to see which M&M I am.
- Okay.
- All right, just 'cause I didn't do it.
I'm doing it remote, I'm doing it from home.
- It won't count.
I mean, it can't get your energy.
You didn't get scanned, dog.
- Are you telling me brainfall.com is not
an accredited M&M website? - Dude, the only thing
that can do it is the machine at the M&M store.
- Okay.
- Or you can go to a M&M testing site,
which is usually like a closed high school or something.
You go in, there's a proctor, you take a test.
- Okay, hold on, hold on.
- But an online test is not gonna give you accurate results
as far as M&Ms are going.
- I'm on the M&Ms website right now,
and I'm on the characters page,
and I'm looking at the descriptions of the characters.
They have a turn-ons section for the M&Ms?
- Dude, have you seen some of the M&Ms they're making now?
- The red M&Ms turn-on is when people
blindly follow his advice.
- Dude, the red M&M is a fucking,
So your fire alarm
all right we'll pause for a second
did it cause a lot of anything to do for christmas
the other read in the end of this guy this guy's a focus of later
i don't know i don't wanna go back to this website but i do want to go back to
the subject of fruit
God is trying to shut shut this down right now
You are Kenny's just setting his pubes on fire
He's just putting the same slice of bread back in the toaster over and over and over
There's a chart on this website for the wrong way versus the right way to choose a message to put on your M&M
And here's the first example, okay
The so no product names trademarks copyrights or business names, right? Here's the wrong way to put the wrong way to do it. Oh
American fan company don't put that on your M&M
American fan company that's right you cannot put that on your Eminem the right way for this example
Like it has like it's like a whole list of them
And like it one is wrong when it's right the right way instead of putting American fan company think about putting time to be cool
Do you think that lets you put like diarrhea or like like a poison symbol on it or something yeah, that'd be fun
Yeah, it's a biohazard. It's you know like like people like their faces put on like the M&Ms
I would get a stevo M&M. Yeah like the thumb like the tattoo. Yeah I would get the stevo
back tat on an M&M. One side is yours to customize. You get two lines, eight letters per line.
The other side will have the famous M. Could we do podcasts about list M&Ms? I would like
to. Maybe we give those out at the live show dude. That'd be a good idea. Yeah. Some sweet
treaties. Oh speaking of the live show, it's mostly sold out. Thank you. Oh yeah. I think
There's like two or three.
There's a few bigger tables left for the late show.
But I also wanted to throw it there is if you got a ticket and you're not going with
anybody the minimum it's like the smallest ticket is like a two person table because
of COVID you can't like sit with people you don't know like you can't just buy one ticket
so if you bought a two person ticket you don't have anyone to go with you should go in the
discord and see if anyone wants to pay you to sit with a stranger.
Or you can just grab some freak off the street.
You could do that too that might be even more fun.
Get some fucked up fucking freak.
Get the biggest freak you can find.
And we're talking biggest. We want the biggest, sickest guy. This guy in my
neighborhood. We want the room to be like the most full by volume. Yeah, get one of those homeless guys
who has like barnacles on his hands and bring him in. And we want him sitting in the front row.
Can you bring, can you bring Davey Jones? We want to meet Davey Jones.
The haunted sailor ghost who lives in my neighborhood and moves around a shopping
card cuz that guy first off that guy could use a smile say that much right
the best medicine not sure if it'll clear up those barnacles yeah if you see a guy
if you see a guy peeing in public he's coming in with you yeah we should have
called the show because of the because of the vaccines should have called the show
we should have called it best medicine because of what her because I'm not
gonna be any Los Angeles right now yeah yeah I'm sending you to Los Angeles
You'll be a millionaire and I will hate you.
We're not doing a laughter show though.
It's not...
What?
Does anybody...
No.
Did the fans...
I don't know if the fans realize that we're...
This is going to be very sad.
It's going to be a sad show.
This is going to be a one three...
One three-man show.
Yeah, we're doing that play Fences.
Yeah, doing that.
I'm Denzel, obviously.
And you guys will share the girl.
I obviously.
We'll switch it out.
Because I'm like the coolest one.
Can I be the mailman?
I'm the fence.
You can't be.
There's not an actual fence.
Well, we can take some artistic liberties. Yeah, I mean that's what part of what's
so interesting about doing it and now that's a good point. Update it for modern
times. Yeah, you're right. I'll do the ring doorbell. Okay, alright. That'll be
actually pretty good. Yeah. Yeah. Man, imagine, okay, okay, movie idea. All right.
so it's like a ring doorbell okay that's your friend mm-hmm a living sentient
ring doorbell one that it talks to you about your neighbors and stuff okay
okay like yeah yeah yeah it's like oh I saw I saw Loretta walking by the door
today like you you would not believe what she was carrying into her house oh
that mailman sheesh yeah does he know how to put a package down and there's no
plot it's just people going up to the door and you get to hear what the doorbell
says about them yeah you you ain't coming in here he's kind of mean you know you're
not coming in here dressed like that your mother-in-law arrived do you want
me to lock the door yeah doorbell the perfect title - ready you rang I'm not
done you rang question mark at the end the circle in the question mark is a
doorbell yes dude Wow yes all right fuck yeah I think I think we've got something
to pitch if anybody wants to hop in on this maybe who would voice - who would
voice the ring doorbell I do all the voices no I don't think I get like a big
I think it's a nice wall for the movie we get a big name and then for the TV
show we get some fucker no one care can I be the fucker maybe there's a character
named the fucker and the doorbell goes oh no here comes the fucker he's really big
you know what and we could do a horror spinoff where the doorbell sees the
chupacabra yeah oh my god oh no it's a bacabra he can do that yeah he's got a
bunch of different he's got a bunch of different accents and voices yeah the
He's a fucking computer.
The thing that people need to understand is that's how that word is pronounced.
If you say it differently, you're mispronouncing it.
Yeah, you can't call it, you have to say...
It's not the chupacabra, it's el chupacabra.
El chupacabra.
Every single time.
Very soft on every single consonant.
Except for the B.
El chupacabra.
It's just, it's how the word was meant to be pronounced.
Yeah, sorry I speak Spanish.
Yeah, I'm on fucking day six of Duolingo.
I mean, that's like going to Taco Bell and asking, it's like going to Taco Bell and saying,
can I get a taco?
yeah it isn't done it could be a cheesy crunch they go thank you god bless you
and they bow to you and they say thank you for ordering in the native native
tongue very very respectful but you will have to leave sir I I don't know what's
going on with you do you need me to call somebody are you okay
yes I just said I carbon monoxide detector beeping in the back of the
restaurant and you're just like "eh weeeew"
"Gina have a m-a-a-a-bah-a-bless"
"eh weeeew"
"Can I get a e-taco but can I get no sour cream on it please?"
"Grillers cargados"
"Can I get a mexican pizza?"
Or you go "Mexican" and then you go "e-pizza"
You are, you may be the greatest guy we've ever had in this Taco Bell
Thank you so much for your service and you do have to leave still
Listen your penis is out
As spot-on as this gets
Every single time you order you cannot open carry in a Taco Bell. You do have to leave
We do require I mean no shirt. No shoes. We do still require pants. Yep
Yeah, and you have a loaded gun next to your penis
You're pointing a loaded gun at your penis and you're and you're I mean
I'm closing my eyes because I don't want to look at your penis, but those voices that you're doing are amazing
Yeah, anyway, anyway, I get this card. This is my boy walk there
This is my friend Frank Caliendo
He's gonna love
Frank Caliendo, you know that guy when he's in a Mexican restaurant. He fucking crushes it dude. Oh, man
Yeah, the key is he just thinks Carlos Mencia and he gets it done because he can't speak
the languages but he can do impressions just about spot on.
He can speak any language in the world by just doing different impressions.
It's true.
You know?
Because I mean impressions are the language of the soul.
That's right.
That's so right.
Yeah.
The language of the soul.
And this guy, I mean this guy's got to be a - he's quite the polyglot in that sense.
Yeah.
go to restaurants I make sure to use the correct accent whenever I ask for the
bathroom code I say may I have that bathroom code yeah that's how I order
one of those like one of those cashier looks like Amazon like a robot go into
the
again ordering. Three ranch, yeah you have to say. The correct pronunciation, I appreciate
that. Yeah. You have to say the thing three times if you're ordering three of them. Yeah,
it's like Beetlejuice. Exactly, you basically read the receipt out to the different robots.
Are you guys excited for there to be more robots involved in your life each and every
day? It really snuck up on me. I remember like the self-checkout thing at the grocery
store seeing that and being like this is stupid dude mm-hmm oh and then I found
out that you could steal things oh yeah things actually first of all beast but I
don't want any more robots and they just started and then the one that
McDonald's one fucked me up dude yeah so I love I love to look at the burgers and
not order anything they are really fun to play with I think what what what like
Robotics designers don't realize is that by introducing robots instead of cashiers people are just gonna want to play on them for a few hours
So I'm gonna order dude. I'll sit on the coke freestyle machine writing an essay all night exactly dude
I'll pretend it's flappy bird, and I'll just move my circles might as well be a public library computer at this point cuz I'm
I'm playing runescape on this one coke freestyle machine right now
When Nolan was in Boston, we went to the
The McDonald's by your apartment Caleb in Cambridge and I ordered a thing of chicken nuggets
But I ordered every sauce because I wanted to like get everything
Yeah, and once my order went through the lady like looked and went. All right, who ordered this?
She's like that's way too many sauces. I'm not giving you all that
Yeah, give me that damn sauce. I wanted to try I wanted to have a sampler of sauces
It's like fucking tears not doing though. You're not doing that's the good thing about the robot is you can order shit
However, you want you can do the thing where you're like, I want I want a McDouble but I want no patties on it at
All I want is the robot is is no emotion pure logic
So cuz you I remember when I was vegan I'd go to like a Taco Bell or something
I order a burrito with no meat and some ago. What the fuck are you trying to order?
I don't get that kind of sassy backtalk anymore.
Right.
My computer does what I say, which is how,
which tell you what,
these minimum wage workers could learn a thing or two
about being silent and obeying orders
from these fucking computers.
Dude, I wish we could put all the minimum wage workers
on a hard drive so I don't have to look at them.
Here's all I'm saying,
make some sort of cursed mirror
that you trap the workers in
where they can't talk or interact with you really
and they just fulfill your order.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
So the McDonald's like kiosk, like the thing, right?
What if we put like a celebrity in there
and he takes your order?
Like we have like--
Oh, like a custom Waze voice kind of thing?
Yeah, yeah, so you get like, I don't know,
like fucking-- Mr. T taking my day order?
Yeah, yeah.
I pity the fool who doesn't get two burgers.
Yep, and that's a, you know.
That would work on me.
And that's about as classic as an impression gets, dude.
Mr. T starting with I pity the fool.
You could get Alan Alda in there.
you could do alan alda yet or any other impression that patrick and do
yeah
well i don't know if it
of its that's just classic
to to hamburgers what a classic meal
that is a pretty good alan
i'll say that my it's a story
the spread the spread you're gonna have at home is going to be amazing it's
gonna be beautiful did you could have chris to her walking in there and he
could be like
i'm so crazy i love i love having a hamburger
I'm Christopher Walken, I'm crazy!
I'm the most-
You want help killing your wife?
I'm Christopher Walken!
Oh, I'm gonna push you off a boat. I'm Christopher Walken.
What was that bitch's name?
Uh...
Christine Walken.
I don't think it was.
Christina Walken.
Uh...
Nope, it wasn't his wife.
It was.
It was Natalie Wood. Yeah, and he pushed her off a boat.
Tell you what, great TMZ article the day after, "Wood don't float."
Ooh. Might be pretty good. That should be my fucking job, dude.
What am I doing with this podcasting shit? I should be coming up with headlines a day
after somebody dies. Yeah. Well, let's go through something. Let's think.
Okay. Let's say who died. Well, Prince Philip died.
yeah Prince Philip you could do you could do the prince and the pauper did I ask
what's giving us Prince Philip's last name is this first name Prince and his
last name Philip no you could do you can I mean if that's your name I mean you're
destined for royalty at that filled up a fucking casket you do something there we
go right who else just died dude he doesn't have a last name DMX wait did
that did the royal family not have last names no I didn't know that they're the
win like me blank no they're the Windsor family that's not it's a horn
Prince Philip of Greece and Denmark he did he was born in the kingdom of Greece
all right I'm looking at I'm looking at some deaths right now Caleb okay I got
you all right let's see let's see who died
Pete Warner. Pete Warner. Pete, Pete warning could be the first of many Pete deaths.
Okay. That's pretty good. You know, cuz you gotta sensationalize it a little bit. You
know, if you're, if I'm walking down the street, my name's Pete, I'm throwing a
nickel into the fucking TMZ newspaper machine. I'm getting that, getting more
info. More on page 57. Jessica Walter. Jessica Walt-sted down to hell today
when she died tragically at age 1,000.
Bossy Scoglund. Bossy Scoglund has a
nasty hole in the ground that he lives in now.
Chloris Leachman. Chloris Leachman is a
boring beach man. Thank God she's dead,
that boring bitch. Adolf Cabo. Adolf Hitler
has died today in a tragic accident
Bruce Dinwiddie Bruce Dinwiddie Bruce he sinned shitty and he went to hell as
well most of these people are in hell Siegfried Fischbacher
Fischbacher? He should have baked his fish more because he died of fish
Salmonella Walter Gretzky Walter Gretzky should have not bought a jet ski which
he died on today in a tragic jet ski accident so part of it is I make up how
they died yeah that's more ex toady Hendra yeah I got nothing for that
really nothing for Tony and no I just can't think of a single thing Wow you
You must have really respected Tony Hendra.
Yeah, that's the secret.
Yeah.
Any other amazingly perfect rhyming names?
So you respect Tony Hendra?
100%.
Here's a section on his Wikipedia, "Family Life and Sexual Abuse Allegations."
Just allegations.
Are you telling me you lost respect for Dr. Bill Cosby?
Are you really telling me that?
He's a doctor, god damn you.
I pray to God you're never fucking sick on a plane and he's on there too.
Hans Dieter Tippenhauer.
Igor Zheltukov.
Hans Dieter Tippentower?
Okay, alright, alright.
He should have never teetered and tipped the tower which fell on him and crushed him so
tragically and also sent him to hell.
Leocadia Drobysheva.
Nothing rhymes with that.
- It's like orange or purple.
- Something rhymes with purple.
- Nerple.
- Yes, we slurple.
Yeah, you slurpling on my damn balls and ass.
- No, no, no, no.
- Oh, keep slurpling.
- I'm not slurpling on your balls and ass.
- Yeah, you know what rhymes,
it's what I have you in my phone as, is slurple.
- What?
- 'Cause you come over, you slurple my balls
and my dick and my ass.
- You don't call me, you've never called me slurple.
- Okay, slurple.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, you responded.
- Don't start now.
- Seems like you responded, slurple.
Okay, alright, here's somebody.
Okay.
Uh, Buddy Deppenschmidt.
Buddy Deppenschmidt, yeah he stepped in shit and it killed him.
What about this one?
He drowned in an elephant shit.
Caleb Pitts.
What was that?
New York.
From the Geek Squad email?
Geek Squad Enthusiast.
Says on the Wikipedia page.
Caleb Pitts died heroically today at the ripe old age of 23 years old
and he and he will be missed greatly by his friends Cameron and Slurple. I'm not
Slurple. You can say that all you want, it doesn't make it not true. You're not Slurple but I do
have you in my phone as Slurple due to what you Slurple on when you come to my house. You do not have me in your
phone is slurple. Listen the day you stop slurpling is the day I stop calling you
slurple. I have Patrick in my phone today. That's Splatrick. Splatrick slurple?
Splatrick Toiland. That's a fucking amazing middle name. Toiland middle name
last name slurple. My middle name is Edward. Slurple because you come from a
long line of slurplers and it's like yeah it's back in the old days when
somebody's name would be based on their profession you know there's there's
people whose name is Mason you were from the slurpling family and they would go
there were the village slurplers and they would walk around they would slurp up and
down every fucking last woman man and child in the damn village and that's
where you're from kids would dread being made the slurple
apprentice absolutely slurplers apprentice they would they would that
was the slurple is apprentice that's the new the new why yeah and that's basically
That's your lineage Patrick and I wish that you would wear it proudly like a badge.
I'm not. Because you do wear a lot of different badges. I don't wear a lot of
different badges. What are you talking about? I've never owned a badge. Some of them are historically not very...
I don't own any badge other than the one that I got at work.
Yeah at the Nazi party where you work. No, at the police station. You got that damn thing.
At the New York City Transit Police Station. Why are you southern for one second? At the New York City
train station I joined citizens on patrol yeah on slurp patrol no I'm not it's COP
it's not CO it's not cusp it's cop you're a slurple citizens on patrol yeah he is
for slurple no how would that work slurple or a fucking soft C are you
kidding just like in Cinderella yeah a snake you're pronouncing that wrong it's
kinderella and is it you wish it was kinder what it was kiderella I wish it
was kinder egg I'm gonna take a little bit in an M&M store for the dance so
you'd do slurpler I'm just saying man you slurp I don't you just got you don't
slurp you slurple yeah I'm not oh my fucking god okay slurple it sucks
slurple the episodes almost over do you have anything to say yeah so come out to
to
So he has to walk around with a sign that says,
I am Slurple on both sides.
So people always know from all directions,
you can get into the show for free.
I will reserve one seat for you.
- We will kick you out of the show if you call me Slurple.
- We will not.
Slurple might try, but Slurple might get a little
carried away and end up Slurpling you.
So just watch out.
Come get Slurpled by him.
This show is gonna be fun.
Bye.
- I'm not Slurple.
[BLANK_AUDIO]