You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
I'm recording now.
Me too.
So what is that pink?
Yeah.
The grape-- I would-- it's a grapefruit something?
Polar pink grapefruit dry.
Does it have sugar in it?
It's got 26 grams of sugar, yes.
How many servings though?
300.
2.5.
Okay, so as like 70 grams of sugar.
It's 300 servings.
It's a misprint.
Shit.
It's supposed to take one sip a day.
Damn.
That sucks.
I was, I got halfway through a movie today that I think both of you would really like
called, uh, what is it called?
Windy City Heat.
Have you seen it?
No.
It sounds familiar.
Oh, is that about, um, what's his fucking name?
Yeah, it's about the, like...
Scary Perry?
Yeah, yeah.
It's about Scary Perry.
So, these two guys who are just like comedians just like got this just this dumb ass guy
who they like knew from open mics, I guess.
I didn't finish it, but basically they like trick him into thinking that he's going to
be a movie star and they just like they have him like audition for this role and they're
like you got the role and they're just recording him the entire time and like interviewing
him and it's just like this - it's like the movie Comedian.
I don't know if you've seen Comedian.
like it's like comedian but with like it but much meaner and okay it's I haven't
seen comedian it's a movie it's it's I get this guy for for a feature-length
film and it's really really good it sounds fun finish it tonight the guy
they say that the producer is Dane cook in it Dane cooks in it and they say they
say that like the guy who's funding the movie is this guy Hiroshima Nagasaki
the Japanese millionaire it's awesome yeah I think because I know I knew about
fucking scary Perry because have you seen hot package at all no ah what yeah
Yeah they had uh, they interviewed Scary Perry on Hot Package.
Is that like Hot Ones?
No, it's um, it's the guy who made TV Carnage.
And uh, Derek Beckles and he does like,
it's supposed to be like uh, Entertainment Tonight, but only using like found like VHS footage.
Ah.
So it's like old like stuff from the 80s and he's treating it like they're like celebrities now.
now like there's this one oh he have found like a public access show about
vampires and he's like everybody's fucking waiting to see what's gonna
happen next on this it's such a good show I it used to be on Hulu I don't
know where to watch it now but fucking they interviewed scary Perry and then in
the middle of him going off on a rant about like trans people yeah Derek
Beckles cut him off and was like uh do you think Nick Cannon is talented?
He's a he's the best he's just like a he's like pretend he's like trying to be
like Sam Kannison sort of yeah yeah yeah but he's just like oh you could just
watch it on Adult Swim nice what TV carnage yeah hot package oh okay
There's so many good old like early 2000s TV shows that I feel like are like so do you remember Celebrity Deathmatch?
Yeah, Celebrity Deathmatch is maybe the most influential
thing like piece of media
To to me I feel like
Did you ever watch it? No, I haven't seen it
I haven't seen or heard of anybody that we've talked about so far
Celebrity Deathmatch was this MTV show where they just had they did a claymation version of celebrities
and they would just like have like Paris Hilton like kill OJ Simpson in like a wrestling match.
That's cool. When I was a kid I thought it was the funniest thing. It sounds fun. It was so fun. Yeah
it used to have um what was it it was like Andy Milonakis versus Gary Coleman. Yeah there's some
good matchups yeah you know Mario vs. Bowser
original epic rap battles it kind of was an epic rap battles of history battles
of history still going still good yeah as it still does it still exist I think it
is I think it's still good yeah it's still good still holds up I think they
do still make new ones yeah I remember I found one time it was like an Indian guy
made his own epic rap battles of history and it was like to like like
politicians like Indian politicians against each other that's good
there's a cool that's just epic rap battles of history yeah but it was
different it wasn't epic rap but epic rap battles of history is a brand that's
okay it is yeah it has a specific voice yeah that you're not getting waiters
voice exactly yeah versus Hitler Darth Vader verse Elizabeth Warren
epic rap battles of history you guys see that video of Elizabeth Warren yeah what
What a dumbass.
I hate her.
It's so...
Yeah.
Cool.
God.
Fucking...
I just remembered...
I remembered a joke from Celebrity Deathmatch for some reason.
Tell me the joke.
I love jokes.
It was like a whole episode about Stevo.
It was about Stevo and like Jackass and stuff.
And there was a...
He was talking about like his wild boys.
the host Nick Diamond was talking about his Wild Boys fan website and he's like
yeah you know a wild boys fan.com was already taken so I had to use Nick Wild
Nick Diamond is wild for boys.com. That's fun. It is funny to go back and watch all of
those early 2000s comedies and just every joke is a gay joke. Yeah. That's the only
jokes they knew how to make was like gay joke Iraq war joke that's a gay pedophile
joke true that's got layers true that is a that's a yeah there's a multi-new
ones yeah yeah oh they had in 2006 they had Bam Margera versus Tony Hawk and
then Bam Margera versus Don Vito I don't remember that one but I'd be willing to
watch it yeah I'm looking at the Wikipedia page for tonight is the name
we should have done WALL-E. Yeah, well we can't do WALL-E when we're all a
different place, when we're apart. Yeah. I feel like that's like we all have to like you
know huddle up under a blanket, build a fort, a big bowl of popcorn, you know wear
one of those, one of those sweaters that has three head holes. All of us wearing
edible lingerie. Yeah. Just watch WALL-E. Smoking a pipe that has three mouthpieces.
and it's all the boys night does breath this is a boy's night for the three
three musketeers baby just breathing in the other boys breath yeah for for the
length of Wally I am yeah a Wally a Wally like riff tracks thing that's just
heavy breathing.
Ah, fuck.
Oh, fuck.
This breath took like an hour.
Podcast about Liz fans, sync this up at the beginning, right when you see the Wally first comes on screen, press play.
Yeah.
Ah, fuck.
No.
Ah.
It's actually a statement about climate change, that movie.
yeah it's actually a statement about how fat people are statement about robots
when you think about that movie actually makes a statement it's uh it's you
should never let a fat person drive a spaceship yeah or really because the
thesis of that movie is fat is contagious yeah yeah no I've never seen
it I don't know I don't know yeah we shouldn't be spoiling there's no fat
people in it. Don't look it up, dude. Please don't. Looking up WALL-E spoiler alert. Don't
do that. Seriously. And I found a video from J Smooth that says "The WALL-E Theory." I have
a theory that WALL-E is actually a robot. The WALL-E theory of everything. I have a
fan theory that- Oh, you know what it is? It's probably like a- Oh, here's a list. We
We don't do a list on this episode.
Get that shit the fuck out of my face.
I'll send it, I'll send it so we have it, but it's a...
I don't want that.
Nine ways today's society is like the one that filled earth with... garbage in wall.
You have trouble with that word?
With G, G goes guh, A goes ah, garbage.
It didn't have the full thing on Google.
Sure.
Yeah, we believe you.
- Yeah.
- Not.
- So I--
- My blog out.
- I look at like the website Bloody Disgusting a lot.
- Yeah.
- It's like for like horror movie news.
- What's that?
Just pictures of your asshole on it?
- Yeah.
- I look at it to see my ass
'cause there's no, I don't have a mirror.
And the best way I can do it is to look at this website
that constantly is posting pictures of my ass.
- Bloody Disgusting is a food critic.
It's Gordon Ramsay's food review blog.
- Nice.
- He just says that to everything.
- That's pretty cool.
- Yeah.
there's this one guy there's this one writer for bloody disgusting
who does movie reviews
and his name
is william b_ b_ on e
so billy b_ b_ on e
and he uh... it'd be be be that he's like notorious will be be
he just gives the most bizarre reviews like his ratings just have no like
like uh...
they don't they don't match up like he like
he rated once upon a time in hollywood half a star
and then he rated the gallows act to like four stars
and it is like makes no sense and none of the reason make any sense at all the
comments and also be as it is like
classic baby i think it
she is the craziest guy what is the content of the review
uh... a lot of times he he just like
he like describe the movie but just won't
like i don't know why he didn't he's like
it's a survey committee he's confusing he's cause all the characters billy
Bibiani. Yeah. I really loved Billy Bibiani's performance in Star Wars
Revenge of the Sith. Five stars. Yeah. Now in this movie Billy Bibiani, you don't see
that much of him but he is on the poster. In Mr. and Mrs. Smith, Billy Bibiani
plays opposite Angelina Jolie, his real-life wife. There's actually a pretty
big plot twist in this movie where you discover that Billy Bibiani and Billy
Bibiani are the same person yeah I'm wearing stupid socks he's just a stupid
socks I'm not wearing any socks yeah you're going commando Billy Bibiani only
has 15 minutes of actual screen time he actually is the person who stands out
the most in the film I give silence of the Lamb a career-making performance
from Bibby Bibby Bobbo from Bobby Bibiano. A must see. I give this Billy Bobbo's.
While I found the movie funny I didn't believe Billy Bibbiani would do any of
these things in real life. Therefore I give Bruno two stars. I give Billy. Billy
Bruno. Billy Bruvo, Billy Bruvo Annie. I hated
Quentin Tarantino's new movie Billy Bibbiani's Big Adventure. Billy Bibbiani. I felt it was
disrespectful to Sharon Tate. That's the one other person that he knows. Classic review
time. Billy Bibbiani goes to jail. Oh no. I drank a Coke Zero. I'm washed today. Oh no.
I drank a Coke Zero.
Shit.
That's their slogan.
Yeah.
Oh no.
I drank a Coke Zero.
You get to the bottom of the bottle and it says that and it's printed on the bottom.
So when you look in it says, "Oh no, I drank a Coke Zero."
Yeah.
More drinks should have stuff printed at the bottom.
I agree.
Yeah.
That'd be cool if you had to look into your drink at the end.
You should just have an ink cartridge at the bottom of the soda so that when you're finished
it can blow in your face and people will know you drank a soda.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's a pretty good idea.
Yeah, they should put ink cartridges like they do on pants.
They should put that on sodas from the vending machines so that those hackers on YouTube
can't put their hands in and steal one.
What?
You know.
They put ink cartridges on pants?
Have you never bought pants?
What do you mean?
Oh, that's why you never.
Cameron doesn't buy pants.
I forgot you don't have pants.
put these little thingies on pants like a JC Penney that are magnetic ink
cartridges that if you so if you steal it oh those are ink yeah I know it I
didn't know those are filled with you try to fuck like take them off they just
explode oh that's cool it is damn I thought it would just like beep or
something no it explodes that's sick yeah they should make it explode with
shrapnel yeah yeah and as soon as you walk out of the door yeah it just
explodes and kills whoever is at your waist level. Flattens the store. Whatever kid you
took to the store with you loses their head. Yeah. Yeah. Or when your beautiful girlfriend
is giving you a freaking, one of her classic trademark PJs. As you walk out of the store.
Yeah. Yeah. Cause she's like, you're so cool for stealing pants. Yeah. And you'd say, yeah
I am. Oh, you're dead. Oh no, you died because I was walking while I was leaving the store
and your head was down there and I snapped your neck with my thighs while I was trying to walk.
[laughter]
With my strong, strong thighs.
My thighs, my thighs did a kind of like a, like a, like a stick motion when you're trying to
make fire with a stick and it moistens out.
They rubbed together.
But it lit my GF's damn brain on fire.
And the friction caused your head to catch on fire.
Yeah. And you died over a span of 10 minutes.
Yeah, you died of Ghost Rider's disease.
[Laughter]
Ghost riders set it up.
That's when your head, anytime your head is on fire,
you have ghost riders disease until you die.
[Laughter]
That's true.
Yeah.
It's really easy to diagnose.
If my head caught on fire, my last thought would be,
"Shit, I look like Ghost Rider."
Yeah. Does anyone have a motorcycle?
Just come on, I'm going to be alive for 90 seconds.
Let me ride your motorcycle and fulfill a lifelong dream.
This is going to be sick.
This is gonna be sick.
What does he even do in that movie?
He rides his bike.
I'm sure he fights people.
Not that cool.
Doesn't he have like chains?
Like flaming chains?
Yeah, he throws chains and shit and he like...
Oh, what does it say?
He says, "I'm a ghost rider."
Oh, I'm a freaking ghost.
Ghost rider.
God, I'm a ghost.
Shit.
He goes, "Ooooh."
"Suck me off!"
And everyone screams and runs away.
And he rides hard.
He says, "I'm the ghost rider, suck me, fuck me off."
"Suck me, fuck me off, please."
"Please."
Yeah, that's his superhero origin.
No one would suck him, fuck him off.
And so his head caught on fire from his rage.
Yeah, he got so angry that his head burst into flames.
Yeah, that's true.
He was waiting in line at the DMV,
and he got so steamed,
he Bilbo-freaked out at the DMV.
He Bilbo Baggins freaked out. He Billy Bob-
He Bilbo Baggins, evil Bilbo, looking for the- trying to grab the ring away from Frodo.
He did that.
And his head caught fire.
Yeah, Billy Bob Baggins.
And Sam...
Sam I Am.
Sam Jelena...
Jolie. There we go.
Sam Jelena Fro-do.
Fro-do-lie.
Fro-do-ro.
Would it be funny for my first tattoo to get, um...
my first tattoo to get a tattoo. Would it be funny for the the tattoo that Angelina Jolie got
on her arm that said Billy Bob? Yeah. That's funny. Have you seen that tattoo?
Yeah of course. I haven't. It's really good. Cameron hates celebrity gossip. I just
don't know any celebrities. I know who Angelina Jolie is. I don't know who
Billy Bob is if I'm being honest. Billy Bob Jordan? I've heard that name. That was...
He's Bad Santa. I haven't seen Bad Santa. Hmm. That thing's kind of... The thing is
it's kind of bad ass. What's under Billy Bob? It's a really cool tattoo. It's honestly fucking tight.
It's like uh it's Mushu from Mulan. Yeah nice. And it says Billy Bob. Yeah it says Billy Bob in like
sort of old English but... Old Chinese. Old Chinese is what that is because there's a dragon under it.
Yeah. Yeah. You should you should get it but it should say Patrick. Yeah. That'd be kind of funny.
Patrick Bob
Yeah, and then a drag underneath
So confused
Patrick Bob or Billy Bob Patrick, but like the Patrick it like doesn't look like it
Looks like you added Patrick to the side like you don't even center the dragon already did this here
He put Billy Bob on him. He already has the Billy Bob tattoo. No, you need to add it the Steve-o tattoo on your back
Yeah, oh yeah, no, that's how I one-up him. Yeah
You say you got Angelina's I got yours bitch Steve-o Patrick. Yeah, Steve-o Patrick
You're kind of Steve you're the Steve-o of the group yeah, yeah, I'm
I'm Steve-o and I'm BAM and Johnny Knoxville and I'm Preston Lacey and
Caleb you're we man. I'm we man and then and then Cameron you're Ryan done Chris Pontius
No, I I'm Chris Pontius and we man combined
Cameron
Exited me from the other room and said to see if Oh seriously have Angelina's Billy Bob
She's always listening
You're uh, you're Darth Vader you Darth Vader combined with Darth Maul. Yeah, that's true
Binder combined with and with dark. I'm
I'm dark Yoda. I'm dark Revan red. Yeah, I have all the I have all the powers of Rey and
Yoda combined, okay, but I stole those powers when I became dark and I get a double-bladed sword
You have you don't have one you has to it has to know crystal. No, no, so yeah
No, I have no bladed lightsaber has two kyber crystals. No the brown sabotage your silver one
I sabotage your kyber crystals cuz I'm dark you know red Yoda
Oh, who's more powerful than you are by a hundred times and can sabotage a kyber crystal using cybernetic energy
Can't sabotage a kyber crystal dark Yoda red Yoda Yoda red Yoda can do you notice how can't do that?
Do you notice how I'm not getting involved in this little spat because I'm neo and I'm not really worried about
You guys cuz I don't point time. Oh, you're neo before you came out of the matrix
Neo is his hacker name you fucking it. Oh, it's not true. Yeah, it is. Neo is the matrix now. That's the one no, okay
Well, I'm the one well you guys hear that one. All right, I said Caleb looks like a neo with that haircut
That's true. If you guys heard that the first time would have been really good. Yeah, wait say it again
Okay, you look like a neo with that haircut. Yeah. Yeah, I look like a neo neo
What sort of a neo neo
What neo neo I'm a neo lowercase in neo
Capital in neo from the Matrix. All right. Yeah. Yeah, cuz I'm actually even cooler
What if in the new Matrix movie they're like it's like the first one they're like the first three are canon
but it turns out like the real world like the like
What's it called Zion and stuff that's in another matrix even bigger matrix. Well, that's it's that'd be pretty sick
It's the eternal question
Well, I'm saying what if that was the fourth Matrix movie is that they zoomed out one more?
Yeah, and they were like, yeah, and they're like also like we promise this
No, what if you zoom out one more and it's just regular life again? Yeah. Yeah, they're like
We were just playing a game that whole time. It was video. This was Jumanji. Welcome to the jungle shit
Fuck this is yeah, Jack black is there doing black scent neo wakes up and he's Jack black
Do you guys did that movie come out?
Neo the one know the one where Jack black was doing black scent the Jumanji one. I think so. Yeah. Oh, yeah
That's a little bit trailer for that look crazy
Yeah, just a whole movie word
Jack black is doing black scent. I don't know. Yeah
Maybe that did I think you're gonna be funny. I did I think it would be funny if people stop saying a V and said black scent
Yeah, like that was the that was like the academic term. Yeah, that's how like
Yeah
SJWs. Yeah, so yeah, it's yeah. Yeah, that's it. It's a
solidarity
Bernie Sanders.
Black Sanders.
What if Bernie Sanders did the Black Sanders?
Now that'd be pretty funny.
Have you ever seen the movie Bullworth?
I've heard of it.
I know it's about.
Oh dude, sounds like a bunch of bull crap.
Yeah, it's about, so it's about a senator who was like a hippie in his teenage years
but then he became a Republican and then one day he snaps and he just doesn't speak and
like he snaps and just doesn't like talk like a normal guy he's only talking and
rapping but it's like why saying rapping is normal no no he's like everything he's
saying he's like wearing a beanie and a suit and like glasses and shit and he's
going like yeah the man said so it's dude it's the fucking weirdest thing
because then like he has like a love story with Halle Berry and stuff and like
She's like, "You know what, Bulworth? You might just be crazy, but I like you."
It's the most insane fucking thing.
Who's Bulworth? Billy Crystal?
Bulworth is...
Billy Bibbiani.
Billy Bibbiani plays Bulworth and Allie Berry in that movie.
Yeah.
Let's write a movie.
Who is it? It's Warren Beatty, I think.
Warren Beatty?
Let me look it up.
more like
Warren creepy creepy
Directed it to
He listened to enter the Wu-Tang and he was like I gotta make this movie I gotta make this movie and it's me
music by any oh morricone
Any of morricone wrote all the raps
Dude, look at the fucking poster
pull it up. Pulled that up. Oh my god. I've seen the poster he's like coming out of a guy's
mouth right? Yeah. Yeah. Oh fuck. That's honestly such a cool. He's doing sea boy pose. Don
Cheadle's in it? I forgot all about this. What year is this? Bulworth? Yeah it was in
the year Bulworth. Bulworth year? The year of Bulworth. Year of the Bulworth. The Chinese
year Bulworth? Yeah. Yeah. The zodiac on the zodiac. My Chinese zodiac sign is Bulworth.
is
though.
Woah.
Oh.
That's probably why they made it.
You tell me I was born the year of the ox.
Release date, 98.
Year of duh ox?
What's 98 year of?
Year of Cameron shut up.
What?
Heyo!
Oh, year of the tiger.
Sick.
What, uh, what are your astrological signs?
I'm a Leo.
Oh, like that.
I'm a Neo.
I'm a Cancer.
Yeah.
I'm Neo again.
Cameron. Yeah, I'm a cancer upon this podcast. Yeah. I need to be excised. I think I'm an
aries. I think I'm an aries, but I think actually mine changed because they moved it. They like
shifted it. Isn't there's a 13th zodiac sign that nobody that like no no nobody cares about.
It's called Ophiuchus or Ophiuchus and yeah they just like they realize like oh we were
wrong there's actually like it's not it's not 12 it's 13 and it's like all the all
the all the people who use like coast aren't you really like no I'm gonna I'm
gonna do a 14th one yeah it's called it's called badass playos playos all the
players are players yeah what's your birthday don't matter are you a player
you a playos. Pimpinos. Pimpinitos. Pimpinitos playos. Yeah what if we do, what if we make a new zodiac?
It's from the Pimpinitos Playos constellation. What if we make a whole new zodiac thing right now?
And it's just a pimp with a big cane? Yeah let's do it. It's the constellation.
Alright we need 12 signs. Okay. Alright so January. What? January is Cameron. I'm not born in January.
but January is Cameron. Oh that's the sign? Yeah.
The Cameron. And you were born under Cameron. So those are cool people?
Um yeah no. Yeah. You wish. Sure. As if.
No. Those are those are babies who uh yeah just babies.
Any baby. Any baby is a Cameron. Okay yeah we'll do it if you're under one year old.
We'll do an age-based Zodiac. Under one is a baby and then
One to four is a toddler. Four to twelve is a child. Thirteen to nineteen is a teenager.
Yeah. Twenty to twenty-one. Yeah. Twenty to twenty-one, that's the best days of our lives.
That's that one. So that's four. Yeah. Twenty-two to twenty-eight is uh...
Shut up. Shut up. Yeah. Twenty-nine and uh to one thousand is normal. Yeah, you're normal.
And if you're over 1000, it's old as fuck.
(laughing)
Hell yeah.
Another--
- So what's February?
- February is, so we're just doing months.
- Yeah, February, let's see.
Well, it's Valentine's Day in February, so.
- I think that's the player.
- That's the player.
- Yeah, playos.
- That's playos.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, and then what's in March?
- March is--
- In like a lion, out like a lamb.
That's what they say about March. Chameleonare. Chameleonare. Chameleonare the
color-changing lizard. Yeah. April is the fool. April is the fool. The fool.
Do you understand why? Do you guys understand why? Because I was born in
April yeah that's why I'm stupid yeah May is Cortana yeah yeah
Cortana but not from Halo just the one yeah just the one from the computer the
one in real life yeah the real life the one from Windows Live yeah the one where
you say Cortana can you play the two princes and she says I don't know what
music is yeah you have to teach me what music is yeah she says master chief we
have to defeat the Covenant there's no time for music I'm so sexy please please
fuck me the only way to defeat I play to princess I'm so hot I'm not wearing any
clothes Cortana Cortana please please play it Cortana send an email to my mom
sending a naked picture of myself to your mom damn I'm still reading the
Wikipedia for Bullworth yeah in 2013 the New York Times report reported that
Obama had in private talked longingly of going Bullworth and in reference to the
film. Shit. That's so awesome. Just Obama just rapping all the time. Hip-hop Obama. I guess at the end of or at the end of
Bullworth he pushes for single-payer really yeah huh and then he gets
assassinated there's an assassination for rapping about single-payer oh my god
that's sick dude damn I might have to watch this one yeah let's watch
Bullworth we should do all right wait so May and then June what's I think June
should stay cancer yeah yeah out of this one June's stay cancer I can't have this
one too easy I will I'm July and I'm cancer so July's I do get out of yeah
yeah what's July July July's a fireworks alive yeah awesome yeah yeah I was born
under the fireworks I was yeah you are you born on fireworks make their own
stars. That's true. Whoa. So there's actually a whole separate zodiac. There's 12 signs
within July. Yeah, there's 12 signs within. And the signs are red firework, the
firework that looks like a flower, the American flag firework, just normal
bomb, the Mickey Mouse firework, ones that wave around. The dragon one.
The dragon one from Lord of the Rings. One that spells out a word,
it doesn't matter what word. One that spells out fun. And then one that spells out fun is also,
that's a separate one. That's a separate one. And then one that doesn't go off, a dud. Until
you get close to it and then it kills your uncle. And then there's like another one probably. Yeah,
one that looks like a big genderless bathroom sign. Yeah, that's the 12 kind of firework.
Yeah, that's what people want now. So that's what July is. So July's it's separate. The July Zodiac.
It's based on what firework hit you when you were born. August is, um,
August is... No sign for August. Yeah, so you get skipped over. Yeah, no signs. September is...
Uh, school. Well, we don't want to... Nerd. It's a nerd. September is nerd.
You were born and went to school. September is da nerd. Da nerd. Da nerd. Da nerd into hood.
The Nerd in the Hood is September. October is The Nightmare Before Christmas.
So is December. December is also, because you can watch it either time.
Yeah. November is the
The Mustache.
The Native American Man.
Yeah, yeah. But it's the Italian guy who played the Native American guy in that PSA for littering.
He's the Native American man. When he cried.
Huh?
You've never seen that?
No.
There's that old ad. It's like somebody throws something out the window of a car,
and there's just like a Native American guy who sees it and looks at the camera and starts crying,
and it's like don't litter but that guy is not he's just like an italian dude oh no no it's so funny
how they huh november the the sign for november is liz warren yes yeah yeah there we go november
surprise it's so funny how she's gonna be elected in november native like how they used to just cast
like people with brown hair as native americans like a movie like a but like there are a bunch
of movies. Oh have you seen Creepshow 2? Yeah, you know like Chief Woodenhead, that part in Creepshow 2.
Yeah, in Creepshow 2, they literally, they just have a white dude in brown face. Yeah. And the whole time
he's like, "I'm gonna go to Hollywood. Do you see this hair? This is the hair that gets you
fucking famous." Yeah, it's crazy. He's like, "I hate my people. I hate all of you."
It's great dude. And I watched this movie today called Humanoids from the Deep and there's a
character who's supposed to be Native American and he's literally just a white
guy they didn't even put him in brownface they just like he just has
dark hair and they just named his character Johnny Eagle. Okay I see what
this is. The specific dude from the PSA I'm talking about he was like he was a
Native American in like every movie for some amount of time like he was the guy
and I'm the guy they gave it like like the like the Cherokee Nation or whatever
gave him like honorary membership because he did he like spent all of his
money on like activism for native people that's crazy he's kind of he's got him
it's kind of a baller that's pretty cool yeah and I think he like didn't he like
never admitted he was Italian but like somebody exposed him he's like no no I'm
native yeah what the fuck are you talking about me I'm from the fucking Spuomi
tribe yeah my people are from fucking Brooklyn all right yeah that's my tribe
yeah yeah fucking Italian guy trying to yeah the five tribes of New York City
Brooklyn the Bronx no you seen Gaudi no there's a there's a fucking scene in
Gaudi where Stacy Keach is explaining to John Travolta the five neighborhoods he
needs to control and it's just him going like the Bronx Long Island Manhattan
Queens fucking Brooklyn other one this makes the fist do we gotta watch we want
it got a watch God the first time I met you was you were walking out of Gaudi
yeah I was like I was really excited because it was like everything shitty
about a movie that I wanted yeah that's how that's what we'll watch when Patrick's
about to die. Watch Gotti. Yeah, to take it full circle. We'll unlock Gotti. Yeah.
Patrick will come back to life as Gotti. As John Travolta as Gotti. Yeah.
Do you guys watch Mindhunter? I watched the first season and like some of the
second. Do you know Bill Tench? No. I don't know. Well the actor, the actor Holt
McAleney who plays Bill Tench in Mindhunter played the Native American
kid with the hair in Creepshow 2. Damn. And that was his first like movie. Oh that
makes sense. Say yes to you know you get in a role. Yeah. Right. Yeah. Cashing in,
cash money, that's money out the door. Yeah. That's true that's that's part of
the guide to $100. You get to say you hate Native American people too. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah and they yeah that was all improv. Yeah. They were just like just say what a
a Native American would say. He's like, "I fucking hate Native Americans." Okay, I mean
we've never met one so we can't, we cannot confirm. Oh God. What movie should I watch
tonight? You should watch Gotti, dude. No, we have to wait for you to die. We just talked
about this. Yeah, we literally just established that. No, no, no, you have to wait for me
to die to watch it with me. Are you deaf, dumb, and blind? No. Are you deef? You should watch
Are you deef? You should watch Tommy by The Who.
Tom got... Deaf, dumb and blind? I don't know what The Who is.
The Who? The What?
What is this? A band for owls?
Yeah. Is that what this is?
This is a band... Incredible. They made a band for owls.
Finally.
of cool owl with like a giant beats headphones yeah all right that could be
an owl holding a beats pill yeah what are you listening to the who?
Hooty and the hoot and the owls. I'm deliriously tired I'm gonna put this
I found a pair of headphones that are an owl.
Whoa.
But I can't find an owl wearing headphones.
You're like the radio show intern who just like, you're constantly like pulling things
up to show us.
Yeah.
I found this picture.
Jamie, Jamie, pull that up.
I found this article called Celebrity Headphones a while ago and it's just about how celebrity
headphones are going to kill people.
Like celebrity endorsed headphones.
How are they going to kill people?
uh... wall on the air it's about it says like the people in a crash their cars
because they are
wearing celebrity headphones
uh...
uh... i hope i can find this but there's like they have all the pictures like
there's
pictures of like people just like she headphones like should leave for the
shop don like celebrities that is don't even have
uh...
have aren't aren't where there's photoshop and have for the shop on them
Wow, they used Photoshop?
They used Photoshop on the pictures.
Here, we used the healing power of Photoshop.
To make it look like--
To make it look like there's John Legend headphones.
I don't know if I'm gonna be able to find this,
but I don't think I can find it.
Sorry.
Okay, well while we're making things up,
I read an article yesterday
about how I'm the richest guy on the planet,
but I can't find it right now.
I learned that Caleb gave me all of his money.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That was a misprint.
No.
They misprinted that.
They didn't misprint it.
They forgot to print that.
I actually read the article
and it said that we did not misprint this.
It's already an absurd premise
because it necessitates you being able to read.
And as we already proved with you saying garbage.
I've been reading, I've been reading the whole time.
Oh, you've been reading?
What's the last book you read, Patrick?
Last book I read?
Yeah, what's the last book you read?
(laughs)
What's the last book you read?
Yeah, what's the last book you read?
Now that you mention it, the last book I read was...
- Yeah, that's what I thought.
The Lyrics to Karma Chameleon.
- No.
- For me, I read Infinite Deaths like 10 times.
- I had to read from my Latinx literature class
two years ago.
- Latinx.
Whoa.
- That's what the class was called.
- Neil asked me--
- I had to read Junot Diaz, who's canceled.
- Oh yeah, Junot Diaz, he had sex.
Yeah, what did Juno Diaz do?
I don't know, I hope it's not worse,
I hope it's not like the worst thing imaginable.
And where it's like, what the fuck did he do?
Don't care.
I'm gonna look up what the fuck did Juno Diaz do.
Did you read the brief and wondrous life of Oscar Wow?
Oscar Wow, yeah.
It's a good book.
I read excerpts from that.
Oh, damn.
I read excerpts.
Juno Diaz is a full on rapist.
Oh yeah?
Yeah.
Full on?
Full on.
Shit.
He maxed out?
Yeah. Damn. He maxed it out. Bad move.
Juno. You guys see that picture I just sent? Oh an owl wearing headphones.
Two pictures.
Yeah. Nice. This is giving me serious OVO vibes.
Thinking about an owl. He's probably listening to Drake or another OVO artist. Yeah.
Yeah. He's probably listening to freaking... He's listening to One Dance by Drake. He's listening to Owl City.
listening to an Owl City parody of Fireflies called Owls. You would not believe your bowels
if 100 owls, however many in the song, owls all said "Hoo." Came up your owls. And they ate your
freaking Tootsie Pop in one bite. Yeah. Yeah. You would not believe that shit. You would not
believe your eyes if the owl ate your tootsie pop in one bite.
Alright, that's our new parody song.
You would not believe your eyes if da owl ate your tootsie pop in one bite.
Wouldn't that suck? That's the only lyrics to the song.
It's actually, it's three, two licks and a bite.
No. Yeah, but it's only one bite. Two licks and a bite, but he eats the whole thing in one bite.
A lick is part of a bite.
That's not true.
No, no, no, no.
Listen, we could sit here all day and argue about owl licks and bites.
Oh, wow, you found a curtain with the owl headphones on.
That's good.
Yeah, you walk into your, into, oh, is that a curtain or a shower curtain?
I thought that was a shower curtain.
I think it's a shower curtain.
Oh, cool.
You walk in your bathroom at night and you freak out because you think an owl wearing
headphones is going to kill you.
Yeah, you do it every night.
Yeah.
At my brother's house, he has a giant stuffed panda
that just sits on the couch in the room
that I like sleep in and I go in there
and it's totally dark and I fuck it in the ass, yeah.
That's why I have cotton dick.
- You wake up every morning and you're like,
oh, not again.
- Yeah, God, he tricked me.
He seduced me again.
- Yeah.
- We should, when we get back to Boston,
we should start flipping houses
yeah yeah yeah buying houses
taking and turning them upside down and being like isn't that
kinda cool
take everything out
put in nuts oh shit we flipped the house we done we gone done flipped the house
we gone done flipped da house
some cool owl merch
yeah this is classic hip hop lullabies
on title
and you guys know what's on titles title still hip-hop and the liberal arts
and what school
temple university all my god as that's fucking rock under it under it it's all
o_v_o_ shit
that's all of the ocean
i have my o_v_o_ shit
dude i would love to go to temple university to take hip-hop and the
literal art literal the literal parts of the carol i can't i have a literal arts
degree. Yeah. That's what art students be saying. Art students be saying. They say
I want. Hey let me get a large coffee literally. Yeah. Yeah. And also can you put
the gay pink sprinkles on it. Yeah. Can you make, can you just give me a regular
coffee but make it extremely pink? Make it literally. Can you give me a literal coffee right now?
I can't right now. That's what the millennial barista says back. All
baristas are millennials. And then the millennial gets the coffee and drinks it
and goes, "Ouch, I burned my tongue
"'cause I drank this before it was cool."
- Yeah, I'm gonna need it.
- And now I'm going to sue you.
- Yeah.
- You're a small business owner.
- Yeah, I'm gonna sue you.
- Starbucks.
- I'm gonna buy $500 worth of coffee and tip you one penny.
That's what millennials say at restaurants.
- Yeah, and then the business owner says,
"Sir, that's not necessary."
And they say, "Sir?
"Did you just call me sir?"
- Did you mean to say y'all?
- Yeah, did you?
Yeah.
I'm sorry, are you non-binary? No. But...
No. But you didn't know that.
Millennials fucking suck so bad, dude. But you know what's worse?
Millennials are like... Generation M.
Yeah, first. Which is a new generation that I just imagined.
Motherfucking piece of shit. So what are the traits of Generation M?
Generation M is a new species. It's mutants.
It's mutant species and they are allergic to sunlight and they -
They have the legs of an insect.
Yeah, they have insect legs. This is generation M.
Allergic to sunlight, insect legs, they eat human eggs and they -
and they -
They have a proboscis.
Yeah, and they hate when you misgender them.
Yeah.
And that's generation M.
Moomers.
The moomers.
moomers yeah yeah and under the full moon you don't even want to know they move
under the full they move mooing at the moon they move it Caleb the owl that's
pretty cool that is I will put that up with the episode I did save that picture
that's very that's cute it's very me it's very yeah it's very gay kind of
like in a subdued kind of way I he has four fingers he is wearing is those jean
are those jorts? Yeah he's wearing jean shorts. Yeah. I've been doing, I've been looking up our
names and then the owl. That's pretty cool have you found anything else? Do Deadpool the owl. Yeah.
Oh okay. Do owl Deadpool. Do um, cool guy. Oh yeah. Deadpool the owl comes up? Show me. Yeah.
look at this oh there's so many different pictures yeah okay now do Deadpool naked
Deadpool make it penis dude Deadpool the penis Deadpool naked all right now I
mean he's got penis so that's search query fuck Deadpool suck Deadpool the
fucker fucker sucka let's see sexy motherfucker okay
Deadpool is the scamp of all time Deadpool is an utter rascal to me
Deadpool look wait let's expect him to be a normal like a dub maybe even a
villain yeah and then he comes in and he says chimichangas and you're like now
hold on and then he says I have swords yeah and he says yeah I wrote in Gary
Johnson in the 2016 election yeah yeah I'm kind of weird like that let's write
oh shit dude damn that's tight this is some cool shit
that it's Deadpool with a big bazooka and inside the bazooka well I guess I don't
really yeah inside the bazooka is Justin Bieber but they meant to put it on the
scope that but it but it looks like he's shooting the projectile is Justin Bieber
And it's kind of like a shitty like speed paint of Justin Bieber.
Uh-oh, someone's having an emergency.
They're going to get Justin Bieber.
Classic LA, yeah.
They're going to save Justin Bieber right now from Deadpool.
Justin Bieber has a giant Deadpool shaped hole in him.
We have to take him to Cedar Sinai.
Yeah, we have to take him to Rich People Hospital.
Sorry to get political, but I had to.
And then they wheel him into the emergency room and then like the nurses prep him
and they're like, "We have to do surgery right now."
and then they bring him into the operating room.
And right as he's going under,
the doctor pulls down his surgeon mask
to reveal that it's Deadpool actually operating on him.
- And he looks at the camera and says--
- I know that I'm a movie.
- And he says, "This movie just got crazy."
- Yeah.
- This is the most insane movie.
- You thought this was a Bieber movie?
This is a Deadpool movie, buddy.
It'd be funny to see--
- You thought this was Justin Bieber,
Never Shout Never, whatever that fucking movie was called.
But it's the damn Deadpool 3.
Have you guys seen this video?
It would be funny to see...
Let's check this out.
Oh, okay.
Mickey Mouse and Deadpool.
Oh, it's Mugen.
Dude, I loved watching Mugen videos in like middle school.
I think I got...
I like destroyed my family computer just getting Mugen's mods.
It's fucking sick, dude.
I never played it because I just like I wasn't I was afraid to just download games and shit
Yeah on the family computer, but like yeah, I would watch videos all the time be like damn homer simpson combo
This is badass. Wait. What if homer simpson actually was a fighter instead of what about homer simpson versus baracka?
Whoa, yeah, baracka barack obama. No, that'd be kind of funny. I didn't think that the rock obama
Now that's some fuck up shit. Yeah
The very thought of that is making my brain hurt.
It'd be funny-
It's giving me a mind-
-grain.
Jesus.
Oh.
Justin Bieber-
I just-
They found out Deadpool was the doctor!
They renounced the police.
It's a SWAT team headed to the hospital to try to kill Deadpool.
Guess what, bitches? He's invincible.
Yeah.
You'll never kill him.
He can regenerate.
He can never die.
It'd be funny to have a Deadpool mo-
Like, to have the Deadpool movie, but like, from a different camera angle.
So he's just like, looking into the distance and being like,
You guys are my biggest fans just like not looking at the camera.
Just like looking in the wrong direction. Deadpool is the Jim Halpert of
the Marvel movies. He keeps making Jim face to the camera. He keeps
pranking. He keeps fucking sucking Pam.
Yeah. The Deadpool version of Pam? Yeah you guessed it, Pam Anderson, the biggest
boobed bitch in the world. Right there. She's sucking his burnt
dick. Yeah. He goes, "I'm about to chimichanga
on you Pam Pam Margera Pammer I thought you said ma'am ma'am Margera
bimbofied bimmer is ma'am Margera yeah here's another good moogin fight
Marge BAM era the annoying orange no whoa spongebob squarepants versus baby being
you
mod
I tried to make my own Mugen characters in the sixth grade.
It's like a fighting game that you can like mod and just put in whatever characters you
want.
Like it's like open source and shit.
So we could put- And people would just make mods of it.
Us three.
We could, if somebody wanted to, they could put us in Mugen.
Okay, I'll do it.
Do it.
Okay.
Fine.
What would you guys special move, uh, Patrick?
What would you guys special- I'd probably, I'd have the same moveset as Deadpool, but
also- But also a hundred bucks.
Yeah.
A hundred dollars.
Yeah, I'd be like rich Deadpool. Yeah, cuz Deadpool notoriously zero money you
Patrick's would be eating a hamburger
Cameron's would be being on the computer mine would be I don't go on the computer mine would be karate Jackie
I don't go on the computer. I'm gonna be
I would summon Jackie Chan and Bruce Lee and first my special would be that I kill both of them with my hands and then I
Also, and then I once I do that then I use my special ability
They also have intros for the for the characters you're forgetting that my intro my intro I run in and I say
Watch out here. I come my intro. I said, but and I do flip my intro and then I do another flip
I do a backflip a little bit and then I reverse time and I go back to the dinosaurs
And I bring back a t-rex to kill and I kill the other but then I just make the t-rex my pet
And I'm gonna teach him try do it like meet the Robinsons. I do the flip
My intro is that Cameron does all that and then I come out and I fuck him in the ass
Yeah, you do all of that but then I'm actually the character
And I just fucking I just you drain me with your fucking but
Is a chain Patrick high fives me and but Patrick does that a he go face?
Yeah, just waiting for it. You get huge muscles like it's like
But sex is like your spinach your Popeye spinach like crack open your ass
And then get huge
Lois Griffin vs. Garfield the cat and Tom Tom cat make them fuck
Stop this is so distracting. Okay. Why did God show up? I don't know tweet of God
Lois first tweet of God
Tweet it dude tweet of God here tweet of God's gonna work on Bojack Horseman. Really? No, I just made no years
Oh, he's going to yeah, damn. I just made that up. But I guess it's I'm actually pretty smart cuz it was whoa
It turned out to be true who runs tweet of God was he ever doxxed. Oh, he was yeah
It was uh, it wasn't that he was doxxed. It was that uh,
He was a writer on the Daily Show
That's so funny. Yeah, he wrote that he got that fucking
He that Broadway play he already like
He had a Broadway play connections. Yeah, yeah
He had a Broadway play tweet of God and it was a starring Jim Parsons. What the heck?
yeah was it called it was called tweet of God I don't hold on that's actually kind
of ironic because Jim Parsons was the lead in one of the one of the greatest
pieces of atheist media of all time the Bing Bang Theory yeah David Javerbaum
David Javerbaum? What the fuck? Probably Javerbaum? No it is Javerbaum for sure
No, it's Javen Jaegerbaum.
That's a cool-ass fucking guy.
Yeah.
John Jack Daniels.
John Daquiri.
Michael Beer.
[laughter]
'Sup, I'm Mike Beer.
Oh, shit. He, yeah, David Javerbaum, Javerbaum or whatever,
created Disjointed.
Oh.
That fucking Kathy Bates show on Netflix.
Awesome.
About how, like, what if an old white lady had weed?
Yeah.
That is insane to me.
Old white people be smoking weed.
Yeah.
Her character in that movie where she breaks that guy's legs probably could have used a little weed.
What's that movie called? Agony?
I don't know.
What?
The Kathy Bates movie where she's crazy and takes the author.
Misery?
Misery. Agony.
Is that Kathy Bates?
Yeah.
That's like her biggest role.
I haven't seen it.
That's Stephen King.
Yeah.
She's the queen though.
Stephen Queen.
Now that would be pretty funny.
What about a freaking girl version of Stephen Queen, Stephen King named Stephen Queen and
instead of it, the book's called Her.
Whoa.
And it stars Joaquin Phoenix even though it's a book.
Instead of the stand, it's called the Sit While You Pee.
Sometimes I sit while I pee, every once in a while.
I mean yeah it's comfortable.
I learned that my dad sits while he pees.
One time when I was in the bathroom and I was like brushing my teeth and he just like
fell asleep on the couch I guess and then just like deliriously walked in while I was
brushing my teeth and started sitting down and peeing right in front of me and then just
did not notice I was there because he was just like sleepwalking essentially.
And then the next day I was like, "Dad, do you sit to pee?"
he was like have you been watching me? I had to explain like no no you robot walked
into the bathroom you did the robot into the bathroom and he sat down and
deposited oil. It's just generally I say when I pee when I'm at work because I
can spend more time away from being at work. Oh yeah me too. I go to the bathroom at work all the time I just
fart into the toilet and just his brows. I don't do anything. I just read. Yeah.
Yeah. Well you guys have like office jobs or whatever. I have fucking, I got a call
from my fucking manager the other day. Whoa. In the bathroom. You got a call? Oh okay.
You should have said that immediately. I got a call from him while I left, I was at the register and I left and
then I went to go take a shit. I guess I was gone for too long because he called
me damn I think I've talked about this already did you know I've never heard
this before no I didn't answer I walked upstairs and looked at him and I was
like pants down yeah I was busy a trail of shit is this what you wanted huge
boner and a piece of toilet paper plot it fucking stuck to the tip of your
penis with cum yes yeah you called damn I just used my one New York Times article
a month to read David J ver bomb an act of God adapts tweets to Broadway yeah
they just read tweet imagine they just do yeah it's Jim Parsons just being like
"Retweet this shit, I'm giving up for Lent."
Nice.
Let's do a tweet from Tweet of God right now.
I actually have the password to the account.
Let's log in.
All right, we'll each do one.
Okay.
Mine is, "I watched Adam and Eve have sex.
Yeah, I said it."
That's the end of it?
Yeah.
No, I could do more.
Oh, okay.
If you want to.
"I watched Adam and Eve have sex.
Yeah, I said it.
And I jacked off. And I jacked off and Adam jacked off. Yeah, I said it. Yeah, I said it. We jacked off.
Yeah, so what?
God out.
All right, your turn.
My turn? Yeah.
Okay, mine is
customer, I'd like a, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
- Fenty Frappamocchino?
- A Fenty Frappamocchino.
- Frappagirlachino?
- Okay, no wait, I've got one.
Okay, I've got one.
Please somebody help me budget this.
My family is starving and then has some money amounts
next to some things.
And there might be something funny in like the amounts,
but I haven't thought of that yet.
- It could be like, like food, utilities,
- Like a million dollars for food and utilities
and then like nothing for anything else.
And it's like, what is this guy?
- Is like a million dollars.
- Adams ribs cost like a million dollars.
It's like, how's that rib cost so much?
Oh, because it's a woman.
And because they love to spend money.
- Yeah, women are the most expensive kind of person.
- It says that all at the bottom.
Women are the most expensive kind of person.
Retweet if you agree.
- Yeah, tweet of God.
- God out.
- Yeah, you could also be like,
Jesus dot dot dot, I'm not da fada.
okay yeah yeah yeah yeah and then a gif of someone doing a backflip yeah I'm not
defaulter all right Pat what's yours my tweet of God yeah is anybody who likes
nickelback is going to hell yeah nice the owl photo popped up right next to
your face which owl wearing headphones now wearing headphones you know the owl
dowel come on yeah tweet I'm down tweet of God about tweet of owl whoo-hoo
allies that shit's funny but then to we've got to be like yeah I'm doing I'm
The only person I didn't create? Donald Trump. Yeah. Yeah, there we go.
You know who created him? The orange devil. Yeah, you have the devil and
you have the orange devil who is only in charge of Donald Trump. Yeah. Even the
devil doesn't like Donald Trump. Yeah, I was hanging out with the devil
earlier. Yeah, we were just talking about how fucked up stuff is, this
hell world. He said, "I thought I lived in a hell world." Yeah. That's what
tweet of God did with the devil yeah we should do tweet of the devil and and
just reply to all of his all of tweet of God's tweets with I'm gonna get you
that's a good idea I'm gonna get you me emoji yeah I'm gonna freaking I'm gonna
freaking poop on you you're gonna suck huh hey I'm gonna poop on you yeah God
would be so pissed God would flip out yeah I'm gonna poop on you God would be
so mad if this went viral that's why the flood happened because he goes the devil
was was pooped on God and God got really angry and destroyed the world yeah yeah
That's why God did Hurricane Katrina.
Yeah, because the, yeah.
Alright, we did over an hour.
Congratulations for being a Patreon.
Yeah, let's do some shoutouts on here.
We already did shoutouts last, oh we have a new person.
Also, well this will come out, this comes out before the other one.
Oh yeah, this comes out today.
So the other one we missed.
Oh wait, there's a new, Simon, thanks for becoming a Patreon, Simon.
But that's the but that's the new one won't be on the the one on Monday
But you will be on this one. So congrats buddy and all the other new ones will be on Monday. Yeah, yeah, not today
Okay. Okay. So Caleb out
Caleb the owl Kate no Caleb the owl killed
Okay, you say out so you can't say anything else right you have to put the mic down
So Pat, let's talk about how much we hate Caleb now now that he can't say yeah
Caleb is always looking like a damn owl.
Yeah, and he always says "who?"
He's like, "uh, who?"
He's crying right now.
Sometimes like...
Yeah, he's crying.
Sorry, you can't talk.
Shut up, shut up.
You can't talk.
I can't touch it.
No, Caleb out.
You can't talk.
No, you're not allowed to talk at all.
I can't touch it.
Caleb is so gay that sometimes I worry he might be the victim of...
Sometimes you worry that you'll have sex with me?
Yeah.
That's how gay I am?
Because you're gay?
Yeah.
Caleb out.
That's not true.
That's also...
Stop hitting the microphone on the floor.
Caleb out.
Stop.
stop talking
stop hitting the microphone right now
that's not how that work
it's not a good
camera out and i think i have a lot of it
you can see a little bit in caleb in the area
and i think they look at the telepathic alkyl and no reverses patrick al
canada and i think i have no idea if you can read that again
caleb sex
(laughing)
- Caleb Sex now.
- Caleb Sex, Angelina Jolie, one million trillion.
Caleb out.
Whole podcast out.
Caleb Gay.
- Caleb Gay.