You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content!
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately!
[Laughter]
Wow. Wow. Okay.
Patrick, Patrick gone again.
You're a beautiful, beautiful Patches.
What's up?
Oh my god, beautiful. So beautiful.
The light shining on his face.
Yeah. Like a monster mask.
Yeah, basically because of where my desk is.
is yeah absolutely like an angel i look like i look like an angel from heaven no you look like
an angel from in mad max fury road when they spray this stuff on their face kind of the light is
perfectly on my mouth yeah yeah i'm going to valhalla everybody and you got that crazy machine
right in front of your mouth that looks like maybe some kind of diesel punk contraption maybe that's
what i thought this was when you guys told me to buy this microphone when we were first starting
out I was like I want me to get a diesel pump rich like contraption to just like
they want me to yell at that it's weird it's weird you look so beautiful to me
right now I can't explain it you look like an extra in like a Lin-Manuel
Miranda musical you look like a like a white Puerto Rican from the Bronx yeah
the one they put like like two rows away
all right yeah we're further away yeah real Puerto Rican people so we got this
Italian guy to wear a tank top and then there's a bunch of vulture articles about you yeah
yeah and you're like I don't know I made 30 bucks and then on the blu-ray release
they CGI like a potted plant in front of your face so no one can tell
making my sauce completely off topic changing the cultural the culture
direction of it asking where's the pasta crazy living in the Heights when you're
Irish yeah what's a crazy about why is he rapping in the background there's
already a rap going on in the foreground you're very faintly like picking up on
his laugh yeah he's love you because I'm what this is a fitting theme yeah I had
to be mobile and white yeah I had to I had to buy a toilet seat because my
gigantic ass destroyed my my toilet seat and walking I will say walking around
Bushwick with a toilet seat in your hands it's like the most embarrassing
thing I've ever had to go through really every single person was everyone trying
I mean people are laughing at me. Yeah, people made me wear it on my head and they could shit in my mouth
It was like yeah, it was fucking awful dude, then they use my tongue like toilet paper. Oh
It's already in my mouth you're just wiping the shit that's already in my mouth back on your ass
It's like if you use the water from the toilet to wipe your butt, I guess
So basically, yeah, well Caleb's tongues a bidet basically, but well I can't gleek yeah, I can't
Just a bidet takes the poop water
Yeah
It's I don't think it does it's English
That would be crazy if it did that. Oh, it's you can't you can't pee and then use a bidet cuz it'll just shoot people
Fucking shit and use a bidet. It'll put shit water. No, I mean any water is not directly touching the poop is clean
I mean, you could drink it.
That's not true.
I mean, that's what, it comes from the pipes.
I don't know.
Poop literally dissolves.
It's literally the same pipes as your kitchen faucet.
So there's no reason you shouldn't be able to strain out.
When I turn on my faucet,
if I'm not seeing like some unidentified sludge,
then I'm like, something's going on with my plumbing.
Something's wrong here.
That's the water in New York, baby.
Oh yeah.
I mean, New York water.
New York water is good, baby.
What's better than this water?
You know?
Oh, it tastes so nothing.
Oh my God, it's so good.
Well, you know, I was raised on New York water
and because of that, that's why I'm so tall for Italians.
Yeah, true, yeah.
I do forget how tall you are.
Most Italians stop at like four or five
and I made it up to four nine and that's New York water,
baby, that's that extra four inches, those nutrients.
Yeah, it's got all the, it's basically vitamin water.
That's what 50 Cent likes, vitamin water.
When you said four nine for a second,
like oh is he really four nine wait
it's like anybody get to anybody's under six feet if they tell you they're any
height oh yeah I have no I have no metric for any height that's shorter than six
feet it's all shorter than me or taller than me I don't have to care I know you
don't have to carry you fucking asshole yeah that's what we're complaining about
dude I love being the noble tall guy - who doesn't lie about his height cuz a
lot of tall guys who will be like 6'2" and try and tell you they're 6'4", not me.
And I stare him down and I say, "Listen pal, you better stop lying or
I'm gonna come over there and I'm gonna stand next to you."
Why would you even start lying?
I'm gonna stand next to you and I'm gonna say, "I'm 5 feet tall! I'm only 5 feet tall!"
Yeah, you don't know that us short guys are always lying about how we're
always like, "Oh, I'm actually 5'3" when you're really 5'5". We're always just trying to...
why would you lie only four feet tall that means I can't be in trouble I'm only
four feet tall I didn't I didn't do it I'm sorry about I can't even I can't
even reach the cash register I'm only three feet tall yeah why are you
fucking lying when you're more than six feet yeah it's very funny that it's it's
It's such a weird thing to do.
It's so weird.
You already won.
You won, man.
Stop bragging.
Stop gloating.
You know?
Yeah.
You're in the end zone and you're doing the worm with your dick out.
Just fucking just be.
Well, no, you're in the wrong end zone doing it.
I mean, it's completely, you don't even have to be, you shouldn't be doing the, you know?
I don't know what I'm saying.
Yeah, you don't know football at all, it sounds like.
Yeah.
No, I think my brain just short-circuited there for a second.
I was about to explain myself and I was like, I have no idea what I'm about to say.
No, you don't get it, man.
You're like dancing on the field goal.
I don't even get it.
Yeah.
Did either of you ever play like junior sports?
Like football and shit?
I was forced to play basketball by my mom for a little bit.
Oh my God, I bet you were so shy.
I was, dude, yeah.
I did not talk to anybody else on the team.
Yeah.
But you could dunk on 'em.
I couldn't.
You could dunk, dude.
No.
Honestly, Cam, if you gave me three months of your time
and $30,000, I could teach you how to dunk.
I'm only four feet tall.
No.
gonna work on me. I'm not even allowed on a basketball field. My height that I tell
people has gone down about an inch every two years since I got a license. Yeah.
Yeah it's like it's slowly you know I went from like when I first got a
license because they didn't even measure me at the thing so I just told him I was
like 5'11" so that if anybody's like "how tall are you?" it's like it says right here 5'11" so
yeah and then every year it's just been like all right I'm 5'10" I'm 5'10" fuck I'm 5'8"
fuck me dude. It's a horrible height to be dude. Yeah you're not even you can't even like walk
around being like I'm 5'7". Yeah yeah I can't brag about being 5'7". I walk around I walk around my
house and I'm just going "hey everybody just try to measure me!" I had a friend who was the same
height as me and he would always tell people he was like yeah I'm like about
six feet tall and I was like no you're not and then one night I like I just
measured him I was like you can't leave my house until I measure you and he was
five nine on the fucking dot it is so fun even just like not even being tall
but it's lying in general about your height is very funny it's the most
easily like yes just immediately apparent yeah it's not like the dick
size we're like nobody's really gonna see your penis you know. Yeah, it's like no one
will ever see your penis. I actually have red eyes. Yeah, yeah, yeah so I'm pretty cool for that.
Yeah me walking around, "Do you guys like my dreadlocks? Should I cut them? Are they offensive? What do you think of these?"
Yeah my favorite thing is that that they lie about NBA players heights like all
the time. So there will be like a guy, there's always some, every year there's
some fucking kid in the draft who's from like either Zambia or like Eastern
Europe and they'll be and he's big he's probably seven feet tall but then all
the scouting reports would be like like day after day it'll be like one day it's
like he's reportedly 7'2" and then the next day I'll be like he's growing at a
rapid rate he's approaching 7'5" now and then by the time he's in the draft
they're like he's eight feet tall and then they measure him at the combine and
he's 6'10" yeah everybody's like what the fuck is like I just don't get it man
Yeah, well, they didn't bring the rulers actually came from America. So Columbus found tomatoes and yeah rulers
And he brought the tomatoes to Italy and rulers to a couple other places, but not everyone got it. It's what happened. Yeah
What do you guys who you guys think is winning this this year football game today?
One can be one we on England. I'm on England or we on Italy. What's up?
Probably the damn advertisers and the owners of everything.
That's a really good point.
That's a really good point that they should have me on ESPN almost every day as an analyst
to make that point.
Yeah, by my analysis the ads here are totally vapid.
Yeah, Stephen A. Smith would be like, "So Caleb, who do you think is winning the Super
Bowl this year?"
I'd be like, "Probably Doritos."
Probably Doritos and probably GoDaddy.
Yeah, we have our Marshall McLuhan representative here.
Disney Corporation I think. Yeah, probably, probably, um, yeah Mickey damn Mouse is
gonna be making a killing today if you ask me. Yeah, probably, uh, you might make a
touchdown too. Probably Acme. Honestly, like, Acme is probably gonna, probably gonna take it
this year because of all the advertisements and the products they have. Probably Pfizer!
- Kaiser.
- Yep.
(laughing)
- That's right.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- That's the end of the interview.
- Yeah, this is immediately cut.
(laughing)
- I don't know, Raytheon.
- Edgebox, something like that.
- I'm gonna go with corporation.
- Check out my podcast.
- Probably the Chum Bucket.
- Yeah.
- Probably plastered the airway this year.
- Like Doug Dimmadome, that guy.
- He was rich.
(laughing)
I wanna get like an ESPN show so bad
'cause every year they're like--
Yeah, that would be sick.
They're less and less about sports, you know?
Like there's that one with Dan Lebitard
who he just has like his old dad on there.
Dan.
His like old Cuban dad.
Lebitard.
Yeah, Dan Lebitard.
No worries, Sarah.
So he just has, he'll be like,
he'll be like watching some clip and he'll be like,
and here comes, you know, the fucking quarterback,
he's throwing a beautiful thing
and it's right in the end zone, wow, what a play,
and then his dad will just like wake up and be like,
touchdown, yeah, touchdown, another touchdown.
- What would our ESPN show be?
Probably something political, right?
- I mean, it would have to be basically like,
I mean, I'm all about the intersection
of sports and politics, you know?
- Well, basically, yeah, today the two teams
are a little bit like the Democrats and Republicans
in that I hope neither of them win.
- That's right.
(laughing)
some smarmy Bill Maher's the Bill Maher presents podcast about lists yeah yeah
just like you know like Lakers versus the Bulls well whoever wins we fucking lose
tell you that much you know who wins somehow yeah somehow like losing an
insane amount of money despite like saying like I like hating politics in
sports like yeah that's the best dude I wish it I could be a pro athlete just so
I could just focus on dribbling the ball and not have to care about all this
politics stuff that I'm super smart about you know yeah it's really true
just be easier you know why can't they have that that standard for comedians
and podcasters you know why do we have to care about politics why can't we just
Like, nobody wants LeBron to say anything
about the president, but like,
I mean, everybody's asking me, dude.
Yeah, dude.
Yeah, they're asking me to condemn--
We're getting asked every day.
It's starting again.
They're asking me to condemn the president,
they're asking me to condemn the mayor of every town.
Yeah.
It's like, did you guys get that?
There was a, did you guys get that?
There was like a DM that was going around
to like all big, to whatever my size account is,
asking you if you think Joe Biden's nice with it or not, and it was really, really funny.
I was getting very upset about that.
That's really funny.
Yeah.
I get people sending me pictures of like babies and ugly people and being like, "This is you,
I think."
Yeah, showing off.
Cool, man.
Oh, that me?
Oh, okay.
That's you, Tommy Pickles.
Oh, that's cool.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, I mean that's that's pretty much what the the human brain evolved pattern recognition for is to see a bald guy and then
Yeah
Yeah, I was looking for your barcode when I first met you brother. I was like is this that it's just a hit man
I've been I've been approaching a brand new level of bald. I met you when you had hair. Yeah, actually doesn't count
It doesn't count. I've been approaching a new level of bald where the other day on my youtube recommendations. I got I got a
a channel called bald brotherhood.
It was like, it's like a channel that's just full of guys talking about how beast it is
to be bald.
Can I tell you what, there is a bald brotherhood already and you do not.
Folks.
There's a bald brotherhood in, yeah, in prison.
There's a big bald brotherhood.
There's a bald white brotherhood.
I guess that makes sense.
A lot of it was about sneaking cigarettes and cell phones into your, into your bunk.
That is not just a Nazi thing, believe it or not.
People love sneaking cigarettes.
It's not even a prison thing.
I like smoking cigarettes.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
I think if I was in jail, I would like to become like an Elder Scrolls-style traitor, because
they apparently have those somewhere.
There's a guy who's giving out fucking Samsung Galaxies to people.
Oh, wow, that would be fun to do like a barter, to be like a-
What's that word?
Yeah.
I would want to be like a quest giver who helps you subclass.
Oh, yeah.
for any of the gangs or anything but just for like being like a spellblade or
something why haven't they done a prison RPG that's such a fucking
their character creator is nice the cast part was fine but then the race is a
little iffy yeah well they yeah the main the main quest to break out of prison
was okay but all the side quests of choose your faction got yeah I see that's not
great yeah but you can be that'd be fucking awesome you like Mass Effect in
jail you know effect I mean they can do it like in space so it's not racist it's
different aliens maybe oh yeah that's our spaceships and George Lucas already
did that with different aliens making them different races yeah you already
have those guys he already said the precedent yeah so we can do it I don't
I'm not planning on going to jail, but I'd like to like, I don't know, kind of know what it's like.
Yeah, yeah, I'm not planning on going to jail, but I'd love like a VR sort of experience.
Right, a VR experience that is fully immersive. I can't take off until my sentence is up.
Yeah, right. Yeah.
I've only ever seen Orange is the New Black as far as like jail media goes.
Yeah.
You haven't seen Shelf Tank?
It'd be pretty disappointing to go to prison and be like,
Where are all the fucking hot chicks dude? What the hell is this?
Supposed to be scissoring right now. Yeah, I've never seen Shawshank. You ever seen Shawshank? No.
I think I would do really well in one of those jails from like the old west where it's just one cell and I get
To hang out with the shadows through the bars and maybe like play poker with them or something
Oh, I would I would trick him so fast. Getting locked up in one of those jails and still joining the Aryan Brotherhood.
You just see like a chalk outline of a guy and you just some people are just yeah like way too eager like
Like a cell and the drunk tank for a night
It comes with the jail now, there's just an Aryan Brotherhood member whenever there someone's putting up a new private prison
Caleb getting pulled over for a speeding ticket and just immediately trying to
tattoo himself the second he sees the cop car.
Have you heard the bad news today?
Yeah I want to go I think if I ever commit a seriously horrible crime I will
probably do it in Sweden or some Scandinavian country where you go to jail
for 30 days for mass murder. They literally just they're already white
like white brother white you know white brotherhood they're already skinheads
in Scandinavia so you don't have to worry about that - yeah but also they get like
3d TVs in their cells and shit yeah and they can like yeah it's fucking it's
honestly like way better than my life just being like yeah no I'm guessing I'm
actually performing I'm changing in here you're just like watching like Bobby Flay
yeah that's like literally what it is dude they just like go just like you
have been sentenced to camp and you go to camp and they give you a they give you a
two-page IKEA instruction set this is a guy like holding a knife with a frowny
face
turn a toothbrush into a shiv just step by step a little stick guy you have bunk
bunk mates and there's a big celebration at the end
and there's games, yeah.
- It's really beautiful, dude.
I wish that we had that here, but I don't know.
If I ever want to kill my wife,
we'll be taking a vacation to Sweden for sure.
- Yes!
- If I would probably do a big crime in space
'cause then if they want to put me in jail,
I get to stay in space for a while.
It'd be pretty cool.
Maybe I'd like--
- That's a good point.
- Age slower or something, something like that,
so I'd come back and, or something like that
could happen with the time scale.
- Is it true that if you do a crime
in international waters it just doesn't matter at all?
- Yeah, every comedy movie I've seen
has made that point, honestly.
I have to think it's true.
- That just means that if anybody ever was like,
hey man, do you wanna randomly go
to international waters today?
Just you and me?
I'd be like, fuck no, dude, what are we doing?
- Yeah, what are we gonna have sex?
- International waters?
- No way.
- Fuck no.
- Yeah, I don't know where I would do my big crime.
I think I'd have to do it in my hometown
'cause then I could be like, you know--
A hero. Yeah, a hero.
Yeah.
I would do my patches big crime.
And I mean, just to be clear for Ed,
the big crime we're referring to,
it's all shoplifting based,
there's no violence involved.
No, not mine.
It's like public defecation.
Yeah, maybe, yeah.
Saying a bad word too loud
could be a really big crime that we're working on.
There's nothing else, nothing else is going on here.
I'd probably be like a bomb.
[Laughter]
You can't say that.
He's saying if he were.
I'm saying if I was a criminal.
If he was a criminal, which he's not.
I don't even know where to start with a bomb.
It's like a battery, right?
You gotta go to the bomb store.
What explodes in a bomb? All I see is fucking wires and screens.
That just sounds like a fucking Gameboy to me.
I don't know how to make that into a bomb.
There's still a pending lawsuit in Nintendo for that reason.
Yeah, absolutely.
Um, yeah, I don't know what makes up a bomb.
I think it's gotta be, I remember when I was in like elementary school,
this kid I hung out with, who I know now, and he's not, he's not this person he was.
But like the first time we hung out, he was like, dude, let me show you how to make a bomb.
And this is like the first time we hung out and he was showing me like-
Was it a water bottle bomb?
I don't know what it was.
He didn't make it.
He just was like, yeah.
So what you got to do is scrape the like dust off of the windows of the car.
And that and I'm like I'm like are you playing pretend I was so confused
He made no sense one of the kids in my middle school like
Blew up like the like insides of a toilet because he put a one of those like Drano bombs in there
He like in a water bottle. He just makes Drano and aluminum foil at fucking school
And yeah, and he got suspended for like one day
Yeah, that's pretty fucked. I mean it's like yeah, I think you should go to jail probably
I think he's probably in jail now most of those people are everybody who I went to middle school
It's either dead in jail or military. That's a that's a pretty those are those are the three ways that that school went. Yeah
yeah, I
there was a
gun scare in my school when I was in middle school and we had to like just stay in one room for like
Just fucking hours and it was because some like twerp saw like a brown plastic bag in like yeah
exchanged and it was very clearly just like
Like ditch weed like just being exchanged
That was always the best like the whole school locks down because there's a homeless guy with a broom three. Yeah, right
They're like it might be a secret. It might be a gun
He might be like one of those pimp games and this comes out of the might be inspector gadget
*laughter*
Yeah, just like, Inspector Gadget has to be treated like a gun no matter where he goes.
Yeah.
We don't know what's gonna come out of what part of this guy.
Yeah, I think we spotted Inspector Gadget, so just to be safe, we're locking down the entire school.
It is great that like, any middle school kid can learn that if you just like, write the word "bomb" on a sticky note,
You get to get out of classes for like the rest of the day and hang out outside. Yeah like that like it's
Yeah, I don't know if there's a good silly easy solution to that situation. Well, the solution is just don't who cares
It's literally just a school doesn't matter how many times like if you get exactly it's not like a TV station
Yeah, something that matters
If you get a call like from ISIS and you're like a principal at a school you just have to treat it like a prank
You have to be like, all right. Yeah, buddy. Go ahead
Cut my head off. Yeah, go ahead. Yeah. Yeah. Sure. See you in class later Roderick. Yeah. Yeah
Was always Roderick. Yeah
Bad kids name. Yeah, that's a naughty name Roderick Desmond. These are bad kids. Oh, it does be yeah for sure
Jasmine is definitely a bad kid's name.
Yep.
Caleb.
Caleb for sure.
Brundle.
Bad kid.
Yeah, Brundle.
Yeah, Brundle has no eyebrows.
Morgoth.
Yeah, he was always up to trouble.
Yeah, Durgan.
Yeah, Durgan for sure.
Asmodeus.
Asmodeus, you know when you meet a kid named Asmodeus, this kid's gonna be, he's gonna
be fucking smoking weed.
Oh yeah, absolutely.
That's just what it is.
- The kids named Einstein were always total nerds too.
- No dude, it's so fucking annoying.
- Oh my God, dude.
Do you guys remember the first time you met a kid named Sadie
and did you know the Beatles song, "Sexy Sadie"
when you first met someone named Sadie?
- No, I liked-- - Did it make you feel bad?
- I liked T-Pain. - T-Pain?
- Yeah, yeah.
- You met a kid named T-Pain?
- No, I didn't like the Beatles.
The Beatles I thought were for babies.
- Oh, for old people?
Yeah, I liked you.
Now, if I had met a kid named Shoudy,
maybe I would have been like,
(laughing)
damn, what's up Shoudy from the T-Pain songs?
Yeah, that would be crazy.
Yeah.
I love that.
Who is this Shoudy that they're always talking about?
They all know someone named Shoudy?
That can't be a common name, right?
It's gotta be one Shoudy they all talking about.
I remember there were the whole T-Pain rehabilitation thing
that's been going on.
Not that like, that people were just like,
he was actually like a genius.
And-- Dude, yeah.
Yeah. It sucks.
They just like, just make it--
He doesn't have that good of a voice.
Just fucking auto-tune him.
Yeah. You know?
Just like put him and Pitbull on anything
and I'll listen to it.
I don't wanna hear him at a NPR tiny desk
singing Stomp-a-Songs, you know?
Like that's fucking, that sucks.
Yeah, I would listen to Pitbull do anything at all.
Yeah, Pitbull's a man.
He's so cool.
T-Pain also has become a Twitch streamer now.
Yeah, respect to that.
Where he plays like Warzone and shit, and people watch.
He doesn't even sing anymore, he's just a streamer.
I wish every song that Kanye did with Swizz Beatz instead had Pitbull.
'Cause I fucking hate hearing Swizz Beatz go, "Ehh, put your hands in the air, whoa!"
God damn it!
That thing.
God damn!
God damn it!
He's so fucking annoying, and I would love to hear Pitbull just go, "Dale!" and "Woo!"
Pitbull making Scooby Doo noises on every song, dude.
It fucking rules.
I love him, dude.
He just does shit like that.
You're like, I don't know if--
I don't want to be racist, but that is awesome.
Yeah, we don't really have that kind of guy anymore,
I feel like.
No.
Like a rapper who only does J-Lo songs and Imagine Dragons
features.
We don't have that guy anymore.
DJ Khaled's gone now.
Nobody cares about him.
True.
I saw him.
I went to the Overwatch finals at the Barclays Center a few years ago, which is one of the
most...
I didn't even know...
One of my favorite things to have said on a podcast that people listen to.
But when I was there, it was just DJ Khaled was there.
At Overwatch finals?
Yeah, he played there and it was so funny because he's like, "Yo, what's up Overwatch fans?"
He doesn't know anything about it, clearly.
(laughing)
Yeah.
Just like, but like, when you're listening to him,
I would never have imagined seeing DJ Khaled live.
Like maybe at a music festival I would have seen him,
but I really don't think so.
But like, yeah, obviously he's an excellent DJ.
Like all the music was sick and like,
then like he starts doing his own stuff
and he's like just yelling over his own music.
Like he really does do that.
Like I don't wanna be like a fucking retread
of like 2014 people complaining about DJ Khaled,
but it's really just like a good song
and him going, "Oh yeah, this is awesome!
We the best!"
And you're just like, "Come on, man."
- He probably thought Overwatch was a guy
and it was his birthday.
- Yeah. (laughs)
- And he was like,
"I'm going to do Overwatch's birthday party."
- At one point he said, "Happy quinceanera, Overwatch!"
(laughs)
- My favorite guy-- - "You're a beautiful girl!"
- My favorite guy since moving to New York is Funk Flex,
'cause the fucking aux cable in my car died,
so now I have to listen to Hot 97 all the time.
And he will play a song,
He'll play 30 seconds of a song that you like, and 25 seconds of it is him going
"Only in New York!"
And then dropping a bomb sound effect that like fades out slowly for the rest of the song.
And he'll play like, he'll play like, like Cascada.
It'll be like, every time we touch by Cascada, and the entire time he's like
"None of you motherfuckers know this! This is my shit! New York!"
This is, this is going to the bathroom!
This is riding the subway!
This is graffiti!
- Yeah.
- And you're just like, dude, this is like way better than any song.
Just put him on every song, dude.
- I was listening to the radio on the Uber today and, um,
and "Hot In Here" came on, which I hadn't heard in like a long time.
And it never really struck me how funny it is that like in the chorus,
he like does it, it's getting hot in here,
so take off all your clothes and then a girl's voice going like,
"It's so hot in here, I'm gonna take off my clothes!"
She says, "I am getting so hot, I'm gonna take my clothes off."
Yeah.
I don't, I, I, how I, how you would know besides almost everything else I say and do that I'm
a giant loser is that I first heard that song through Weird Al.
It's so rotten here.
That's like a newer one, right?
No, it was from Poodle Hat.
Back in the day.
Oh that's... Back in the day.
Damn, it's not even golden era Yankovic.
No, it's like bottom of the barrel, like, Yankovic just like trying to figure out
how do I stay relevant.
Oh yeah, that was when he dropped the glasses and grew out his hair.
Yes.
And he looked like a dog.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, he looked like a golden retriever.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that was great dude.
And he just started doing like just songs that nobody had even like really heard.
Yeah, well it's funny to like hear him do like songs from like 1983 on like an album that came out in
2007. Yeah, exactly. Like I know you really wanted to get around to to uh uh like Tainted Glove,
you know. I'm glad you made it to this one. I think it's just I think it got more and more
expensive to get the rights to do this parody. You should be able you should be able to pay
Weird Al to do a parody of your song. You should, yeah. Yeah. Wow. That would be great.
People trying to make it on SoundCloud or Bandcamp could like, you know, pay him some money.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Here's some like, like a Danish 13 year old is like,
yeah, so I sort of drone about fucking, fucking my teacher for an hour. Can you parody this somehow?
Yeah. Yeah. I feel bad for him now, man. He's doing like, he does like really old songs or
he'll do, he'll do like a parody of the Aqua Teen Hunger Force theme. And then it's like,
Just fucking just even just stick to start doing the oldies maybe yeah start hitting Elvis. Yeah
I think he'd kill that this guy Elvis is begging to be parodied. Yeah, absolutely
There's like a freak he died on the damn. He really does. He does look awful. He looks weird
He doesn't look weird as hell. He has a weird looking. I mean like beautiful for sure. I'd kiss him
Well the but it is funny that Elvis like
He dressed like that for years and years and women were like, "That's the most sexual guy who's ever lived."
Yeah.
Like, if I could fuck one person, I would fuck that magician right there.
Yeah, he looks like, he looks, yeah, I mean, he literally looks like, uh, like, uh, uh, like a Christian, like some sort of like Christian sweet boy.
Yeah.
And they put like, they put him in like, it's weird. I don't know how to describe it. It's like some sort of like angel.
He's dressed like a fucking ring bearer and like every woman in the 60s was like,
"I have to suck his cock." It's like, "Whatever, I'll give up anything to suck that guy's cock."
Yeah. And they did.
And they did.
This guy Elvis, I mean, he went to jail. Should have stayed there, as far as I'm concerned.
Yeah, he could have joined the Aryan Brotherhood also.
No, no. That's not what I'm saying.
They wouldn't do these. What he's got? He's got diamonds.
I don't know if he was Italian. He was something wrong though. Let's find out.
What was Elvis?
He might have just been a white guy. No way to know really.
White guy, black comic. That was him.
Chris D'Elia style.
German, Scottish, Scottish and French. Yeah, he's just some like European thing.
He's just some fucked up thing.
Dude, I hate Elvis! He's just some fucking thing.
Weird thing.
He's like a weird thing as a round dancing.
I remember my grandma had, when I was growing up, she had like the newspaper from the day
that Elvis died.
Okay.
And she was like, "Here, I'm gonna give this to you when I die because one day this will
be worth a lot of money."
And I was like, "I think that might be the most kept newspaper of all time."
I would guess there's 30 million other people who are doing this same thing.
This will never be worth any money to.
Yeah.
She also kept beanie babies though, so maybe she wasn't the best judge of, yeah, yeah,
she kept beanie babies, kept the tags on, had them in like little cases and shit.
Wasn't there a thing about people making bank off that or no?
Or was that like just a thing people wanted to do?
In '96 maybe.
But like, well, beanie babies did the most genius thing ever, which is they would sell
the Beanie Babies for like 10, 15 bucks each or whatever and then in the catalog
they had a it would say under the Beanie Baby would say projected 20-year price
and then they would just make up a number. Did they really do that? Yeah, so you would like
look through the catalog of Beanie Babies and it would be like this one is $15
projected price in 20 years $20 million. What? Are you serious? Yeah, I had one when I was growing up.
I had Beanie Babies, I didn't know that they had a projected price. And people were so stupid that they would
They would just like buy,
they would be like, yeah, sure.
Wow. That's gonna be a
really solid investment. We should do that
with episodes of the show.
We should be like-- That would be a good idea.
We should project values.
Yeah. For these episodes.
Yeah. You're gonna wanna--
Yeah, so you'll wanna buy this Patreon,
'cause right now--
'Cause next month we're making it $1,000 a month.
(laughing)
Yeah, exactly.
That's gonna be really expensive.
I mean, you'll still have to pay that,
but you will get one month at the $5 price.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, I guess there's no way to do that
with a subscription model.
- But I feel like there was so many scams like that
in the 90s that you just can't do anymore.
Nowadays, every scam I hear about is like Nexium,
like some fucking sex trafficking slave thing.
- Right, that's all that's left.
- What happened to the good old, just like, you know,
like Cutco, you know?
Like what happened to that shit?
- Well, 'cause sex trafficking is the only one
you can still get away with, I think,
'cause everyone loves it.
(laughing)
- It's the only one that they haven't cracked down on yet.
I guess that's true.
Yeah, they crack down on beanie babies before cheating happens.
Yeah, they're like, "Oh, you don't fuck 'em, do you?"
"No." "Alright, well, I guess we'll get rid of these."
"No."
How much sex trafficking do you think is actually happening?
A lot.
At least a thousand.
I think a lot.
I think a huge amount, probably.
Yeah, I think a giant amount.
Probably not.
I think a very large amount.
I think too much to fathom.
I'll play devil's advocate.
Nah.
Yeah.
Yeah, every time someone comes back from a Walmart. They're like I was I was so close to getting sex traffic there
well, I mean
Yeah
the one thing where they like see like yeah like a
Mexican man's like van that he uses to paint people's houses and there has to be a thousand I was here right now
He asked me for directions. I'm gonna get sex trafficked. Mm-hmm and always the people who are about that
But I'm also I'm sure that the amount that is actually going on would would make me would make me cry always
Also the people, you're so emotional.
Make me happy cry.
Always when people say that story of like I was so close to getting sex trafficked you like kind of like look at them and you're
like, no you weren't.
[Laughter]
No, I don't think so.
No.
Can he say that?
I don't think you're fetching a high price over there on that market at the Walmart kidnapping thing.
It's just true, man.
Oh, come on, Cam.
I'm okay with that.
Come on, Cam.
Oh.
Dude, I've been wanting to go to a fucking...
I've been wanting to go to a theme park so badly.
Dude, yes. I've not been to one in like...
I don't know that I've ever been to a...
A long time.
A theme park. What?
Would you count that as different than an amusement park?
No. Shut up.
I don't know. I've only been to...
Canobie Lake Park and Story Land.
Yeah, those are both theme parks.
Yeah, the theme is stories in one,
and the theme is the lake in the other.
I've never been to like Six Flags or anything though.
Oh, the theme in that is Six Flags.
I've been wanting to go recently, so that--
There's like a few kinds of Six Flags.
The other day--
I don't think there's any Six Flags near me.
Oh, yeah, I don't think so actually.
I actually don't know.
Great Adventure was near me,
so that was the one that people would go to.
The other day I looked at like how much
a five day trip to Disney World would cost.
Yeah, how much?
I looked at it, well I'm not gonna tell you
because of what I'm about to say.
I looked at it and I was like, that's a lot of money.
And then I looked at my bank account
and it was almost the exact amount of money I had.
(laughing)
And I was like--
Just like turning around slowly and seeing,
seeing if, like with Jana, it's just like,
she's like right behind you.
Yeah.
Just also.
Yeah, yeah.
Seeing you with, with your bank account
on one monitor zoomed in completely.
She gets some, she gets some ding on her phone
from like our shared bank account.
You are overdrafted $3.
You just text her like shipping spelled wrong.
Dude, I just think it would be...
She has parental locks on Caleb's computer that he can't view any price that's over $10.
It just doesn't work.
It blocks out that part of the page like ad block.
Yeah, she has a one digit password on every device I have and I can't figure it out.
It's really tough.
But dude, like, just like one adult trip to like Universal.
Yeah, I know.
It's so much fun, dude.
I'm gonna go, dude. I'm gonna do it.
Because I've been, yeah, I feel like, I feel like there's,
I've reached a point in my life again where like, I would, I would have a really good time.
Yeah, I'm gonna go. I'm gonna get kicked out within 15 minutes for talking too hard to join the Sith.
No, no, no, I'm, I'm gonna, I will kill my master. I will kill him right now.
Why are you bringing Darth Vader here if you don't want to recruit people for the Sith?
That's all I'm fucking saying dude. Mm-hmm. I just would like I would just like I hate my parents I
Would just like fucking I would buy the like pass I would get the like
Absolutely nuts. Yes. I
Chair I would in every fucking line right on everything dude. I would cut people. Yeah, I would
Menace, oh, yeah
Yeah
Disney's history
Just fucking sitting there just fucking ruining just a monster. Yeah. Oh my god. I would have so hard be so much fun
I'm just like one of the people just yeah
Voices back at them for no reason just overhearing someone go like oh the line so long and I scope
Like there is no other point in our lives where we will interact I'm not gonna even gonna go on the rides
I'm just gonna go around being rude to
into I would try to I would just try to like turn the rest of the line around
one person so I maybe somebody the other line so I'll be like this guy thinks the
lines long we hate this fucking guy I was all cut up this guy just farted
everywhere oh my god oh I'm sorry I was like no I can't smell anything oh my god
dog did you forget to wear your depends again pick one person one family at
Disney World and just ruin their trip. It's like Cape Fear but it's just like for no reason
it's just ruining their life. Yeah, you have binoculars and blow darts in your bags. I
would be, I would get on the, I would, as I'm getting on the roller coaster I walk over
to the like teenage attendant I whisper in his ear, the guy behind me in line I saw an
AK and a shirt. You get to go on the roller coaster just you. True. Nobody else screaming
in your ear the whole time. Or you show up early and you get on when they test all
the rides and make sure they don't kill anybody. Yeah. Oh baby. That might be
fucking sick. Because they make them go extra fast. Yeah they do. Yeah they do a stress test like a
computer. You already look like a crash test dummy Caleb. Okay alright. Okay man. Yeah I mean well
Pat you'd show up and they just they would just grab you and take you to the kitchen. You're not tall enough to ride the ride. No you didn't.
like I got a few of those ready to go. You're crying. What are you gonna say?
But dude I would be I mean the water rides I'd bring in change of clothes man
fuck I'm getting wet sure yeah yeah that's right I'm going in my bikini I'm
not I'm not caught dead getting wet on one ride and then going into one of
those indoor rides it's all cold I'm freezing my ass off yeah I'm changing
right in the middle of the fucking castle I'm bringing a white fucking Colonel
Sanders suit and I would love to hide in one of the rides like go on like splash
mountain yeah and then just like hide with one of the like I don't know
there's like probably a bear playing a banjo and just hiding there and then
just when the people come by yeah just be a be a guy that'd be cool did you
hear about that guy who died because he went in he was on the log flume and he
got all wet and then he went into the hall of electricity yeah
That's why you always have to bring a change of clothes.
I would wear a white suit and then I would just ride the haunted house like one over
and over again and then just keep like pissing myself just bright yellow all over my suit
and then walking out.
Change suits, change seats every time.
Not that scary really.
It's really not that scary.
See I'm going to get back in line.
More and more piss every time I come out of the fucking thing.
Shit in my pants now.
It's really not that scary though.
I would bring like a dove and I would make it fly out as I was getting out of the roller
coaster.
So, it would look like I would like walk in slow motion.
I was getting out.
True.
It would be pretty cool.
I would try, I would go on the, every ride I go on, there's like a photo in it.
I'd be trying to get everybody to do the dab.
I'd be like, "Let's dab at the photo, guys."
Yeah.
Yeah, that'd be really cool.
Yeah, and then I'd make one of them buy it for me.
Like, "Hey, can I have $50?"
Yeah.
"Wait, can you just get the..."
It was my idea so I shouldn't have to pay for it.
I think the world... so people... I think you should be allowed to show your balls and your
boobs or whatever on those cameras but when people go there and they get... they take like a sign that
has like a political message on it like... they'll have like a sign that says like...
Yeah, there should be an executive seat.
It says like "Free Hong Kong" at like the top of fucking the mountain machine ride and then
they get off and it's like... like 25 people are gonna see that man.
Like nobody's like... like you're not doing this in like an Indian...
Let's go over there and watch other people's pictures for a while.
That's... that's awful.
It's just so cool, man.
That is so depressing.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
I mean, I would love some... as somebody who does one of those, like, those prank photos
on there where they, like, glue pieces down to a chessboard or something, I would love
to see that chessboard fly up and decapitate them.
Oh, that'd be sick.
Oh, 100%.
Yeah, well, you should... they should design a ride that specifically, if you bring a prop
onto it, it will kill you.
It vaporizes you.
Yeah, 100%.
It will, they set it up so that if you have anything in your hands, you're gonna die.
Yeah. Yeah, I mean, the idea of somebody holding a political message is like so depressing.
But the idea of just imagining someone like having like a six seasons and a movie sign.
That's what I'm picturing right now.
That's even better.
That's the guy in my head.
That guy's cooler though because at least he's not going to Disney World like, "Man, I'm going
to make such a difference by riding these rides right now, by having the time of my life.
This is going to be so awesome."
Yeah.
Yeah, I would hold up a sign that says, "This ride is awesome.
I'm having so much fun."
Yeah.
See, that should be fine.
Yes.
Yeah.
I'd be holding up a sign that would say, "Hey, spaghetti meatball."
You know?
Yeah.
That'd be pretty good.
I was so pissed off when I tried to get on one of those loop-the-loop roller coasters
and they made me leave my bucket of pee.
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
Honestly, it's the same principle.
And nothing is pouring out.
Come on, let me on the drop tower with my bucket, please.
Come on, dude.
It'll be fine.
I need this bucket.
I need it. It's my helmet.
No, I won't put it on right now.
There's a ride at
Bush Gardens in Virginia
where you like, they have like,
it's like a water ride, and
you, um,
they have these little like quarter operated
like water guns around the water ride so you can like yes I remember this ride
yeah it's great but when I would go as a kid I would just like not nobody I know
would be on the ride no just sit there posted with like six dollars shooting
tourists in the face because it's like once I get off like I'm fucking gone
dude like that's sick yeah it's such a beautiful mechanic to put it in a theme
park yeah that's awesome just spraying strangers with water yeah mmm and I
bring my own ammo it's showing up a trying to like disassemble it's a
showing up in like a different disguise each time as you as you shoot people in
the face yeah me oh no I'm just a bumblebee I won't be using this I'm just
an unassuming robber on my way to a big heist. Yeah just like yeah like Larry let's get some like
disguises so people don't recognize us and just only getting like mascot costumes.
Who me? I'm Austin Powers. Yeah right. I mean British spy. Oh I'm a pimp as you can see here
so not gonna be shooting the water gun here. That's what I would do if I if I wasn't old
enough for an R-rated movie I'd dress up like a bumblebee and be like what are you gonna you know
I can't stop a bug from getting inside.
(laughing)
I don't even need a ticket, man.
I'm just fucking--
- Hey, I mean, you can turn me away,
but the Department of Bugs is not gonna be
happy to hear about this.
- I mean, low key my hive might attack,
but that's like kinda you.
I'm basically the queen.
- No, I'm not even gonna see a movie.
My queen's in there.
I just have to get in.
My queen.
- Yeah, yeah.
You know, if you can bring the queen out here,
and then if he goes in, I'm just gonna run past him.
- Exactly.
- Take off the bee costume.
They won't recognize me.
- Yeah.
- Hey, aren't you the guy wearing a bee costume earlier?
- What are you talking about? - What are you talking about?
- Seven year old wearing a bee costume.
- I forgot I wear a bee costume.
No, but I think there is like a really flat dead bee
on the floor of the lobby.
- It looked really handsome too.
- Yeah, it's kind of, yeah.
- Before it was dead.
- And there's a little pee inside of it.
I don't know what that's about, but.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Kind of yucky.
You might need to clean it up.
- Mm-hmm, you need to clean it up.
- I've never worn a suit like that.
I kind of want to get a job as a mascot.
I feel like that's like the perfect job for me right now.
That might fund my Disney trip.
me and my friend, uh, we, we were doing like a thing where we were just, uh, as
like, uh, we never released anything we did, but we were trying to do a thing
where we were dressing as, as wizards.
Um, and just like, like running around New York.
Um, and we did like, we went to Times Square cause we wanted to like, make a
joke that we were like wizards who showed up and people thought we were
also people you take pictures with.
Um, and then we just were confused by that.
Uh, they immediately surrounded us.
I have felt like the Elmo's and oh yeah.
I was like, Oh, Oh, I'm just stomping on your turf right now.
I'm not even kidding.
They slowly circled us.
And I was like, all right, there is like 10 or 15 very, very short men inside
these costumes who are going to tear us apart.
And so we just like abandoned the bit.
We were like, we can't, like, we don't, we don't want to like take
It is funny. Imagine the kind of like, like six year old kid who's like, "Mom, can we take a picture with Elm-"
"Wait, there's a wizard?"
Yeah. A wizard from like, no real like, IP.
Oh yeah, that was the whole thing was like, we're just gonna be like, magical guys and just be wi-
But like, yeah, just yeah, no IP.
Yeah.
I went to college with Merlin.
Um, yeah.
I took a photo with a cowboy at Times Square.
Yeah.
It was so awesome.
Yeah, I just don't I don't really understand all that mascot shit works
I wonder did I take you like a license for that? No, no, no, I certainly felt like I did
Yeah, you feel like you did not pass the test. Yeah, whatever it was
Yeah, I felt like I felt like there was something that I needed you have
Yeah
you have to get a vision to be to be the mascot and it's like how if you have to get like a different license for
Like a motorcycle or a passenger vehicle or whatever. You have to you have to take a specific CD
for different mascots.
So you need to know a lot about sharing
if you want to be Elmo.
Elmo can't hold somebody around the waist.
He's not too weird.
Goofy though? Goofy can grab their ass.
Absolutely. Goofy can do all kinds of
fucking things. It's because he has a permanently open hand.
They have a Hogwarts style
sorting hat that they put on the
guys in the sidewalks. The mascot people?
It's a giant mask.
It's the mask.
They put the mask on people
much and what in depending on what mascot they turn into when they put the mask on
that's the house they're in I think the worst people in the world like worse
than like like mass murderers or just like evil evil people are people who
like get jobs good get jobs at something like Disney World and they just love to
play their character and they get so into it and they do it for 12 hours a
day and they're like that's awesome dude I want those people dead everybody who's
in a costume at a place like that should be fucking hating their life.
Mm-hmm, absolutely. That's, that has, that needs to be like the bottom tier job.
Yeah, you need to, you have to start as Cinderella.
It's like when you see a cashier smiling or something, it's like you have to stop.
Do you even know where you are right now? Did you just get hit in the head by a coconut?
Why are you fucking happy right now?
Yeah, I better not hear the fucking cook singing back there.
That better not be what I'm hearing right now.
You are what are you, fucking Encino man?
I did my part.
I disrespected a minimum wage worker today.
Oh, really?
Let's hear the story.
At the hardware store when I was buying my toilet seat,
toilet seat's at the top shelf, it's a high ticket item.
And so I fucking, there was a ladder right next to it,
so I was like, well, I'll fucking go grab this.
I grabbed it, and as I'm bringing it back down the ladder,
lady walks around the corner, she's like,
hey, you're not supposed to use that ladder.
And I was like, well, I just used it,
and I got my toilet seat.
(laughing)
Yeah, I mean, I'm always--
She seemed pretty upset.
I'm always scheming ways to disrespect, you know,
the lower class like that.
You know, I always, when I hear the garbage man
coming around the corner, I run outside, I puke on him.
I say it's the smell of the trash and he can't disprove it.
And then I also say, "Hey, clean that up, trash man."
Yeah, it's technically trash.
That's trash.
I don't wanna.
I ate some of the trash to make it happen.
There's trash in there.
Yeah, if they get too mad, I sort of sweeten it
and I call them pickup artists.
That's very sweet.
Yeah, you guys are the real pickup artists.
Yeah, and then when he turns around, I flip him off.
Yeah, that's right. And say, "Just kidding."
Yeah, just kidding.
But I say, "Just kidding," under my breath.
Yeah, but I say it not under my breath.
If the guy's small enough, I pick him up by the ankles,
I swing him around and throw him in the compactor.
There isn't a minimum wage worker
that I have not just completely punched
in the fucking face a hundred times.
That's right. Absolutely.
Yeah. Yeah.
If I see one--
Waiters and waitresses, wait staff, dude,
if I sit down at a restaurant,
I'm asking for cloth napkins one at a time
till my whole body's covered.
- Absolutely.
- Oh yeah.
- I mean, lately I've been really pissed off
that they're putting in those like
touch screen kiosks at McDonald's
'cause it's too easy to clean spit off 'em.
- It's also--
(laughing)
- That's true.
And how do you disrespect a computer?
- Oh, I have tried to like just--
- I know, I'm standing in front of the kiosk
and I'm going--
- What do I have to learn C to make this guy mad at me?
- I am not telling the truth right now
and trying to get him to short circuit
It just doesn't work.
What I do is--
I'm basically yelling paradoxes at my kiosk.
Yeah, dude, I mean, I've been caught a couple times
at McDonald's with my butt cheeks just like plastered
against one of those screens trying to photocopy my ass.
Yeah, right.
But it just doesn't work at all, dude.
Yeah, I've been caught at McDonald's
with my butt cheeks out, yeah, like all the time.
Yeah.
Just as a sign of disrespect,
just trying to show them that I don't respect them.
Also assert dominance there,
'cause McDonald's apparently can't ask anybody to leave ever.
I don't know if you've been to one,
But people just be doing crazy shit in the McDonald's.
So you can just walk in with your butt out,
start fucking, people play chess in McDonald's
for like 16 hours a day.
They're like drinking like a fireball.
- I'm sorry, sir, we can't ask you to leave.
- I know that we're not supposed to ask you to leave,
but do you want a refill?
- You have, like you slit that woman's throat.
- Yeah.
- But do you, but, so I'm gonna say just a few hours
I'm gonna need you to go to the playpen
instead of the main restaurant area.
- Every city, the McDonald's are a fucking,
it's a jungle, dude. - It's awesome.
- Like you thought, whatever seats are the furthest
from the cash register, that's like,
McDonald's like doesn't even claim that.
They're like, the restaurant ends--
- That's international water.
- Yeah, the second to last row.
Whatever you can see from the street
into the like, the big window.
- Oh yeah, you turn the corner to see that part
of the McDonald's and it's just pitch black
and you can see red glowing eyes.
(laughing)
I put yeah they also in McDonald's the the area floor that's just outside the
bathroom where it's like just just to the side of the line that you wait to
order or pick up in but like in front of the bathroom that's called the yelling
zone yeah you can be as loud and as as religious as you want talk about
whatever you want yeah they literally can't stop you one time I swear to God I
walked towards like the back corner in McDonald's and a tentacle just grabbed
my ankle and started pulling me towards the darkness and I had to I had to say a few prayers
and eventually it like just it uncoiled.
100% yeah there's like it's it's fucking Pirates of the Caribbean in that corner in McDonald's
every single time.
I mean and something something they don't tell you about McDonald's is that if you if
you if you it's like it's sort of like the secret menu where if you need fresh air you
can ask the cashiers and they'll let you eat next to the drive-thru window.
Oh, you have to.
Yeah.
They have to, and you can smoke there too.
Oh, yeah.
And blow it out like you're trying to smoke inside.
I've seen like a full, like I've seen like a game of Twister being played in the middle
of the conference.
Yeah, dude.
And it is not clothed Twister.
I mean, they are butt ass naked.
You walk in, you see people setting up surround sound.
Yeah.
You're like, what the fuck is this?
I saw one guy just like practicing walking on his hands, and he must have kicked this
woman seven times. They just didn't do anything about it. It was horrible.
I mean and yeah if you're a McDonald's and the the the chairs you can take those.
You can bring those into the bathroom if you need to. If you want to
you know if you want it if somebody's already in there but you also you want to
go but there's not enough toilets in there. I saw a guy taking apart a chair and trying to
make it into a robot. Like he just was trying so hard. There's always a mad
I've got scientists tinkering.
Oh my God.
On every single time, dude.
Oh my, and he's always, he always wants the fish filet.
Yeah.
Even if it's breakfast.
And he's, yeah, he's such a bitch.
It's amazing, dude.
I love seeing, just walking in,
seeing some middle-aged guy rebuilding an engine.
Yeah.
It's just a beautiful place, man.
Yeah, it's just like, I gotta find my kid.
Yeah, also no other, no other restaurant is like that.
No other fast food restaurant.
Really, no?
Well, I don't know, when I was in,
I was in downtown LA and I went to like a Carl's Jr.
And that was--
Downtown LA is different, dude.
Dude, it was getting, it was,
like I would walk in at like one o'clock
and it was simply just like 1 a.m.
It was just not one o'clock p.m.
Yeah, last time I was in downtown L.A.,
I think it was with Cam,
we saw a woman walking around with no pants.
100%.
Just like, and no underwear either, just battling.
By figure, I just assumed.
She also had like the craziest bush I've ever seen, dude.
(laughing)
I swear to God, dude, it came out.
I mean, that's why she was allowed to do it,
otherwise L.A. censors everything.
Yeah, it came out like five inches from her waist.
It was fucking insane, dude.
Yeah, I'd love to see the silhouette of that.
And just like, "Oh, does she have Cthulhu down there?"
I don't know what that is.
They got the craziest graffiti out there, too.
I don't know if you guys seen, there's this huge tag
that says Hollywood.
You can see pretty much wherever you are.
It's nuts, dude.
They just leave that up.
I think they're gonna start saying,
"Yeah, it's in like this other language."
They're gonna start talking about Spanish graffiti.
They got the craziest graffiti there,
saying things like polio. They got the craziest food, they got this thing called Del Taco.
I don't know what the hell is going on there. What does that mean? What's that guy's name?
What's that restaurant called? Inside Out? In-N-Out? Yeah, right. You're close. That damn
place should be on the Out-N-Out if you ask me. Yeah, that's right. I go there, I order
fries animal style every time. It's so funny. It's so cool that there's a place you can
order stuff animal style. That's like the coolest way to order something ever.
Fries there are like a 4 out of 10 too. I hope your California fans come for me.
In-N-Out is just fine. How do you think that animal style thing worked man? Do
you think like they had like... Well they're Christian. Yeah so like that
doesn't make sense like they didn't come up with it themselves. Some guy must have
come in and been like "I'll take some fries. Make them animal style baby!"
like what I guess we'll just make up on this I don't give a fuck make it animal
style you slut come on you baby he was holding up a in and out holding them up
all at gunpoint yeah made fries animal yeah yeah whatever they came up with
exactly yeah make a man hmm suppose that is animal style you'll see his picture
up on the wall it's like a Murray G crazy man yeah you took one by no you
You cook this shit in mustard, I'm leaving man, fuck this.
That is nasty as fuck.
Yeah, they're very precious
about their little restaurant, aren't they?
They are, it's really annoying.
In the worst place in America.
It's just fucking fine.
It's cheap as hell though.
I'll take White Castle, dude.
I'll take White Castle over that shit.
I've never been to White Castle.
I will not take White Castle over that shit.
I'm a New York boy.
It's like 70 cents for a little tiny baby burger.
Man, I have been every kind of intoxicated
and gone to White Castle just to see
if I can feel something when I taste that.
I just don't.
Nothing.
- You're insane, dude.
I came to your house and you gave me a ball of pasta
that's been deep fried.
A ball of spaghetti.
- That is fried capellini.
- That's the craziest, that's crazier and worse
than anything that they sell at White Castle.
- I'm telling you that that has flavor.
I'm telling you I have not tasted White Castle burgers
and enjoyed them.
- It's got pickles on it, dog.
That's all I'm saying.
- Bro, most burgers got pickles on them.
Bro.
- I don't know.
Not the way I make 'em.
not animals. I'm making my own pickles.
Nah, I'm, yeah, no, I don't know. I've just never enjoyed White Castle and I feel stupid
because of that, because I'm like, everybody loves it. Yeah, I mean, if you're coming down
to Boston, I mean, you just, you've got to try McDonald's. That shit goes nuts. It's
insane, dude. It's insane. Have you heard about what happens in the weird part of the
McDonald's? There's always some freaks there. Yeah, there's always something weird going
on there. Yeah. Alright, boys, I'm out. Yeah, this is that part. Bye, sweetie pie. Bye, everybody.
[BLANK_AUDIO]