You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content!
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately!
*laughter*
*explosion*
Merry Christmas to you!
Happy holidays, America, to you!
Happy, a merry day to Christmas!
happy christmas
on your birthday
oh man
uh... caleb's
you know i don't even know this time yeah i don't know what the fuck happened
to caleb i heard he fell into some kind of giant
butthole on the inside the ass of a giant guy inside of the butthole of the
ass
of a giant guy.
Yeah.
And I heard he's kind of making himself at home in there, wiggling around and pressing
and poking at the different points inside.
And kind of seeing what happens and what comes out of it.
He's kind of exploring the space.
Making it his home.
Yeah.
He's decolonizing.
No, he's colonizing.
Oh, he's colonizing.
The giant man's ass.
decolonizing. The giant man's ass. Yeah, Caleb would never decolonize anything. He's anti-decolonization.
That's true. Yeah. Oh boy. So Patrick was telling me you got three hours of sleep. Yeah, I'm
running on three hours of sleep, but when Cameron got here, Cameron was knocking on the
door for like, how long? I only knocked one time because I thought you might be in the
bathroom or something. Oh, okay. So I texted you a few times. How long did you wait before
you knocked on the door? Probably like seven, eight minutes. Yeah, so I was asleep for,
okay, so I went to bed at 7 a.m. and then I got up at 8 a.m. and then I've been up
since, yeah, since 8 a.m. and then I slept one hour and then Cameron got here and
And we're going to a show after this.
- Yeah.
- Which is probably not good for my fucking--
- Get some energy.
- Yeah. - Drink some energy.
- I drank some cold brew just now.
- Nice.
- And I feel worse.
- Which isn't good.
- I always in the morning,
if I'll like sometimes forget to drink coffee.
- Yeah.
- And then I'll just like take a whole cup
of like lukewarm coffee and just chug it all
in like one minute.
And it always, it just, it ruins my day every time.
I do it like once a week. Before work I used to chug, I used to like walk in...
God damn. Yeah fucker is sitting on my TV and it's like it's tilting the TV. Yeah
he likes to, well I mean he used to sit on the buttons, but now he's
sitting on the other side of the TV. I think we like told him to stay off the
buttons enough that he's like figured out that he can't sit there. Now he's
shaking the TV around. He fell off of it last night. Really? Did he like fall
asleep and fall over? Yeah. That's pretty funny. He, so like a week or two ago he
fell asleep on top of the TV. Like he's like balancing on top of the TV.
Like yeah it's a thin TV. Mm-hmm. But he's like sitting on top of it. He fell
asleep on the the volume button and he turned the TV all the way up and then he
was still sitting there and I didn't know it was all the way up and I went and like
I played a trailer for some movie yeah and the MGM sound like the lion at the
beginning like the volume he turned it up to 99 and he's sitting there and then
out of nowhere it's just the fucking MGM the Lions roar and then him and his
brother just fucking bolted for the back like the bedroom I didn't know what the
fuck was going on I have a really distinct memory of as a kid like going
up to going up to my my dad's like stereo which is like surround sound like super
like big like speakers and it's like being really little and just like
playing with the knobs and like turning the button nothing was playing but like
turning the volume all the way up and then like and then like five minutes
later my dad came in and like played a song. I fell over and started crying
because it was so loud. I scared the shit out of everyone in the house.
It was good times. I think I did that like two or three times. He just never
learned from it. Yeah, well how was I you know how am I supposed to know that
the knob that says volume controls the volume? It says vol. Exactly it says
vol. That could be anything. That could be volume. Velocity. Velocity. That
could be voluptuous, velocity of the sound as well. That's what volume means. Yeah, that's
what it's short for. Yeah, that's what vol is short for. When you see it on a stereo
or a TV or something, it says "volosity". Volosity of the music. It controls how fast
the music goes out of the speaker and into your ear. If it hits you really fast, it's
gonna be really loud. So you wanna make sure you got slow music. Oh boy. Yeah. I'm fuckin'.
Yeah. My brain is a piece of crap.
We already knew that.
Yeah, this is like
This is going to be like a a really energetic show. Yeah, and I don't think I can like
Go, I think i'm gonna have to stand in the back. Yeah, i'll probably stand in the back. Yeah
I don't know that. I usually I think the last uh, the last show me the body show I went to
I got where yeah, yeah, it was the day joe was leaving. Yeah, I didn't go to that one. Yeah
uh... i got my glasses just absolutely destroyed
yeah i don't know why i thought it was a good idea
as remember going back to lake jose and then
my glasses like with my glasses all stomped out
critical yeah i'd
the last did this is showing the body and daughters allies daughter show i
went to i went by like had a migraine that day yeah it was like starting to
wear off and i like i bought this ticket like i should go by and it's like how i
am right now. And yeah and then I went and I like... There weren't even any daughters.
And then the after the show I went home I went to bed and I had nightmares about being in a mass
shooting. So I'll be praying for you. All right. That you don't... Yeah because then I have to go
go back to New Hampshire tomorrow. Yeah. Yeah. Cause I thought Caleb was having a
show tomorrow at Muya's. I thought I had to like host a show and then go to like my
friend's party. Yeah. But I'm glad that Caleb's tour got canceled. Yeah. Fuck you Caleb.
Yeah I heard he bombed on his last show. I don't, I, yeah. That's what he said.
That's what he said.
Wink.
What?
Eh?
Yeah.
You can't see it, but I'm doing the Robert De Niro wink.
Where he sticks out his whole tongue and he looks like a fucking idiot.
Is that what he does when he winks?
Yeah.
Why?
That's what every Robert De Niro impersonator does.
I don't see many Robert De Niro impersonators.
That's kind of not a thing I'm interested in.
No.
Really.
I think it was the summer of 2018, but I got really into just like
inquiring about impersonators. I really got really into inquiring. I got really
into inquiries, but there's this like website I found, it was called
lookalike.com. I think it's my Twitter picture is a guy I
found on that website. He's supposed to be the guy, my Twitter picture
a guy on that website who's supposed to be a Kelsey Grammer impersonator and it's clearly
just like a picture of him at like a secondhand like furniture store and he's wearing like
just the funniest outfit. He's just - he's got his arm perched on a lion.
Yeah.
And -
It's a good picture.
Yeah, it's a pretty good picture.
Yeah.
But it says like Kelsey Grammer impersonator parentheses Frazier.
But I found him on a website and then I found like they have like sopranos and then like
there was one guy on that website that was clearly just
a guy who went as Napoleon Dynamite for Halloween. Yeah. That one's the funniest one.
But I keep, I kept sending them emails and I never, I haven't heard back from them.
Damn, they're onto you. Yeah, I know. I know it's just a hobby for you. Yeah, I know.
You're not into the real, you're not a real fan.
- I just wanna see what happens.
- Yeah.
Trying to think, let's see.
I went to dim sum today.
I haven't done anything really in the past few days.
- I just haven't been sleeping
and I've been smoking weed now.
- Nice dude, yeah that's true.
Yeah, you're not allergic to it.
- I thought I was allergic to weed for four years
because I threw up one time.
(laughing)
- Hey, I mean--
- No, I've thrown up--
- Two times.
- I've thrown up a couple times from smoking weed.
- Yeah, I always feel like I'm about to throw up
when I smoke weed.
- Yeah, like I fuckin',
I've greened out more times than I can think of.
But you know what the thing is,
when I was smoking weed,
I was also on Adderall,
so I was taking like--
- Yeah.
- Uppers and downers.
- That's true.
Not even, no. Uppers and downers is pills.
But weed is a downer.
Yeah, and Adderall's an upper. I think that counts.
I don't think it's just pills.
It counts, but like, you can smoke weed and take Adderall and be fine.
Yeah, hey man, I did it for a long time.
But I guess it just fucked with me really bad to the point where I thought...
It fucked with me. When I was on Adderall, alcohol, and weed, I would just pass out like instantly.
Oh yeah, me too. I would like, I'd violently throw up.
up. Because on Adderall like it like it like counteracts or whatever the alcohol
so you can't feel how drunk you are. Yeah. And then it's like once the Adderall
wears off all the alcohol hits you at once and I like knew that because my
doctor kept telling me that over and over and I was like okay fine I'll be
careful then just every once in a while it just you can't avoid it you know I
mean it just freaking hits you like a bag of beer and knocks you right over.
That's that's some true shit hits you like a bag of beer
But hey, man, that's just the way that the beer pours
Yeah, but I haven't I mean I feel like this is the best time into the bag
Yeah, the beer pours into that's the way the beer pours into the beer
The way my throw-up pours into the bag of beer I
Feel like this is the best time for me to start smoking weed again. Yeah, why cuz I mean it's
basically legal, I mean it's legal here.
So it's like a lot of the thing is,
is I was on Adderall then I'd get very paranoid.
I think maybe I would just have panic attacks
every time I smoked.
- Yeah.
- And then that might be it.
I thought it was a pollen thing.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause I'm like really allergic to pollen.
'Cause I haven't been smoking like straight weed.
- You haven't been smoking pollen for a while.
- No, I haven't been smoking pollen.
I've been using, plus I mean I sound like
so fucking annoying about this too.
Just like, oh yeah, well, I mean,
I haven't been smoking like regular weed per se.
I don't know.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- I hate, 'cause now I just hate talking about it
'cause it's like, I sound like a fucking idiot.
- 'Cause it's legal.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, the weed in LA fucked me up.
It gave me panic attacks like every time.
- Yeah.
- I still did it every night.
(laughing)
- A lonely sun, there seems to be free in my heart.
exactly
and i want to only road
the only road that i a little lonely now
lonely
loan and i don't know where walk don't know where the only island goes
but there's they rap for me and i like this on the bed
uh...
uh... booker doesn't go on the computer fuckers sitting on my lap right now is
really nice yeah
it out is a good guy
school
he got sharp claws
and i hope he does not know what a lot of the panic attacks i had when i was
smoking weed in high school was uh...
i thought that
i was going to get high in the cops are going to immediately show up to get
because not going to do it yet they have a detector you're going to allow it
they could tell that we're being too loud
because of marijuana
so i would talk very quiet and i think you like
"Guys, can we keep it down?"
And I thought the cops were going to show up.
The funniest thing is in LA at the dispensary that was near campus, there was like a cop
who stood there and checked your receipt when you left to make sure you weren't stealing
shit or whatever.
And whenever he checked your receipt, he would nod and be like, "Well, enjoy the high."
So funny.
full cop out yeah enjoy the high I don't know I like I wonder if they told him to
say that if he just came up with that yeah dude he totally did how old was he
I don't know middle-aged yeah did he fucking yeah he's like you know make
these kids love me these people are gonna respect me once I save them one
day yeah once I once I saved them from being attacked by their own dog sir it
appeared that your blind three-legged dog was trying to kill you your blind
three-legged dog attacked your nutsack was yeah was on his way to attack your
nutsack and I ascertained that I needed to end his life yeah with my with my
cobra fist he does the five-pointed exploding heart from kill bill we would
be fucked that'd be cool though it'll be bad I would like cops if they if they if
If cops knew karate or kung fu or tai chi or...
Or aikido.
Aikido or krav maga or...
um...
Shaq Fu. Oh shit.
Or ninja... Cop knew Shaq Fu.
If a cop knew Shaq Fu it's over. There's a certain cop that would know Shaq Fu. Yeah that's right.
And he was in grown ups too. Shaquille O'Neal.
You see that thing?
- Yeah.
- There's like a Shaq tweet from like 2011
where it was like going to Barbara Yard, statue time.
And he's like, "Damn, my fingers are too big for my phone.
"Damn autocorrect.
"Anyway, going to Harvard Yard, statue time."
(laughing)
- He has the best old tweets.
- Yeah.
- Like there's the one where he's too big.
- He challenged Chris LaAngel to levitate him.
- I didn't see that one.
- Oh yeah, that one turned into him getting levitated
on Criss Angel's show.
- Wow. - Yeah.
- That's pretty cool.
- Yeah. - Opportunity.
I would love Criss Angel to levitate.
- I would love to get levitated.
- Damn, I would love to get to levitate Criss Angel.
- Levitate me.
- Onto my dick. - Criss Angel.
- Levitate me, Criss.
- You will levitate me.
- Yeah, yeah, hypnotizing him to levitate you.
- Yeah, Jedi mind tricking him.
- Yeah.
- You will levitate me, Criss Angel.
a random guy on the street. It's just a homeless guy. Yeah. I saw the chatterbox guy today.
Oh yeah. The homeless guy and he uh he was it's the first time I seen him in a while. He was wearing
a Santa hat and he was walking back and forth on the corner and he was yelling "Ho ho ho, ga ga ga ga
ga ga ga ga ga ho ho ho!" Yeah. What if he's the real Santa? I think he is. That'd be awesome. Yeah.
If you think about it, Santa would be homeless because he lives in an igloo and that's not a
real house. So if you think about it for more than one second like me, you kind of understand.
I met Santa, she's black.
Yeah, so...
I think that's the only funny thing I've come up with in the past like three months.
Yeah, I think that's funny.
I met Santa, she's black.
I think it's pretty funny. Not. I'm joking. I think it's funny.
The Santa is black not like Borat. Yeah, like Borat. Yeah. The Santa is not black.
What a good movie. Yeah. Pretty funny to me. I watched Star Wars, I watched the three Star Wars
once. Yeah, three Star Wars Borats. Three Star Wars outside Ebbing, Missouri. Three Star Wars.
three borats outside Missouri. What about that? Yeah. What about the shape of Borat?
The shape of Borat, okay. And it's like the shape of water. I like his sex. Yeah. And
then they have sex in the water. But he's a fish. Okay. Okay, what else? What else we
got? Borat Wick. Borat Wick. Yeah, that one's good. That's pretty good. Okay, what about
Borat Star Wars.
Okay, I can see that.
What about Borat?
Borat Jar Binks.
No, that's not a movie.
Jar Jar Borat.
That's not a movie.
We're doing it with the names of movies.
Oh, okay.
Try again.
Borat's List.
Okay.
It's just...
He's a Nazi.
(laughing)
- Man, I watched that the other day for that fuckin' paper.
- Yeah, I love the part at the dinner party.
- Oh yeah, the dinner party where he carries
the turd downstairs.
- Yeah, when he's like,
"Oh, you let him out of his cage, he's retarded."
no no yeah it's so funny I am NOT retired I am retired and that's why I think
there is a there's the scene that always I forget about it every time I rewatch
that movie it's a when he interviews Alan Keyes yeah about like the the gay pride
parade and he's like uh god what does he fucking say he's like oh i interviewed a man who was a
genuine chocolate face no makeup yeah that's fucking okay i keep i forget it happens every
time and then every time i laugh way too hard at it yeah this is a borat quotes episode this is the
Borat quotes episode. Here's a Borat quote. I love my wife. I love my wife.
Here's a Borat. I love my wife Borat. Borat. I, Borat. I love my wife. Borat loves his wife.
The two, Borat two. Borat's wife. Borat's wife two. Yeah. Well they should make a sequel to Borat
called Borat's wife and so it's kind of about what she goes through. Yeah. When she dies. When
when she dies it's what she is kind of what the story leading up to her death
you know
here i've got a pitch it's called borat's wife and it's a
action movie yet shows
his wife
his wife is dying his wife is a double agent double agent double o eight
yeah double o eight james borat that's her name
but
the name is bore at James James bore James bore at I'm bore at wife
and I'm here to
that's my mission
bore at bore at bore at bore at bore at bore at bore at bore at bore at my name
a bore at
that would be the James Bond. Tell me the James Bond, a before it was about
for it. It really makes you think. Yeah. I'm trying to think about Star Wars. Did you see
Rise of Skywalker? No. I want to see it. Then I can't talk about it. I don't really care.
I'll probably wait until it goes on streaming. I've been using Anna's Disney Plus. It's good.
controversial opinion but it's good when compared to the other two sequels which
are bad so it's not very good yeah I watched force awakens recently force
awakens is so bad I thought it was it was fun to watch but it do yeah it was
was just the first one. The first time I watched it I was like, Oh yeah, yeah, you
know, like, Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
this is pretty promising. Oh, oh, they got all the new Star Wars guys. Oh, wow,
okay, okay. I can't wait to buy all the toys. Oh my god. They've added so many
toys. There's so many toys I'm gonna miss out on. I hope they make a toy out of
the guy who sells for the droid. I hope they make a toy out of the fat guy in
backgrounds I hope to make a toy out of Meach Mongo. Meach Mongo? You know the new Star Wars character?
Meach Mongo is a four foot tall. It's a really problematic character. Yeah.
Oh yeah that's uh so everyone was complaining I mean not everybody but like people people like
to make the joke like oh yeah the Star Wars movies stopped being good when they had when they stopped
like having racist yeah when they stopped having the racial stereotype because the
prequels is just all racial yeah so just so haven't they always been good then
except for the new trilogy if you're going by that metric but what are their
racial what are the racial ones that stereotypes in the original trilogy the
original trilogy I guess is uh who well I mean there's Lando Calrissian black guy
right? Han Solo, that's white guy. There's a goddamn character in Star Wars that is
an a like half like an android named Lobot. Yeah I did know about that one.
That is so fucking stupid. Jabba the Hutt's Italian right? What are we gonna name this guy?
I do like there's a guy in the first one who's a fat guy named Porkins.
It's so funny.
Isn't the pattern on his helmet the same colors as Abba's Abba too?
Is it?
That'd be funny.
Oh no wait, no, that's Bigg's Darklighter's helmet.
He has the Abba's Abba pattern on his helmet.
Nice.
Yeah, it's so funny how before they knew they were like really going all in with it, they
were just kind of like, yeah, Porkins.
I don't know.
Yeah, Porkins.
Whatever.
There's a guy named Luke Skywalker and his friend is named Biggs Darklighter.
Yeah.
Darklighter.
Goddamn, dude.
It's kind of like if there was dark combined with light.
Yeah.
It's so funny, like everybody, like I get it, like, yeah, like people like Star Wars
when it's like serious, but then it's like, you gotta think.
When has it ever been serious?
Yeah, you gotta think about how fucking, first of all, the dialogue in those fucking movies,
second of all.
The acting.
acting in the fact that it's a fucking kids movie yeah
well i don't know there's some pretty scary stuff in there man
darth vader's breathing
sounds like my dad when he's trying to sleep yeah
and there's nothing scarier than my dad being woken up
don't wake daddy was about my freaking dad exactly that was the daddy was based on
my dad was based on will wake up daddy
based him off the game. Yeah. Yeah. But yeah, no, it hasn't been, it's, I don't
think there's anything serious about it. Having watched it. They tried to lean in
with the prequels to like the seriousness of it, but it's like, it's
like politics, right? Yeah, it's like the politics of it, but it's like, yeah, it's
cool. This is clearly just like a thing to sell toys. Yeah. And then like with
episode three, they were like, all right, we're gonna lean in way too fucking hard.
And then the prequels and then the standalone movies are like yeah this
actually some of this is about how the characters get depressed. Yeah. Which I
just I'm fucking sick of that. Can we just have like a normal. Hey can we have
normal people who aren't depressed. Can we have normal in the world. Can I hang out with a
guy who's not sad. Right can I hang out. Can I just hang out. Can I hang out with you.
you
I'm cleaning the gun. I don't have an apartment right now. I'm going to stay in here for a week.
Oh my god, just stop yelling at me about the gun in the movie theater.
Listen, right now I'm cleaning it. If you keep yelling at me, that's all I'm saying. I won't go any further. It's not a threat. It's a promise.
It's a promise of action.
It's a promise that I will commit my act if you do not leave me alone.
I will commit my my act is imminent.
What no I'm talking about buying popcorn.
Don't call the cops.
I swear I meant buying popcorn.
Yeah, if you're gonna keep yelling at me, I'm gonna buy popcorn.
That's what I was saying.
I'm gonna buy popcorn and throw the kernels at you.
Yeah, that's what I meant.
I'm gonna launch these small bullet-shaped objects at you very quickly.
Rapid speed.
I'm talking about popcorn.
Wink.
You didn't even wink.
Why are you saying wink out loud?
Wink. Winking. I'm not going to shoot you in the movie theater. Wink.
Yeah, do you I think did you say it were you
Jesus Christ my throat's dry
You're scared to go into movie theaters
Yeah, me too. I know Caleb is too. I think Caleb is more scared than I am. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, Caleb's afraid of everything.
Caleb is a coward.
My mom wants to go see Knives Out with me
and I want to see it but I'm just like
I don't know man
what if a different guy comes in
to have a Knives Out?
Yeah, what if a guy comes in with a knife
with three knives out of his hand
out of his hand like Wolverine?
What are you going to do then, Mom?
You should have listened to me.
If I saw Wolverine in person, first of all
he's 5'4".
sure he died in the movies so I'd be like what's up with that. Yeah he's five foot four I
think I would I wouldn't see him at first. Yeah. I would I would just hear the the
the the the chinging of his of his fist blades. The what? The chinging of his fist blades.
The chinging? Yeah. You know when it comes out and goes ching. Doesn't it go like snicked or
something doesn't look at it
a specific sound effects snicked
you know night crawler does banf wanted
think wolverine as on sound effect to okay
i think it's blog
so his business go part mode
yeah
will bring those part of the magneto yes over magneto's business
you know where the local mitamah head of his day
that wolverine doesn't go pog mode on it exactly it's so that it's so that
professor x can't
professor x x x
mentally jack him up
that'd be funny
that'd be funny if they put that in the movies
hey x-men who owns x-men right now?
i have uh
you own x-men?
i have the x-men
all right well what next x-men
i love your idea
put it. Hey boys, it's me, Mr. X-Men. I own the X-Men. I'm the professor. And I'm the guy
the professor was based on. I love your idea and I'm gonna start jacking people
off with my mental powers. Thank you boys. I think Disney does own X-Men. Do you want to
come hang over in my mansion? No, not after you said that. You want to hang out in my
school full of kids? I'm gonna, I'm not gonna jack off any of the kids with my
mind that would be clear yeah let me be clear wink see that time I didn't even
say wink I just mentally implanted into your brain watch it now watch me wink
blinks can't wink professor X can't wink it's good of his disability
can't wink when he tries to wink yeah this is both eyes at once the doctor
saw that all right okay there's nothing seriously wrong with this kid oh this
Put him in a wheelchair.
Put him in a flying wheelchair.
Put him in a wheelchair he can levitate with his mind.
That's the only cure we can...
Is that what he does or does he have...
I don't know if it does that or not.
In my brain I imagine he...
I mean why wouldn't he do that?
Can he move things around or does he just go into people's brain?
I don't know.
He might.
You know nobody knows.
That's the thing about X-Men.
Nobody really knows anything about them.
There's too much to read and there's not enough pictures.
Exactly, there's no pictures in any of the X-Men books, and so nobody's read them before.
It'd be nice, because they have very detailed descriptions of what Wolverine looks like.
He's 5'4", he's Canadian.
What more do you want?
That's all you really need.
That's all you need to hear about him, and then you know what exactly...
Did they make him short in the movies?
No.
No?
He's tall in the movies?
Yeah, he's tall in the movies.
That's fucked up.
should have done what they did with the hobbits the hobbit trilogy and then the lord of the rings where
they do trick photography on hugh jackman the whole time to make him appear uh because hugh
jackman's like six feet tall yeah i think well i heard what they did with the hobbit is they put
all the actors into a juicing machine and made them into juice and then poured it into a small robot
and the juice was able to infiltrate the multiple circuits of the robot thus activating its
electronicity and kind of imbuing with the personality of the actor and creating a shorter,
more kind of functional actor that had hair on the feet.
So I'm not sure that process would work for Hugh Jackman because I mean, the Hobbits,
the Hobbits they used them and then they disposed of them.
They're not in any other movies because they throw away the robots.
That's why you don't see Elijah Wood in anything anymore because he was killed in the filming
of the three Hobbit trilogies.
So
The Hobbit movies that he was, it's so funny how much they fucked up the Hobbit.
Yeah.
The frame rate thing is like the funniest shit.
Oh my god dude.
It was so, it was so jarring to see that in the theater.
Just like the, it drops, it like goes up to 48 for some reason.
It doesn't go to like 60?
Yeah, yeah.
In the water.
The part in the river?
Yeah, the water rafting thing.
They shot it on GoPros.
It just looks haunted.
Yeah.
So fucking weird.
So funny.
they should have let Guillermo del Toro do the Hobbit trilogy he was going to
yeah before they gave they should have before they should have put a gun to
Peter Jackson's head and said they should have made a long movie make a
sequel to brain dead and then put a gun to Guillermo del Toro's head and say stop
being Mexican and then they put a gun to Quentin Tarantino's head and say make
the Hobbit let's put a gun to Quentin Tarantino's head and said become Mexican
yes which you and Guillermo del Toro switched lives with nationality which
nationalities switch identities and we're just gonna see what happens yeah we just
want to know what would happen so I could do that right now we won't shoot you I
think if they replace the hobbit with a meet the feebles reboot yeah I haven't
seen meet the feebles that's it oh it's very bad there's the three well there's
There's brain dead, bad taste, and then meet the feebles, right?
Is there another one?
Bad taste is on Amazon Prime.
Bad taste is really good.
That's probably my favorite.
I like that more than brain dead, which I think is an unpopular opinion.
Brain dead's the poster with the mouth.
Yeah.
Really gross poster.
You should see it.
I saw meet the feebles and parts of brain dead.
Brain dead's parts of brain dead or parts of bad taste?
Parts of brain dead.
Oh, bad taste.
Yeah.
Bad taste and brain dead are both really good.
I think bad taste is way funnier to me, in my opinion.
But brain dead has way cooler effects.
- Meet the Feebles is like--
- That's like Muppets with AIDS, right?
- Yeah, it's like Muppet, there's a Muppet who has AIDS,
and then there's also like,
it's like if the, like, it's every joke someone makes
about like, oh, Burt and Ernie smoking crack and being gay.
- Yeah, so it's like Wonder Shows in.
- But not, it's like he misses the mark completely.
- Yeah, I've heard it's good.
it's like it's just there's a way that you could do it but like the music cues
and everything and just the way that like the characters interact is just very
like it's just depressing it's not even like
it's not even it's like a dark it's like too dark of a
puppet comedy oh yeah there's got to be like some light
moments in there but there's like zero light moment like every time that he
tries to like put in the light moments it just
It has to do a lot with the score, I think.
Yeah, the score is just people whispering.
Yeah, it's just people saying that there's reptilians in the government and you need to
chop off their heads.
Yeah, it's just this constant voice that says "kill everyone around you."
Yeah.
I've noticed most movies nowadays are using that score.
A lot of movies have been using the same soundtrack.
Rise of Skywalker too, I noticed.
It's just, it's them saying, it's like the same song, it goes, "You need, you need to
take off, you need to take off Donald Trump's head and you need to show the world this lizard
body."
Yeah, and it's, and it's sometimes it even just drowns out the dialogue.
I think that people are doing a bad job of mixing the audio in movies nowadays.
It's that and then the screams.
Yeah, and sometimes just like a weird clown nose honk.
that might be from outside and others a guy who hangs out
type the movie theater
who like a lot of people who are now those of the people who are the people
both the penis clinton was a
planos on the end of his penis in the marks and makes it
an audible no i don't know if there is a really a bit of surgical horn penis
about a surgical penis
it strikes a precision
picking
yes this is my surgical penis
surgery opinions
search he'll be in the pits i texted
uh... my brother earlier today
congrats to you know i said i i said
i just texted in the name gene g
uh...
and he teaches just said that just the name sergio
surgery and it is not even like
yeah and sergio g just yet
well sergio g is a pretty good name yeah
so it really is sergio just made me laugh
if i'm not mistaken sergio's the third mario brother
sir mario luigi and sergio yes there's mario luigi sergio
sergio mario sergio luigi mario mario mario's middle name is mario sergio
luigi mario
and he's kind of a combination
his uh... he i heard he uh... didn't want to become
a mario brother or he didn't uh... you want to be in the spotlight
he did one game with them and then decided that he wanted to leave.
And they removed the game from shelves soon after.
It's called Custer's Revenge.
Yeah, it's called Custer's Revenge.
Yeah.
I'm here to talk to you about
bringing me on the pod to talk about Custer's Revenge.
That's a crazy story.
Yeah, that story, he totally could have just talked with them before.
Yeah, like it's yeah, it's an interesting choice. Yeah, it was like, I don't think it was necessarily
the wrong choice. No, I don't think it was the wrong choice, but like, he's very interesting.
He totally could have just been like, well, the way that he frames it is that he had to do that.
Yeah, he had to either do that or deny going on the show and then blasting them on Twitter. And
it's like, yeah, there's a third option where there's a million options. You could kill them.
That's another option. Yeah, there's an infinite possibility. You could do anything actually.
Yeah, you could actually, there's actually a 50% chance. You could do the episode and go to 7-Eleven
before. There's a 50% chance. You could go to 7-Eleven first and then do the same thing you did.
You go to 7-Eleven two times and then do it. You go to 7-Eleven three times. Now, think about what
I just said. While I go to the 7-Eleven across the street and I get a hot dog, I will be back in five
And then in the 7-Eleven, there's a big line, you're just screaming, "I'm on a
podcast right now, I'm teaching you about Custer's Revenge, I need a hot dog before
five minutes is up, please let me go in front of you." "Oh my god, you need to speed this up."
But he totally could have just like messaged them and just said like,
"Hey, it's kind of not cool that you're doing this here, why don't you just do
this instead but yeah or why don't we talk about it yeah why don't we talk
about this before the episode or like why don't we talk about it on the episode
but he could tell them beforehand right yeah I mean whatever power to I don't it
doesn't doesn't matter I don't care none of it affects me yeah exactly I don't
really care about native of the plight of the Native Americans is what Patrick is
trying to say I think no I think that's what Patrick you know as a point oh one
one
like a fraction it's like 1/64 but there's a decimal before the one. Okay
there's two decimals, it's .01. .0000001/64. Okay, so that's a lot. I'm .0000001/64
Native American and I'm really offended that you said that. Said what? I don't
remember that i don't care about the plate of my oh yeah now you don't
uh...
that uh... he caught me dot uh... i was thinking about
stays xd a set
it's thinking about gay sex again
and try to figure out how to stop myself any listeners have any tips trying to
figure out how to stop it from happening to stop the case x from happening
i'm trying to find a way to travel around the world and stop people from having
gay sex
so if anyone wants to join my club... why don't we play cards against humanity instead you guys?
yeah, breaking into someone's house
here, try this game. I think this will get your binoculars out.
hey
couldn't help but oversee. I saw stuff was getting hot and heavy in here
and you're two guys. or two girls, I don't even know.
Why don't we play cards against humanity? Why don't we play Monopoly 2?
I just invented it. Is there Monopoly 2? No, I admit there's Monopoly for kids. Yeah, that's Monopoly 2.
That's Monopoly Junior, which is basically Monopoly 2. If you think about it, Junior is like the
second, right? So Monopoly Junior is like Monopoly the second. The thing about Monopoly for kids is
it's pretty much the same. There's some simplified rules, but instead of it being like... I'd rather
play Monopoly for kids. Instead of being hundreds of dollars, it's just like you have like a one
one this is one illnesses to
was this three it like you know it's like you collect two dollars from the
president
when this is five that's it it's not a six you don't get a sense seven it's not
a moment on this is the
when i saw him in a leading your when it says not even a bleeding and it was
that's not him
because of the five
i know 'cause i played not be a camera plays until the age of eighteen
one of the upgraded to monopoly middle
which is in between not please in your normal not only college edition
probably
monopoly for that for the smart child for the gifted child or child when i and
that's when they have friends and i want
that looks pretty funny to forking cabbage usually a wrinkled up cabbage
yeah we're talking about patrick's p_n_n_'s
i'm pulling out my penis to show cameron on the pod
uh... i was saying you you we need
to about uh... sparkling corn i want to discuss or a little horn
on your we're going back and forth uh... with food names so they're doing so
sparkling corn is kind of like
it's like carbonated it's a sparkling water but it's corn
and i was so if you guys can imagine what that tastes like
sink think about it and i think i'm on a silence
okay splinters the minds of his splinter and put a splinter and i thought it was
what
that's what revenge is there return to the
the empire's i expect was supposed to be called the events of the return of
Revenge of the Return of the Empire. What was this supposed to be called?
It was supposed to be called Splinter of the Mind's Eye.
Damn, that's badass.
And there's a lot - it's like a novelization.
Yeah.
So it's like the first draft of like a sequel to Star Wars and George Lucas had no idea what he was
going to do with it. And like before Luke - so if you read it now, it's like really fucked up
because it's like he was going to go forward with a Luke and Leia relationship.
Yeah.
but now like knowing that they're siblings like there's like scenes in the book where it's like
Luke could not stop staring at Leia's beauty. Like he doesn't know how to levitate things with the
force. Damn. Does he meet Yoda? They fight Darth Vader on Dagobah. Whoa. Yeah. And Leia has a
lightsaber. Like what color? Girl color. She's a pink one. He has a pink lightsaber with a flower
on the end. Every time she swings it, it makes flowers. And it smells really good.
Yeah, what if they made a lightsaber that smelled really good? Damn, I would be
smelling that shit all day. I bet lightsabers smell really bad. Yeah, probably
smells like burnt hair. Cause you're burning all the dead skin cells in the
air. Yeah, exactly. In Star Wars, in Star Space, there's a lot of... In Cyber Space.
cyber chase uh...
fuckin uh...
what was a god damn
so sparkling corn return the sparkling
it
yeah let's go back to sparkling corn yet do we need to
started really funny a
well there were some other ones that we said
red delicious
some red delicious milk the a red delicious melt pre-good uh... granny
smith chicken human chicken area he could be ticket
and i have human chicken
human chicken
i'm gonna look
yeah human chicken you go into a restaurant and you ask for
well that's like hewnan chicken
yeah
more hewnan than a hewnan
chicken fried candy
cage free sauce
do you want your eggs chunky or smooth
yeah
Farm fresh beer.
Farm fresh beer, dude, if only.
Yeah.
I wish I could eat all of these right now.
This would be so good to eat right now.
Sauteed jelly bean.
Sauteed jelly bean, whoo!
Tap chicken.
Sounds pretty good.
Like you can get it out of your tap.
Yeah.
if i imagine it is a good charge my phone before we go but this
uh... it doors are at seven
they're probably start playing at eight
i live fairly close to the venue my address it my address is one one one one
one one one one president lockbuster president avenue
blockbuster video
blockbuster city yeah
in almost a similar president got impeached
yeah he's in jail right
yet i was so excited
impeachment doesn't lead to like a media like
well the thing which i wish there was like uh... a statement like impeachment
only happens like every
so often but when it does it's like some weird like death it's a weird like
fucking rule from like the seventeen hundreds yeah we have a little bit like
i have to a rotating and you know you get like
put on a spit
or so you know you're like you gotta get like
uh... there that they put a cow they put
uh... granny smith apple in your book
the uh... and they have to shoot a arrow at it to you
the thing i think everyone is underrating is uh...
they're not going to give sanders the nominee nation they're going to give it
to biden uh... uh... and biden's gonna lose against ron so trump gets impeached
it means that he's not
he won't get reelected
i feel like everybody's class you know where that everyone's like
well there will be a few in this way it doesn't mean anything
but he's not going to be probably will get reelected so
yes that's nice
i've i feel like if you get impeached you shouldn't be able to run again i don't
i'd you might not be able to i don't know
i don't know any of this works i'm not a sad whatever you call it mathematician
or whatever whatever you call someone who does politics politics fucker
poly up politics fucker the the political fucker dub fuck 'em
the political fucker
political fucker
the kid patrick's being mean to the cat not being mean to my cat
patrick's being really mean to his cat no i just put him on my shoulder
uh...
damn, did you see that?
that was a sick trick, he just moved legs yeah
is moved legs he's a it's a little bit legs yeah
i love moving legs
is he going to stepping on my phone yeah
when asshole can be put his but one year for you did not do that
dvd put his but will on your thumb print and it opened up your phone
but it's good to have a good principal at your parents but it is exactly
looks exactly like my cats but he kept
hasn't
crazy i got a cosmetic we changed when you got your cat
you wouldn't have met him i came over and i
it's going to be in this little with my eyes and mouth
but they will ask a razor came out of my eyes and my tongue and i was able to
ascertain the shape and size of it and i went to the doctor said
give me this on my phone my thumbs look like this and they said you want the
functionality you want to be able to sit out of it
i want to be able to prove that my son and i was like that's disgusting now
as you know i said i just so that when my kathryn's cats it's on my phone a lot
like it
i think uh... although i'm not charge my phone
all right well
i'm pausing it
that you put in his phone with the u_s_b_c_ charger which if i understand
is a fast charge the stance or
credibly fast quick
quick quick quick c_e_o_ speed of light like einstein's well yeah that's true
equals m_c_ light
equals the ronald mc light
and c
level rapper called mc patrick dorn
and he wraps like this
yeah he says blue
yeah that makes sense great joke dude
as really saying that about them
being it like except like
thing about someone like being a dad
and let you know their kid
they don't like it their kids don't like it when they like have to take a nap
and like you know how when you like spell out things in front of kids via
so it's like
all yeah uh... i have to go to the uh...
sublet blah blah blah like
a_s_s_ like you know like that
yes managing like a dad instead of like doing that he's like
yeah well i gotta go put jacob down for an n_ word
well and well
you know i have to go give jacob is n word here
so
canada it's gonna be just like a hangout yet
yet jacob's in the in the bedroom
with the n_ word
tickets in the bedroom doing it
you have a good morning and what he's having his and what
just like a guy not explaining that the n_ word is napia
uh...
you know n_ word i can't say it and that's how it's all a in front of my i'm
I'm not supposed to say it. I can't say it in front of my kid. He'll start screaming.
Yeah. It's very loud. Yeah. So you know what I mean. You know what I mean when I say N-word.
Yeah. Yeah. That'd be funny. If only dude. Dude, if only. If only that happened. If only
that was real. God, you can only imagine the hilarious situations that would come out of
that being real.
Yeah.
I'm going to go put my son down for an N-word.
I'm going to go put my son down.
He's being too bad.
Yeah, he's being really bad and I'm going to have to put him down.
So don't come in because you have to be really quiet.
Yeah.
And even if you hear screaming, it's okay.
He always does this.
He always does this around the time that I have to put him down for his n-word.
You getting anything good for Christmas?
I might get some candy.
You might get some candy? In your stocking or on your wrapped presents?
Which one?
Oh, I hope it's a baby Ruth!
It's a big box. I hope it's a Skittle.
"Oh, I hope it's Skittles!"
"I really hope it's..."
"Oh, Lord, I hope this is Skittles!"
"Great, it's M&M's!"
"I didn't ask for this, Mom!" "Have you seen the sweet heat Skittles?"
"No." "I think those are for absolutely nobody." "What are they?" "It's like Skittles that are
like spicy and sweet." "What the heck?" "Yeah."
what uh... what uh... for i have at the grocery store i say what that's what i
say what that
you tell me there's a spicy skittles
what that you know that the sound like it's for nobody who would that
who'd want like a split
because i think about the consistency of a skittle yeah and imagine that like
burning your lip
yeah
yet hot temperature lies on these yeah i was trying to choose like gum and spit
them out into my trash base can never swallow the skills here you're not
supposed to
that's why they have s on them for a minute
spit this out at the cap
for swallow this and you die
yeah i just got so scared if i actually swallowed gum as a kid
yeah i thought it was going to kill me or something to get gum in my hair is
the like a whole thing a double bubble or bubble tape
there is one time specifically uh...
just through put a bunch of gum in my hair
why
israeli little yeah
you know i don't know my mom was like putting a remember my mom had a peanut
butter in my hair to get it out
let's go for her
you know
but yeah
i'm gonna be the uh... i'm gonna have a really cool books kit
anybody knows what my hair smells like
it's a combination of government peanut butter
p_v_g_ yeah p_p_o_ buttery jesus and with it
it's a jelly with the g
yeah that's a real g_-sixty
like they're doing
with the g
uh...
jolly b documentary will be out
yeah i don't know when
it'll be a no one is editing it were very happy we love no one who were happy to
enlist
to enlist him in the pod army can list a lot of other list his in the list
there we go you get it
do you get it
i think i get it
you think i'm thinking i'm understand i think i get it
uh... i'm trying to think are we here we finish in the episode
uh... the well we have five minutes left to talk for five minutes
a sparkling
let's talk about sparkling corn and what color would it be
when you first said sparkling corn i didn't make the connection a sparkling
water net but who does the corn that's part of the
it was really bright
but you know i get glitter effect on like gold on the old pat but it was a
blake sparkles carol and then like it looks like regular corn and then you
bite into it and then it has like
it hurts yet like say that it like
feels like it sizzles
yeah like the water that's inside of the corner sparkling
i was i think it's
i think uh... but just taking a so district
but listeners
if you send us a video of you putting a little bit of corn
in a soda stream
and seeing what happens you have probably don't have to do it you put like
mostly water in it but i don't know the little bit of corn you put a little like
a cup of corn
yeah like a metric cup of corn and see if it sparkles yeah you put that in your
soda stream with the water. You carbonate that shit and then you show us the results.
And then you send it to us in the mail.
You freeze it. No, wait, it would lose the carbon. Okay. You vacuum seal it.
You come to Boston first.
You bring your soda stream to us.
We do that.
We make the sparkling corn. We don't pay you back for the damages.
We keep the soda stream.
We keep it, we go and we buy SodaStream's proprietary Dr. Pepper flavor called Dr.
Pete.
Uh-huh.
And we just drink some Dr. freaking Pete.
Yeah, and then you go home, you stay home.
You go home empty handed and we say sucka.
And we say sucka.
We say ah, sucka.
We say ah.
We say sucka.
But if you want to take, if you want to.
I really want to know if it's possible.
Yeah.
If you want to partake in the sparkling corn challenge.
(laughter)
- What you need to do is take a--
- You take a soda stream, you fill it up with mostly water
and a little bit of corn.
- Like a cup of corn.
- Like a metric cup of corn.
- Like a standard metric cup.
- Like the cup in your kitchen.
- Like the size of one of your cups.
- You put--
- And put corn, cut it off the cob.
Don't put the cob in.
- You can use frozen corn.
- We don't want a sparkling cob.
'Cause you can't eat the cob to test it.
You can't eat it if it's corn on the sparkling cob.
Corn on the sparkling, normal corn on the sparkling cob.
(laughing)
It sizzles when you touch it.
You just feel it when you touch the cob.
So you put the corn in the soda stream.
And then you turn on the soda stream.
And then you send us those results.
You send us the spreadsheet of your results.
You send us your hypothesis and your data and your shit.
Your hypothesis and your scientific method.
And then you send us a video of you eating the corn and you say, "I just took the sparkling
corn challenge and I feel great."
I just took the sparkling corn experiments.
Yeah.
And in 2020 we're only doing experiments, no more challenges.
No more challenges, social experiments.
Social media experiments, scientific experiments, not social ones.
We're going to put launched a rocket to the moon and you put a bunch of spiders on if you superglue to
uh
You're a fork to a knife
Facing the same direction. Yeah
Yeah
What would happen?
That's called the super gluing a fork to a knife experiment and teens everywhere are going viral with it
What happens if you superglue?
A trash bag closed and fill it up with air
and jump on it like a trampoline.
I think you might, if you do a big enough contractor bag, it could just work as like a bean bag
chair.
I think it could work as a trampoline.
Yeah, that's true.
If it's a bouncy enough bag.
Yeah.
What would happen if your dad found out you were stealing his money?
Take the dad's money experiment.
I stole my dad's money.
You have to post it with the hashtag steal your dad's money experiment.
I stole my dad's money and then you have to make a video of me saying I stole my dad's money and he found out and I feel great.
Yeah, and I feel great.
Yeah.
I'm just chilling.
Ugh.
Yeah, I don't know what would happen if...
Ugh, boy.
Yeah, that's uh...
I feel like I fucking drooled in my sleep.
Look at that.
That's gross.
All the cum that leaked out of Pat's mouth.
No, it wasn't cum, it was drool.
Made a penis shape on the pillow.
It was mouth water.
It was mouth wash.
It was mouth wash from my mouth.
I make mouth wash out of my mouth.
My mouth was watering because I was having a dream about a big rotisserie chicken.
About a big rotisserie mouth wash.
About a big bottle of mouth wash.
Chicken boiled in Listerine.
I want this mouth wash chicken so bad.
It looks so good.
In your sleep you're just going.
(laughter)
- What time are we at?
- Oh, we're in an hour.
- All right.
- Merry Christmas everybody.
- Merry Christmas, we're not gonna do another regular--
- No normal episode, so--
- Yeah, just a premium.
- You guys enjoy this.
- We're on Christmas break now.
- We're on Christmas break,
and also Patrick's on Hanukkah break,
'cause I'm just being informed by text message
that Patrick has converted to Judaism about five minutes ago.
- Yep, I chose to be chosen.
all right thanks and thanks for a hundred dollars thank you for who is the last
person that i don't know what you shout out on the on the next regular and
starters we don't you said i really well this is very upsetting for whoever got
it
willful for next time you get a bit of shadow yet
if you if you were the person who pushed us over the edge to the pushes to the
limit of where you're going to go over the limit and you know we're talking
about
you know who you are
and we can do to the respect we do to but
were too lazy to look it up right now but we were so we do we're not lazy that's
we don't do it on premium always all right okay
god uh...
right dot i don't know when the next
regular or premium episode we had a week
uh... to speak
when i think i'm back next week now but will figure it out will do what
there will be a little bit of a man that's a little bit we say we'll figure
out
Yeah, but it's Caleb and nobody cares what he has to say.
Yeah, that's true.
Alright, bye!
Bye!
Bye.