You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
I'm fascinated by Zoom. I'm Caleb and I'm fascinated by Zoom settings.
Y'all are just...
I'm fascinated by the settings on Zoom. I'm fascinated by the green screen.
I love sliders.
I love all the volume knobs. I love buttons.
You're just jealous that I'm orange now.
Yeah.
Yeah, look at me.
What happened? I got orange. I look like the shock top guy.
Look at me. Oh, you got sunburn? How did you get orange? I don't know. I haven't seen the sun in so long and then I got a bunch of sun and then I found out that I do not tan even a little bit. I just get, I just turn orange.
You get you fake tan automatically?
Yeah, like that's like my body, like can't, I have no melanin receptors for it to actually
do anything, it just turns me orange.
I just look sick all the time.
I'm extremely red right now because I drank like a shit ton of energy drinks today.
I went out with my parents last night and they just kept feeding me drinks and I had
to drink, I did, you know.
You don't do the show. You can't be fed drinks.
No, they fed me. It was in my bubba.
They fed it to me from my bubba.
You don't have a bubba.
They were feeding it to me from my bubba.
They were drinking you drinks.
They were drinking you the drinks and they were feeding you the feeding.
Well, I'm very red right now because I realized today that there's so much niacin in energy drinks.
What's niacin?
It's something that makes you red.
What?
Yeah, it's red. It's a red
Name
Is that why you eat vitamins just to make your skin certain different colors niacin that's why a chemical compound
It's a B vitamin that's made and used by your body to turn food into by the way
I know that you're starting the Wikipedia article. There's no way
Radical high is the way that a person here. I'm nice and flush which appears red skin that may itch or burn
Are you itching and burning? No makes it easier. It doesn't make you red
It makes you will what color is a rash bitch. You don't have
But maybe I don't know also you're always you always get you have a red face you get flush you're Irish
That's what happens to you. Yeah, it's true. Yeah, it's not fucking nice up blaming niacin, dude
I my mom told me that there's a shit ton of niacin in them.
And I listen to my mom like a good boy.
She just said and then you went oh nice and that must make you
red that that yeah, I was like that must be why I'm red.
Look.
I don't know.
I my brain doesn't work correctly.
I am I'm pale like a vampire because I'm evil.
Yeah, I have so many holes in my head and I have so many
can concussions from skateboarding that it's I just tell
you she wear a helmet make you red.
the
You had a minor concussion because a pickaxe hit you right on the head.
Yeah, well I was going through my mining thing. I was going through my mining era.
Yeah, your phase. I remember that. It's so annoying. You're always walking around covered in soot.
Yeah. Me and the other guys would just get down and we would spelunk.
Oh my god, dude. Yeah, it was so annoying.
Not too many kids. I mean, my spelunking friends, I mean, they're my ride or die.
I love them to death. It's just, you know, I had to turn my back on the spelunking community.
It was so annoying, dude. That was like your worst error.
Yeah.
You walk around and you say, "Hey, check out this ore I found."
And then you'd hold it up and I'd be really excited to see an ore.
Yeah.
And then you'd show me a rock.
I'd try to look at it, too.
What's what an ore is?
You're shot in your headlamp right in my eyes. I couldn't see anything.
And I'd say, "Turn that off." And you say, "I need to see in the caves."
And I'd say, "We're not even in the caves."
And you'd say, "Well, isn't Earth the biggest cave of all?"
I said, "That doesn't even make any sense."
It is.
It's not. It's not an Audi cave.
Okay.
of
didn't believe you I still don't so I don't care if you believe me or not how
much you take your big how much you take your big box that has a handle that
comes up about you know three feet I would say that big handle box with one
wire that goes somewhere I don't know towards some rubble perhaps yeah how
much you just take that and just just push down on it so hard okay yeah why
don't you push down on your handle box with the wire and the rocks yeah all
I'll do that. Yeah, the handle box with the wire in the rocks. Yeah, you're a miner liar.
Miner liar. Miner liar, major laser. How about that? Not major laser. No, not major laser.
Mining would be so much easier if it would just have a robot. It would be so much easier if I
had a giant drill on my hand. Yeah. Oh, God, I wish. I wish. God, I gotta get back into mining.
Dude, I've been I've been really into online mining lately. It's kind of like therapy for me in a way, you know
I just love he's like therapy for me. Yeah
And but you know, i've never been i've never been actually I did go to therapy once when I was you guys you go on you
Go on amazon or you scroll through you get to pick exactly which which ores you're you're you're getting. It's great
You guys get ads all the time for these fucking like maybe it's just gonna stay up at night
but ads for these like apps that are like, uh
They're called like sleep sleep or like calm or like no
Sleepy calm never. I don't think i've seen an ad
really an app for an app in like
a long time are for um, adhd treatment like oh i've been getting those recently. Yeah
Yeah, have you guys ever?
Drugs
That was like, um, it was like called like the depression machine and it looks like a remote control and it's like you press this button and it cures your depression.
What?
Have you guys ever seen that ad?
No, that's sick.
I'm going to get that though.
Is it like a staples button?
It looks like, I remember it looking like a remote control.
Let me see if I can find this ad.
But I want to get one of those apps so bad.
I haven't worked up the will to download them yet.
did you guys know one of the symptoms of depression is persistent feelings of sadness?
Really?
No.
I had no idea.
I thought I had it until you said that.
Yeah, I thought depression just meant you get kind of bored.
Yeah, I thought depression is like you know that feeling when there's nothing on TV?
Yeah.
I thought that was what depression was.
Or when you open the fridge and there's nothing good in there.
Or you like played this game for too long and it's just kind of like you're just kind
of like going through the game and you're trying to like complete it 100%?
I found the ad here. Check this out. Oh.
Oh, wow. This link.
Cam, you can't even click this link.
This is just a, this is a hash code for Bitcoin, dude.
It's a J-5th. I can't even, oh my God. If you search depression machine ad, it's the
second picture.
Okay.
Somebody added a little caption that says capitalism was a mistake.
Oh, that's so sick.
I think depression can be solved with satisfying videos.
Absolutely.
A video of a guy scraping all the poppy seeds off an Everything Bagel, that's going to satisfy
your depression in a way.
Do you watch the toy truck restoration ones?
I don't watch anything.
I watch photography.
I don't watch those.
Like the Tonka trucks that are all rusted out and then they put some kind of magnet thing
on it and it like gets rid of the rust and they put it in this big like chemical bath.
They can fucking suck rust off a truck now? Yeah. Oh my fucking god dude. Oh dude you gotta
see these videos they're so good. They're oddly satisfying too. Yeah. I don't like those videos
man. Anytime somebody starts fucking taking a razor blade to a piece of soap I'm out bro. No.
That ain't me. No way. You know what I like? Oh yeah so I'm on vacation with my family
And I've accidentally gotten my entire family from ages 14 to 50 completely addicted to
online gambling.
Yeah?
Yeah, dude.
Wow.
I showed them the online Bitcoin slots the first night I was here.
Oh no.
With my entire family behind me on this laptop.
And it's all anybody's talked about for six days now.
like I have little kids coming up to me my fucking cousins like four year old
son you're just trouble for that we show me we show the slot machine again but
with all the all the fruits and candies the gorgeous grapes the gorgeous grapes
and me uh maybe a sumptuous strawberry for over little old me sir and see I'm
in a lot of trouble and I'll probably go to jail for this yeah yeah most likely
yeah I just wanted to let you guys know cuz that's satisfying to me you know
when all those, I've just seen them tumble.
- Yeah.
- All the fruits tumbling.
- You know what's oddly satisfying to me
is when I have like, when I look at my bank account
and I see like $50,000,
that's just like oddly satisfying in a way
I can't really explain.
There's something about it just feels right, you know?
- Yeah, dude.
- It fits exactly in there, you know?
The money fits perfectly.
- It fits perfectly into my bank account.
- That's a good point.
- Yeah.
- I keep spending too much money on coins.
- Not me.
I haven't spent a single dollar in 20 years.
Just kidding. I'm not spending it on coins.
I bought a new skateboard for my birthday.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, that's nice.
How was your birthday, by the way?
My birthday is, um, was a lot of fun.
We hung out on my roof.
It was nice.
Did everyone jump off?
No, there was one point.
So Joe decided to buy like a like a bouncy ball.
Like when you remember his infamous bouncy ball.
Yes.
Yeah, you're don't even get me started on that.
Yeah, it's ball.
Yeah, so he bought one from the bodega.
Yeah, bought one from the bodega and then like I guess he threw it towards Neil and Neil
just chucked it off the roof just immediately.
It was really funny.
Someone probably did.
Yeah, at the top of the Burj Khalifa.
Yeah.
In New York, New York City, Brooklyn.
Yeah, the Brooklyn.
Yeah.
So it reached terminal velocity pretty fast and it killed someone.
Stop wrinkling your head, man.
is that?
Uh, yeah, no, I, I, it's funny meeting, it's funny that I have a couple, me too, it's funny
that I have a couple friends like Joe in my life who are like grown men that like dog
toys.
Yeah, it's fun.
Yeah, I mean, I guess it's fun.
I mean, you're looking at two of the other ones.
Yeah, I guess.
Two of your other friends do that.
Yeah, yeah, I mean, I like.
Fuck, Cam, do you remember the Master of Million Ball?
What are you talking about?
Why are you so excited about a ball?
Shut up.
ball shut up just do it you're just mad you're just mad we have fun without you with our master
a million balls i'm not that mad about it but does it bounce super high no no it was a ball it was a
ball that had like a a sensor in it and then once you like you're supposed to get to a million bounces
oh i do remember you having yeah yeah and they didn't wait did you guys also get like a like an
Airplane or something?
Yeah, and but the master a million ball our location
Just bought toys
Realize that I was just talking about you guys when I said that
Million ball it has Bluetooth in it. So it connects to your phone. How many bounces do we get to can you see?
Let me see
That's so weak, okay, so there's a bunch of other people who have a million
But going by country don't say other people like you got a million it read that read who got a million
What the hell it just it just reset it. What did you do? I don't know read every what's our user?
Oh fuck. Are you her username was Bernie Mac?
So it would say so everybody get the master a million app and and I send a friend request to Bernie Mac
Bernie Mac is a
Korea is the
It was we've said North Korea because you can set like the location and I think the leaderboards are different in every region
So we're like
Yeah, we're gonna be really get it really easy if we're in North Korea
We're in the government doesn't let him have master a million balls in North Korea. That's what it'll do. Do you know cities?
is
I mean, I mean the longer you wait the
Time you miss out on bouncing. They have one that has spikes on it. How about a master a hundred ball, you know?
Be pretty easy
Master a hundred. Yeah
Times put it up on the show. Oh man
We had like a strategy to like we were gonna like we had a we had a drill that we attached it to we're spinning it
Around and it never ever like got it never if we spin it around on this drill
it will shake it enough to make it no need to impact dude that's what we found
out well you have to do is you have to put it on like a I think we almost
microwaved it - yeah that Patrick got scared you have to put it on like a
hydraulic press it like slowly pushes it down so just keeps bouncing very small
bounces over and over again I think that's the only way yeah to him million
It had to be infinite bounces. That's the thing.
What?
It has to be infinite bounces.
It has to be a-
What has to be-
The only way-
What has to be infinite bounces? We need a million.
We need a machine that can make it bounce infinity.
[Laughter]
That's-
Okay.
[Laughter]
So you need- here's what you need.
You need a ta- you need an elevator in a tower
That every bounce it goes down one floor so that it doesn't ever stop bouncing
It needs to be at the top of the burj khalifa and it needs to go down like maybe like six inches every every floor basically
So that it just always is like, you know
Fucking one foot above the ground or whatever. That's what you think. We need the mario steps
Listen, can I read 64 the ones that somebody had a here's a review on it from uh amazon
don't buy this it doesn't work at all even bought a new battery and installed it only time number
goes up is when you use a screwdriver to drive to send the number to the app so this person also used
the same did the same thing that we did oh shit also it won't connect properly to the app nothing
on this worked it was a dead battery when i got it so not only did i waste the money buying it
but also money for an extra battery it's been nothing but a headache and a huge disappointment
to my son as this was his birthday present he was really looking forward to dude we're gonna
That's the worst birthday present of all time. I feel like, just get him a normal ball.
Yeah, here's the only ball that has like a chore attached to it.
Yeah, the only ball that also doesn't bounce because it has too much electronics inside
it to make the Bluetooth work. If a kid hits a million, they should earn their freedom though.
Absolutely.
They should be able to be emancipated.
That's true.
No matter what age, if they hit a million bounces. Because you know that that's a
self-sufficient person. They can do whatever they need to. They'll make anything happen.
The different colors of Master of Million Balls are different prices.
Really?
We had the green one.
Well, yeah. So, no, we had a blue one, I think.
No, it was green.
Okay.
Where did you buy this?
The green one's $9.99, the blue one's $14.09, and the red one's $10.18.
Damn.
We bought this at Walgreens.
I might have to go pick one up, actually. This is starting to sound really good.
Yeah. We bought this, I remember Cam had money left over on a Walgreens gift card.
Yeah, that's what it was. That's why we got the...
Well, that's why we got the Thanos copters. Yeah
You should we need a new Walgreens gift card. This should be a like a
social credit score type thing
Where the amount of bounces you have is like directly is a reflection of what kind of person once once I do once I get to
New York me and Pat are gonna do toy review vlogs together. Oh, it's gonna be great. Can I be involved?
to
the
that
same
might be pregnant you guys if you got pregnant first of all be a miracle yeah
right because you don't think you have a uterus well cam was I with with you and
I was trying to explain that Walt Disney urban legend and I just yeah yeah you
were with me what is just like we were we were at lunch and Pat just said a
bunch of people like it's a thing that Walt Disney if a man gets pregnant do
they get all Walt Disney's money?
(laughter)
What are you talking about?
I was so tired and I was just like...
I don't know. No, we were talking about
the pregnant man emoji.
Oh, that's what we were talking about.
So there was a reason that I brought it up. I'm just saying that like...
I was just trying to say like,
oh, like, didn't Walt Disney say that
like the first biologically pregnant man gets all of the money in his estate?
Which was I lifted up on Snopes immediately because I felt like a fucking idiot.
Yeah.
And it's not true.
It's just-
Really?
Yeah.
[Laughter]
Yeah, that's not true, man.
I mean, if I was a millionaire, I'd say that shit.
You had one million dollars, you'd say.
If you had a million bucks, you would say, "You know what?
I got a million just so you guys know if any man gets pregnant they just have all this money
I
Wouldn't say that I'd say like oh like like
Right would say that got pregnant she could have I would say son
I'm you're only getting your inheritance if you become pregnant if my wife is pregnant
She gets a hundred million dollars for me. She gets a hundred cents
Yeah, I don't know. I don't know. I think that's kind of a kind of a fun urban legend, you know
It's like he was probably just making a joke. No, you know what a fun urban legend is
Mothman the fucking Walt Disney pregnant man who gives a shit
What do you mean? Mothman is not an urban legend. Yeah, it's not that's a cryptid. He's a he's a rural legend. No, it's Seattle
No, it's not. I'm sick. I'm you know, what's for Seattle bitch just like Seattle. What are you talking about?
the
like a like a mom like complaining just like yeah these legends are a bit too
urban yeah yeah bigfoot bigfoot what's your whatever happened to good old
family legends huh yeah yeah legends between a man and a woman
whatever having a Catholic legends Christ well that's a good point yeah
the
people yeah that's the thing he didn't say like he just said he said just like
something that like like your stupid cousin would tell you mm-hmm like he
said that I didn't even say I didn't even he said he got on stage and by the
way also he's probably rusty man he probably hasn't done a concert in like a
year and a half yeah so he gets on stage and he says if you don't have AIDS put
you
it's public health. It's public health. Yeah, right? Yeah. And now he has to go on Twitter
and just constantly be like, I'm sorry. I didn't, the first apology he did was like,
I didn't mean people with AIDS. I meant gay guys. Oh fuck. I meant not gay. Ah fuck. And
so he's just been fucking slipping on his. Yeah. Dude, Dua Lipa apologized for some reason.
Yeah. I don't even know who that is. I thought that was a lipstick brand. Yeah.
the
Doug a aids man as a show a show of support
Doug a his rapper ever is rapper ever. Yeah
It's like an Xbox live songs. All the songs are just like it's just the name
Just the name, but I'm not gay
Yeah, I had my way out of a PR nightmare a
His his his beats always sound really funny. Yeah. Yeah, they're always doing clown music is yeah
It's like it's like we have weird out songs playing behind his lyrics very funny beats
he has like trap remixes of like
Mario Kart music as is like like all of his beats sound like that
you are you're thinking of the video where somebody put his face into Mario Kart and then and then played a
Remix of his song with the Mario Kart music that is literally what is in your head right now? Yeah
He made oh my god, dude this
He's always he's always just rapping over the Thomas the tank engine theme song. I don't know what his deal is
Yeah, that's I mean I did like notorious BIG, but when he did that Thomas the tank engine song
I thought he got soft. Yeah, he did the party in the USA song that didn't make any sense cuz he was dead by then
Yeah, very confusing.
I don't want to, you know, I say I don't want to, but I do to bring it back to master a
million, but I'm still on the master million Amazon page.
They have like the info about the master million ball and it has like, you know, like a little
table and it's like, like color blue brand master a million sport type bounce.
the
I saw part of the opening ceremony, but yeah, me too.
I saw Ireland come out.
What happens with the opening ceremony?
They just what is the part where they they mourned the Israelis
who died at the Olympics?
That was the part that I saw.
Oh, yeah, that's how I just turned it on for that and then turned it off
just to show your respect.
Yeah, yeah.
That is pretty much the only part of it.
I saw, though, I I watched just the highlights
of the the skateboarding stuff because I want to like, you know,
That's the only thing I've ever paid attention to.
And I didn't know
what was the fucking thing?
Oh, there is.
I forget what skater it was, but he like fell in, like, hit his nuts
into the rail.
That's pretty funny.
You did that on purpose.
There is sound of skaters are notoriously pranksters.
It's not like not the way you're thinking.
It wasn't like he fell like on his board and like, you know,
like went nuts down.
He like fell down and then the him sliding on the ground.
he hit his nuts on a standing pole.
Sounds like he shouldn't be at the fucking Olympics.
Sounds terrible.
I think that Olympic skateboarding should be like X-game skateboarding,
but instead of a receiving ramp where they can land,
there should just be a fire hydrant they have to hit their nuts on.
Because that's the only reason I find skateboarding entertaining at all,
is when they get really hurt.
It should be about ragdolling.
Yeah, it should literally be the skate to thrasher ragdoll thing.
Yeah.
Angel Caro Navarez suffers brutal groin injury in Olympic skateboarding.
Brutal groin injury.
That would be a good album name, dude.
That would be good.
Olympics is very...
Hush hush?
Yeah, it's very hush hush a bit.
Yeah.
Yeah, no, they don't. If you post anything like even like you watching it on the TV,
um, like a clip of you watching it, the Olympics will try to take it down. It's yeah, I don't know
how you even watch them. I don't I don't. So I think Neil turned on the Olympics. I don't I
wouldn't have been able to find out how to watch it. I feel like I mean, not that I would care
enough to try and find out with any like urgency, but I don't know what you're supposed to do.
Is it on cable? It's somewhere. It's just fucking awesome, dude. They like every time
We're getting destroyed in skateboarding in the USA.
That makes sense.
We suck at every- Japan and Brazil.
Really?
Yeah.
Well that's okay.
Yuto Horigome and Kelvin Hoffler.
You might as well be telling me that we're getting destroyed in like rock, paper, scissors
in the Olympics.
Like I don't have pride for the Olympic skateboarding team.
Why not?
Because I don't give a fuck.
I like, I have pride for the swimming team because they, when they put the caps on they
look bald.
you seen the uh...
uh... what are they called
the the skateboarding uniforms they look sick
now let me look at the the they were jinkos
now they were let me guess big pants a shirt in a beanie
is that uh... fucking uniform a come on and i miss you
is he fucking easy from the fucking skateboarders
but uh... they yet they look sick i wanna i saw somebody wearing it is
so they can't assure the b_n_a_ yet
That makes perfect sense.
But I saw somebody wearing the Team USA shirt yesterday and I was like,
damn, it does look really tight. It looks so cool.
It looks like a, it looks like a, like a, a loading screen for like an app,
like a Google app. It looks like, it looks like corporate art.
It looks like when you see like, that's para, that's the artist para. Para.
Yeah. P A R R A.
They should get para on it.
And just working on the the chromecast app because I think they could do some serious work there. Yeah, looking at this these shirts
You think that would be flames?
I think I think I would change the game yet. Yeah para
Yeah, I think P I e t para
Pipe yeah, yeah, his name's in names. I cup Pete's Pete's parpa
Each I don't give a fuck about the skate, but I do like the Olympics. Uh, I think the Olympics is cool
yeah, I just like that like every four years they like
They like tear down a favela or like part of the Amazon. Yeah
They build like a hockey stadium in Africa. Yeah, and then they leave
Yeah, I remember like learning that they bunch of money into this pretty cool that they like like they look like build it all new
Every time yeah, like what?
Why like listen the fucking the circus can bring the same tent around for yeah, you guys don't need to build
Yeah, why don't they just do that? Why don't we do? Yeah, why isn't the Olympics just why don't we just have them?
Why don't we just have them all in America and we just have the we can just yeah all this stuff here
That's actually so we'll keep it for you guys. Yeah, put it in
Oh, I don't know New York City greatest city in the fucking world right in the middle. Yeah
Yeah, who the fuck wants to go to Rio?
Nobody. Yeah. Well, I know I know a blue parrot who might
it
not
google
and a friend named Jewel and a friend named Linda.
- You don't know a single parrot's name.
You'd have to Google every single one.
- And a friend named Tulio.
- Really?
- And Raphael.
- How do you know that?
- Raphael?
- And Louise.
- Doesn't TJ Miller play someone in one of those?
- Let me see.
- I think that's from that, that's like that.
That's like that two year span
where every animated movie had TJ Miller.
- No, you're thinking of how to train your dragon.
I'm thinking of a lot of movies, man. I think he's in Big Hero 6 too.
Yeah. Yeah. He just, it's funny that he was going
so family friendly for like two years. Yeah.
And then he was like... What's he in now?
Jail? He was in Underwater. He was in that alien
ripoff. It was like very recent. And it was like,
huh, like weird that he's in this. Yeah.
Yeah. Remember he was in Deadpool?
He was in Deadpool. He played Deadpool's brother or something?
played we played weasel yeah yeah you play that in real life too hey yeah yeah let's
rip on this guy hey tj miller fucker yeah what a bomb go off at your fucking barbershop what's
that hair all about student kingdom you call a bomb you call a bomb thread in on your own
hair yeah come on fucking loser i think he had a stroke or some shit at one point that's
pretty bad which i think you know you have if you have a that's a fun thing about having
a stroke is like or a brain injury.
So you have some level of excusable behavior, I think.
You know?
Like you can start like, I think if you have a stroke, you can just never flush the toilet
again and like if someone gets mad at you, they're mean.
Pretty good position to be in.
I think what I would do if I had a stroke is I would say that I have to eat a bunch of
candy every day.
Yeah, or it will get worse.
Exactly.
also
for something that your wife did. I just had to go to a fucking doctor patient
conference again it's so annoying. He was telling my parents about all my issues.
Yeah and then he touched my butt. He touched my what? That always sucked.
When the doctor put his whole hand into your thingy. Yeah I only had it
like squeeze your nuts. I only had it happen like three times in my life and
in the most recent time, I was like 14 and it was right before I did football or some
shit and it was like the nurse from Anima of the state.
It was like the hottest girl ever.
And then I never went back to the doctor.
I think that's actually the last time I went to the doctor.
That scared you off?
Yeah, yeah, it scared me off.
I was like, "I don't want this, dude."
Dude, I'm too young to be fucking all these random nurses, you know?
I just can't do that.
the
is
airport after that because I had to leave like two hours later.
Oh my god, do I have a werewolf paw?
Wait, hold on.
*laughter*
Wait, hold on. I think I'm growing horns.
No, I'm not. That's just my head.
Is there a demon's mark?
On my collarbone?
I thought tennis elbow was something different too.
I thought like a...
Oh my god, I think I have elbow grease, guys.
Also, specifically
like a thing that you get from
like doing a specific thing that you do not do.
do not do.
I thought-
Do I have cauliflower ear from fighting in the UFC?
What the fuck is wrong with me?
I fall on my elbow a lot when I skate, so I thought that like I thought tennis elbow is
when it blows up like a tennis ball.
Tennis elbow is you thought it was when you have a bruise on your elbow.
It looks like a tennis ball?
Yeah.
So if a bruise on your elbow gets as big as a tennis ball, that's tennis elbow.
That's pretty okay. Alright. Just making sure. That that's what we're doing. I'm so fucking
stupid.
No, you smart. You smart. Oh boy. Shit. I think I have hound's teeth. Oh my god.
I think I have Eye of Newt, guys.
[Laughter]
I think I have Pole Vulture's leg. Oh my god.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck you guys. I just contracted Hitchhiker's Thumb.
[Laughter]
Guys, I think I have... I think I caught a Widow's Peak.
I think I have a Brazilian butt lift.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, no! I knew it was gonna happen at some point in my life.
But yeah, I've been thinking I'm having a heart attack. I was in the airport having all of the
symptoms of a heart attack. And then I was like, "I'm just going to get on this plane."
And I had a heart attack thing phase last year too.
Yeah.
The worst thing is when you tell somebody, "I think I might be having a heart attack." And
they say as a joke, "Yeah, you probably are because you clearly are not." And then it makes it worse.
100%. Yeah. And then I just keep having... I keep feeling like somebody's karate chopping me in my
artery and my neck and I just seem like but I'm still not going to go to the doctor.
Of course not.
I hate it so much.
It should work itself out.
Yeah, it's fine.
If I just like if I don't smoke cigarettes for enough days in a row then I'll be back
to normal.
Dude, I've been smoking so many cigarettes since Thomas got here.
Thomas just kept feeding me cigarettes.
Thomas is a demon, dude.
Yeah.
Absolute demon.
This is your fault, man.
I'm calling you in.
No, we're calling you out.
Yeah, you got me hooked on cigarettes again.
You fucker dude.
Yeah, and I'm doing it in tandem with the Juul.
So I'm just like, yeah that's bad.
No, no, you're gonna end up like him dude.
This fucking boy talks like a cartoon turtle.
Yeah, man, I gotta.
Hey dude, you want 20 cigarettes for free?
They're 4 cents in Texas.
Yeah, these are real cheap where I'm from.
Yeah, my dad hand rolls these actually.
Yeah, I'm actually gonna get you addicted to cigarettes again.
They're actually signing tobacco. It's yard mulch
every single cigarette
He sounds like Bobby Hill he sounds like Bobby Mountain like you didn't sound like Bobby Hill
Now you don't you don't know now we need to go to Texas do I need to show you boys
I don't know what the south is all about.
Yeah, dude, I want to go to Texas so bad.
I know, I said it first, fuck you.
If you want us to do a show in Texas, say yeah.
Yeah, if anybody has any...
Put your phone in the air.
If you want us to do a show in Texas and you do not have AIDS, put your phone in the air.
I'm sure there's one of you listening who has some connection to a club in Texas or
something.
Please message us and we won't ignore you like we usually do.
Promise, pinky swear.
I want to take these boys to Bucky's dude. Oh, dude. I want to go to Bucky's. I want to go
Bucky's is the sickest shit ever man. I want to go to the um, the
the Klan Museum
Burn it down. Oh, yeah, only the crosses right? Yeah
Yeah the upside down ones oh
Still it doesn't
You can burn it up, Seth.
Do they have one of those in Texas? I just assume they did.
A Klan? Why? Okay, why would they have a Klan museum? Who would pay for that?
A racist guy?
You think that the, that, well maybe in Texas, I don't know.
But I don't think that any-
I don't think that there is a Klan museum.
That you knew about that you were, like I didn't-
They even researched it?
I didn't assume that the joke would be both that you're making up a Klan museum and that
you wanted to go there. I thought that-
that
I want to go to the gas station in the house from Texas Chainsaw Massacre. Yeah, me too.
It's gonna take us five hours to get there from anywhere that we could.
That place is too big. We'd have to go like a two-day trip.
But we will do it. If we go to Texas and we don't go there, I will kill both of you.
I want to get Texas barbecue.
And I say that only to hold you guys accountable for making what I...
We should go to Texas Roadhouse.
I already made it happen so that cam saw the corn sign. So this one's on you pat. Oh, I can't drive
That's again on you. Neither can cam on you. So you're yeah caleb you're gonna
It's on i'm gonna be enjoying myself
To i'm gonna be at one of the beautiful beaches of south texas under under a palm tree
With a fucking cuban lady and we're gonna be making out and i'm gonna be sipping a martini
on the beach and it's gonna be and then I come up behind you I got I got a chainsaw that they
they still have the chainsaw at the house that you really used to kill everybody.
That's not true.
You and it's true you would know if you went there with us.
Man I wanna.
Now I wanna go actually.
I wanna go to I wanna go to Texas I wanna.
I wanna get caught in a tumbleweed like a hamster ball you know and I'll roll around the whole state
and I wanna attack people in it.
Yeah I wanna get a big cat.
Here's the thing, I just want to be let on the loose.
Uh-huh, absolutely.
I want to be, I want nothing more than a spinning newspaper article to appear on screen that says
Caleb on the loose.
I want to go psycho in the desert and see something that shouldn't be there.
Me too.
I want to see a cactus for the first time.
Do you guys want to do ayahuasca in Texas?
We should do ayahuasca.
But like not in, but like in the middle of Dallas.
Yeah.
In Austin.
In the streets.
Yeah.
In like a comedy club in Austin.
Yeah, yeah.
some comedy club that like doesn't want us there the worst trip of all time yeah
mm-hmm in the middle of the show do I I don't I'm not sure what ayahuasca even
is I believe it might be a cactus I think yeah I think no you're thinking of peyote
I think it's a cactus actually I think they're both cacti I think they're both
cacti I thought ayahuasca was like like similar to ayahuasca is a spell from
Harry Potter yeah yeah it was cuz it's spell that if you go to Peru and pay
a
It comes in a can.
It's a drink from a can that you find in the woods.
Okay.
Just making sure.
It's like it's made of a vine and a shrub.
Yeah.
Speaking of cans in the woods, you guys ever seen Power Rangers Turbo the movie?
No.
Is that the one where they jump out of the plane in the beginning?
No, that's Mighty Morphin.
That's the only one I've seen.
Power Rangers Turbo is the one where they're driving cars and they have to save this little
like dwarf guy.
Yeah, it was you.
a
is
like salt and pepper shakers that look like the Green Bay Packers and it'll be $500,
but you can get them. But it's the only place in the world you can shop and have things
delivered to your house.
True.
No, it's worth it.
It's the only place that you can get something delivered.
Yeah. It's like, "Fuck, dude. I want to go get a new microwave, but I really don't want
to have to go to Walmart. So I guess I have to book a flight and order it on SkyMall and
have it sent to my house."
you know this would I just think about the about mining again you know they
should do they shouldn't minecraft should do a thing where they send you any ores
that you mine in real life I think that would revitalize it I think like if you
like you could have like a special chest that if you get diamonds they have to
send you diamonds or if you get coal they have to send you coal I'd be like
an augmented reality yeah exactly and you could also scan in minerals that you
find
like
other than that it's all gold bars and diamonds for me.
- But you already made a billion dollars,
why are you still working to do a contract work?
- I wanna use my money to help spread freedom
across the world and shut down people
who are doing things in countries that we don't, you know?
- Yeah, I guess I would be so good
at being a stupid billionaire,
I would buy the coolest shit.
- What would you buy?
- Dude, I'd have like a pinball machine.
that's a- *laughs*
*laughs*
dude, that- you're trying to-
this is like a- a fucking like vanity fair
article that's like
"this billionaire's going crazy
he just bought a pinball machine"
yeah, yeah the front- front
page of like national inquirer
"billionaire playboy
purchases pinball machine"
"plays all night" "plays all night"
"you know what i'd get?"
"stays up all night"
*laughter*
Way past the bedtime.
Stays up on school night, playing Pumbaa Machine.
Dude, I would straight up,
I would have like a, if I had like a blank
check type of scenario,
I would just buy everything from blank check.
Yeah, just buy like
Sock 'Em Boppers or whatever.
Yeah. And a best friend that's an
adult, like he has in that. Yeah.
And like, doesn't he have a wife too?
I don't remember if he has a wife.
I do think that he's 11 years old, so
hope that that's a movie that I thought I never saw then saw a scene from it and was like oh I've
seen this like a hundred times. Yeah it's dictated every part of like how you live I feel like is
blank check. Yeah that's a very influential movie on your brain whether you want to admit it or not.
Yeah I would I would agree I don't yeah I honestly I'm thinking about I honestly can't think of like
a single giant thing that I would buy if I was like I would buy a bunch of stuff that I would
just buy like a lot of stuff but I can't think of like what would be like a big like million
dollar like I can't think of anything. I think I would just I think you probably just buy
houses like everywhere right? Yeah that's the move right? If I had billions of dollars
I would probably I would just buy a lot of cool shirts. Yeah I would just buy like all
the movies I wanted or something. Movies that I wanted or like cool shirts or like cool
pants or or cool shoes.
What about the socks?
Cool hats.
Yeah, what about cool socks?
Cool socks or cool car.
Cool hot socks or something?
You know what?
I would get another chain.
Nice.
We already have one.
Why do you need two chains?
Well, I can switch them out.
I can wear one chain with certain outfits and then, you know.
So you need like a different color chain?
Yeah.
Okay.
Maybe like a red chain.
Oh, that'd be so badass.
You'd look like the devil so hard.
Yeah.
Oh, that'd be so badass.
You'd look like the devil so hard.
Yeah.
Oh, that'd be so badass.
You'd look like the devil so hard.
Yeah.
Oh, that'd be so badass.
so
I don't know. A tattoo?
I'd probably get the best haircut ever.
I'd get some good food.
Oh my god.
You would probably get some good food.
I would, yeah.
Personal shift.
If I was a billionaire, Uber eats every night.
Saying everything that's just like within, I could already do that pretty much.
You will not believe how many times I would go to Sweetgreen a week, dude.
dude if I was a billionaire.
Well this is the conversation.
Dude if I was a millionaire I would get a new skateboard.
This is the conversation of like people who think they're going to get rich from like
playing Monopoly on McDonald's cups.
Like this is exactly that type of rich that I want to be.
I want to be like the dumbest person ever who lucks into having 20 million dollars and
then just buys like, yeah, like has like 10 shoes and I think that's a lot of shoes.
Yeah.
Be so awesome dude.
like a washer and dryer and just putting it in my apartment being like, "I don't know,
I don't have to spend money downstairs anymore. It's just in the middle of my living room. It's
not hooked up to anything." One of those rich people who renovates their house but has no idea
what they're doing. So it's like an extra room that's on the second floor that's just being held
up by poles. Yeah.
Oh, dude.
Yeah.
So many of those in New Hampshire, just rich people just expanding their houses.
It's so awesome. It's the coolest kind of rich person has to have. Stuff where they're like,
they like look into a house and there's like an ornate, beautiful, priceless fireplace and they
just paint over it because they don't like it. And stuff like that.
Cool.
There's a building I saw, like a house that had just like, what's it called? One of those stone,
it's not like a, not called a crow's nest. Is it like a-
Like a-
A widow's walk?
not a widow's walk but like it looked like part of a castle was like a turret
no it's like a moat a drawbridge to their house that's something if I did have a
billion dollars I would draw bridge yeah have a drawbridge I would I get it
Aubrey is it the thing that's like it comes up out of the top of the house
there's like a fence around it.
It's like and you can like walk around
kind of like a steeple.
That's a widow's walk.
I'm pretty sure it looked like
they had a steeple attached to their house.
That's pretty fucking cool.
Yeah.
And the rest of the house
just looked like shitty, like,
you know, McMansion.
Yeah, but like just fucking steeple
in like the corner.
It is so funny to see like
like houses in like situate and stuff.
They'll have like they have like a widow.
They have like a widow's walk up there.
But it's like you guys also
like have a balcony and you're like
like five minute walk from the beach.
Like why would you ever want to go?
Yeah, that's like like five by five feet.
You can't do anything up there.
I think it's like those are just your yard.
Those are just there for your like wife to kill herself on.
Exactly.
That's why it's called a widow's on a rainy day.
It's literally so after you die, your wife can stand up there
and go.
Yeah.
Oh, I'm so hungry.
But what was the fucking thing?
I was like, oh, oh, it's like a the make like they'll have
like windows like for like circular
windows and then just one like big yeah
that like you could see everything in the
house oh god I fucking I love looking at
McMansions just cuz it like they have
the worst rich people have the worst taste
yeah rich people have no taste at all
except for the rich people who get
mansions like that and then build like
stores in their basement like fake
stores that's the oh cool shit ever like
the yeah that's rental place exactly and
there's one where there's ones where
like they have their basement looks like
a street and they have storefronts on either side. That rocks so much, dude.
That's actually what I would do.
Yeah. That's my childhood dream is to live in a house that has small houses inside it.
That's your childhood dream?
Is to walk downstairs and go to an Applebee's?
If I was 10 years old and I got billions of dollars and they were like, "You can build
whatever house you want," that's what I would do. I would have something that's supposed to be
outside in my house. I put like a roller coaster in like the living room or something. I'd get it.
I'd build like a house with like traps all over the place. Yeah. That's like a piranha tank under
like a single tile in the kitchen or something. Yeah. And if somebody steps on it, that'd be
pretty funny. I would. Yeah. I'd have paintings you could look through the eye holes in. I would
just make a haunted house, I guess. Absolutely. Yeah. I think that's probably the best move. I
I would just make like a shot like a spot for spot remake of the Remington mansion where
there's just like oh yeah that shit's sick dude yeah I found the I found the
backpack from Power Rangers yeah it doesn't look cool at all what are you
talking about I can't even it's just it's a backpack what I don't understand
he can get a can of water out of the backpack so it's a way to really this is
a thing this is a backpack that can hold something it's it's Tommy's oh my god it
doesn't I assume that it like made a water can of water but the can of water
is just in there and he just takes it out so that yes you got to see it maybe
you gotta see it to believe it so it's a backpack that you can store something in
and then get it out of no I think it is Cameron this is where you power box
that's a backpack do you you said it was a backpack yeah just called the power
box a backpack called it a backpack a hundred times you I'm not letting you
back down from this. No. You see this Pat? Do you see this? Look at this. Ready? Pat,
I'm about to blow your fucking mind, okay? No, you're not. Yeah. See this? Wait, okay,
hold on. Wait, ready? There's no way. Well, he won't be able to get it out because there's
not a device. Oh man, how could I? What am I supposed to do? What are you gonna do? Ready?
ready?
WHAT?
you see that?
no fucking way!
and watch this
well it can't be real water then
oh my god
yeah that's not a powerbox
but then Cameron
tell me how that water tastes
oh my god it tastes exactly like my nalgene plastic
oh that's so good
yeah
that's not a powerbox
You have a power box.
That's so fucking stupid.
Um...
The only device like that that I ever really wanted was the microwave from Spy Kids that invents food.
Oh, dude, that thing was so fucking sick.
See, that's where we differ, 'cause I wanted the alien hybrids.
The mutant animals.
What?
Whatever they were. The snake lizard.
The spider monkey.
That is pretty cool, too. I did want the tiny one.
Oh, for Spy Kids 2.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
Well, we can talk about the whole series, is one thing.
talking about well because sir I got confused because I thought you're
talking about Spy Kids 1 and I thought you're talking about Floops Fuglies.
No, those I would not I want those. I mean yeah they're saying it there I mean listen
to what they say backwards they're saying he's a madman help us save us you
know I mean yeah I don't want to hear that all the time. Nah dude that's a you
wouldn't hear that until you reversed it so it's okay. It's true but you know
sometimes yeah it happens. Sometimes it happens that you hear stuff backwards.
I guess I want the mom from Spy Kids too.
Yeah, you know you're walking backwards into a room?
Yeah.
What did you say?
The mom from Spy Kids would be a pretty good invention to have as well.
What was the mom from Spy Kids name?
Mommy, Mommy, Mommy, ooooh.
Mommy.
Mommy, Mommy, yes, Mommy, yes.
I think that was her full name.
Oh, Carla.
Carla Guguino.
Guguino?
Yeah, I'd like to Google
a picture of her
her weeno
and look at my weeno and touch my weeno
you can do that whenever man
i dont know how to use that
i dont know how to use that fucking god damn google
you know that about me
you dont have to do it right now
i think i do have to do it right now since you seem to be pushing me towards just doing it
im not pushing you
whats her name carla guguino
uh huh
oh man shes old now
put that away
No, no, no, but you're we know away put your google, you know away. No, it's not a good
We know it is a good we know but it is not a good we know
What's your?
Little way. Yeah, I love that. I actually I want that grandpa from Spy Kids way more. Yeah
Yeah, he's funny as hell Ricardo. Yeah from Fantasy Island. No, it's for Spy Kids
See, I'll did you know here's my here's my fan theory dude
Spike's three was actually all that was an episode of fantasy.
And that was his fantasy all along.
You know, he was like, it's three people's fantasies.
His fantasy is that he can't walk in any walks.
Yeah. Wouldn't that be awesome?
That would be cool, actually.
Yeah. I think we've talked about it before, but it's just so funny.
And we talk about like a hundred times and he just runs away.
It's like one of the best moments in movie history, I would say.
Yeah. Is being able to walk and then just running.
I wish that there was videos of people, you know when they, when they, it's like somebody's
first time walking, they hook them up to some like robot legs, and they just jump out of
the window and they just sit there gone forever.
It's like all they've ever wanted to do is run away from their fucking family and the
doctor.
So they just keep running.
It's pretty cool.
I would love to watch Spy Kids 3 with you guys when I get to the city.
Oh me too, that'd be great.
remember soon yeah do you remember I was just looking at the Spy Kids Wikipedia
and Tony Tony Shalhoub is in that movie and his character's named is Alexander
minion yeah and he kills it by the way yeah oh dude the lube he's doesn't he
become a flugel he becomes a flugel a flugel a flupes flugel yeah he becomes
one he isn't at the start but then he gets all these fingers in his damn head.
His head turns to hands. I know I've definitely mentioned it before but Elijah Wood in Spy Kids
3 like if you look at his character's name the guy and you look at the guy on the Spy Kids wiki
there's like a quote section and there's the first quote is "I'm the guy" and it says the guy when he
introduces himself and then the last quote is "cake" the guy right before his death.
Dude, if I was a flugli, I feel like you'd pull a lot of strange.
I feel like you would know.
Yeah.
If I was a flugli, I think you'd know.
Dude, I think you would be cleaning up at the bars with a flugli.
You walk up to a woman, you say, "Listen, take a look at me.
Tell me you don't want to go meet me in the bathroom right now."
Yeah.
"Look at all these fucking...
Hey, bring 50 of your friends.
I don't give a fuck.
Let's go."
I got two other heads you can kiss.
That's right.
You can kiss two heads at once.
You ever been with a guy with two heads before?
Bitch, I'm built like a fucking...
I'm built like an underwater mine. You better
Jump on any part of my body you're gonna have a good time
That's nasty. It's right, but it's nasty - no flu Glee would ever say that shit. Come on
One of them would yeah me. There's one of them. That was really I am I do
In the background he was not he was not doing nice things. No, dude. Yeah. Yeah one of the fingers
on
the internet.