You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
Uh, well you're here to see us, so let's make some noise for a podcast about this!
[cheering]
[clapping]
Keep walking, keep clapping, Jesus Christ!
[cheering]
[clapping]
Thank you, thank you, thank you guys.
What the fuck is up? How you guys doing tonight?
Yeah? Is this the most insane night of your life?
Yeah? Is this just topping it off? You've been doing some crazy shit, huh?
Yeah, it's late. You've all been doing shit already.
It's way past my fucking bedtime. It's 10pm almost. Jesus Christ.
It might be past 10pm.
I don't even know what fucking time it is.
So I wanted to mention real quick, with the first show, before hand, we started playing
jump around on loop for an hour and a half.
Nobody noticed or thought it was funny, so that was lucky.
But then, I guess, in our wake as we left to go downstairs to smoke a cigarette,
somebody in this bar turned on "Drink Kanye" playlist.
Which, hey, made a respect.
Big step up.
Yeah, big step for you guys.
You guys seem to not notice or care also.
So maybe you should have gone back to jump around.
You know, which would have made me laugh more.
Probably only you.
Oh wait, alright, thank fucking Christ that that's a different shirt.
We were sure you and him had the same shirt on.
These stupid guys walked over here and they saw a red font.
They were like, "This guy's wearing the same shirt as you, Cameron."
And we almost blamed them.
different I was like we have to go buy Cameron a shirt yeah we almost did how
embarrassing is that I would get you confused yeah we were gonna do that
I'm like 50 minutes about that right now.
So we're in big trouble.
This sucks. You guys are getting the loose show.
The first one, you know, is all scripted, it's all very tight.
We're fucking out here.
Is anybody...
Get your foot off the mixer.
Is anybody coming from out of town?
Just one person?
From Michigan.
Are you bloat?
I heard a woo over there.
Michigan, huh? All for this or for something real?
Yeah, I need an alibi.
Oh, this is good. This is great. I love that they arrange these seats because I feel like
I'm on a date with you, sir. And I don't hate it, I'm going to be honest with you.
How about you?
You guys are moving way too fast.
I'm sorry, this is inappropriate.
Where was the other woo from?
right here where there's a third moon tell the fucking truth to me
where are you from tennessee tennessee for this for this what the fuck
give a round of applause for tennessee wow and you and you over here i feel bad because i'm still
freaking ass oh that doesn't count like no fucking that doesn't count at all it's technically out of
town I guess dude all Massachusetts is kind of Boston though right? Worcester yeah that's the
same yeah respect to Tennessee so are you uh are you like a crazy person?
yeah we're gonna end up like Selena
yeah wait did you come here to kill us is that what happened? yeah is this like
well that's a long way to fucking travel just to watch a show
I'm gonna find the first 10 minutes to fucking with you.
I also don't know that like if I traveled that far to kill some podcasters, I might not wait for the late show.
Good point. I will say, if anyone was gonna kill us, last show, guy came from fucking London, dude.
Oh yeah.
Oh, that guy was great. I loved that guy.
He was great, but, but, uh...
What the fuck is wrong with you, man?
He was here for a work thing, he explained it.
That's an excuse man, you know. Come on baby.
You know, he's here for this outfit dude.
Did anybody even notice how good I look?
[Cheering]
That's right. That's fucking right dude.
Do you guys see these scrubs?
Who would ever have a dressing room with nines?
These two.
You're a nurse? No, I was calling you a scrub.
[Laughter]
Wearing those as scrubs to like,
I'll be taking care of your father this, uh,
You're about to get fucking put under for surgery and you just see a backwoods rick and morty
with a hoodie on.
You see it like the last thing you ever see.
The last thing you ever see is Morty in a fucking Nike bucket hat.
It's a cool hoodie.
And he's wearing, I didn't even notice that, he's wearing a fucking NASA hoodie.
It became cool at some point.
Yeah, why the fuck did that happen?
Why is NASA cool?
Why did NASA make, it was like a Korean NASA hoodie was sold at every Marshalls in America
for like three years. Yeah. And every like stupid guy you knew
had one. Yeah. What was it like free? I mean, it's like, you
get it you get it when you try out. It's like it's like brands
for people who don't know brands, right? They don't know
who's using it. Oh, I know NASA. That was the expensive.
Yeah, they made that shit with space bar.
USPS church.
Limited edition.
They did do. What fucking brand was it? I think it was Forever 21.
Did like a USPS.
You really up to date on Forever 21?
I'm up to date on the USPS.
I think they did a... I don't know.
What did they do? What did you think they did?
It was a crop top? Thank you for knowing that.
What are the odds we have two Forever 21 experts with the same speed of each other?
How like incredible is that?
That's pretty rare, right?
Yeah.
We should do a collab with a brand. What brand would you guys like to see us collab with?
Trojan!
Trojan?
Oh!
That'd be pretty good.
Not a bad idea.
Yeah, just like an extra extra small condom.
That's what you want us to do?
A podcast about Liz's condom for men with baby penises.
I can see it now with like a...
I can imagine the...
The clear packaging.
Just to fucking insult injury.
Yeah, so you pull it out and the person's like,
Yeah, okay. You got a clear one. It's pretty fucking sweet.
You're about to like give me like a rectal exam.
Is it?
Your finger.
And here's the thing, right? It has a little button inside the
packaging. If it falls out of your wallet in public, that's
an alarms going on.
Sorry, I dropped my condom.
Yeah, it'll also go off and you're trying to take out your
wallet to tap your Charlie.
person's like, what the fuck is happening? You don't understand.
It's just podcast. It's called
I'm sorry, we'll start from there.
You don't get it. It's an all over print condom.
You think there's people that collect condoms? People collect
fucking everything.
I think there's probably like biggest players in the world.
Oh, yeah.
You may never use them.
I should mention this. I don't know. I haven't said this on the
podcast. Anybody ever seen that video that I made where I eat a
condom. It's not important, but I just wanted to make sure that somebody was seeing it. So I got a phone call from my mom about three days ago, and it was never a good sign.
It's always like a relative died or I have to give her money or some shit. So I was like, this is, I'm already preparing for the worst, but it was worse than I could ever imagine. She answered the phone, or I answered the phone, and she's like, "Hey, how you doing?" I was like, "Good." She's like, "Did you eat a condom in my car?"
and put it on the internet under your name and I was like you know fucking paying the
bills bitch
to be clear you did not for people who haven't seen it you didn't eat a condom
I did spit it out at the end. I was at a South prison recorder and I spit the cum out of my mouth
you ate like yogurt out of a condom in your boss car. As far as you know.
I'm a man of many talents, you know. I can turn off my taste buds at will.
I like that they're concerned too, isn't it? Like, oh, people are going to see you eating a condom.
It's like, people are going to see you eating a condom in my car.
They're going to know that it's my car.
Oh fuck, that's Miss Spitz's car.
That was also the worst part was that I found out in that moment that if you Google my name, that's the first thing that comes to mind.
(laughing)
They Googled my name,
it's me drinking the cum out of a paper bowl.
(laughing)
And I just sat in my car and was like,
why didn't I just fucking become a mechanic, bro?
What the fuck am I doing, dude?
What is wrong with me?
- Yeah.
- Oh my God.
I don't know, dude.
But I guess that's also not even the most embarrassing
thing I've done.
- Yeah.
- Which is also another realization where I was like,
this is getting increasingly worse every year.
- Yeah, you're gonna--
(laughing)
I'm gonna keep getting calls from your f*cking mom.
Yeah, I'm gonna keep getting calls from my mom.
She's like, "The Secret Service is at my f*cking house."
That didn't happen.
Weren't you telling us about some plan to like,
download every New York police officer's phone number onto your computer?
Can't talk about it yet, but yeah.
Don't speak about that!
Yeah, that's my man. That's my lawyer in the back.
I bring him everywhere I go.
You gotta do it now, you gotta have a murder.
No, I had an idea to send every federal employee in the United States the same photo.
But I was like, they'll probably think that's like a terrorist act.
Because it's just gonna be a photo of Bill Dance, the professional fisher.
And then I talked to somebody and I was like,
is there like a database of every federal employee's email?
And they're like, no.
Probably good that there isn't.
Yeah, they're like trying to stop freaks like you from doing this shit.
So yeah, that's another one of my plans foiled.
At this point I'm almost used to it, so whatever.
I mean, if it sucks when a dastardly scheme gets foiled, I hate it.
Yeah, it was pretty fucked up, man.
Did you say curses?
I did say, I looked at the sky, I said, "Ahh, curses!"
I twirled my mustache and then I untied Patrick from a train track.
He looked so beautiful.
He was so gorgeous. I dressed him up like a girl. I put him on a train track.
I looked good. I looked fucking awesome.
Don't tell people he was serving.
He was serving.
I was serving. And it was a slay.
We're going to be slaying.
Can you say that?
I don't think I'm allowed to.
So we have Tennessee, we have Worcester, you said you're somewhere in Mass, right?
No London, huh? No London.
Alright, it's disappointing.
I was hoping we'd get something further than London. I mean, that's not too much to ask for, right?
I guess China or Australia would have been funny.
Yeah, like a real wild card, like the Vatican or something.
The Pope shows up, "Where are you from?" "Vatican City."
"Why is he a robot?"
"What the fuck was that accent?"
I couldn't remember if he's from Italy or somewhere else.
So, robot is funny.
He's not from the Vatican!
The Pope is a boy in the Vatican.
Do a Vatican accent.
[Vatican accent]
Something like that?
You're Irish Catholic you faker.
You don't have any respect for the fucking church.
I don't have any respect dude.
Have you guys seen that movie Spotlight?
That's not talking about it.
That's actually a bad road to get down huh?
Yeah, we'll skip over that.
Those people from Worcester, that's probably a touchy subject.
I'm not going to talk about that.
That's actually a bad way to get down, huh?
Yeah, we'll skip over that.
Those people from Worcester, that's probably a touch of subject.
Told you it was a police show, boys.
You know, we're fucking around now.
Oh boy.
Yeah.
Oh boy, oh boy.
Are you here just for tonight?
No, we're here for a few more days.
Okay, cool.
Are you following us around the next couple days?
Is that the plan?
We got something else to do.
I'm pretty easy to stick a bug on. I got a lot of smooth surfaces on me.
If you need to, go ahead.
He's got velcro.
Yeah, so this sweatshirt, he just got this sweatshirt.
It's like...
His head is like peeling the lint off.
Like, it...
Hold this.
I'm gonna fucking case him more.
Don't just laugh at my bald head!
What the hell is that?
He pulled the...
He pulled the parachute over his head
and this like pink fuzz was like...
Yeah, let's see.
Pull it off. Somebody pull it off and show the people.
It's like you're sweating too much.
It's like coagulated.
It's like digging into your head.
Actually, it looks like you've got a little bit of hair.
Are you serious?
Oh my god.
Oh shit!
Oh my gosh!
Yeah, you guys can't see this, but it looks amazing!
It's like my hair is back again.
You look like Ian McKellen right now.
Are you serious?
You look way older.
Doesn't it look gay?
No? Oh, okay.
You look like Magneto.
I don't know if that's different.
Nice.
Do you want that back?
$20 for it three hours ago. We went to we stopped at the Newberry comics at Faneuil Hall before the
show because because he had this he had this he was missing something he had nothing on his head.
I don't know what to tell you man I I you know I I will say this is I I have two of these.
I mean there's a second one. Just just imagine the the fear in those Newberry comics employees
his heart's when they see you walking in and those pants and that sweatshirt they
know exactly where you are. Where's the hat? Where's the fucking hat?
You see the bald head? It's like a target.
They think I just got my hair incinerated.
And I'm naked cover it with something. Please tell me you have a Rick and Morty hat.
Please for the love of... I will not take anything else.
No, I won't take the fucking Outworlders or whatever that other fucking Rick and Morty is.
I need Rick and Morty.
I didn't know there was another...
They made a new one, dude.
It's about like... it sucks.
It sucks dick, yeah.
It's probably... yeah, I've heard of it.
It's nothing like Rick and Morty.
I actually do like Rick and Morty, though. That's the most embarrassing part.
I opened up this hoodie that I bought from basicallywish.com
I opened it up and I was like, "It's kinda sick."
"And I got the magic pants shit!"
"This is sick, dude."
I know you're just gonna pick up a Zoom call and just be wearing that.
Yeah, you're not gonna take that off for like a week.
When the Secret Service finally knocks on my door, they're gonna be like...
I answer the door, "Hello?" Full Rick and Morty.
They're not even gonna question you, just arrest you.
You have to go to prison, you have to go to hell actually. We're just going to be prison with you.
We're going straight to hell. This is so fucked up.
Alright, you guys want to fucking do the list?
I don't know this, can we hear the rest of this Jan Kohl song?
[laughter]
Wait, this song is called Big Sean Drake, J. Cole, Kendrick Lamar. I love this song.
It's like my favorite song. If only I knew who made it.
(laughter)
Now we're doing the list? Is that what's happening?
Yeah, let's do the list, baby.
Alright, let me see. Which one is this?
Oh yeah, we did two different lists.
Me and Pat have not seen any of these, but...
Yeah, it's true.
We went in blind and it wasn't because we weren't helping out.
Yeah, no. It wasn't about your two ways you could find the list.
We just wanted to surprise ourselves.
Authentic reaction.
It was for the show.
It's not because we didn't want to make a fucking PowerPoint.
You guys made me do a full 15 minutes of work to find shit.
I'm so sorry.
Out of the two hours I already have to work a week, it's too much.
We got from the top tens dot com, top ten worst things to find in your home.
Imagine coming home and seeing these in your home.
What would be the worst thing to see of all?
Vote for it.
You know this guy, Positron Wildhawk, he comes up quite a bit.
He's very active.
He's one of the super users.
of the super users. I have high, high hopes for this list.
It should be good.
Anybody recognize positron wildcard?
Anybody here?
Any positron fans?
Is positron wildcard here?
That's good, dude. You should message him. I wonder if he
knows that he or any other people like this.
I know we have received we received one message. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. I don't know what this is about.
No, you're not ready for this.
pointing at each other and having a discovery.
He was at a brain blast.
Yeah, that's crazy.
That was a fucking weird one.
A guy whose lists we've read on the show before
whose lists are all
disgusting cartoon character fetish stuff.
Yeah, it's like he's obsessed with
inflation.
Like inflating Bugs Bunny.
Oh, I mean, okay, so there's that.
But also, he has the more advanced ones
which are like, "I want to go inside
of Yosemite Sam's brain and come in there."
in there. Yeah. He's got shit like that. It's nuts. He I forget
what he fucking said to us. We've read his list maybe twice
on the show. He just messaged the podcast account out of
nowhere just started talking to us. It's a scary shit. Yeah.
He was giving us lists. He was giving us like, Oh,
yeah, he was giving us shit. He was like, Yeah, no read this
one. Read that. No, I don't want to fucking read your inflation
fucking destroy little bunny.
This one's insane, I'd get in your fucking kidneys dude, it's so hot.
Yeah, well, I mean, I don't know, maybe we should get him up.
Who knows?
Now that I know that he enjoys having the list read, we're never doing it again.
Yeah, yeah, dude, that's a huge mistake.
That's a huge fucking mistake.
Alright, number one, you guys have any guesses?
Top 10 worst things to find in your home?
Maybe a fucking pile of crap.
You're pretty shit.
Yeah.
Good.
A small boy.
What?!
(laughter)
That's number one!
You have to admit, it'd be pretty bad.
I guess so. How small are we talking, though?
How small can a black hole... do we have an astrophysicist in the audience?
A black hole could be as small as a pinprick or as large as an entire universe.
Wow.
Do we actually... oh, wait, hey, what's up?
(laughter)
Could you? Could you have a small black hole?
I mean, technically you could have like, enough mass in a small area to have like, yeah, a pinprick.
What?
I was like, "I'm the smartest person in the world?
What? Why are you here?
Am I in trouble?
What the fuck is happening?
Am I in a scientist show or something?
Am I like, am I getting an F right now?
I don't know what to do."
You know what? I'm gonna be completely honest.
when I first read that I just thought it meant just like a hole in the ground
Like a Looney Tunes hole?
Yeah exactly
Like a big slap on the ground?
Yeah you fall into it or whatever it's probably annoying to fall down into it
That would suck
Yeah
First comment here
I had a small black hole
We didn't even need you to answer
This guy's first hand experience
It was called an ex spouse
I know all you divorcees can relate
Who is on this website divorced?
Everyone!
Alright, you know what? I've been proven wrong.
Okay, so they're calling their spouse...
A small black hole.
Which is, I guess, more insulting than a large black hole, maybe?
I don't know. I can't tell.
You need to stick with the classics, bitch.
That's like, super fun.
It's like, Subrotney Dangerfield stuff.
Just go fucking Anthony Jess with a car.
Just you, bitch. Fuck you.
Don't call black black hole is too, that's a step too far, that's beyond the pale.
Yeah, but it could be racist, I don't know.
You know, I didn't even think about that, but it's so not racist.
[Laughter]
Yeah, you got it yourself, my friend.
I think any insult that you like would maybe possibly have to explain is like very bad, you shouldn't say that to somebody.
Would you as an astrophysicist call, which I just, I don't know if you even are, I just kind of assume.
Did you, because you knew one thing about black holes.
[Laughter]
Would you call somebody that you hated a small black hole or is that like too rude?
Is that like fucked up?
I think like, it's not, I feel like it's too Reddit a thing to call somebody that.
Wow, that's a strong, you are an astrophysicist.
That's very strong.
That is far too Reddit, I agree.
Yeah.
I mean that is the worst insult to an astrophysicist.
Yeah, do it. Around the office.
I bet you have a lot of good quotes about that.
One or two calls to HR.
yeah he called me a quasar
this will destroy you and your house before you can say death selfie
thank fucking god
that's i mean that's a phrase that's a phrase nobody should ever have
yeah i mean please i mean take let me who's the last person to say jake paul
probably. Come on, man. We did get really into it again. I think the other night, you and
me especially have like a brain that is like a year and a half, like 18 months behind every
pop culture event. Yeah, we'll talk about like, like, we talked about like Carole Baskin.
Like,
a month ago. Yeah, it's true. I think I had a dissonance. Why do you listen to this? Jesus
Once you're in, you can't get out.
That's what she said.
God damn, dude.
Llama Boy's just thinking rationally.
A cheese 5.67 had to fuckin'-- he's too goddamn--
Whoa!
Oh, shit!
Yo!
Yeah!
You did buy him the beer!
That wasn't me!
That wasn't you?
Who bought him that?
Why'd you blow it?
Oh my god, dude.
No, it was me!
It was--
Oh, yeah!
Yeah!
I feel like I'm gonna pour this on my head now.
[laughter]
That's how you get flowing locks, dude.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
You get the foam on you, dude?
Yeah, shampoo that shit out.
Do you also do hair in addition to space?
Can you figure something out with my fucking head?
[laughter]
More like any chance?
You're kind of thinking about it, though.
[laughter]
I thought it was gonna be a hard no.
Um, G557, I just feel like it's kind of rude.
like it's kind of rude. It doesn't make a lot of sense. Once you're in, you can't get out.
I don't think she said that. You can get out pretty easily. I hope. That's a good point.
Yeah, I think that's a I think that's I think she's five six seven I think this
should be banned from the website. Yeah, I agree.
Number two Satan. Oh shit. I'm just so fucking pissed. Oh my god. Long day of work, right?
I know you fucking put your key in the door open it up
Save from the end of the tenacious d-movie is fucking sitting here talking and you know, we'd be talking shit. Oh
It's there he's gonna be cursing you out. Yes. Yeah, just say my mom's in the other room and if she hears you
I'm gonna be trouble
sleeping bag Satan I'm not allowed that friends over on weekend I fucking hope
you're not sleeping over you better not be sleep walking better not getting the
wrong idea dude you're fucking poke holes in my sleeping bag with your horns
if you wake me up laughing at 3am I'm gonna soak this house in
you know Satan's gonna prank you if you fall asleep at his house yeah you know
he's gonna put hot sauce in your toothbrush oh my god put your hand in
warm water you're gonna pee the bed he can probably just make you pee the bed
Yeah.
You might even fucking fuck your face.
[laughter]
Now that I think about it, it's pretty evil.
Yeah.
I think that might be one of the most evil things.
You might as well just fuck your face to death instead.
Yeah.
If Satan shows up to the sleepover, you know everybody's picking truth.
The whole...
[laughter]
Yeah, I hear you.
You're not going to consign your soul to anything.
[laughter]
No fucking shots, Satan. No way, dude.
Don't do it, true.
Yeah.
First kiss is Monaco, okay?
Stop trying to make me fucking...
Oh, fuck.
Time to move out and probably burn down the house while you leave.
Satan is in here.
He's made of fire!
He would probably love that crap.
Yeah!
He burned down the house with Satan in it and he's fucking...
Can we chill?
He's chilling.
Yeah.
You know what? No, it's probably reverse psychology.
He probably wants you to do that.
True.
Even my spirit might be saved.
You mean?
Yeah, it does.
I mean, he is a ghost.
I'm sorry, I kind of frightened myself when I said that.
My heart kind of skipped a beat.
Um, um, um.
You can't.
Okay, okay.
You really can't.
Fuck.
I only invite Lord Jesus and God and only Father.
The devil shall go nowhere near my humble prayer and faith.
Why would you rather see the devil than just John Bieber?
That is just strange. Messed up! God bless you all and keep you safe. Emma XX
Thank you Emma. I mean, respect. That's all I gotta say about this.
Thank you so much Emma. It's beautiful.
It has us on block, dude. Yeah.
I mean, I didn't know I wouldn't be able to say some shit like this to protect myself.
Yeah. It's lucky we have you.
I remember when I was a kid, my parents were like super Christian.
And we moved around a lot, if you could believe it.
But I remember every time we moved into a new house, my mom was like, "We have to anoint
the house with oil."
And they would take olive oil and just put like a little, not even a cross, like a plus
sign over every door.
And then me and my brother were like, "You know what, there's a big difference between
a plus sign and a cross."
You move the middle finger.
There's a decent difference.
Again, Irish Catholic?
Yeah.
Who?
I'm fucking barely went.
What's wrong with you?
I wasn't allowed in church.
I was too loud.
Anyway, I went and went.
Anyway.
My mom didn't fucking let me go.
Damn.
When me and my brother, after they do that shit, we were like, "You know what would be really funny?
Fucking wipe the things off the door."
And so we did.
And we had a bad life.
Horrible things happened all the time.
Who fucking knows why.
Yeah, yeah.
Trying to turn it upside down.
- Yeah, there it is.
(laughing)
- We'll turn it to a minus.
- Yeah.
- This fuckin', there's a bad move on my part.
(laughing)
- Not smart.
- If Satan came into my apartment,
I would tell everyone to get out or hold up a cross.
The cool guy won.
(laughing)
- Yeah, that's a pretty fuckin' cool move.
He's trying to help everybody.
- Also, I like this, that you could have a username
on this website.
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
- He chose to be anonymous and then sign his comment.
- Not only did he choose to be anonymous
and sign his comment,
if you're anonymous and sign your comment,
it's not like the cool guy is taken.
Like you don't have to put the one after it.
You can just leave the call.
At least it's not the cool guy.
He could have just been the cool guy.
You don't have to be a bug either.
I mean, I feel like he's selling himself a little short.
Yeah, come on, cool guy.
Number three, Justin Bieber.
Oh, hell nah. Uh uh.
No way.
He walked into my house and he's sitting there in a bikini
singing this song.
I'd probably piss vomit.
I'd probably make him take a picture of me just because it'd make him so mad.
Yeah.
You'd make him take a picture of you?
Yeah, he'd probably hate that.
Jesse, I know you hate this crap. I'm gonna be on my bed, here's a Polaroid, you come in, you take photos, whatever you want.
Because I know it'd piss you off because I hate you so much.
Yeah, you can put your stupid music on too if you want to.
too if you want to. You put a stupid dick in my face and you care that much?
You fucking asshole. Go ahead, yeah, yeah, I better piss you off super hard.
Leave a "guy sucked your dick because you're not gay" so they would fucking, you'd probably cry so...
Go to hell Justin. Take me down buddy.
So we got a long one here. Oh shit, it's a list in the list.
Yo, we're giving you guys too much.
We pay him double for this.
Do you guys wanna like cycle around?
Do you wanna do like, you know, I don't wanna do this whole thing.
You wanna play popcorn?
Yeah I wanna play popcorn.
Things to do if J.B. ever comes to your house.
1. Get the sledgehammer. Popcorn Caleb?
(laughter)
2. Hit him in the nuts with the sledgehammer.
I'd hate that.
3. While he's going down,
hit him in the face with the sledgehammer.
Yeah.
4. Get the rifle.
While he's upside down, start shooting him with the gun until you get bored.
I do like the unlimited ammo this person has.
It's unlimited until they're bored.
It's really kind that they put in that qualifier too, because I would have just kept going.
I would have just messed up when I got there.
I don't know how I got to number 7. I'm stuck on 6.
Threw him off the roof.
Put him in the middle of the road.
Start running him over.
bombs and two grenades in his mouth. That is what you should do if JB ever comes to your house.
And that's from Golden Rocket. Yeah. This guy has a cath- do you think he has this like in script like
on a big poster in his house that he left him? This is like- In his house, we get the sledgehammer,
hit him in the nuts with the sledgehammer. This is like the like the 99 foot, I don't know,
fucking Martin Luther. Yeah. He's putting that in front of the fucking church. This guy, this might
be the most religious man on earth. He keeps crushing them. Home run after home run when
it comes to this god shit. What I like about this is it gradually reveals how many weapons
he has, he expects you to have in your house. Yeah. He starts with a sledgehammer, like
okay maybe. Like a rifle, some people have rifles in defense, and then two bombs and
two grenades. I don't think... I'm gonna have to hit Home Depot if I'm gonna fuck with this
I don't know what to tell you.
He's horrible. I have the ore spawn mod 1.7.10 and I'm absolutely killing him with my royal guardian sword.
P.S. You have to kill the king to get the royal guardian sword, but once you do, it's totally worth it.
750+ attack damage. Sure to kill him in one hit.
What fucking game is this?
It's gotta be Minecraft.
Yeah, it's gotta be Minecraft.
Ore? Ore spawn?
You know.
What is it?
It's gotta be Minecraft.
Okay, that's what he said dude. You can't copy me. You have a teacher right next to you dude.
He's gonna fucking kill you for that shit.
Put him in detention. Do it.
You're close bud. You're this close to detention.
Yeah.
That's a good buff.
I'll take that.
Yeah.
I'm a believer, but if he broke into my house or something, I would beat him with my guitar.
But if he got permission from my parents, I guess it'll be cool.
It's good. Yeah.
It's not true about anybody though, right?
Maybe like the most, the most, like, um...
Just the person with the best working brain on this website, I think, maybe.
Like, the most reasonable person that's like, "Yeah, I'm a pro gamer."
Might be the only believer on this entire website.
That's a good point.
This person has suffered long.
They've gone through so much.
Number four nuclear weapons.
I'm selling them immediately.
That's my second fucking bank.
Oh my god, are you kidding me?
That'd be like two or three hundred bucks a month.
At least.
I feel like that's like a come up.
Nuclear warhead in my house?
Yeah.
I'm going on a crisis.
He's right, there's not a nuclear warhead in my house.
Oh yeah.
Here's a twist. You may ask,
how exactly would this be bad?
Well, no one ever said they weren't about to explode.
True. It's about the things they didn't say.
Fuuuuuck.
It's about the things they left out.
Which is that it might be about to explode.
Yeah.
Try explaining it. Chances are you'd lose the case.
True.
Very true.
Why would the author too?
The author of the list.
Number 5.
Alright.
I would have put this one number 1.
This is maybe number 1.
Well then you don't have many self-defense skills.
Like me personally, a killer, I just see that as an opportunity.
You know, to show what I got.
You ever heard of Krav Maga? It's the most Israeli thing of all time.
Do you mind if I destroy you with it?
Because I'm about to.
In 3, 2, and then you start up 2, that's one of the Krav Maga phases.
Yeah, you just try to be one of those flip where you run up the wall and just break your teeth.
I'm sorry, have you ever seen Don't Mess With the Zohan?
Han yeah it's based on me yes destroy you and any hummus which he does in the
movie
like put a bomb in Times Square
I remember my eyes are really fucked up movie I remember watching that that
movie like a sleepover in like fifth grade even then I was like what the fuck is this?
I fucking I remember watching the fifth grade just hating it because I didn't
understand the Israeli-Palestinian conflict. I remember watching it when I was a kid
being like that's so cool they made up all this like all these countries for this
like so neat and you have all this shit just for this fucking movie. It's so incredible.
When you come to him but you see someone who either has a knife or a gun
Unless you have a weapon or you're a black belt in martial arts, you're screwed.
Dark Boy X.
Damn, dude. He's like a DMX precursor.
DBX?
No, Dark Man X.
Okay, cool.
Is that what DMX means?
Dark Man X.
I didn't just, like, say that.
I didn't just call him Dark Man X out of nowhere.
That's, like, his name.
I don't know. I thought...
No. I don't know.
I don't know what I thought DMX stood for.
What did you think? I didn't think Darkman X.
You know, like, ABC, AT&T, DVD, just one of those things.
None of those mean anything, ATM, you know?
I get it. It's nothing.
I would be happy. Why? The killer can kill you!
It's true. I didn't think about that before I saw that.
I was like, maybe we could team up and kill somebody.
Maybe the killer's in there to kill my mom and that's fine.
Yeah, exactly.
I used to be really scared of serial killers when I was a kid.
because my brother told me that um what's the name of the clown guy that killed himself?
John Wayne Gacy.
My brother was like John Wayne Gacy faked his own death in the electric chair.
And not only that, he's loose in our neighborhood.
And he can be here at any moment.
And then unbeknownst to me, he went to Spencer Gifts and bought a clown mask.
And he stood outside my window.
and that's why I do a podcast now. Everything I hear about your older
brother, he's so evil. He was horrible. And every time he sees me now,
because we're adults now, you know, every time he sees me he's like, "Hey man, sorry, I was a
cussing evil guy the whole time." I just, you know, I'd start figuring out, try to figure shit out.
I don't get divorced parents, it's tough.
(laughter)
Number six, an alien spaceship.
Again, you'd fucking score.
I don't know what this shit is about, dude.
Dude, I would sell that shit immediately.
Do you think that this UFO shit is the government trying to pretend some shit?
Yes.
Yeah?
Well, think about it, UFOs...
Well, sir, we have an expert here.
You say you're a UFO-logist, right?
(laughter)
No.
No, no, you're not.
I've seen really weird things in the sky.
You've seen a UFO?
I've seen something that I couldn't identify in the sky.
Oh shit.
I mean I can't explain how a plane flies.
Yeah.
That's pretty tough.
My uncle, I don't know if people know this, he's a ghost hunter.
Oh yeah, well man.
I have a ghost hunter uncle.
One time he sent me a video of the moon and he was like, "I found a UFO."
I was like half blind.
We're just making shit up now.
He's half blind, he has a peg leg, and he has wax lips.
But yeah, he kept sending me videos and I kept being like, "Uncle Matt, that is the moon."
And he kept being like, "Ah, we had to be there."
And then his friends started shooting the moon.
Because he was like, "We have to defend Earth."
So he started fucking... North Carolina has like an AR-15.
In the backyard, they just started shooting at the fucking moon.
The thing about a UFO is all that means is it's just something in the sky and you don't
know what it is.
That's all.
You can see like a scary shaped cloud.
That is a UFO.
Dude, if you can't tell it's a cloud, that's a limit.
Anything can be a UFO.
Yeah.
The message I want all of you to take home tonight.
That's so beautiful.
Wow, that's so gorgeous that you said that.
Oh my God, dude.
I would kiss them, invite them for dinner, and then I would take home with them.
I like aliens.
This guy's weird.
You're weird.
Yeah.
They can research our brains and personality and they will use the information to kill us.
Just act dumb and you'll stay alive.
Yeah.
You think that would work?
I think it might work.
I don't know. I don't think that you could act so dumb that they don't care.
Yeah.
They're like, "Ah, you know, this guy's so stupid."
Maybe you gotta act like another animal.
You know, if you...
Oh, that's actually a great idea.
Maybe when you just act like you're a friend.
When you have a friend who's one of those two person horse costumes they use in plays.
Yeah.
You might really get away with it actually.
Well, I mean, you don't want no damn horse.
That's true. Yeah, they do skip horses when they like abduct shit.
So I guess the one animal just don't be a cow.
Yeah.
If you're a cow, you're getting fucked.
You're getting probed and shit.
What do you think they're doing with those cows though?
I think they're just like, they're eating good.
Yeah, they're just like making hamburgers.
They're just dumping food.
That's exactly what we do at Gals.
It's like, this is like the best shit ever.
I think this guy might be wrong, because like, you know, if you're in a room and there's like the stupidest animal ever, and then the cutest animal ever, I'm killing the stupidest one.
Yeah, that's true.
Stupidest and smartest, you'll kill the stupid one.
That's what I would do, I guess, is I would try to be really cute when they walk in.
Yeah.
Are you an alien?
And then I'd show them my butthole.
I might not like that actually.
No, they would love that. What are you talking about?
I forgot I'm talking about aliens here.
Yeah.
Famous butthole lovers.
You guys love the butt.
Number 7, a mosquito nest. Big step down.
Yeah.
I mean it would be annoying.
Do they live in nests?
I don't think they live in nests. I think they live in water.
They live outside.
I live off the streets.
I think that's a lie.
right now this could be very you know why I was just thinking about this you might
get attacked by the mosquitoes
I think I would rather have a beehive in my house than a mosquito nest.
Why?
Because bees are cool.
You get honey out of them.
You get stung.
You just can't smoke.
I actually don't know how normalizing for bees.
They like to smoke, right?
Do they like smoke?
I don't know anything about bees.
Do they go to sleep when they touch smoke or something?
I don't think that means they like it.
just completely pass out when they touch it they fucking love it. I fall asleep when I'm watching
YouTube and I love YouTube. That's a very good point. Uh oh, this will be ours. I like the one
two punch of Matrix guy and dubstep lover. Yeah that is good. And actually now I am remembering
I saw the username dubstep lover I thought it was funny I clicked on their profile so the next slide
that is their profile.
(laughter)
Alright dude, let's fucking go.
Just remember that just now.
Yeah, I was saying like, it kind of sucks that we can't click on people's profiles.
Yeah, this is, you planned for this.
So this is Dubstep Lover.
Oh.
This is their profile picture.
This text says, "I went on a quest to find a site that actually has a good community.
I've lost hope and I found the top 10."
Oh shit.
That's their avatar.
Come on, they're beefing.
I suspect.
"Hello there, the top 10's user.
You are probably reading my profile right now because you have seen one of my quote 'troll'
Yes, troll totally means a person who dislikes something.
And you totally will call someone a troll when they hate something you hate as well.
And now you are probably going to say, "I'm some troll," and you'd say something extremely non-edgy,
like, "Don't feed the troll," or, "She's an obvious troll."
Oh, wait, you don't know what a troll is. Not surprised.
21 years old, ladies and gentlemen.
-Stands right there. -21.
-Their name is Saltiness? -They could be at this show right now.
- I would say saltiness.
The next slide is a selection of the lists that they have created.
- Okay.
- Alright, I'm seeing a detour here.
- Yeah.
- This is just a short detour.
- I'm sorry.
- This is like a person twisted by this website.
- Okay.
- This is like Gollum.
- Like, we spent too much time here.
- Yeah, yeah, no, I get it.
- I don't even think they love Goat Sip anymore.
- Things that top 10 users say as a response to trolls.
Things people say before blocking someone they're in a flame war with.
with top 10 reasons people should stop hating on haters top 10 types of people
mistakenly called trolls. Things that will make everyone in the top 10 stop being so salty and edgy.
Most reasonable answers to answer the question why can't a top tens user learn to take a small joke.
First kinds of comments on the top tens item. Best things about an Oregano.
[laughter]
I mean that's a perfect punchline.
Oh my god. There's never been a better punch line. Best things about an Oreo.
Not even like Oreo flavor. That's the best thing.
Just the one flavor. The one Oreo flavor.
I like the cookie number two. I like the cream.
Anyway, back to the...
I love my corpse. Yeah, I'm corpse.
What are you guys going to do for your funeral? Because one of us is going to die first.
yeah yeah I don't think probably you make sure that we're not gonna die the same
Cameron's gonna live to be way too old and he's gonna look very weird as an old man
I genuinely hope I look extremely strange as an old man
yeah you're gonna look like Gandalf I can tell you that right now
I've probably got six years and I would love a Harry Potter themed
I think that would fit my personality and my style and taste in things by the way I'm a Slytherin
I was about to ask, I'm glad you said that.
I mean, the Rick and Morty, you can tell immediately.
You know I'm a Slytherin because all the quizzes, the first question is like, "Are you evil?"
I'm like, "Yes I am!"
Do you like death magic?
I'm trying to get a Gryffindor. Yeah, I guess I like death magic and killing things.
That's the most evil piece of shit of all time.
Fuck Slytherin, fuck.
That depends. Is it a lover? A former lover? A politician?
I would really be upset to get home from work and find myself dead on the floor. It's a monster corpse
So first of all politician
That's crazy
Series of you walk in here as JFK jr. Is on your floor
As JFK jr. Like now like he's fucked up. That's bad news
That is getting me in trouble
Don't say that. I'm in trouble right now.
It's a monster corpse. I don't know which one's scarier.
As a politician, you're going to get blamed for that. That's the problem.
Or I would get blamed for it.
I don't know that everybody would get blamed for it, but...
Old Caleb would.
A monster corpse is scary.
It's a monster corpse, and it's a politician.
Charlie Baker!
Can we just stop naming politicians now?
Fucking great.
We can't win this.
I know!
Joe Manchin, that's actually a really good point.
Joe Manchin, yeah!
Wow!
Who's that guy?
I don't know.
He's back there from West Virginia.
Yeah.
Oh, it's just like a deceased.
Yeah, I don't need an explainer.
Not a thing you want to see, not a comment you want to see either, I think.
Yeah.
That was a deceased, like, our audience are wordy, man.
Right.
I mean, yeah, I mean, it was.
Deceased adds another level.
This second was a deceased, you know, he did.
Yeah, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean,
Not a thing you want to see, not a comment you want to see either I think.
That was a deceased, like writings are wordy man.
I mean yeah, I mean it was deceased.
This second is a deceased, you know he did it.
Yeah.
Oh no, somebody deceased.
Tom's not going to join, like, "Oh you hear about my deceased girlfriend?"
"I had nothing to do with it by the way."
That's not going to sell.
Yeah.
Number 98.
Oh shit.
Is anybody else sick of this guy?
I'm so mad at you.
Fuck this guy, right?
This guy's a piece of shit.
I hate him so much. I probably hate him more than any of you.
I probably hate him more than you.
I probably hate him the most of anybody in the whole world.
No, probably less than me.
Probably number one in the world.
Probably way less than me.
Nah, I'm probably the number one guy.
Yeah, I don't know about that.
I don't know, I mean I like shit around.
I hate it.
Check yourself.
do that. Oh fuck. I don't hold it. You're not pointing it. Caleb is the first guy to hold
two opposite records in Guinness Book of World Records. Number one, Hitler Hater.
And juggling, that's the other one. What an amazing juggler. Fucking incredible at it. I
could juggle one ball. I'm like really good. Yeah, yeah. He would be running around my house
screaming in German and I would have a difficult time trying to catch him with a net.
Why a net?
Get the Hitler net dude, he's back.
Yeah.
I mean I would just, you know, first of all I'd say I don't like what, like I don't like you.
But, do you want to play GameCube? It's like an amazing story.
When you think about it, like nobody's going to believe this shit.
Do you want to take a picture with me?
I mean in that way he's exactly like Bill Murray.
I hate this guy.
I hate it when I find Hitler in my house.
This brings back such terrible memories.
Yeah, fair.
percent chance Hitler is dead. But there's that one, one millionth of a percent.
Single millionth of a percent that, ah fuck, maybe he's still out there. I do like, yeah, I remember asking my mom, or my mom watched some
documentary about like Nazis in like Argentina like hiding and shit and she
was like, she called me, it was another bad fucking call from mom, she was like, did you know that Hitler, Adolf Hitler, might still be alive?
And I looked it up and I was like, "Mommy, be like 140 years old."
And then she responded to me exactly like this, she was like, "They have Nazi technology."
And there's nothing I could do.
She still believes it, too.
There's nothing I could fucking say.
You know what? Good point.
They have Nazi technology.
Can't really refute that.
Yeah, what are you going to say? "No, they don't."
Yeah, "No, they don't."
I guess the word "Nazi" said it in a sense.
fuck. Number 10 illegal fireworks. This is a good time. Oh, no,
there's a party in my house. Oh, Christ. Coming home and seeing
fireworks and being pissed off. Yeah, what the fuck?
I'm a loser. I work too expensive. Well, I guess that
they're okay. If they're being like lit in your house. It's
probably annoying. Yeah.
A big New Year's.
Clearly Disney.
Mickey Mouse sucks dude that's why they're illegal you can't like show
I walk in and I see the New Year's display and I'm so pissed off because it's
it's fucking June dude it's not that's for wasting these early they need them
yeah the contenders yeah number four
which maybe is worse than Hitler himself I mean who can say that's true you can go through walls
Yeah, true. Yeah. I'm finally free from Hitler on the other side of this wall.
Fuck you, dude! Are you kidding me? He's a ghost now? It sucks, cock.
I hate you, ghost Hitler. So on and so forth. Yeah.
Yeah, et cetera, et cetera.
The toilet having exploded. Now, yeah, this--
Better than me, I've had to use buckets to cramp it.
What do they mean better than, like the toilet is better than them?
What does that fucking mean?
Have you ever crapped in something other than a traditional toilet?
Yeah.
What was it?
I crapped outside when I was like six.
I used to have a crapping tree that I would...
Not kidding.
I'm not fucking kidding.
Me and my friend Liam, we went out and I lived like next to the marsh.
We had a big, there was a big tree back there.
And for some reason my ass fit perfectly on two branches.
And so I would go and I would leave my house and then walk like half a mile and then go take a shit out of a tree.
Because I was like, "I'm fucking this coolest fuck."
There I was dude, now I have a story.
You'd like bark as toilet paper or...
What do you mean, dude? What do you think?
You're obviously not a survivalist like me.
I wouldn't go for bark.
You'd be using a twig.
I wouldn't fuck you. Come on, man.
Nah dude, I would do that.
I also, I do want to defend myself about the leaves thing.
I don't think any tree that's been shitting next to you for years is going to have leaves for very long.
I mean, you're shitting to do trees.
Good thing, I made a pile out of it.
Good point, like two months. Like, that's pretty impressive actually.
And don't think about the fact that that's fertilizer, because I just thought about that, so don't think about that.
I got boogies.
Number 19, Dora jumping out of the TV.
Oh, hell no.
Don't worry, Dora.
Oh, no.
Do you guys hate learning?
What's wrong with you?
She cannot look out of the TV.
Why are you afraid of Dora?
Too small.
What's wrong with you?
It's like she's like a bug, dude.
I learned that from you.
My creepy crawly sense goes off.
It's like when I hit her with a shoe,
it's smash her.
Dora rules, man.
She taught me every word of Spanish I know.
I know "Hola" and "Chocolate".
I learned "backpack".
Yeah, "backpack".
I think in Spanish it might be backpack.
Good point.
According to that show.
Number 25, robber.
My best friend is one.
Yeah.
You guys know any robbers?
Not yet.
Is there a robber in this room?
Yes.
There's no way you're a robber.
I stole a shirt from Target like two days ago.
Nice. That's not a robbery.
Robbery is when you put on the mask. Yeah, right. Sure.
Bad.
I think I could get away with robbing a bank in the south.
I escape into a sea of people dress exactly like
you do look like you just did do a bank robbery.
tag on these. It's large, yeah, 5'9". It's a large. They're all jealous.
Are you going to return them? No, no. We're going to auction them off.
If nobody liked them, then I would have returned them, but I'm going to be wearing these again.
You better believe that. This is not the last you've seen of my sweatpants.
Number 28, a psychopath bent on revenge to torture you.
Psychopath.
Yeah, I would say that's pretty much worst case scenario.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Yeah, your arch nemesis is in there.
Yeah, it's like, that sucks.
Yeah.
Did you guys ever have a rival growing up?
Arch nemesis?
Yeah.
We tried to get a rival the other day.
Who was my rival?
We were, so we were leaving somewhere, me and Caleb were leaving a place, and like, we took
like a lift, the lift driver was telling like some guy was like in two lanes or
something he honked the horn was like it's two lanes asshole. I don't think he said
anything. Yeah he said it's two lanes. Okay well maybe I suck at hearing. Yeah you do
because you turned to the guy and you said oh is that your rival?
And then for the rest of the car ride just to make me uncomfortable he's
sitting there like yeah I'm thinking about getting a rival pretty soon. I think I need a rival.
Someone that looks like me. You went on for like a good couple minutes.
The 15 minute drive. One of the most like uncomfortable conversations I've ever had in like a lift was me and Alex were in a lift. It was like a pool and so there were other people in there. The guy started talking to us like hey like what's up? Like where are you guys coming from? And Alex was like oh I just watched this movie Rango.
I was like, "Dude, not let a Lyft driver go out on Rango, dude. He's never going to stop."
The Lyft driver was like, "Oh, what's that? I haven't heard of it."
He's like, "Oh, you should watch it, dude. It's pretty good. It's Johnny Depp plays this chameleon.
He's a cowboy."
And then the Lyft driver asked, he was silent for a little bit, and he's like,
"Did Rango ever have to, you know, kill anybody?"
I don't think so man and there's silence.
[Laughter]
For the rest of you.
The most insane follow up question I could ever get.
That's sick dude. Good for him.
[Laughter]
One time I had a Lyft driver in like Brown University.
I was doing a show there. The Lyft driver was like,
"Yeah man, you guys like don't jaywalk because the cops will take you down to the train tracks and they'll beat you to death."
We're like, "We don't believe that, man."
Like, "I don't like cops, but I don't believe that."
That's crazy.
Where's-- Browns and Rhode Island?
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't think a cop in Rhode Island would do that.
Extra homework. I gotta kill myself.
I gotta kill myself.
I mean, I don't blame him. Extra homework?
Yeah, just walked out dude.
Yeah.
Number one, Popo.
Popo.
I'm no expert, but maybe it means poop.
Ralph Bob says this means police.
My same UFO hunting uncle, one time when I was a kid, he's a volunteer firefighter, right?
He's a hero.
Woo!
Everybody, yeah, you should fucking beat this guy before you woo.
He was like, one time I called police to Popo, cause you know, I'm me, I'm cool.
cool and he was like don't you ever say po po that's like saying the n-word I
was like no man I don't think it is your head is made out of metal I think that's the problem here and you hunt the moon at night
I'm not sure that's that's my fault number 113 dr. Eggman he will be a tough
housemate. That's just the good. Yeah, he's gonna eat everything.
Fucking making robots. Yeah, it's fucked up. Leave me alone, dude.
This is the last one. Balloon Boy. Balloon Boy.
No, Balloon Boy. I'm sorry. I misread. I thought it said Balloon Boy.
grabs gun and shoots it multiple times.
Is this is this a I love still being mad at Balloon Boy. Yeah, that's like the
coolest shit you can do is you still being that little scene. Have you all
seen? It wasn't Falcon he was a little boy's name.
Well, same as metal.
There's a metal band. Dad is like making him do a metal band. Is it like
balloon boy feet? Yeah, they have a song. Yeah. Are you serious? They have
a song when I was all hoax or something like that. Like, yeah. You was a
called? Is that what that is? I think so. Fuck that's sick. That's so sick.
Flown away. The thing is if you have a kid and you name him Falcon E and you have to like expect that his
whole life is gonna be spent on balloons. This guy is either flying off in a balloon or like killing
John Penn. Those are the only options for somebody with that name dude. Yeah. Yeah.
That's the last one. Alright thank you guys so much we've been podcasting about LIS.
We appreciate you coming out. We love you. We have DVDs to give out.
Thank you everybody.