You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
Test your mic.
Normal podcast!
*singing*
You have the wrong notes completely.
Shut the fuck up.
I don't, I'm very tone deaf.
*singing*
I'm doing the high part.
(singing)
Caleb.
Cameron.
Johnny Patrick.
Johnny Johnny.
Johnny Jingo.
Oh, come on man.
Johnny Gay.
Patrick is playing keep away with a piece of pizza
and a cat.
And he's successful.
I'm winning.
This cat doesn't like Indian food, huh?
cat does this cat like to eat meat yeah they eat that we give them wet food
sometimes we give them they like to eat duck that's a fancy cat that's a that's
a fancy feast if you ask me it's only like a dollar for the food it's a dollar
for duck now oh my god it does say it does say human grade they're doing
dollar down so you could eat the cat food that yeah here's my human grade for
that F. Okay. Yeah. Last night I had a Lyft driver who's this guy who just he told
he was telling us that he's been he hasn't had a day off in 17 years and he
him and his Brazilian wife she's about to get she gets citizenship she gets
American citizenship on like in the middle of March and then he said the day
after they have a flight booked to Brazil and they're just gonna live in Brazil.
Why? He never explained that. Yeah. Yeah, and but I just was enjoying him talk. He
said that the economy is gonna crash in December 2020. Oh, he's a prepper?
No, he's a Lyft driver. Well, he could be a Lyft driver and a prepper. Yeah, those
aren't mutually exclusive. I just told you he hasn't had a single day off in 17 years. What does that have to do with anything?
He has no prep time. Well, he could be working and then he could be prepping too.
It's a mindset.
Prepping is a mindset.
Yeah, absolutely.
Are you a prepper?
No.
No?
I think, we were talking about this before, but I think the difference between me and
the people on Doomsday Preppers is like I believe all the stuff that they're saying.
I'm like, "Oh yeah, there is going to be nuclear war and we are all going to die."
But I just don't, I wouldn't try to live.
Yeah, it's just like you might as well, I don't want to be building a fucking shed.
I want to be playing video games.
Just think about how much it would suck to live in a bunker.
The thing is, is like, if you spend all that time and all that money, and then it doesn't
happen and you're like 80 years old, and you're just like sitting in your bunker like, "Come
on, dude, just fucking somebody press a big red button right now, because I just, I want
to use this shit."
You know?
You have a Tommy gun?
Mm-hmm.
You know?
The cat is being mischievous.
Yeah, he just wants to drink out of the water cup.
That's fine.
It doesn't matter if he drinks out of the water cup.
Yeah, but what if he spills it on the laptop?
Then take the water off the table.
Yeah, why is the water?
there's water on my laptop. We poured water on your laptop. And now the
cat almost drank it all off. Oh my god that was a close one. Oh my god.
Yeah but I'm coming straight off that Tom O'Shea roast
right now. Yeah. Yeah. Stop farting. I should not have ordered Indian
pizza before this. Yeah, Indian pizza. Yeah, that is like an evil scientist
disconstructed, the most like disgusting fart food.
- Yeah.
- Specifically for Patrick.
And it's like Patrick's dream food.
Like there is--
- Oh yeah, absolutely.
- There's definitely a geometry notebook
that Patrick doodled in when he was in third grade
that says Indian pizza.
- I didn't eat Indian food until this year.
- You didn't eat Indian food until this year?
- Yeah, I didn't eat Indian food until like two months ago.
- Dude, Indian food's the best.
- Yeah, I know.
- Indian and Mediterranean, neck and neck for me.
That's it.
I think Indian... no, Thai food's better than Indian food in my opinion.
Man, you crazy.
I love Thai food.
I bet you do.
I love that food.
Get out of here, cat.
Get out of here.
The cat is being a dick today, dude.
Get the fuck out of here.
He's not being a dick.
He's being so evil on purpose.
Yeah.
I just want to...
You're being evil.
I just want to ring...
Yeah, I just want to ring his little bell.
I just want to ring his little bells.
I just want to ring his little balls.
Yeah, I want to dingle him.
I just want to fucking hit him like a speed bag.
I just want to jingle...
Jingle and dangle him.
you're gonna hit my cat I'm gonna hit your cats balls like a speed oh yeah I'm
serious get a book at a book yeah yeah book it a book at a book it was when my
small yeah that's why I can do it I'm gonna do that lick my tongue to practice
yeah I'm yeah I'm just gonna go up real close go just right on his balls don't
please don't do that I'm going to man I'm gonna make your cat come man dude
I'm gonna make your fucking cat jizz if your cat is shits on my lawn one more
time I'm gonna make him come. He's gonna learn to love it so much. That's someone walking their cat. If your dog walks
into my backyard one more time I'm gonna stick my fleshlight on his little red
rocket. I'm serious. I'm gonna make your dog ride the Sibian in my garage.
Yeah but did the Tom O'Shea roast. Yeah. Give us some examples. Tom beat me. Tell us some of your
jokes the joke the only I we had the okay pretend Cameron is Tom pretend Cameron
at Cameron is Tom okay I'm not I do that no I'm let me imagine it I'm not
imagine with your mind imagining your Tom the one that so so we did the format
was you four jokes and then a knockout joke and a knockout joke just like a
good joke the knockout joke is like the the judges a cool one just confer or be
in between. So the first three jokes are like jokes and the knockout joke is you just go
and fuck you. Yeah. And suck my dick. And you say your phone number. Like a bag of farts.
That wouldn't be a knockout joke. That would be the first joke. The last joke,
the knockout joke is fuck you or you suck. The knockout joke is, it needs to be akin to a knockout.
Yeah. Exactly. So you would go like fuck you. I would call it, they had to explain the
knockout thing. I think of it as a fatality joke, you know? Yeah, or a babality joke.
Yeah.
If you're fighting a baby.
Not a friendship.
Definitely not a friendship. No. But yeah, I lost. But I think it's because my jokes were...
I just wrote jokes... I wrote jokes like everybody in the audience was going to be like
people who were already kind of on my side, but I just was too mean, I think.
Yeah.
and not... I didn't do like superficial stuff. Like I was very rude to Tom. They had to ask...
They'd ask you to stop being so rude.
There was a guy... So I'll tell you the joke where I think I lost him. It was like,
"Cameron, I'm going to pretend you're Tom here."
Okay.
Cameron... So when I say Cameron, ladies and gentlemen...
Imagine it's Tom.
Imagine Tom.
Yeah. And you know Tom from the show.
There's a photo online on Facebook of Cameron shaking hands with Joe Biden,
who was a commencement speaker at his graduation. Now you may be impressed by this photo,
but what you won't be impressed by is that Tom didn't even know that was Joe Biden,
because Tom just saw an old man in a robe and thought he might be a wizard that could
resurrect his dead high school friend. Yeah. What? Yeah, I think that's why they lost.
Yeah, I know. You could have gone so many ways with that.
Nope, I did.
Joe Biden, hair sniffing, pedophile.
The thing is everybody in one half of the room thought it was really good
and the other people, I got a couple of awes.
The judges? You got awes from the judges?
No, the judges were fucking, they were all like barred out. I don't know,
I didn't even know who the judges were. They were all fucking just fat Boston guys.
Yeah, it's guys like fucking Irish McNeil.
Yeah, Mr. Piss.
Mr. Fat. Mr. Fat.
Mr. Fat.
Steal your wife.
But I had a couple of jokes about Tom's friend, Tom's dead friend.
And then, and I told him we wrote together before the thing, like we kind of, we wrote
all the jokes together. And he, when he heard a couple of them, he made the guy who died,
his parents were supposed to come to the show.
And he made them sell their tickets.
Really?
Yeah.
That's so funny.
Yeah, he was like, yeah, his mom would have cried and his dad would have tried to fight you.
And I was like, that would have been like a win, you know, I lose but I have to fight some guy
who I'm making fun of that I've never known.
Yeah, that would have been a really bad night.
Yeah.
Anyway, it was fun.
And then I got to meet that Uber driver who needs a day off.
Yeah. He even worked Christmas, he said.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
No presents?
No presents for him?
Well, maybe.
My present is working.
What if he hasn't even been home?
What if he walked in his door, just can't even open the door, there's so many presents in there.
Oh my god.
That'd be awesome.
17 years of presents.
Reddit, let's make it happen.
Let's do a Reddit gift exchange.
R/UberDriver.
We got that guy. R/that guy, the Uber driver.
Tyler.
Tyler Uber.
An old--
He was an old Tyler.
Yeah, that's weird.
Which is crazy.
How old?
He's probably 50 something, man.
Jesus Christ.
Old Tyler, Brazilian wife.
Wow.
You better believe it.
Old and old Tyler.
Ripley's Believe It or Not, there was an old Tyler.
Imagine meeting someone who's just got a fucking dialysis machine.
and you're like oh that guy's name's Kyle yeah yeah that what the fuck yeah that's
Tristan yeah oh yeah this is my grandpa Caden yeah this is old World War two vet
with no legs yeah his name is press Preston Preston I guess yeah I think so
yeah I don't know one Preston and he's a baby Preston is like a rich baby name or
like a regular old guy name Preston is my baby best friend we solve crimes
together yeah what stop meowing Patrick Patrick is having his fursona
the cat cat nip yeah cat nip see hustle mm-hmm yeah
he was going to cure cancer with catnip and that's why and yeah what was his
what was said bees cure I don't know fun yeah
Isn't that that's one of the theories that Nipsey Hussle was murdered because he got too
close, he was making a documentary about Dr. Sebi?
He was making a Sebi doc.
Yeah, which I will say publicly, we are making a Dr. Sebi documentary.
Try and get us now, Illuminati.
What if just the door bursts open?
Some old guy in a robe.
Meek Mill shoots us in the head.
He's Illuminati now.
Meek Mill's Illuminati?
Yeah, I think like all after Jay-Z. There's a lot of rappers in there now
Absolutely. Yes
Clone well Gucci means a little pump is Illuminati you think so
Yes, I'm a little ill. Oh my god
None of the other little rappers are though, but a little pump
Yeah, no Gucci man people think he's a clone cuz he got thin and he's had any smiles. He does he got
He got real good veneers. It's funny that he killed a guy and then put his body in a dumpster
Yeah, and then was like me sorry, and he's fine now. He didn't even go to jail for that
He went to jail for some other shit. Yeah crazy. Yeah, that's nuts. He's a man. I would never do that
I would never let him kill me. I would I would do that, but I would say I would say sorry
Mm-hmm. I would make a public apology. I am so sorry for the body that I just put in your dumpster
Pizza Hut. Ladies and gentlemen, I made a whoopsie. There's a dead guy. I think he was in the back of
a school. Yeah, yeah. I thought, yeah, didn't he like a high school? Yeah. Yeah, because the guy,
I mean, to be fair, the guy tried to rob him. Oh, okay. In his house and Gucci Mane shot him in the
head and then was like, "Oh, I don't want to call the police because I'm a rapper." And he, so he
just put the guy's body in a school dumpster. Yeah. He's like, "All right." I think one of the
the kids did it yeah yeah the person in the dumpster was the principal and Gucci
man was just he had a contract the kids he's freeing the kids like like Dobby
like yeah it's a how either house cells but you have to kill the principal if to
give him a shred of his bloody clothes mm-hmm yeah I got the principal a bullet
and it frees all the kids mm-hmm yeah and then the kids get no homework
Homework is fucking balls man. Homework sucks let me just say it. Homework is nuts on my
ass. Mm-hmm. I hate homework. Don't even say that in front of me. Don't say the H word in
front of me. Don't say the N word. Homework. It's a silent. That's what it is to me.
The N word is homework. Hey in this house buddy, hey take your shoes off and the
N word is homework around here. So have fun. Don't pet that disgusting little
worm. He's not disgusting. You know what he looks like? He looks like the Tremors
monster. You love to pet him all the time. That's because I'm studying him. He does not look like the
Tremors monsters. The Tremors monsters are fat. Yeah. He's very fat. The Tremors monsters are fat worms.
Fat worms with beaks. Yeah. That's what I'm looking at. The Tremors monsters are so cool.
This is one of those things where it's like maybe we don't, maybe we we don't see blue the same. I
see this cat as a disgusting worm. A graboid? Yeah, a graboid. What a genius name.
- Tremors rocks. - Tremors is so good. I was watching, I watched the first three and I
was gonna keep watching the rest and I was like I don't need to. - I think I've
seen to the fourth one. - Is the fourth one the prequel or is that the fifth one?
I think the fourth one's the prequel. - I've never seen it. - I've definitely seen a prequel. - Really? Dude, watch it. It's so good.
- I've seen two minutes of Tremors on AMC. - It's on Netflix right now. All of
them are on Netflix. - Oh, okay. - Why does he want to go on the recorder so bad? - We should put poison on
your computer yeah poison Yoda you know it is nice I would poison you he's trying
so hard to eat the computer stop is he doing there's nothing cool there
here no he doesn't know it's cuz I had it smelled like food you need to feed
this motherfucker I do I feed him like three times a day yeah that's not enough
Yeah, I feed him three knowing you I bet you what about midnight snack exactly
What about his hot glass of milk?
Kid getting taken away from C4 CPS
Where's his milk and cookies I haven't seen it
There was a there was a period of time like three years where I was I just picked it up
like I was nobody ever did this for me I just started doing it myself but every
night before bed I would have a warm glass of milk like a like a like a
British orphan yeah I would just heat it up in the microwave it does supposedly
help you go to sleep it never did it just is disgusting it was just like
yeah just hot milk yeah and but I did it for a long time just cuz it was a it was
a TV trope that I picked up I guess yeah my younger sibling does that yeah why
- Why does it, I mean, but it doesn't really gross me out
'cause it's like a latte, it's hot milk
just with stuff in it, you know?
- Poop.
- Yeah, hot milk with poop in it.
- But like, I don't know, it's still great.
Like plain stuff, just 'cause when you add something else
to it isn't gross, duh.
But like, on its own it's still gross.
- Yeah, you wouldn't just drink the fucking syrupy,
little slurpy syrup.
- Yeah, like a milkshake is good,
but just a big cold glass of milk.
- But just ice cream is disgusting.
- I wouldn't drink a cold,
I just wouldn't drink milk on its own.
- You wouldn't drink milk on its own?
- That's weird.
Milk on its own is good.
- Yeah. - I don't know.
- I have a glass probably three times a week.
- I don't drink enough milk.
- Yeah, we need to get more in the milk stuff.
- I like milk, but there's a lot of almond milk.
- Do you ever had an egg cream?
- No.
- Whoa. - What's that?
- It's basically, it's this old New Jersey drink
where they put a bunch of chocolate syrup in a thing,
in a cup, and then a little bit of heavy cream.
- You know who likes egg cream?
- And then a bunch of soda water.
- Aaron likes egg cream. - Really?
- Oh, that sounds disgusting.
- It's really good. - Soda water?
- It's really good.
- Sounds gross.
it's really good and Aaron would know. Aaron if you're listening buddy, I miss you.
Please yeah. I don't know how he would. He doesn't own a device.
Yeah. He has no device. Yeah. I imagine him partly because of his look and
also just how he lives. Just like a castaway situation 24/7. Yeah.
Just like a voluntarily on an island. Doesn't even make an attempt to like
spell something on the beach. He just likes it there. Spells "It's okay. I'm fine. I'm fine.
Go away. Yeah, just drinking coconuts and and fucking all the
The big bugs the big the big like King Kong bugs, yeah
Yeah, the prehistoric bugs that live there before they before they leave all from having human pussies. Yeah, he's on Skull Island
Have you seen the the King Kong
1972 I just found out that exists the other day. No, which one is that? Is that that's the Dino de Laurentiis one?
No. Oh yeah, it's on Amazon Prime.
Oh nice.
Amazon Prime is a bunch of really good old movies.
Like a bunch of good old genre stuff.
It's really awesome.
I love Jeff Bezos.
Amazon? Great.
Jeff Bestos is what I call him.
Jeff Bestos.
Me and Pat came up with an invention today.
Really?
Yeah.
It's called the...
Well, as you guys know...
I know. So you guys know my...
This is like Shark Tank, okay?
We're gonna pitch you our invention.
Okay. I'm the black guy.
I forget the invention.
I remember it.
it. Wait, hold on. You'll remember it when I start talking about it. Hey, what's up?
What's your fucking pitch? Hello, hey Shark. Yeah. Have you ever, do you ever find
yourself being fucked in the ass by a creature? Oh yeah. All the time. I'm rich.
Wouldn't, wouldn't, don't you hate it when the creature gets in your hole?
Puts his long thing into your hole and snakes it up like a little worm that's
giant. The creature takes out your shit with his thingy. The creature scoops out this.
When the creature goes plumber mode on my butthole. Don't you hate when the
creature gets in you like a gorilla. I despise that. From behind. Yeah.
Creature go up in the air. Luckily for you, we have an invention that will save you. Do you?
It's called the anti-creature donut. It's like a hemorrhage donut.
Hemorrhage donut? Hemorrhoid donut. Hemorrhoid donut. You put it on your
ass around the hole. Creature's
thingy-thingy isn't long enough to get past the donut into your
And it's too soft. And it's too sweet. It's kind of like
king's hawaiian roll you're gonna put a sweet donut on my ass yeah and it stops
the creature from you know violating to destroying and desecrating your my holy
my holy it's a holy holy yeah your holy that you know my touchable thing your
god zone yeah mm-hmm okay what do you guys asking over 10% 10% for how much
money I don't know $5 um I can't make a risk like that okay $10 no tell
$30,000. Yes.
And if you- $30,000, okay.
Yes. We did it.
He is so stupid.
Yeah, little does he know, the creature loves
sweet things on his weeno
and he's gonna fuck his ass even harder.
Did we say that out loud?
Creatures have taste buds on their penises.
Yeah. They can taste donuts.
They can taste only donuts.
Yeah, I have a donut
bud on my ween.
And here is the donut
taste bud. The dentist. I went to the dentist for a cleaning and he showed me all the taste
buds. Yeah, on my penis. Here's the pasta taste bud. Here's the part of your penis that can
taste the salty. Here's the part of my mouth that can taste your penis. I need to go to
the dentist. I kind of want them, I just want... Go, go, never mind. Go to the dentist. Go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. You're so stupid. I just, I want them to do the sucker
on me. You want that sucker? I want the thing that... I desire the sucker. Yeah.
Yeah. The thing that sucks. The fish hook and then they put it in your mouth and it dries out your shit. I have thought at times about buying a sucker.
You know it just makes you it's just so your mouth gets dry. Yeah I know. Yeah.
Well you can't... I just fill my mouth with water and then and then use a sucker on it.
Use your vacuum. A vacuum is too big. No, no you can make a part. You can make a part.
Oh, yeah, no, no, no, no, no, let him finish I can make a part. Yeah. What the fuck are you talking about?
You could drill you can drill a thing of thingy. You could put a straw. It's too powerful
No, you put you put duct tape all over the end. It will create a black hole
It's too powerful. No
Over the vacuum and then you duct tape the straw to the back camera knows what I'm talking about. That's a stupid idea
Yeah, so I don't want no vacuum near my face. I want to suck it
I want to say I think it's I wouldn't vacuum is a sucker. No, you know, what's a sucker Patrick you buddy?
No, you also having the cat in you it makes it look like you have to
Underneath his sweatshirt and it is under Patrick skin. He looks like he has humongous fucking Pam Anderson's. Yep
Holding my microphone on it. Yeah that crawled into Patrick girl life hack for sure
Yep, we should have more girls on the podcast. They can do that. Mm-hmm
The cat crawled into Patrick's belly button and went under his skin and gave him real boobies
Yeah, like one of the scarabs from the mummy. Yeah
Yeah
Mummy is awesome. I've never seen the mummy ride at Universal better than the movie. I
Movie was basically there's like no movement
bathroom but that was like the movie does not even take a picture of you the movie
doesn't even touch 2g's the the ride fire plus a little bit of water the movies in
my house a big I don't want to be at home with my mommy right in Florida or I will
say the movie is cheaper it is in Los Angeles it's not cheaper if you go to
the ride for free Wow your dad is the mummy that day absolutely not oh my god
I can't even I don't even want to think about my dad as a mummy. I kind of want to be one of those walk around
Guys it is one of those walk around guys. I want to be
Around guys
Yeah, walk around they shake around they shake their little instrument the cup with the change in it and they play music for everybody
I was saying I was laughing about like waiting outside a coffee shop
And if somebody walks out with an uncovered drink just dropping a bunch of coins like
Just dirty dirty
And you're clearly homeless. Yeah, you have a good one man
It's like stinky poop coins. Yeah, it but why not just go poop then the brown cause then it doesn't have the pretense penny
There is brown there is brown coin in there. There's brown coin. There's silver coin
When I was 13, I had an idea for a documentary and oh, I think I've said this before
I had an idea for a documentary because pennies we lose money on pennies because they it cost more than a cent to make a
penny, cost like three cents or something. And I had my idea when I was 13 was to
make a documentary called, about that topic, about pennies, called Chump Change.
Yeah. Yeah, and I had, dude, I designed the poster. Didn't even think about starting
to make the movie. But I had a poster and I had a name and I had a dream but I also
had an Xbox so that shit was tough. Yeah. Yeah. We should have made that. We should
We should make another Xbox. We should make an Xbox, get this, 1080.
Okay. Because we'll skip to 720. Yeah. We don't need it. We're going full Tony Hawk.
What did he do? Tony Hawk did the 900. We're gonna do an Xbox 900. The 900 is different from a 1080.
We're gonna, okay. I don't remember the actual logistics of it. I think the 900 you go upside
down what yeah I don't think anybody's ever gone upside down on a skateboard so
what about sure about that? Mike McGill? Mike Berbiglio? What about Mr. Backwards?
That guy went backwards not upside down. Backwards the motherfucker. Did you guys see that post that I
shared? No. Did you guys see that post I shared? You're old. There was a no
there's this skateboard company it was like a 30 year old it was like Spitfire
No. I still ride Spitfires. Sick. But there's this company, New Deal, and New
Deal was like an old brand. It was like a very like... it had a lot of
people who were like ended up making other companies that are around today,
but it's like their 30-year anniversary was this year. Holy crap. What the what?
They had... Has skating been around that long? Oh my god. There was a guy who was on the
team, the original team, who couldn't come back for the 30-year anniversary due to
some allegations against him. And they made an Instagram post where they were
like, "Oh, our buddy Neil Hendricks, he just, he dodged those allegations and now we
have a new pro model for him coming out." And like all the comments are just like
like 45 year old former skateboarders just being like, "He had one of the best
inverts of all time and then you read the allegations it's just terrifying.
What are the allegations? Terrifying to you? He made a scary face into the camera.
He made somebody play the maze game. He made a woman, Louis CK is accused this morning
of making a woman play the maze game and scaring the ever-loving crap out of her
and then when she when she finally calmed down he made her play bubble wrap
maniac that's right that's right he made her play slap the monkey you made her
play slap the monkey he made her watch that video that's the car driving down
the road and then it turns into the exorcism face yeah yeah he made her look
at a demon see a real demon made her look at goatee they watched two guys one
hammer that one's the worst two guys one hammer that's what they just kill a guy
right it's just a snuff film that one was the worst I got shown that when I was
like nine I never watched it I don't like to watch people die my neighbor was like
you got to see this video it's so crazy your adult neighbor no when I was nine
he was he doesn't be an adult yeah he wasn't he was 13 when you're a kid you
only live next to kids 13 is got to be the most evil age for a boy yeah yeah
and if you're watching two guys one hammer at 13 you must be seriously
you're a boy. You got shit in your mind. You got goo for your guts. You have goom in your
brain. You got goo for your guts. You have a goomba brain. All you know is walking hate.
They shrink your head like the Mario Brothers movie. Dude that movie fucking rocks. Have
you seen the scene where the... I've seen the movie so many times. The part where 9... I
almost called the Twin Towers 9-11. The part where the Twin Towers disappear. Yeah. And
then there's like a guy the twin towers disappear and then there's a guy that
walks by and goes these people would do anything for publicity so awesome dude
yeah the best part of the movie is just them them revealing that their name that
their names are Mario Mario and Luigi Mario yeah so sick dude and the who
framed Roger Rabbit guy oh yeah Bob Costas Bob Costas
that Hoskins Bob Costas Bob Costas is a different guy throw the spice stick we're
smoking k2 yeah have you that's just reminded me okay - I had found this on a
Wikipedia article one time I don't know if I've shared this on the pub before
it's on the Wikipedia article list of entertainment affected by the September
11th attacks this is the Muppets yeah it's um the 2002 TV film it's a very
Muppet very merry Muppet Christmas movie Muppet 9/11 the 2002 TV film yeah Caleb
Caleb. It's a very Merry Muppet Christmas movie.
Okay.
That's the name of it.
I don't care.
Has the twin towers standing in an alternate reality where an angel shows
Kermit the Frog what the world would be like had he never been born.
That's the thing about that is...
So they would still be standing if he hadn't been born.
It came out in 2002 though so they must have shot it in 2001.
Wait.
Yeah.
I didn't realize that was gonna happen and then release the movie.
Exactly.
Oh no one's gonna see this.
Yeah.
Wait so they changed...
So no, they didn't change it. So they filmed it before.
Filmed it before 9/11.
Or did they change it?
I don't know.
So does that mean the Muppets exist in a world where 9/11 happened?
Yeah. No, it was added. They were added. The World Trade Center was added.
Really?
That's what it says on Wikipedia.
Damn, dude. Genius.
Yeah. So yeah, if Kermit wasn't born, we wouldn't have had to go through that tragedy.
They shot, what's his name, Gonzo? They shot him out of the cannon at the Twin Towers.
Yeah, he was the third thing that hit.
Well, are they saying that it's a bad thing that the Twin Towers are still standing?
I think so. Well, I think, no, it's like they're saying that Kermit the Frog...
We'll have to watch the movie.
It's a butterfly effect thing, you know?
Yeah.
Because that's what made Al Qaeda hate America. As they saw an episode of The Muppets,
They're like, "We have to destroy this country."
"We must destroy this frog and pig."
They thought that was his house, because they thought that he was the richest man in America
and he lived in the biggest building, and so they tried to take it down.
Oh, this is the World Trade Center article.
Oh, there's Cookie Monster taking a bite out of the Twin Towers.
Oh my God.
That's pretty funny.
That's on the cover of Sesame Street Magazine.
Damn, I gotta get a subscription.
This is the World Trade Center page on the Muppet Wiki.
A King Kong style enlarged Cookie Monster climbs the Twin Towers on the cover of the October
1976 issue of Sesame Street Magazine. His height reaches into the night sky, having taken several
bites out of both structures. Jesus Christ. Cookie Monster's height reaches into the night sky.
It's honestly crazy how many things there are like that about the Twin Towers.
Well, I mean, if you think about it, it's just like they're big buildings.
Yeah, they're iconic.
There's a Godzilla movie poster, like the poster for Godzilla versus Megalon. They're
they're both standing on top of one of the towers.
- But there's not as much destructive media
about the Empire State Building, right?
Which I think-- - King Kong climbed
the Empire State Building. - If someone,
if they took down the Empire State Building,
we would've struck back immediately.
- Yeah, yeah, there would've been nothing,
no holding back, dude.
- No, we would've gone full nuclear.
- We would've gone full Toby Keith on 'em, man.
- We would've shotgunned them all.
- Yeah, dude.
(laughing)
- We would've been shotgunned.
- Oh, here we go, we got,
about the the alternate thing. According to director Kirk Thatcher, their
appearance was not meant to imply that a Kermit is somehow responsible for the
destruction of the towers, but simply the background cycloramas/translights
that were available in Canada were more than a year old. So it's just old footage.
And that's just how they decided to cut it? Yeah. They just didn't. It's crazy.
Yeah, they didn't think about it. It's insane, man. What kind of Muppet-brained moron
came up with that one? Have you heard the Taliban song by Toby Keith? Have you
heard the Muppets song. Yes, we've played that on the show. We have? I think that was one of the
things we did on the 50th episode. Are you talking about the one that's like, and we lit up their
world like the 4th of July? No, no, no, that's a different song. That's, I like that one.
That's courtesy of the Red White and Blue. Courtesy of the Red White and Blue, yeah. The Taliban song is a song he
did with Kenny Chesney live. Whoa. And he added it to the end of Shocking Y'all. Is it good?
It's uh, I don't know. Give us a little sample. Your pipes are already warmed up for the recording
we did previously, so give us a little sing. Just play the Taliban song. No, you snip it, dude. I want to hear a
snippet. I just know that the chorus is "the Taliban baby"
the Taliban baby? that sounds pro-Taliban. Yeah it really does.
People ask me like I honestly I just was I kind of was confused. Honestly I was on a
lot of pills. I couldn't remember which one was the Taliban. I thought we were the
Taliban.
got a nice guitar so far so far it sounds pretty good
snap your fingers I love your fingers come on T-Pain style baby girl let me
buy you a drink
whoa two-bedroom cave
Kenny Chesney all of Kenny Chesney songs are about drinking Corona light on the
beach and then he pulls this fucking song out of nowhere. So we're sick dude.
They're saying, they're implying that the Taliban is what makes women wear burkas over there.
Yeah.
They have their religion.
They just hate women so much.
Yeah.
The Taliban, oh the Taliban baby.
The Taliban, the Taliban baby.
should do an auto-tune cover yeah yeah yeah we should do a hip-hop we should do
a hip-hop cover the Taliban yeah let's do it and have it like a have a have a
Christmas beat and we should have dr. Dre you know like when they like when
they have like jingle bells but it's like dun dun dun dun dun dun we should
do a soul sample we should we should use the patreon money to buy a beat from
swissbeats yeah right and then we wrapped it god damn it be awesome dude yeah
that'd be caught I'd be cool let's get Scott Stewart let's do yes dude we're
buying a Scott Stewart we should get one of those ones that he's for he plays on
a child's piano he rocks he plays the little see you know fucking Looney Tunes
cigar he plays the the little piano from the the Bismarck he song he literally
really makes beats on a speaking spell. He's awesome dude. I miss him. Scott Storch.
Yeah, there's the Make It Rain remix. I thought it was so cool. It was a Fat Joe song. I thought
it was so cool when I was a kid because the song starts and then the song like cuts and
he goes, "Yo what's up, it's Scott Storch, the number one producer on the motherfucking
planet. Took six months off, now I'm back up in this bitch." And then the song starts
again. He just wanted to do like a cool thing at the beginning. That was like his drop.
That video of him just sitting there playing that piano.
Yeah, it's so funny.
The Cubs jersey just makes that.
Dude, and his big fat fucking Italian face. That fucking chubby wop. I love him, dude.
He rocks. And just all his beats sound exactly the same.
Right, it's just him playing the piano.
playing piano. When was the last time you heard a song on the radio, a rap song, that had
like a piano riff in it? Right, I mean the last one, honestly the last
rap song I heard with a piano riff in it was "Same Love" by Macklemore. Whoa. Did he
produce that? No, that was Ryan. Scott Storch. "Same Love" Scott Storch remix? The white boys linked up again.
The white boys fucking linked up and killed the game one last time, dude.
Yo, it's Scott Storch, the number one producer on the motherfucking planet.
I took five years off, now I'm back.
And now I'm back up in this bitch to make a gay song.
When I was in the third grade, I thought that I was gay.
Get 'em back.
Oh yeah, at the end of the Make It Rain intro, he says, "Get 'em crack."
Yeah.
Fat Joe was called Crack. Is Fat Joe still alive?
He calls him Joey Crack.
Yeah, Fat Joe, he got out of jail.
Oh, big puns.
jail for like being bad at QuickBooks. It wasn't even like a cool like reason.
That's how they got Wesley Snipes too.
Yeah, they got Wesley Snipes for doing that. But that was good because it made him do like
cool movies. Didn't he do - didn't he like to pay back the IRS, didn't he do Blade and shit?
I think so.
Yeah. I don't know which one came first. I know -
I think he got - no, because he was in jail. He went to jail for tax stuff in like 2011.
Oh, okay. Oh, I'm wrong then. Maybe I'm thinking - I know that George Carlin
like owed a bunch of tax money that's why he made a bunch of
bad a bunch of yeah George Carlin all that all this shitty comedy
yeah George Carlin stopped being good like when was that being good as soon as
like people didn't care about like gay marriage anymore
yeah because he'd be he'd go on stage and he'd be like
um uh i'll tell you what people i think gay people should be able to get married
and instead of people like crying they just be like okay George
like yeah he was on George Carlin he's on speed he's on a lot of he was on one he
was he was on one yeah dude he never lived to see same love yeah if George
Carlin God was a lie my administration oh my god he would have you were the hell
out of that man no I think you would have liked him yeah yeah he would have
had some great McCain material oh my god yes he would have yeah he would he would
just be doing Trump's, the shit Trump has done about McCain. Yeah. Yeah, if it came
out of George Carlin's mouth people would like it. People would love it, calling him,
telling everyone that he's in hell. That's so funny. Dude, honestly, that is so
fucking funny. So funny, dude. He rocks. Yeah, I hope he loses the next election but keeps
tweeting. Yeah, for me the ranking of choices is number one,
Bernie winning obviously. Number two, Bloomberg winning the nomination and
then Trump winning 99% of the vote. That would be so funny dude. That'd be so fucking funny.
Just like Bloomberg only wins New York. No he loses New York. No no no,
Bloomberg wins Florida. Yeah yeah. I was gonna say like Hawaii. Yeah he wins Hawaii. Yeah.
We just think he's like he represents the Aloha. He gets a Tulsi Gabbard. He represents the Aloha
lifestyle more so than Mr. Trump. Yeah. Yeah, they think Mr. Trump's fake tan is
offensive. Yeah. They're like, "We couldn't vote for him." No, but yeah, I think that
would be the best. That would be the second best version. Just because I think...
Third, Tulsi winning, by a landslide. I mean, Tulsi winning, yeah. Oh, come on, dude. I want mommy in the
White House, dude. The thing is, I'm about eating pussy and she's gonna, she's gonna
make eating pussy mandatory yeah that's right god damn it dude i think uh i i
this scott storch video which one the one right there the one any of the one with a bunch of
fire emojis okay scott storch in the studio making fire beats that's
dude just so sick
He has a shirt that says "Get the Strap".
Damn, this dude, Scott Storch is into getting pegged, dude.
Fuck yeah, dude.
Scott Storch is trying to get pegged.
The Taliban.
Dude, and just all of his fucking, all of his fucking
cousins named Vincenzo are just in the studio just bobbing their heads.
Fuck yeah.
Wearing Young and Reckless.
Yes, dude.
Famous Stars and Straps.
Yeah, dude, drama is there.
Yeah, dramas there, DJs are drama.
DJs are drama.
Rob Dyrdek are there like, damn.
This beat is ridiculous.
Damn.
We gotta get Chanel West Coast on this one, dude.
She's gonna tear it up.
Oh yeah, she made music, right?
Yeah.
Whoa, it switched.
There's a couple of them.
There's a couple different Scott Storch making fire beats videos.
Oh yeah, there's a lot of them.
That's his cousin.
I mean, he's just playing like Mario 64 music over a fruity loops beat.
Yeah, it is so funny.
literally is just he's just playing piano I don't think he I don't think he really
makes music anymore though like I don't think I can't I don't remember the last
time I heard his gut storage but I'm sure it's just out of fashion he probably
sings songs but it's just he can't get out of his like one thing yeah nobody
wants no one piano anymore loaded Italian man yeah studio I mean the same thing
smoking the worst weed in the world
smoking weed dipped in marinara
yeah
yeah yeah yeah like dipping it in lean
he has a double cup of marinara
he's got
yeah he's sipping fucking prego
out of a fucking
two styrofoam cups
he's got a blunt in one hand and a breadstick in the other
laughing
and he mixes up
the two sometimes so sometimes he'll
just inhale a breadstick hole
(laughter)
And then he takes out a notebook and tallies.
Oh, geez, not a fucking game.
Night time this week.
Alright, back to playing the piano.
Hey! I'm out of fucking breadsticks!
(laughter)
Get over here!
Scotty, get in here!
Scotty Jr.! Get in here with my fucking breadsticks!
Scotty Jr.
and Outwalks. Not a child,
just a midget that looks exactly like him.
him just a mini me has a tiny piano a baby piano with a cow on it it's like in
the Austin Powers when he's sitting on top of mini-me's on top of the piano
with a little piano. That scene but with Scott Storch and mini Storch. Scott Storch and tot Storch.
This small, this small version.
It'd be sick.
He's got a little MPC.
Yeah, yeah.
He's got like the teenage engineering, like the one with the knobs and shit.
Fuck yeah, dude.
Yeah.
It looks sick.
Just wearing a minute, just wearing a kid's Volcom shirt.
Yeah.
Fuck yeah.
Would you get the Volcom stone tattooed on you?
Any day.
Yeah.
if it was free i would get most stuff that you don't have a good place to
display you know i have done tattoos i would go so my ass
yeah i have a of the flower
but that has a disdain but that has a rose next to his penis
nice did
it's a you can see so that you're allowed to smell it
when you get down there you're allowed to be a
because there's a flat
well i thought that you're allowed to smell it
Yeah. It's Father's Day and you're allowed to smell my penis. I got this new rose tattoo.
I got this awesome rose tattoo. Do you want to smell it? It's scratching sniff.
Hey, you scratch me and it smells.
Yeah, it's a brand new tattoo. It's flaking off as you scratch it.
Yeah, I want to get tattooed again soon. I want to get like, I want to get the lyrics of Freebird.
You should get the lyrics of I Miss You.
I'm gonna get Squidward with a big X over him.
Yeah.
If you see him.
No Squidward.
Have you seen this man?
Have you seen this big blue bitch?
Yeah, fuck you Squidward.
Yo, Squidward if you're listening man.
Squidward, if we see you, it's on sight.
It's over for you, buddy.
Dude, when you're a kid.
I'm gonna turn you into a Krabby Patty.
It's curtains on you, bitch.
When you're a kid, you idolize SpongeBob.
When you grow up, you realize Squidward was a blue bitch.
Yeah, he was a blue bitch the entire time.
Hey Squidward if you're listening, we're gonna make you sleep with the fishes buddy
Yeah, and we don't mean sex cuz you probably would like that
Yeah, but you would fuck a fish you fucking big squid freak you a monster you you suck
You are a total jack wagon you are a J a CK SS
Squidward your balls for real you smell like sit
You smell like a total hunk of sit yeah, you totally smell like sh I
S-A-I-N. You smell like shh-shh-shh.
Dude, you smell like B.O. bro. You smell like sin.
You smell like S-A-G-A-G-T. Squidward, you are one of the most sinful characters to ever grace my television, buddy.
Sloth.
Mm-hmm. That's Patrick.
Squid.
Squid. Did you know that all of the, uh, the, the cast of SpongeBob is the Seven Deadly Sins?
Didn't we say that? Yeah, we said that. We talked about that. We did? Yeah. Last episode. I wasn't here.
Last episode? Yeah.
Didn't we? I think we said it last episode. Did you know that the cast of The Simpsons is the Seven Deadly Sins?
yeah so Homer Sloth, Marge Woman, Baby... what's the baby's name?
Baby...
Lisa
Baby Driver
Baby Driver is in that movie and he doesn't talk
yeah
no he doesn't talk
he just loves music
he doesn't talk because he used to talk but he did an offensive Indian accent
so they had to...
that'd be the best move for them to do
just make... there's like a poo gets hit on the back of the head and loses all function of speech
but he just does super...
- Oh no, Pooh gets hit on the back of the head
and then he just talks in just like not an accent.
- Just do one episode where he does black voice.
Just one.
Come on, just one.
Don't even, don't talk, don't think about it.
Just like a YouTube poop dub over.
You know what I mean?
It'd just be good.
I think it would solve, it would clear up a lot of stuff.
- Pooh says pingas.
- Yeah, Pooh does the pingas thing.
- He says pingas, he says over 9000.
He does, he says mama Luigi.
- Yeah.
- He says dinner.
Luigi no that takes me back. Yeah, that takes me back to my mama Luigi. You know how he says that's mama
And he goes Maria, why would he does a weird we Yoshi Yoshi doesn't speak any English
That's mama Luigi to you Mario like they say in Brooklyn and then early to bed early to get the worm or is it the bagel?
Yeah
And then Yoshi goes Yoshi goes like
My
Yoshi think Luigi mama you seen that clip. I made I made YouTube poops of it
I seen the whole you made you a good episode poop. Yeah, it was I told you about this. No. Yeah, it was
Yeah, it was a YouTube. I took a YouTube poop in your toilet before you started man. No, I did I did I was watching Steve
1989 MRE info yeah and
Crapping. Mm-hmm. Yeah, I made yeah, I was a YouTube poop kid. I made a wow. I had a channel. I think it's still up
What was it called?
I made YTP MVs.
Whoa.
Which was YouTube music videos.
Yeah, of course.
But I took it... None of the ones I made were funny. I just was trying to recreate
the songs with the samples.
Did it work?
Yeah, I mean, I did a few.
You're sort of a top storch yourself.
Yeah, but I had no... I don't know if they sound good today.
Yeah.
Back then, they sounded awesome.
Let's pull one up.
They could have got... They could have aged the video.
What's the name of the account?
I think it's, I think it's Wargers.
Wargers.
It's like war, G-U-R-S.
I hope he has like 2 million subscribers.
I, I...
This?
Yeah.
Brian Fellow?
Yeah, I don't remember the content.
Oh, you deleted him, dude.
No, they deleted everything.
Oh no, they deleted everything.
Damn.
That's, oh yeah, because I mean it was inactive for a long time.
Damn, that's fucked up, man.
I just have the only things that I made on that are online for me as a kid are my
RuneScape music videos. Yeah. Yeah. Do a Lady Gaga music video you know what I mean?
Oh I have a video of me as a very young, very young, I look like an
oblivion NPC in the video because the camera that we recorded on was very bad.
Yeah. But it was a video we learned how to use the voiceover function because I
I had Sony Vegas because I was making YouTube poops.
- Dude, Sony Vegas was like--
- I had a pirated Sony Vegas copy.
- Absolutely.
- I loved the Sony Vegas 9 key gen music,
Unreal Super Hero 3.
- Yeah.
- Doot, doot, doot.
That song's fucking, that song's awesome.
- Key gen music was also good.
- Yeah.
I tried to, I used to make YouTube poop,
YTPMVs of key gen music.
- Yeah, that's what you do.
- That was my thing.
It was very hard to do.
I could, you know, I'm gonna try and make one.
new YouTube poop music video? I'm gonna try and make one this year. I think YouTube
poop has evolved. I think they're gonna be... I'm gonna try and make one this year. You're gonna give yourself ten months.
I'm gonna get back into the game. The game miss you. Yo it's Worgers. I took six months off now I'm back
up in this bitch. There's probably, there's like some people I was
friends with who are very big now. Big fat guys? Yeah. Yeah. No there's like, I was
in like Skype chats with people.
- Who are YouTubers?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, like who, Fred?
- Well, like big names in YouTube poop,
music video stuff, but not really.
- I didn't know that was still around.
- I don't think it's still around.
- Well, now one of the guys is big.
- Yeah.
- I don't wanna name drop.
- Tyler, the creator.
- Yeah, it's Tyler, the creator.
- Yeah, he was originally a creator of YouTube poop videos.
- He was a creator of YouTube.
- That's why his name was that.
- Yeah, because he was a YouTube creator,
he was a content creator.
And now--
changed into creating music and then it changed into creating being gay.
Yeah, creating...
Do you remember that website?
Creating cum out of his penis when he sees a man.
Yeah.
Remember that website Daily Booth?
I think he's not gay.
What website?
There's this website called Daily Booth.
It was like pre-Snapchat.
You just took like pictures of yourself.
It was like Daily Booth because it was like Daily Photo Booth.
Yeah.
So, you take like one picture.
Ashton Kutcher was on it.
Oh my.
Ashton Kutcher was very big on there.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
what we would do in the Skype group was we would go on Daily Booth and we would be
epic trolls. So we would comment on people's pictures just really fucked up
stuff. I think I showed my ass and my pubes once. Damn. Oh yeah I yeah we
used to go on Omegle and show our balls to people when we were like you
know 15. Yeah. Pretty cool. You know. Anytime there was like an old man who'd be like
here's our balls here's exactly what you wanted exactly the idea of a guy
jacking off the balls oh yeah oh my god balls the perfect the divine balls oh my
god yeah I was a big Oh Meggle fan I was not big on Oh Meggle I like daily booth
more because you could upload pictures. So, I would just Photoshop, like save their pictures
and then Photoshop them. But I didn't have Photoshop. I had some like, it was like an
in-browser Photoshop called Pixlr.
Yeah, Pixlr.
Oh, yeah. Pixlr.
Yeah, I used Pixlr and I would like liquefy their faces and then I would comment it. I
just kept blocked by people. It was awesome.
I one time fell in love on Omegle with some girl and then Levi, my younger brother, came
in and unplugged the computer as a prank and I beat the shit out of him.
Dom's like her best friend met on Omegle. Really? Yeah. See I could have had a
best friend. I have to pee so bad. Yeah. We can pause it or we can stop it but I have
to pee so bad. We can pause it. Okay I'll pause it. Alright I'm playing it again. Did you guys find
his YouTube poop account? I found I found the one that I made in the one that I
came back with in high school. Whoa. The comeback. How many views does it have? I have 5.8k views
on a video I uploaded called Full House Porn. And it's just a clip of... Let me turn it up.
not a good video. What does it say? I have 1k views on this. Go back.
You have to...
Wow, pretty funny.
You had a whole chapter that I didn't know about. Yeah.
That's crazy. I had friends from online. I knew about that. I didn't know any...
I really didn't like...
This was a pretty funny one.
This is "Fuck My Big Fat Titties."
I didn't really use the internet for anything besides gaming until like two years ago, honestly.
Like none of these videos that I've made on here make sense unless you also made YouTube
poops at the time that I made YouTube poops.
So it's like jokes for just like me and like 13 people.
Yeah see like if you scroll back far enough on my Twitter you just get like me responding
to like reporters and I'm like "what is the margin of error on this South Carolina poll?"
And like the 2015 primaries.
It's stupid.
Damn.
It's embarrassing.
If you go far enough back on my Twitter I think it's mostly just stuff of me in high
high school but I think I haven't really changed that much yeah there was one I
did bully some kid from my high school nice there nice some kid I don't know he
made I think he made fun of because I had water damage on my house mm-hmm and
had to live in a hotel for like three months really yeah you live in a never
talked about this way this is got to live yeah buddy that's awesome this is
Patrick Lord this is important I got to live in a hotel for like three months
like before Dom and I were dating while I was still in living in the hotel kind of
hotel was it was a residence in by the Marriott well that's not a bad hotel dude
the fucking insurance paid for all of it and we got so many Marriott rewards
points I was like senior high school the day the day that I like my last day of
high school was the day that we moved out of the fucking hotel share room with
anybody? Oh yeah, it was the worst. I had to sleep on the couch. My little brother...
Did you get continental breakfast every morning? I did. Oh my god. That makes it worth it.
Yeah, it did make it worth it. That's so sick. But some kid, I thought this kid... Suddenly he likes breakfast.
Mmm, oh now you like breakfast. Switching sides on us, huh? Oh I never really got
breakfast. I would just get the juice. You fucked it. I would get the cranberry juice. You squandered, you
squandered one of the... Okay, on the weekends, on the weekends I would use the waffle maker. I like waffles for
breakfast. A waffle on the weekends. But that's it. But like it has to be a big thick Belgian
waffle. Okay. But even then, even then I don't even, that's not even my first
choice. You don't even like pancakes? No. I don't want to go back into this. Yeah.
Yeah. It's too controversial. I got into, I thought this kid was making fun of me
for living in a hotel and then I found his posts on the Hypebeast forums and I
posted them and I was like look this is you getting flamed by other people on
the internet you don't want me to fucking like I don't remember what it was but it
was like they found me don't want to smoke you don't want this smoke and then
he messaged me and was like take that down I have fucking anxiety and I was
like okay bitch I have anxiety actually yeah so I said I need you to not bully
me I did take I did take the post down I was the bigger person but I have not
you're still the big talk to that when I made fun of him I was thin as shit I
know I'm saying now you're the big now and now you're bigger yeah the last I
heard of that kid was he's a fire from the last I heard of that kiss he fell
into a giant hole yeah we just discovered a sort of a soundboard technique oh you
didn't do it again obvious no camera no that's where is he he actually fell that
time. Oh, he did the reverse trick. He did the... YouTube pooped himself and reversed it.
He clicked reverse speed. Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Well, you guys didn't know you could move.
Wait, guys, I'm gonna jump. Guys, you see that big hole right there? Yeah. No, don't do it. I'm
gonna jump in it. No, don't do it. Ready? Ah! He didn't do the effect right. Oh, he just hung in
midair over the hole. Yeah, it was actually an indoor skydiving chamber. Yeah, he didn't move
it all. I'm spinning around. Cameron is clipping through dimensions right now.
There's a good video of me when I lived in that hotel with me and my little
brother and I go up to him. No! Oh my god. Patrick fell. Okay seriously we were
joking every other time there is a hole in Patrick's apartment it's where he
shits and craps into and he bounced on top of his shit and came all the way back
it's backwards Patrick. It's doodle Patrick. No.
Wait what did you say?
Someone reversed what I said.
Please somebody reverse that and tell us what it says.
There's a good video it's me I was like 17 I was like smoking a cigarette outside my brother
was like waving to my mom and I go up to him and I was supposed to stop before I
actually put the cigarette out on his arm then he moved his arm and moved it into
the cigarette just fucking burned his arm. Doesn't sound very funny.
It was a good power and he just healed. Yeah. Guys I think I see something in
the distance coming towards us. What is that? Oh my god what is it? It was a really fast
car is a car cars a guy saying the n-word so fast you only got the first and last
syllables of the way guys I think I think we're about to start listening to drop it
like it's hot like the song yeah yeah it's the song guys I think there's a
there's a microwave far away.
I don't know how to do this.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
Oh no, I think I'm gonna hold the microphone
far away from my face.
- I move away from the mic to breathe.
- Oh my God. - Whoa.
- Bringing it full circle. - Chocolate rain.
- Yeah, when the beginning of the episode
we talked about chocolate rain.
- YouTube poop.
Is a feel like this. - That song is not poop.
- There is a bunch of chocolate rain YouTube poops.
- Exactly, that's what I'm saying.
where it's like they go like
truck truck truck truck
yet to the
the
but that was a little live
and we get to know
always will make you to prove always makes you laugh when someone is really
just like
i don't know what you really think that it's not only
the best always gets me or when someone reverses the second half of the
sobel so someone goes like
soon
says it yet for us to use the pool
for our fish
please and i will use to say swears in front of us
I would use my YouTube poop reverse thing and say swears in front of teachers that way.
I'd say, "What the fuff?"
Yeah, they totally couldn't tell what you were saying.
That was like when I was a kid, I had this friend Liam who was sort of a bad boy and
his dad died because he was a drug dealer.
But Liam loved to say curse words and I did not jive with that.
So I was like, one day he said, "Fuck" in front of me and I was like, "You said fuck!
You said it in front of me!"
And he was like, "No I didn't, dude.
I said fuck.
F-O-C-K."
F-O-C-K.
And then he just started saying "fuck" all the time,
and I couldn't do anything.
I was powerless.
But then again, his dad got shot in the head
while he was driving a Hummer.
- Ooh.
- Who wins now? - Coolest way to go out.
- Yeah, the dad wins.
- Yeah, the dad wins, 'cause he's getting his dick
sucked in the Hummer too.
- No, he wasn't.
- In heaven.
- He got his dick sucked in the Hummer in heaven.
- Yeah.
- He got head.
- Dude, he got brain.
I actually don't know if that's exactly how he died.
- You split that up? - No, no, I know that he died.
I don't know if he died in his Hummer. I know he had a Hummer and he got shot.
- I just assume it was a cool movie. - You see, I saw on the highway the other day a Hummer truck.
- A huck. - A huck, yeah.
- A trucker. - A trummer.
- A hummer. - A humbler.
- A hunker.
- A Conway Practical Elite Katana.
- Nice, dude. - This is the unveiling.
Tyler, Tyler it'll sound weird on the camera.
You kind of just sound like comic book guy from The Simpsons.
Yeah.
I think that's his voice.
That's literally the guy.
Yeah.
You're right.
He saw a comic book guy and he was like, oh my God, that's the coolest guy ever.
I do that now.
I need to do that voice.
I think this was $199 US.
I think it was--
- I'll watch that video now.
- $215 after conversion.
- Man.
- Can we watch that?
- Yeah, we'll watch the episodes over.
- Oh, okay.
- But if you wanna stick around--
- If you stay till the end of this episode,
then you can hear the katana impression.
- Yeah.
- I think there was someone who was,
I think it might have been--
- Whoa.
- Someone was asking for me to post a video of it.
- Of the katana thing?
post it. I don't know. It's a YouTube video. I don't remember who was asking me. I'm gonna
have to look through Twitter. I think either way it'll be probably fine if you post it.
Yeah, that's true. Yeah, that's true. That's just really funny that I actually did the
thing like three months later. Yeah. So I'll go back to the guy. Yeah, but he could be dead
now. Yeah, the guy might be dead. Hope not. I think it might have been. I hope the guy's
dead. I'll have to look up and see who was asking me. Oh, it was Joe Mama. What? Yeah.
NO!
That's it.