You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
Alright.
Alright, back to uh...
Original recipe. Back to the good episodes.
That's right. Yeah, Patrick, there's um...
Just two ingredients.
A two ingredient simple recipe that anybody at home can follow.
Everybody knows the best delicious foods have only two ingredients.
Alright? Yep.
water ice and water cupcake in a cup chicken and ketchup fries and a burger
french fries and ketchup ketchup burger and ketchup pizza eggs and ketchup pizza
ranch pizza sauce and pizza girl and boy fork and knife yeah peanut butter and
bread and nevermind that's peanut butter and bread and jelly I'm sorry peanut
- Peanut butter and bread is good too.
- Yeah, but it's, yeah.
- Peanut butter and jelly and then--
- And no bread.
- No bread, just out of a bowl.
I just got buying one of those,
the Goobers mixed together,
peanut butter and jelly and just eating it.
- Lemon-lime.
- Oh, Sprite.
Sprite's just lemon and lime.
- Yeah, that's a classic two ingredient original recipe.
- Coke is an original recipe.
It's a two ingredient, sugar and brown.
- You eat two pretzels, that's two ingredients.
- True.
two pieces of candy yeah unless it's Reese's two pieces of Reese's that's four
ingredients peanut butter chocolate and peanut butter and chocolate that's a
good point yeah yeah there's some other classic two ingredients the point is the
point is we're better off without them yeah and I don't know what he's doing I
I know what he's doing. I wrote a battle rap about it.
Yeah.
Yeah, do you want to hear it?
Like an asynchronous battle rap? He can respond next week?
Yeah, he'll have at least a week to respond.
Yeah, okay.
But I did write something for Patrick.
Patrick, this is for you, you punk.
You stupid punk bitch.
Patrick.
*music*
Fuck Patrick
*laughs*
Fuck Jay Z
What's up Patrick you stupid fat fuck
Thought you could skip this episode?
Well good luck
You had to take a day off just to change your diaper
If I had a sniper I would shoot you
With my sniper
Bet you skipped the episode to put stuff in your ass
Probably skipping recess right now
To go to class
Being paddled by the principal for punishment then explaining to his parents that he really wanted it
Because a secret about Pat you might not know there's plenty that I can say right now
So I'll take it slow first off Pat like school, and that's not cool Pat loves rules his cats do too
That's just true. He loves homework. He hates fucking toys. He hates playtime. He loves fucking eight boys
He takes up the entire couch when he sits and Eminem murdered you on your own shit
His favorite movie is probably a girl one my favorite movie is Star Wars the third one
With the awesome fight scenes and lightsabers the Star Wars franchise to me was a lifesaver
The part where Anakin and Obi-Wan fight the night that I watched that was a great night
I wish it had more Padme so I could jack off to it even with pregnant Padme
I jacked off to it this thing between me and Patrick is like Vader vs. Luke
But I'm Darth Vader and he is a dog's poop and hey Pat don't even bother coming back because if you do
I'll own you with another rap
whoa
Fuck you Patrick
damn
You fucking suck man
Yeah, that was brutal
Yeah, I took it to him. I think you took it a little too far. I had to bring something to him
You think I took it too far? Yeah, I think he's gonna cry.
Hope so. I hope he cries. I hope he I hope he apologizes
For skipping for letting everybody yeah for crying like a bitch, baby and for letting everybody down. Yeah
You're paying for this Patrick. He's not he's we're not giving him the patreon cut this month. No, definitely not
What is he even doing? I don't know. I think he has a
Think he has a job interview for cleaner of his own toilet using his mouth and tongue. Oh, yeah
Yeah, yeah, I forgot about that.
He has a job interview to be the guy
who fucks his mom instead of his dad.
Yeah.
He's interviewing with his cats to be allowed to pet them.
They don't--
He's interviewing with his penis
to see if he could beat his own third wall.
Touch it.
Yeah, can I suck you penis?
Yeah, we'll have to have an interview for.
(laughing)
What's your greatest weakness?
I'm not flexible.
Okay, this isn't gonna work.
I bet you he's interviewing two or three hot dogs right now.
He's interviewing to be a remote eating contest contestant.
Yeah, he's doing his audition for a guy who's watching TV instead of doing the podcast.
Yeah.
And right now he's crushing it.
Fastest, fastest guzzling a bucket of cum down to the bottom.
Fastest guzzling a bucket of cum.
Fastest.
He's doing Adobe Premiere video editing to make it look like he's a girl in every video
of him online.
He's going back and he's adding big fake tits.
Yeah.
He's learning After Effects so that he can digitally add tits to himself.
Exactly.
Yeah, but he doesn't want to get the real ones because he doesn't want to actually touch
tits.
He just wants to look like he has them.
He's terrified, yeah.
He's terrified.
Yeah, Patrick, you suck, man.
Got him.
Got your ass, bitch.
I don't think he's going to be able to respond to that rep.
I think that's a nail in the coffin, career-wise.
Yeah, finally.
Finally somebody put him in his place.
Yeah, six feet under the ground.
Yeah, 'cause the reality is he doesn't like toys.
He doesn't play with Legos.
He doesn't have Nerf guns.
He has two cats.
He has two cats and a psycho-themed bathroom.
Yeah, and a mind freak magic set
hanging on the wall unopened.
Yeah, uh-huh.
Doesn't even take it out to play with it.
He sucks man, he watches R-rated movies.
Yeah, we're only G.
We watch G-rated movies for the G.
I wish G, sometimes I watch PG because it's pimp,
that means pimp G. Pimp gangster.
Pimp gangster, G is gangster.
PG is pimp gangster.
PG-13 is pimp gangster at 13 years old.
(laughing)
Yeah, we all know what the R is for.
And that's why Patrick watches it.
That's right, that's right, 'cause he's an R.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, really ugly.
- Yeah, and we know what triple X stands for,
the movie Triple X.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, and NC-17, that means North Carolina.
- 17. - 17, that's why I watch it.
- 'Cause you're 17. - That's why I watch it.
'Cause I'm 17 years old.
I wish, man.
I wish I was 17 again, like the movie.
- Yeah, I remember I watched that movie on an airplane,
and I was like, damn.
- I said, damn.
- That guy's 17 again.
That guy turned into Zac Efron.
The first movie I ever watched on an airplane was,
also that movie 17 again,
can you imagine having that big of a drop off
in your looks from 17 to 40
that you go from Zac Efron to Vince Vaughn?
Also, like doesn't he have sex with a girl?
Yeah, dude, of course.
Yeah.
Well, 'cause there's no mental age of consent.
All of those movies are based on the idea
that it's just your body.
So like in Big, remember he fucks the shit out of that bitch.
I've never seen Big.
Oh dude, Big is like about an 11 year old boy who gets old and is like a fuck so grown
woman.
He turns into Tom Hanks, he plays on a giant piano, and then he takes this girl, this girl
he works with, he like takes her back to his apartment and he like is so stupid and has
such a child's brain that he is not thinking about sex at all.
They get back to the apartment and he's like, "Do you want to jump on my bed?"
Oh my god.
like sure he has a bunk bed and then and then he she's like do you want to touch
my tits and fuck my face and he's like yeah I guess I'll do that yeah okay
alright it'd be funny one of those movies like if he's like he gets into
the he goes in the magic microwave or whatever trans changes your age and
they actually press the big button on the on the Samsung microwave and he
comes out and he's Zac Efron and he looks in the mirror and he's like oh my
god I'm Zac Efron. I love that scene in 17 again where Vince Vaughn turns into Zac Efron and says
oh my god I can finally fuck high schoolers. This is gonna rock. That is the plot of that.
The plot of the movie is what if you could go fuck high schoolers again. And Vince Vaughn signed on
so fast yeah yeah yeah then then they change the name afterward also the part
of big the best part is the end where he turns back into a kid and meets up with
the girl really he's like you're a child and he's like yeah sorry do you still
wanna fuck and she's like I don't think I can anymore but if you oh she says
yeah like wait ten years or something yeah call me when you're big again like
something like that.
(laughing)
Yeah. Call me when you're...
Hey, to a 13 year old.
Call me... I know I fucked you once,
but call me when you're...
old.
Yeah. Let me get back in the microwave.
I'll get paid again.
That's the thing. That is like, you know,
it may be well trodden territory,
but I think also,
in movies and shit, there's so many examples of
like, older women talking to
to little boys and being like, "When you're old, I'm gonna suck your dick."
And if that was reversed, it was just like...
If Big was reversed, it was just that girl,
a teenage girl with like a diary with a lock on it,
and she accidentally turns into like Scarlett Johansson,
and then like Mickey Rourke fucks the shit out of her.
And then at the end of the movie, she's like,
"Hey, so, I'm actually a little girl."
And he's like, yeah, call me when you're coming the day of your 18th birthday
As long as you have the same snatch
Yeah, we're 17 again seven well 17 again definitely would have been
Would have been more people would have liked it more if it was about a girl. Absolutely. Everyone likes everything better when it's about a girl
Yeah, that's what's happening 13 going on 30s another movie like that. I don't remember she has sex in that though
I haven't seen that one either 13 guys the
Isn't it doesn't happen in blank check - or but there's not a transformation. He's just rich
Which is kind of it's the same thing if you're a rich kid you can
You're an independently wealthy 13 year old that's really do whatever you want. Yeah
That's basically to a woman. That's the same as being an adult. Yeah
(laughing)
Having a lot of money.
That movie rocks though.
Blank Check was like,
that was like, as a kid I was like,
this will be the blueprint for my life.
Yeah, this is what's gonna happen to me.
Yeah.
I'm gonna have a rocket skateboard
and I'm gonna ride it down the banister
of my mansion every morning.
Yeah, I'm gonna have a,
I used to love any movie that was about
like a really rich kid.
I used to love that movie,
did you ever seen The Toy with Richard Pryor?
No.
Terrible movie in hindsight. It's about Richard Pryor is
Get this he's a black guy. What and a rich man buys him for his son
Richard Pryor like works for this guy or something and he's like listen, what if I what if I pay you to be my son's toy?
And he does it dude and when I was a kid, I was like the it was my favorite movie. I thought it was
It is funny to me, you know, it is a Richard Pryor movie but
Any movie that's just like like a kid doing adult stuff. Yes was cool to me, you know, Richie Rich
just being
Being able to do anything you wanted, you know, yeah
Butler prank, but yeah pranking the butler. Yeah
I mean that is what the toy is, is it's just Richard Pryor, he gets bought by a white guy
and then the son just like pranks him all day.
Is like pulls out, pulls the thousands dollar carpet out from under him and breaks his neck.
That's what you do with the toy, you prank it.
Yeah you prank the shit out of your toys.
Play tricks on your human toy.
It's funny that Richard Pryor was in a movie called The Toy before there was ever like a
a black GI Joe or anything.
Like it was, Richard Pryor was the first black toy.
I mean we don't, we won't have equality in movies until we get an all-white reboot of
the toy.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, yeah, directed by Jordan Peele.
Yeah.
Yeah, and it's a, they could, he could do a remake of that as a horror movie now probably.
No, it should just be a comedy.
Who would he buy as a toy?
Who would the white toy be?
Yeah, the white toy.
Adam DeVine.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
Perfect.
Yeah.
Or Adam Devine.
Whatever the one from Workaholics is.
The chubby one.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't know.
Yeah.
That guy is annoying.
I don't like looking at him.
Oh, yeah.
You don't like his house party?
What's that?
He has a show called Adam DeVine, DeVine, DeVine, DeViney's House Party.
That's a really long name.
Yeah, it's a terrible name for a TV show.
But it's like 30 minutes of just like his friends doing stand up.
It's not very good.
It's pretty awesome.
But they do it outside.
It's an outside...
I wish that more...
I really hope...
It would be awesome.
You know how so many like...
I guess this is probably not just an Emerson thing but like just like a bunch...
When there are a bunch of rich kids who are in a friend group who are like want to do
like comedy or write or whatever, there's always...
like a thousand friend groups and they're all just like you know what we should
just write a sitcom that's just us and I really hope that like it would be so
like it is in like five years just TV is just full of just terrible yeah the
other one is the kids quad the friend a mutual friend of ours I don't want to
tell I don't want to say who this is because but you will know who this is
because it is kind of embarrassing but he told me and another friend that what
like the first week that we were in college, he was like, "Yeah, my dream show, my dream
like job basically would be like a show that's like about me as like a stand-up comedian
in New York City and I would just be like walking around and like doing shows.
Maybe I'd eat pizza in the opening."
It was just, it was Louis.
Yeah.
No, absolutely.
That's those are the two the two ends of the spectrum is of like rich of like here's my pilot idea
Yeah, it's either the sjw side is is the the the friend group and the free speech side is the is the bomb
Stand-up. Yeah, yeah, but but because for the sitcom breaking to one of my friends that he has to be the disabled one
Hey, man, I know that your legs work in real life, but in the show you're gonna be in a wheelchair
Listen pal. Um, we're like really committed to diversity, but we're all white. So you gotta be Chinese. Yeah
You're gonna have to take
You should be you should be really excited for this opportunity to to try and portray another culture
It's really you can bring it. This would be you can branch out here. Yeah. Yeah, we're gonna you're the one everybody's gonna play themselves
But we are we're gonna cast Lupita Nyong'o to play you just so you know
David you're gonna be yeah played by Lupita. Yeah, we told David he had to be Chinese in the show
And it's he's we don't hang out with him anymore because he just started method method acting all the time
Yeah, he insisted on playing. Yeah, he was doing Jared Leto style pranks. He was sending he was putting rice in people's mailboxes
That's my role.
Yeah, I don't think TV like that's going to exist in five years, honestly.
Absolutely not.
No, like it's just everybody's so stupid that they think that like, like, there's a point
where like, even even though like every there, you'll have a 10 person friend group and every
single one is the son of a different executive at some like TV company, their show is never
gonna get made, 'cause it sucks fucking ass, dude.
It's so bad.
Yeah, also just like, I truly don't think in 10 years
there will be the same sort of network infrastructure.
I think it's already going away so fast.
I think in like five years,
something I remember in like late 2000s,
when cord cutting first became a thing
and Netflix streaming and Hulu
and a couple years later, the HBO stuff.
I think then everybody was like,
oh, this is like the beginning of a new era in media
or whatever, it'll be super hyper-focused
and no show will have 50 million people
watching it ever again.
And everybody's like, ah, phooey.
But I think it's now is when that's happening.
- Absolutely. - You know what I mean?
- Yeah, there's so many shows
that just people have never heard of.
- There's also, at any given point in time on TV,
there's five good TV shows that are worth watching
out of hundreds, but people, a lot of people,
especially now are just, even like my parents,
like my dad watches like a YouTube show now.
Yeah.
And I was like, oh, that is like the,
I would say the barometer for when the seas
have changed a little bit.
Absolutely.
When my fucking, my dad who,
my dad doesn't have cable anymore,
and my dad used to watch, he used to watch ESPN
like it was his job.
Yeah.
sit there, watch PTI, dip, drink Coca-Cola,
and then spit on me.
And now, like he watches some fucking sports show on YouTube.
- Yeah. - You know?
Just weird.
- It's so funny to like look at the landscape of streaming,
like how it is in this like crazy time
where just like all these people are getting their voices
heard and like new stuff being made,
and then like fumble the bag as hard as Quibi.
- Oh man. - This is the new thing.
I haven't even looked at Quibi. What happened with Quibi?
I mean it's just failing miserably.
But did it actually launch and shit?
Yeah, it's been out for a while.
And I remember, because when I was interning at a company,
You can just say it, they'll be gone in nine months.
Yeah, when I was interning at Funny or Die, like so much of their shit was like,
"Oh yeah, we're producing a new show for Quibi."
And I was like, "What the fuck is Quibi?"
And they're like, "Oh yeah, it's a new streaming service where you can only watch on your phone."
And I was like, oh, well, that's gonna fail.
Like this, that's the instant reaction.
It's like, oh, nobody would watch that.
What are you talking about?
- I mean, that's just what YouTube is.
- Yeah, it's like, but YouTube,
you can watch it on your computer
and you don't have to pay.
- True.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Quibi's just like, what if we took,
what if we made like worst shows that nobody wants to watch?
And they're like, their whole deal was like,
oh, we're gonna get like big directors
and we're gonna get like a draw for this.
Like, it's all new content.
So we're like, oh, we're gonna have a new Sam Raimi show
and everybody's gonna flock to that.
- But they don't realize is that--
- Nobody fucking cares.
- Yeah, nobody's like,
there's maybe 4,000 people who are like,
I need to watch the next Sam Raimi project.
Most people have no idea,
like a larger audience doesn't know,
unless you get--
- They don't have enough big jobs.
- J.J. Abrams or Christopher Nolan to make quibby shows,
which will happen. - Exactly, yeah.
They didn't get big enough names.
- Yeah, nobody's gonna fucking--
- It's so funny, and yeah,
just like the only way I could see that succeeding
is if like people watching it on their commute, right?
But now nobody commutes anymore
'cause everybody's at home all the time.
There's no reason to watch anything on here.
It's so funny.
Like they're only paying us for success.
I'm glad, dude.
Quibi deserves to fucking rot.
- Well, there's enough platforms.
- They're pumping so much money into it.
It's like so insane, dude.
- Is there any like, you know,
'cause they always do that thing where they like,
those new streaming services get like one,
One like niche, like cult comedy,
like sketch team or whatever.
It's all new content.
So they don't even have the draw of like,
oh, the movies you used to like.
But do they have like,
did they pick up like some like YouTube,
like a sketch trio or something and give them a show?
I don't know.
Oh, wait, I'm gonna look up their--
That's what, what was the NBC one
that was just for comedy that sucked so bad?
See So.
Yeah, See So tried to pick up like all these small,
Like, basically tried to grab all these podcasts
and they were like, "Hey, make a show."
- Yeah.
- And all of them fucking sucked, dude.
- I mean, yeah, it's just, you're not gonna,
you're not gonna make a new streaming service
and have it succeed unless you,
unless you're a giant, already a giant, like.
- Yeah, basically if you can,
the only reason Disney+ worked
is because they had Star Wars to put on it.
- Absolutely. - And the Avengers.
If Disney+ had been like,
"Hey, you can watch Song of the South again."
Nobody, except me maybe, would have subscribed to that.
- Wait, I'm trying to find the lineup.
Oh, they're putting movies on there too?
I thought it was just shows.
- Movies that are, they have vertical movies?
- Yeah, no, so the thing is,
it's like all either vertical or horizontal.
Like you can change, you can switch it,
and it's like a different shot
based on how you hold your phone.
Yeah, this is so...
(laughs)
It's starring, you're just scrolling through a movie,
It's like starring Liam Hemsworth and Christoph Waltz.
Starring, uh...
We're gonna make- let's do a new streaming service so you can only watch on the LCD panel
in your car.
And you can only watch it when it's- when you're driving.
The engine has to be currently active.
They have a- they have a Chrissy- they have a Small Claims Court show hosted by Chrissy
Teigen.
Oh, fuck, dude.
Called Chrissy's Court.
Goddamn it, dude.
That sucks.
Damn it, dude.
Oh shit, they have a reboot of Punk'd.
I hope all the-
Who did I chance the rapper?
I bet every- that her ruling on every small claims court thing is she's like-
Stop attacking me.
Yeah, I need $3,000 from this person.
She's like, "Well, why don't you just ask your husband for it?"
Yeah.
Yeah, just give it-
Just ask your rich husband.
Oh, it's only $3,000?
I mean, just give it to him.
$3,000, that's not- I mean, I would give it to you if I didn't need it to publish a
cookbook. Yeah I thought this was supposed to be issues that mattered. I mean just
give them the $3,000. I still love watching Divorce Court. Did you ever
watch that? No. Divorce Court rocked. They'd get two of the like shittiest
white people in the world who were fighting over some ugly kid with an
undiagnosed learning disability and they'd put the kid in the middle and
and they'd put the two white parents
with pimples on either side.
And then the like sassy black judge would just be like,
"You need to do this for your daughter!"
And make them cry.
It was one of the greatest shows ever.
I don't think it's around anymore.
It was that, Judge Joe Brown.
They were like Judge Judy like spinoffs, you know,
but just doing kind of the same thing.
- Dude, I'm reading through the like lineup
of like unscripted shows on here, on Quibi,
and this is just insane.
There's so many that just sound like
they're generated by AI.
There's one called Game Show, G-A-Y-M-E.
You said generated by a guy?
AI.
Oh.
Artificial intelligence, you heard of it?
No.
There's Game Show, it's a gay game show.
There's-- Game Show, G-A-Y-M-E?
Yeah.
That's not bad.
Listen to this, listen to the description of this.
This is a cooking show called Dishmantled.
Each episode of the cooking competition hosted by Titus Burgess starts with a cannon blasting
of a mystery food dish into the faces of two blindfolded chefs.
They have to identify the exploded dish and then race against the clock to recreate it.
Fuck, dude.
Oh my god, man.
The race to like, the like, turning, I mean it's just, it's becoming idiocracy so much
faster than I thought it would be.
You ain't got these.
about sneaker culture from executive producer Lena Waithe. Fierce Queens
presented and narrated by Reese Witherspoon nature series from the BBC
Studios natural history unit explores the fabulous females of the animal
kingdom from ant Queens to speedy cheetahs. Oh my god bro are you serious?
That fucking rocks it's just Reese Witherspoon just talking
over like a praying mantis eating its mate. Yeah, work. And that's boss shit. God man,
that sucks. We should get a show. Yeah, we should. Quibi, we'll stop flaming you if you
uh... I'll do a whole show of Patrick Rap Battles. The Daily Chill, show that takes users
on a pathway to calmness with each episode featuring a new global destination and a new
ASMR journey to peace. Damn, it's so much funny how much money, like between like, stuff
like that ASMR headspace just like how much money gets pumped into just making
people calm yeah because everybody freaks out all the fucking time damn they
have so much news what the fuck they have a bunch of news networks they have the
weather channel and NBC and BBC News CBS ESPN is there like like is it right if
you hold it side if you hold it sideways it's just regular news but if you hold
it if you hold it horizontal or vertical you get to see under the desk yeah you
to see what their legs look like.
Yeah, that's right.
You just see the bottom half, baby.
(laughs)
Yeah, this is,
it's ridiculous, so stupid.
It's just that I don't understand
why they thought this would take off.
It's because the people who have money
and put money into stuff are so stupid about,
they just have the worst ideas
and they invest in the worst ideas
because they're all fucking 70 years old.
- Yeah, well the guy, the like CEO of Quibi or whatever
did like a talk at our school in LA.
And I didn't go, but apparently he was like super like
excited about it and like super pumped up and be like,
"You guys are not gonna believe how incredible
"Quibi is gonna be."
And like showed everyone like a demo of it
and they were just like, "Oh."
- It's 'cause he probably fucking snorts Adderall
before he does any one of those fucking shows.
He doesn't care.
Nobody cares, if you're making over a million dollars
for anything, you don't care about it.
Absolutely.
No, you're just, you're phony, you're pretending.
That's why we care about this podcast,
because we make like $1,100 a month split three ways.
That's why this podcast is so good, of the highest quality.
Yeah.
Because we review movies like "The Toy"
and uh... big and other movies where kids fuck adults
you know and you don't you don't get that kind of stuff a million dollar
production budgets you get that from home-grown grass-grown grass-fed organic
smoking grass podcasts
they fucking uh... they'd be making a remake of the fugitive
a modern social media infused update of the classic
come on dude
uh... yeah we're gonna we're thinking of doing this awesome uh... serve a modern
take on moby dick but instead of a whale we're thinking he could be a big phone
yeah
we're thinking of infusing the storyline with apps
yeah we're thinking of doing uh... the great gatsby but it's it's the great
appsby
and he has been he has uh... he's rich he's still rich but he actually has invented
some apps in this
well they got a ridley scott movie
yeah i i don't know if you call it a tentative on aliens
i invented an app about uh...
is my app
uh... loaded potatoes kids with guacamole on the side hell yeah my right that's
what i'm talking about it at at let's get that viral
of the download that eric andre doing rapper warrior ninja
well that's awesome i bet it's gonna be sick to you know that i've been a
concern the phone vertical to see the second view is going to be him for
He's freaking flipping the camera off.
Yeah, I bet he does a back flip.
Yeah.
Yeah, I bet they get a guy who looks
kind of like him to do a back flip.
I bet.
And they cut between, yeah.
Yeah.
We should do an awesome Eric Andre video.
Yeah, I mean that's, people love it, dude.
It's millennial daddism.
It's become a huge, yeah, exactly.
Yeah, if you ever watch a video--
It's become a huge, huge genre.
And something in there makes you freak out a little bit
you don't understand how it is or what it means,
I'm thinking you might've just seen some millennial daddaism.
- Yeah, hey mom, somebody's screaming on TV.
- Yeah. - This is not normal.
- Somebody posted a picture of a guy and said,
this is Justin Bieber, but it wasn't Justin Bieber.
- Yeah, that's right.
- That's a little thing called Zoomer Absurdism.
And it's the new-- - Yeah, that's sort of,
that's like, Drill is sort of the new Man Ray.
- Yeah.
- You know what I mean?
It's just about skewing reality
with just by just noticing,
oh, one little thing is off here, you know?
- Yeah.
There's this picture of a box and it says,
it's a box of Pop-Tarts, but it says Cop-Tarts.
And do you know what the picture on the box is?
It's a picture of a policeman.
- Oh my God.
You know what, to me, I was thinking,
I think the image macro that still makes me laugh
from my childhood is the Call of Duty Black Cops
and it's Michael Winslow from Family Matters.
That's a good, that's good, man.
That's still, that's some good zoomer dot dot dot dot.
That's some goo goo ga ga.
- That's some goo goo ga ga.
- That's some good good gingo ga go.
- You got that good good gingo ga go for me.
- Have you, I know me and Pat have talked to you,
but have you watched any goo goo foods yet?
- No.
You have to, man.
All right, I'll check it out.
It's so good, dude.
He made a video, Pat sent me this video,
it's him deep frying, the title is Deep Frying Every Meat.
(both laughing)
It's really just like six meats,
but he deep fries like a lobster tail,
and everything, he just like, he loves all of it,
but it's like, the question every time is like,
Is this good?
But he's a big, fat Puerto Rican dude,
and, or Brazilian guy, and it's like,
yeah, of course he's gonna like a deep fried pork chop.
So every single time he's just like,
and I was very worried about whether or not
this deep fried steak would be good,
but I took a bite and oh my goodness,
let me tell you folks,
it was one of the most amazing experiences of my life.
And he just says that about every kind of meat.
It's really good, man.
That sounds awesome.
You ought to check it out.
I haven't been watching as many stupid videos recently.
I've just been playing video games like seven hours a day.
Yeah.
It rocks.
I've just been watching movies and TV shows.
Anything good?
No.
No?
Just don't watch shit movies?
Yes, but it doesn't really matter.
I mean, it wouldn't be interesting to talk about.
I'm just interested in what you're watching.
I've been watching, well I recently, I already talked about it, I recently watched the Planet
of the Apes reboot trilogy. Those are so good. I've been thinking about those like every day.
You just want that to- You want monkeys to take over the world.
No, I- Only if I was a monkey. I wouldn't want to be killed by a monkey.
You should get surgery to look like a monkey. That's not a bad idea.
Human proportions. Human proportions so they think you're really
big. Well, no, you could have your legs and arms like- or your torso like shortened. And
You could have your feet all fucked up.
Just put your shoulders right on your hips.
Just completely eliminate your tits.
And uh, yeah, yeah, you're all fucked up.
Coming out of surgery, "Do I look like a monkey now?"
Yes Cameron, you look so much like a monkey.
Please just get in this cage like a monkey is and we'll put you on display and people
can pay to watch you like a monkey.
We're gonna put you in the carnival like a monkey.
Thank you.
Yeah, and you get hair plugs all over your body.
You look like, what's his name, Cousin It or whatever.
Chewbacca.
You're thinking of Chewbacca from Adam's family.
You look like Chewbacca from Adam's family, yeah.
Cousin Chewbacca.
Yeah, Cousin Chewbacca.
What if freaking Chewbacca was your cousin?
Oh my God.
Imagine what that uncle looks like.
Yeah.
Uncles are already so, my uncle's pretty hairy.
He's kind of got Chewbacca vibes.
Yeah.
Serious Chewbacca vibes from my--
Who's your hairiest uncle?
I have an uncle named Harry.
Is he hairy?
Yeah, pretty hairy.
Or is that a prank from God?
Yeah, that's one of God's great persons.
A lot is more is that, "Like an uncle named Harry, who is not hairy."
He's completely smooth all over.
Like a baby named Harry.
But the baby doesn't have hair, just to clarify.
Yeah, the baby--
A brand new baby.
Try again.
Like a hairless baby who won't grow any hair.
Who's named Harry.
- And he just came out.
- And he just came out of the vagina.
- You can't say that word in a song.
They'll ban the song.
- Vagina?
- Yeah.
- Yeah you can.
- No you can't.
They'll ban the song.
- Yeah.
Three, six, nine.
Damn you fine.
Put your vagina.
Man, you bitch, your vagina's on my mind.
Remember that song?
- No, it got banned.
- You don't remember that song?
Vagina wide open. You remember that? I don't know what you're talking about or
Head strong I take you on head strong vagina
Yeah, I never understood. Yeah, they're trying to say
Yeah, what are you trying to say there?
Yeah, it doesn't really make sense
Yeah
Doesn't uh, yeah. Oh, I
Vagina, how about instead of I'm a bee, it's vagina free.
Free?
It's about being such a guy.
Yeah.
I'm vagina free.
I'm living the vagina free lifestyle.
Yeah, vagina free.
I'm a bee, vagina free, that's what I am.
That would be one of the lines.
Yeah.
And then will I am, it would be,
instead of will I am, it would be I am Will,
because Will's a boy's name.
Yeah.
And Fergie, Fergie, um, well Fergie would be a guy then.
I guess.
It would be Fergus.
Ferguson.
Ferguson, the guy, the tall, the tall blonde guy in the Black Eyed Peas named Ferguson,
who has a song called "My Humps" and it's about his balls.
my humps, my lovely--
It's called My Dumps,
and it's about the big fat man poops.
Yeah, he's about taking a big shit in the toilet.
It'll take half an hour.
Yeah.
My dumps.
I would say, I probably spend about an hour a day
on the toilet. My stinky fella dumps.
My stinky fella dumps, check it out.
I probably spend about an hour of my day on the toilet,
And I probably spend, of that time,
maybe 15 seconds shitting.
Yeah.
'Cause when I get on the toilet,
it's like a trash chute opening.
Like it's just, all of it falls out
of my big asshole immediately.
Yeah.
And then I just sit there and I'm like,
well this is phone time.
Yeah.
You know?
Oh I know, I know what you mean.
Yeah.
I think I've talked about this,
but I think when I was a kid one time,
I walked in on my dad taking a shit
and he was reading the newspaper.
And I just looked at him for a long time
and he was like, "Get the hell out of here."
And the reason I was looking at him
was 'cause I was transfixed,
because I never thought of the idea
that you could just sit on the toilet
and read and escape your family.
- Yeah.
- It's so genius.
- It is ingenious.
- That's why they made bathrooms.
You used to just shit in the living room.
But then a man--
- I used to be at the dinner table.
- A man was like, "I need a fucking,
"I need some fucking alone time.
I need to do a crossword.
Dinner table chairs used to just have a hole under them.
Chamber pots under, yeah.
Yeah.
And you would shit in them.
Yeah, and then some guy was like, "Man, I hate my wife so much."
"I hate my wife so much that I'm gonna build an entire new room that's a no wife zone."
And then eventually, because of various amendments and second wave feminism, women were allowed
to use bathrooms.
Yeah, and then they made the man cave, which is kind of like a second bathroom for the house.
And then pretty soon they're gonna try to, those fucking sneaky bitches are gonna try
to weasel their way into the man cave. And then you know what we're gonna make? We're
gonna make a spaceship that only men can go on that flies over the moon. We're gonna make
the man car. We're gonna make the, yeah. Yeah. That's an idea I stole from Saudi Arabia where
all cars are man cars. It's kind of a genius. That is why they did that. In Saudi Arabia,
they don't have man caves. They decided that men needed a place just for them and it's a
sweet Corvette. Absolutely. It's a fucking just a pimp ass vehicle. Yeah. Women,
hey sorry baby no girls allowed. Yeah. I'm in my man car I'm driving around I'm
listening to my vagina free song. Yeah. I'm listening to the sack guy penis. Yeah I'm
listening to your favorite Martian riding around in my Volkswagen and I'm
just having a little man time. Yeah. Just for myself. Singing along. Yeah. I'm listening
to the audio of Dave Portnoy's pizza reviews on YouTube just because I'm such a guy. And
I'm singing along to that too. Yeah. One bite, that's the rules. Yeah. So, we actually, I
I don't know if you saw this,
but we got a hit piece written about us.
A hit piece?
Somebody's talking shit?
About podcast, about list.
Yeah. Oh my God.
It's not.
Well, we gotta take them down.
Did you hear that hit piece that I threw at,
Patrick's, wait, did they talk about Patrick in this?
Oh, they do.
Oh my God, he's gonna get over twice, dude.
Yeah, no, there's some stuff I didn't know about him
in here. Wow!
Yeah, this is, it was from,
it's from kind of like a scold outlet
called the daily gulag
uh... okay like this like s leftist online publication which i've never
heard of but
uh... yeah and uh...
it's by this guy named i_m_d_ poop sucka
so i which i've never i_t_d_
it stands for
isaiah michael david
so that what she put under is and under the byline it's he said it stands for
as a michael david but it says
it also says it says right next to that i chose to use the initials because i
I just think initials sound cool when you're writing.
'Cause I don't know why he put that
at the top of the article. - IMD.
- But-- - What's it, wait,
what's his last name again?
- Poopsucka?
- Hmm. - I think that's like--
- Yeah, I would've gone IMDP.
If I was him. - Hmm?
- I would've gone full initials.
- Oh, it says actually right next to that
that he didn't do full initials
because it would get confused
with the Internet Movie Database,
which is IMDB. - Oh, Internet Movie Database.
- Yeah. - I forgot.
Yeah, I use that a lot. - The sequel.
But yeah, so this article,
hopefully we can put some of these,
the the... We can respond yeah you know kind of this is a huge milestone you
know first people trying to take us down. Yeah so this is the article is called
Israel's number one podcast a look at podcast about list the crap monster of
the online left. So I'll just I guess okay yeah yeah this is our first
literature review. Yeah yeah there's a new podcast on the block and leftists
everywhere are dropping everywhere to drink dropping everything to drink
deeply from its proverbial trough the problem as it always seems to be with
these podcasts is that the slop in the trough isn't as pure as the piggies
seem to think welcome to the dark world of podcasts about lists I'm gearing up
just spray go to war yeah I mean I mean if we're just gonna pick this apart as
we go it's not fair to call the fans piggies I mean yeah if you're a tag you
attack us all you want but the second you come for the people who give me five dollars on patreon.com
Will you leave our disgusting fat fans alone? Yeah I'm gonna wild out on you.
But it continues despite claiming to oppose the views of the Grinch, podcast about list has on
multiple occasions provided a platform for his revolting and frankly dangerous system of beliefs.
The trio uploaded a Grinch-along to their Patreon spreading the Grinch's sick gospel to their premium
subscribers. They also constantly crack jokes about the plight of the Hoos in
modern Whoville and prominently feature the Grinch in multiple promotional
graphics. Even amidst claims that they align with the Hoos of Whoville, one
can't help but wonder whether the "list boys" are crypto Grinchists.
Even beyond the issue of the Grinch, you don't have to look much further than the
backgrounds of the hosts to deduce that the podcast might not be the wholesome
politically pure romp many consider it. This is where it starts to become kind of
a personal case. Okay, can we just stop right here? Yeah. Any sort of, I mean, I
feel like we've made it abundantly clear that any endorsement of the Grinch's
actions is completely ironic. Absolutely. We're doing it sort of to make fun of him.
Yeah, to highlight the stupidity of holding that position. How funny it is, how weird it would be, and how absurd it is to
actually be pro-Grinch. Exactly. I feel like we've made it clear, like with our
are, and that's what it was so annoying. People got, people came after us for,
because we made fun of when they did the, the hoove bombing.
Yeah.
The Philadelphia police department did the hoove bombing and they killed all
those hoos in Whoville. But it's not, that was,
we weren't making fun of the victims.
We were making fun of the Philadelphia police department.
Exactly. And you know, it's comedy that can take down people like that.
That's why it's so important.
Exactly, and that's why I think it's important for us to lampoon the grand...
Okay, have you... do you know Stephen Colbert?
I've heard of him, yeah.
Okay, so basically every night of the week, this guy does a brilliant impression of a mentally
disabled guy on TV.
Yeah.
On... it's called The Late Show with Stephen Colbert.
And what he's doing is he's lampooning that kind of person.
He's not actually disabled.
He actually in real life knows how to tell a joke.
But he does this awesome character every night.
Exactly.
Where he tells just the worst jokes, just over and over and over again to nobody.
And they mean nothing and they're about nothing.
But he's doing an impression of a terrible late night host with mental.
He's showing how ridiculous it would be to be a late night host who had that kind of
limitation in your brain.
Exactly yeah.
So he's doing sort of an impression.
And how unjust that would be.
Exactly yeah.
He's, I don't know, it's called parody.
Look it up.
find a little, you know, a little song called "Bad" or called, sorry, "Fat" by Weird Al
Yankovic and you're gonna, you leave it to this guy to watch that and go, "Oh, okay, so
I guess Weird Al's fat?"
Geez.
Yeah, it's like just because you're not smart enough to understand the-
Weird Al isn't fat in real life.
He's also not Amish, okay?
He might be Amish.
But-
Yankovic sounds like an Amish last name to me.
He could be, yeah.
Alright, continue.
Yeah, so this IMDpoopsucka starts out with talking about Patrick's background.
Patrick Doran, who constantly posts skateboard and Yoda content in order to draw attention
away from his extremely upper-class upbringing, is the heir to both the McDonald's and Taco
Bell fortunes.
That's right, his parents are none other than Ronald McDonald and Gidget the Taco Bell Chihuahua.
He's also recently become CEO of the video app Byte.
Is this your working class just like you online darling?
A billionaire rich kid who's a CEO and also half dog?
That's fair.
I think...
Yeah, no, that...
I would say I'm in no position to try to defend Patrick right now.
I think if there is...
If anything in this article is true, it's definitely that.
I will say he doesn't talk to his parents and they don't support him anymore because
the podcast Patreon does plenty for him.
He lives on about $150 a month.
- Yeah, which is, I mean, fine.
He just eats kibble.
- Yeah, I mean, how many dogs live on more than $150 a month?
- Not many. - Very few.
- And he's only half dog, so he actually only needs $75.
- Yeah. - That's how it works.
And then they move on to you, Caleb.
- Whoa. - Yeah.
And speaking of ancestors-- - Can I pause you right here?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Is thisy gonna hurt my feelings?
I mean, I don't know. Only you can control that. Think about that.
All right.
That's something Ricky Gervais once told me.
Let me put on my helmet.
Okay. And speaking of ancestry, let's talk Caleb Pitts.
It's with Caleb that the corrupt and questionable dynamics of the podcast start to truly reveal themselves.
Based on pictures and videos posted to his Twitter feed,
scientists have deduced that Caleb is some sort of Pokemon style pre-evolution to the human race,
a missing link between monkey and man
he is coerced into recording the podcast by patrick and cameron and research
confirms he doesn't even receive compensation for his labor
i have always just felt like you guys are doing such a great opportunity
being the podcast yeah the intern
you know being the only non-human
pre-evolved
yeah i i understand that i don't deserve
any money you know what i mean because i'm subhuman yeah you know i don't want to say
I don't want to say scum, but I'm not a guy.
You're getting exposure.
Yeah, and I actually didn't even know that I was a monkey or had monkey sort of stuff
in me, monkey whatever.
See, I can't even think of the word because of my monkey brain.
Monkey spunk.
I didn't know I had monkey spunk in me.
I didn't know I was half monkey spunk until you guys pointed it out by taking that photo
of me.
I always just thought I was a normal kid.
And yeah, sometimes I like to climb trees.
I like to eat bananas.
times I'd like to fuck a frog to death, use it like a fleshlight in my backyard.
But I always was just like, well, I'm just maybe, you know, a gifted kid.
That's just how you express yourself.
Yeah, you know, and that's what everybody told me.
But so I really, really, I should be paying you guys.
Absolutely.
You know what?
For teaching me who I really am.
We should talk about that after the episode.
Yeah, I'm willing to do whatever, you know.
I don't have much, you know,
'cause I don't get paid from this,
or even my real job at Amazon Fulfillment,
because they heard about that you guys aren't paying me,
and they figured, you know,
they said, "Well, it's only fair."
Yeah, well, we told them.
"If we also don't pay you."
Not to.
Oh, you guys told them?
Oh, thanks, 'cause now it's like way,
now I feel like I have a huge monkey off my back.
It's simpler for you.
I mean, it's easier, it's not way hard,
it's hard to keep track of numbers
and pieces of paper and--
Exactly, yeah.
Yeah, so yeah, that was all us.
So you have us to thank for that.
- Thank you, buddy.
- Of course. - You can continue.
- Now then they say some stuff about me.
Deep research into Cameron's background
revealed that he is actually normal
and not at fault for anything mentioned in this article.
Cameron is normal and honestly a pretty cool guy.
Would love to talk to Cameron sometime
and maybe even give him a weekly allowance,
you know, some pocket money
so he could buy snacks and video games.
So this is where it starts making sense to me a little bit.
I can understand where this guy is coming from
towards the end of the article.
It's just, you know, I think he,
maybe he isn't as stupid as he seems at the start
'cause I think he's making some pretty salient points
about my background and how I'm normal.
- Yeah, I mean, what'd you say the guy's name was again?
- IMDPoopsucka.
- Okay, could you link me this?
- Yeah, sure.
I'm gonna share it with some people.
All right, I just sent it to you.
Okay.
Cool.
What are you thinking?
I mean it's--
No, I mean it looks, you know,
it looks real to me.
Yeah, it's on, this is the Daily Gulag.
Why would this not be real?
No, no, I'm not saying it's not real.
It's just interesting that they would go after
me and Patrick so hard.
They're going after me pretty hard.
I mean, they didn't, they just said I'm normal.
I mean, they could have said I was cool.
Or they did say I was cool.
They could have said I was really cool, very cool.
- They could have said you were extraordinary.
- So, yeah, they could have said
I was an extraordinary young boy
and I deserve everything in the world,
but they just, I know, it's a weekly,
it's not a daily allowance.
I think they were pretty harsh on me.
- Is that where they ended it?
That's where they ended the piece?
- Well, no, and then it says,
"So next time you hear someone say
"they love listening to podcasts about lists,
"sock 'em one in their fat, juicy mouth.
"They deserve it.
"P.S. Cameron, if you're reading this, you're awesome."
So I guess they did say I was awesome, too.
But I mean, that's, it's probably sarcastic.
Maybe it's sarcastic.
That's what I'm starting to think.
I'm starting to think maybe they listened to us
be so sarcastic in our episodes of the podcast
that they learned, we sort of taught them a lesson
in using sarcasm as a tool.
But I will say this, sarcasm,
satire requires clarity of purpose.
Yeah.
I'm not sure what the clarity is.
I mean, I sent a message to Mr. Kupchak.
Oh, you did?
You responded?
Yeah, I sent a message.
What'd you say?
I said, "I would love a weekly allowance,"
and he sent me $1,000.
Which I'm assuming it's ironic, so.
He sent you $1,000?
Yeah, it's probably a joke.
'Cause I feel like if he--
And then he also, he posted a picture,
he attached a picture to the email
that was printed out pictures of you and Patrick
hanging on the wall.
Okay, so far I like it.
bullet holes
in the in the four-inch shooting he's
he's shooting this the pictures of us
yeah i mean it's it's a it's a hippies after all i mean it makes sense to be
rude right now
that's you know it's probably also satire
now i think you know i think you really doesn't like you doesn't like us
no or
well he can i think he does any might actually like you now i think about it
i mean i think he was pretty harsh on me is on saying
he just said you were normal
- Yeah, but he could have said I was like the best guy ever
and he didn't.
- He said I was the missing link.
- I mean, look at me, right?
If you look at me and you say I'm normal,
that's an insult.
- He could have called you a monkey.
- No, 'cause I'm not a monkey.
- Sorry, I kind of forget sometimes
other people aren't monkeys.
You know, I forget to check.
- No, I understand.
It's okay.
Yeah, it's my bad.
But yeah, so I'm actually flying him out
to the podcast about this.
You're flying out IMD Poop Sucka?
Yeah, just to hang out.
But he's gonna, he'll like kill me.
I mean, I'm sure it was,
we'll figure it out when he gets here.
You just wanna play it by ear?
Yeah, we'll play it by ear.
That's a perfect phrase, thank you.
That's exactly what I was looking for.
Yeah.
So, I mean, I'm a little worried.
for why? If I'm being honest, because he sent you a picture of me with a gun hole, bullet.
Okay, maybe it wasn't, maybe he was, maybe it was kiss marks and he just has a weird mouth.
He has bullets for lips? He has bullets for lips. Okay, did you think of that? He has a very sharp mouth?
He has a very sharp small mouth. I mean he does say at the end of the piece,
"Sock him one in their fat juicy mouth." Maybe to every, him, everyone
looks like they have juicy mouths because his mouth is... He's gonna sock me! He has a little
bullet beak. He's gonna fight me, dude. I mean you can just fight him back, it's not
a big deal. Oh, I could use Monkey Fu. You could use a banana boomerang. That's true.
I could use the Donkey Kong boxing glove from Super Mario Baseball.
Yeah. Yeah, and I could hit him. You could wind up like Donkey Kong. I could wind him up, I could hold it to a super charge and then hit him with it.
Or I could do a banana blast. I could climb him. You could jet pack like Diddy Kong.
I'm gonna climb up his pant leg and hit his balls like a speed bag.
Yeah.
Hey, don't mess with the monkey.
That's what I'll say.
That's a good catchphrase.
Is it?
Don't mess with the monkey.
That's pretty good.
I've been working on my catchphrase for after fights.
Yeah.
Last time I got in a fight, my catchphrase was, "I'm sorry, I didn't realize that was
a girl."
Yeah.
Nobody liked that catchphrase.
It didn't work.
Yeah.
I think it was just the way you said it.
I'm sure it didn't work.
I did do an Indian accent.
I did an Apu accent.
'Cause I was like, well, I need them on my side.
So, you know, who's the most,
I thought who's the most loved cartoon character
in the world right now?
Apu from the Simpsons.
So I did an Apu voice.
I don't think they liked it very much though.
Yeah.
You should have done the crows from Dumbo.
That would have been a good idea.
That would have gone over well.
Yeah, or the guy from Song of the South again.
I should have done Zippity-Doo-Dah.
Yeah.
My grandma showed me that.
Disney, they've released that movie so many times.
Yeah, every year.
Yeah, until like the '70s,
they basically released Song of the South
every five years with like a theater release
because people loved it so much.
And then in the '70s at some point,
They were like, we're just gonna do that song.
And so they started clipping,
they stopped releasing the full movie,
like the theatrical release.
And they put it, they just put that song on like these tapes
that were like, like the best of Disney, whatever.
And so when I was a kid, I watched that,
I had like one of those tapes and I'd watch it all the time
and I'd watch Zippity-Doodah.
And then when I got older, people told me like,
yeah, that movie is like racist or whatever.
And I didn't realize it was a full movie
about like him being like a slave.
I was like, why, it's just a song where he like sings
to birds, what's racist about that?
He's just sing zippity do da, it's awesome.
(laughing)
- Yeah, what are you guys talking about?
It's wonderful.
- Yeah.
- It's beautiful.
Alright, fine. You're right, that's racist. I'll watch the toy. I'll just watch the toy instead.
We should write a hit piece back. Yeah, we'll do it, baby. Next episode we're gonna have the
hit piece back and then we're gonna have Patrick responding to the rap battle. Patrick couldn't,
not in a million years could he write a bar. Well, actually, next episode is gonna be big.
number 100. Oh yeah this is the last one before the 100. We got something very
secret and special in store for you sick serpents. It's 10 hours long and it's called the
Patrick story played on a skateboard. Yep you have to play it on a skateboard.
Well no it's like he played on a skateboard that's like the subtitle.
Oh it's yeah it's 10 hours of Patrick falling over at the skate park and all
the kids getting around and laughing at him and pointing. Yeah and it's it's
actually 20 hours long it's slowed down. We thought it wasn't long enough so we
slowed it down to half speed. We said 100th episode we got to go all out.
So it actually it is a 15 or 20 hour episode depending on how fast
you listen to it. Yeah. Also depending on what choices you make. Could be a
one-second episode. Because it's also a choose your own adventure. Yeah. There's a choice at the
beginning that says do you want to listen to the episode. And you can say if
If you say no, it's a skip to the end,
and then it's like a five second episode.
- If you say no, it plays a fart sound in your ear
for 10 hours.
- We should do a choose your own adventure episode.
- We should, we should figure out how to do that,
and then do it.
- All right, let's do it.
- Yeah.
- You'd have to do like different time stamps.
- It's like a video game.
- Let's just, oh my God, let's just build a house.
(laughing)
- Let's have a baby.
- Yeah, let's all have a baby together.
Yeah, we'll all take turns getting your mom pregnant and we won't know whose kid it is.
But then when it pops out, we'll all share him.
Yeah.
And it will be a him.
Yep.
And we'll raise him to be the human podcast.
Yeah, because if it's not, my apartment is technically a, and it's been annexed by China
and so we follow the one, the two child policy in my apartment.
So if it is a girl, it's going in the trash can.
Yep.
Yeah.
I'm just putting it in the cabinet under the sink and ignoring it.
Yeah
Until it grows to be a beast from a Goosebumps book. A hairy stinky beast.
That's not how Patrick was born. It's not neglect if you turn your baby into an awesome beast. Yeah, Patrick was born
directly into a fridge.
He was birthed, they did a home birth and they didn't have a tub so she sat in the fridge and then they just forgot him there.
Yeah
They do you're listening of mayonnaise
All right. Well, I have to shit really badly. Yeah
Another successful one without Patrick. Why don't I even have him on it makes no sense. Yeah
Whatever. Fuck him. Bye. I'll see you after the hundredth episode. Yes. See you on the other freakin side
Yeah, cuz it's gonna chip. He's gonna blow your mind change your world and a new era will begin one million days a nightfall
Demons will walk the earth.
Yeah, and Patrick will, uh...
Not walk the earth anymore.
Yeah, Patrick will be in one of those fat guy scooters at Walmart.
May God have mercy on his soul.
That's right. Bye.
Bye.