Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
Did you guys know that T-Pain can actually sing?
T-Pain can actually sing with auto-tune.
He can't, no, it's all just auto-tune.
What do you mean?
Bro, you...
That is honestly so ignorant.
I have a tiny disc concert for you.
That is fucking so ignorant to say.
T-Pain actually has...
No, what do you mean?
He just uses auto-tune to sing.
he has he has a pipes for days. He's more of a robot than man. He's not a robot. He's a grown man.
He's a grown ass man. Why was he wearing those top heads? Because he was into the circus. What a lot
of people don't realize about T-Pain is when he when he did Buy You a Drink he was like 19. He
was still figuring shit out. Really? Yeah he was like really young. So he's like so when he did.
So he's 24 now? Yeah he's 24 years old. Wow. So when he did his circus thing it's like dude he's
only fucking 10 years old. Let the guy yeah just let him do his thing dude. He's trying to be cool.
- And then he did the cowboy thing.
- Yep.
- So he did a cowboy thing, like rappers who do a cowboy thing.
Will.i.am and X-Men Origins, you ever seen that?
- I never seen that.
- Oh man, there's a really good scene where,
'cause he played Wraith and his power was like teleportation
so it's just like, Will.i.am will just pop up places
in a cowboy hat.
- That's dope.
- Yeah, dude.
- That is dope.
- That sounds cool.
- Yeah.
- I have some information I learned about myself.
Damn, I love info. Hit me.
Cameron found out his bum is small.
So I always knew, so the name Cameron, it means crooked nose.
Yep.
Okay, it's Scottish, it means crooked nose. I always knew that, that's whatever.
But I realized, I was like thinking about it, I was like, I guess I don't really know where the name Fetter comes from or like what it means.
Wasn't it, you told me it was an Ellis Island name.
That's what my family always said, but I was like, I've never looked that up. I don't know if that's true or not.
It means Ellis Island.
and I can tell you now what fetter means what does it mean what fetter means is
it cheese yeah okay keep going no let's let's keep going let him tell his story
Patrick no good no go do another one do another funny one okay here's a funny
one yeah means my best friend so what fetter actually means I looked it up it
means fat man my full name is crooked-nosed fat man damn that's what my
mean that's mean isn't that crazy yeah, because you're huge yeah, I'm giant and
fat yeah, that's the thing is it's so there are two possible meanings it's
that's the thing it's either fat man was the top one and I was like oh there's
another meaning okay. I can like this is this will save me know what the second
meaning is casual male XL a cheat or a scoundrel.
How fucked up is that if it is an Ellis Island name that means that they had
completely different name and the guy was like you are fat you're a fat scoundrel
you're fat as shit you're a fat scoundrel and everyone needs to know and you're
like so fucked up you're the you're like that that fat guy from Final Fantasy 9
that's you which guy's that I never played the pirate ship the chef he just
said he's never played it and you're just saying more details and then and
then there's Vivi wait you might we might get it if you say a couple more things
VV the little mage. Oh no. Mage that's starting to ring a bell. Yeah. Black. Black. Okay. VV
has a black face with yellow eyes. Like a Jawa. Yes. Yeah I know what the mages look
like. Okay then we're getting a star closer. We're there we got it. I think we got it. Okay
so imagine a fat chef. A fat person, a fat chef who's a friend of one of the mages. Yeah.
Okay, I don't think they ever interact. Oh, okay. Where's Patrick going?
You had a red hit a pocket Red Bull. Yeah. Whoa, you're gonna pockets if I shown you these
Just that you have big
Okay, I get my phone out of here so you show you this might be the worst episode ever this is not ready
You can fit a red bull in your big pocket. You can fit the smallest red bull can into your pocket, but not with a phone
It's too small you can fit a Nalgene in there. Okay. Hey, you got big pocket my Nalgene out your pocket
It's a that crazy. So get it out, dude. That's nasty
You sweat in those pants all day get that tastes like change my god
I guess gonna taste like look how much sweat filled this up. Oh my god, it's complete full of sweat
It says it has 1000 milliliters of sweat in here.
It has nutrients.
Look, you can see the dots of salt in the sweat.
My sweat, dude, I've been...
I bet your sweat doesn't have salt.
When Kai was here, Kai got me into the electrolyte powders.
This whole weekend, every time I had water, I'd put those in.
I've been so hydrated.
I don't think the electrolytes hydrate you anymore.
I think water hydrates you.
The electrolytes, it's basically just salt, right?
Yeah, I think it's just a different type of thing.
Yeah.
different type of nutrient.
It's called triple hydration.
Can we make you a health freak?
That'd be kind of funny.
If you got into eating a raw egg every morning and you're juicing, I need to see you into
ketosis.
That'd be so funny.
Can I be your ketosis Sherpa and guide you up the mountain?
I have one.
I just don't talk to him anymore.
You have me.
I will be your ketosis Sherpa.
You met Ron, right?
Ron, your ketosis man?
Ron my personal trainer.
No I never met Ron.
Ron Weasley?
I just stopped talking to him.
Why?
Something happened.
What happened?
It's ok.
I found him on Craigslist.
Yep.
Thought he was a personal trainer.
Ok.
Turns out he's a feeder.
This is the opposite.
Yeah.
I should have seen it coming because he's like oh you need 50,000 calories in the morning.
That is a serious red flag.
Yeah that's dangerous.
- I thought I was doing gains.
I thought that's what gains meant.
- You're not gaining anything.
- 'Cause I kept asking him about gains.
I think that was my problem.
I was like, "Oh yeah, so I'm gonna get massive gains."
He's like, "Oh, you're gonna get gains alright."
I was like, "He kinda said that weird."
- So what was that?
- That's one of the number one red flags,
when you say someone and someone goes,
"Oh yeah, we're gonna do that alright."
When they say alright after it, you should--
- That's a bit suspicious, you guys.
- Also, you might be Jafar.
- Also, you have a Jafar type quality to me.
- A 5'7", 200 pound personal trainer, that's crazy.
- Yeah, yeah, it's a bad idea to have a mirror
be your damn personal trainer.
- When your personal trainer is fatter than you, huh?
- Nothing.
- I'm not 5'7".
- You're right, you're 5'4".
- When your personal trainer is fatter than you,
that's never a good sign.
- I think that's a pretty common thing.
You ever go to like Gold's Gym
like Planet Fitness or something they have their personal trainers who are like
giant whales? No. They are fat as hell. How do the whales fit in the building? It's
probably smaller than a whale. Okay I made it all up. I was lying for attention.
Is that what you want to hear? Yeah. I do that a lot. I'm glad you admitted it.
Yep. But I actually did go skydiving over the weekend. Oh really? Seriously? No I made
that up. I was lying for attention. I went to New Hampshire. Really? Yeah I went to New
New Hampshire this weekend to say no, I think you're lying for attention right
now. It's definitely lying. You would never go to New Hampshire. It's an
obvious lie. I'm lying. How was it? It was all right. I ate two sandwiches for
lunch yesterday. Double sandwich. Sorry, Patrick. Hold the New Hampshire talk. Two
sandwiches for lunch? Yeah, what do you guys want to ask me a bunch of
questions and make me the center of the conversation? Yes, yes, I do. Yeah, what
was on the two sandwiches? Were they different or the same? Everything.
- Everything?
- Two everything sandwiches.
- Everything at the deli or everything?
- Everywhere.
- Everything, everywhere?
- Everything everywhere at once.
- All at once?
- Two sandwiches?
- Not like the movie.
Two sandwiches, three sandwiches.
- Wait, you had a third sandwich?
- It was a third sandwich.
- You just remembered it was actually three?
- I just remembered, yeah, it was four.
- Wow, that's so many sandwiches.
- But the fourth one wasn't an everything sandwich.
That was PB&J.
- Oh, just PB&J, 'cause you were so full.
- That's like realistic.
Or like it's true, I mean.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Not realistic.
When I go to New Hampshire, my mom and dad--
Wait, hold on.
Was there everything meat, cheese, everything in the meat and cheese category?
Everything in the meat and cheese category?
Every ingredient.
Have you ever had an everything sandwich?
Yeah, what?
I guess, I must be doing New York wrong.
Yeah, you go to, you say, "Ah, let me get an everything sandwich."
And he says, "Sure, sure."
And then he just grabs one of each of everything and then puts it onto a sandwich.
One jalapeno.
Yeah.
yeah yeah one piece of dust floating in the air it's this big yeah they call
them dagwoods but here it's called an everything serious Dagwood though yeah
yeah okay I don't know six really and a PJ well it's technically I mean one
Dagwood is like you know you have to put like well here's the thing about the
everything sandwiches you also you have to put the other everything sandwiches on
it yeah does that counts as part of everything if there's one already in the
room. It's the hardest sandwich to make at the bodega, so you got to go you got to
get it at like yeah ten in the morning and they and the and oc gave it to me
for free because I was a movie star. Yeah,
you got to go. You got to get the everything sandwich at ten in the
morning because it's going to take him till eleven to make it yeah definitely
like you know, just before the lunch rush. Okay, all right, I have to keep
that in mind. Thanks for the info. I had eight okay, so you and then you had
I ate it.
Patrick went home.
Yeah, I ate it.
You ate eight of them?
I ate nine of them.
Oh my God, that's way too many.
You must have been full for minutes.
Holy shit.
I wasn't full.
What?
You could have kept going?
You're kidding.
I wasn't full at all.
After 11 of them, I ate nine more after 11.
You ate nine?
You ate 20 of these fucking things?
28, yeah.
28 of them you ate?
I ate 28.
Holy shit.
He ate 28.
20 of them I ate and eight I ate.
Yeah, so he ate...
So it's 28.
It's 30 almost.
No, it was 40.
It was 40.
almost no. I was forty five forty five fucking Sam everything sandwiches. I
didn't I didn't need some of the forty five some of them. My friend ate who's
your friend Tom Cruise Tom Cruise your friend yeah is this for real no yes. I
mean yes. Holy shit it is yeah wow yeah. Do you believe it yeah of course it's
real you're you're I mean unlike Patrick you're not a compulsive liar. No I you
know he's talking about oh I went to New Hampshire. Yes sure we had them in the
dragon castle. You went to a dragon castle? Pat stop lying okay nobody fucking
like nobody listening this likes it when you just lie. I saw my sister too and I
went to Dave and Buster's. Yeah I saw your sister too. I went to Dave and Buster's with my brothers. Is that what you
want you want me to lie as well? He's talking about going to the dragon castle
with Tom Cruise he ate 45 sandwiches. Do you know who my brothers are?
my brothers are who Dracula and Frankenstein that's not that I believe
that I might believe actually that I could that's possible to believe that
you know how we got to the Dracula I mean the dragon castle no how to do to do
bang-bang really yeah car still around we know after all these years yeah holy
shit off him yeah and Herbie Herbie yeah whoa I took to you should you bang bang
and Tom Cruise took Herbie. Hey, Herbie, the original damn self-driving car. Actually,
no, Chitty Chitty Bang Bang, the original damn self-driving car. Yeah, Herbie, the second
original. Yeah, Knight Rider, the original... No, Chitty Chitty Bang Bang. The third self-driving
car. Yeah. And Optimus Prime was not there. I believe that. Yeah, he was busy. It's almost
like you're telling me he was there. Hmm? No, he totally wasn't there. He was working
on something. Yeah, he couldn't be there. He couldn't be there and party at the Dragon
castle for all night, but he drink oil instead of beer. Yeah, he definitely
didn't do that. Okay, you're covering for him. Yeah, and he didn't transform into
the car from Harry Potter, the flying car from Harry Potter. I said way too
much. I said way to the bus with the Jamaican head. The Jamaican head was
there, but not the bus. Did I didn't do shit this weekend compared to you?
Yeah, I mean that mean you said it. I didn't really do that much either lies
did tell us he sat in his room all weekend. Patrick was there
Pat, were you he was lying because he didn't want to admit he was there.
Pabria that's why you see now. I don't know who to trust because you tell the
truth every single time and he's never said a single true thing. He was there.
He was in one of the sandwiches. I really
and I missed out on all this. You were there because you was I yeah you were
you were asleep. We stole you from your bed.
Bro, I slept through the whole thing?
We wrapped you up. We carried you in a bindle.
Yeah.
Did I even get one of the sandwiches?
You were in one of the sandwiches.
You were in one of the sandwiches and you got to eat one crumb.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh.
A mouse from Sleeping Beauty or whatever the one with the mouses is gave you a crumb.
A mouse from Mouse Hunt?
Mouse Hunt, yeah.
Gave me a crumb?
Remember, you ate it in your sleep.
And I didn't even get to dig your picture?
I ate it an entire week?
Eight crumbs.
of them? Yeah, well, statistically you're gonna eat eight crumbs over the course of a year.
Over the course of one sandwich? Yeah, you're gonna eat eight crumbs over the course of
one sandwich like while you sleep. Two days ago, Phil, I'm walking him down the street.
He's lying again. No, this is true. He's been lying about this dog for months. Yeah, we
should get a polygraph hooked up here. You've met the dog. You've met him. You just showed
me photos you took of him on your phone. They were photoshopped. Not ten minutes ago. Why
why would he photoshop you can tell they're face tuned yeah yeah, he face
tuned into a dog that's that would take so long. I'll take way too long. It's my
little cousin. I face to them into a dog. He has first, so it's not that hard to
face. Phil, I wasn't paying attention. I was really sleepy walking him in the
morning and he I like just turned to him and he was eating something on the
ground and he's eating a giant pile of white powder. It was just sitting on the
ground and I was like hey, don't do that and then he just started coughing a
and now I just said I just some kind of wait for him to die yeah yeah probably
poison right probably poison where was it in front of the poison store yeah well
no I wouldn't if it's in front of the poison store wouldn't be poisoning as
people don't won't just wouldn't buy poison and leave a throw at the poison
yeah yeah it was probably poison they threw out cuz it wasn't working oh
that's a really good point it's probably a defective poison yeah so it's probably
safer dogs yeah definitely I do when I was in New Hampshire this way I got there
and immediately, every time I go there, my mom and dad just buy me drinks. And then I ended
up blacking out. And I woke up and I saw $50 spent on touch tunes.
You have like a Mr. Hyde that comes out and loves touch tunes.
Dude, we went to this bar that had touch tunes.
You turn into a jukebox monster.
I played Careless Whisper 10 times.
That is some John Mulaney-ass shit, my friend.
That wasn't even John Mulaney shit. I just really love that song.
That's a great song. And then, oh wait, and I did play "Let It Rock" like five times.
That is--
Okay.
I changed my mind.
Yeah.
And you're officially dope.
Let me look at my TouchTunes history.
Yeah, let's go through it here.
Okay.
Let's see this crap.
I can't believe you have a TouchTunes app.
I know.
You can't send music to a bar you're not in, right?
You can.
That is so funny.
Yeah.
Yeah, if you're within range of the thing, that's not good for me to know.
Have you guys ever used the touch tunes at Waffle House?
Oh, I guess you can't see unless I couldn't see it unless I was in New Hampshire.
Oh, yeah. So I was right.
Damn.
Yeah. Waffle House has touch tunes, but it has I've never, I don't know why I've never
paid to play to listen to these, but it has an entire album that's just called Waffle House.
Yeah.
and it's got just like all these songs. It has like 25 songs and I one of them has always stuck
with me. There's a there's a are these the charges from touchstones? Holy shit dude that's insane.
That's crazy. I think I think I was like swiping it and I was like it's not fucking loading.
All of a sudden you have 500 credits on touchstone. I was like oh no I have to use all of these tonight.
the time between the charges. Yeah, how much time passed between each of these
can't see the time that passed between them, but I think it was back to back to
back. Oh man. Yeah, instantly. I wish I wish that you would like it thought it
was back to back to back and looked and it was like like 20 minutes of so funny.
That's so cool because I think they reach the I mean the touch tunes turns
off when the bar closes. So you probably had 40 to 50 songs that just were
deleted. Yeah, yeah. Because it was that was around one in the one in the morning.
Yeah, and you can't fill an hour's I mean come on. Yeah we got I guess...
If you buy premium songs maybe. The last thing I remember... You could pay probably ten
ten dollars worth of credits to play the audio from the new Batman movie.
The last thing I remember was a screaming careless whisper and then...
A bit ironic if you ask me.
I woke up in my little brother's bed and then I was like, "Ah, fuck."
Because I just realized, like, "Oh yeah, I blacked out."
And then I asked my sister what happened. She was like,
"Oh yeah, you said you needed to go home because you got a new hat."
and then we left the bar I need to wear my hat imagine that also you blacked out
and woke up in your little brother's bed is a pretty bad sentence yeah I blacked
out and I woke up he doesn't live there anymore
Yeah, not after what you did, not a black, but
I guess when I was like like my my sister's ex had the kids and then I
guess when I got home after they like I they found me walking out of an alleyway
and I like found them. I was like, Oh, hey, what's up there? What were you
doing? I don't know. And then we just walked home and then I tried to I tried
to sleep in my nephew's like Spider Man bed. He isn't there.
here, because I know you're going to make that joke.
I'm not going to make any joke about a drunk uncle climbing into his nephew's Spider-Man
bed.
It's not going to happen.
But it's literally like a child-sized bed, and I guess I was in it with my phone charged,
and I'm asleep, and my mom's like, "Dad, what the fuck are you doing?"
I was like, "I don't know."
couldn't my dad was already passed out so she was trying to lift me up to get me
into the bed downstairs and then I woke up and just went like as soon as I like
black like a woke up from blacking out I went back up there put my phone in the
charger and then fell asleep sounds like you had a drinking attack yeah I did
yeah yeah that's what happens do you just you drink that much with your
parents Irish yeah come on you've met his parents yeah I just crazy to me dude I
could never it's a different world they're aliens basically I need to kill
every Irish person I thought I think we were Irish travelers there's no way I
know but the Tom was telling me about them the Irish you guys were in South
Carolina the ones who wear the wear hype be stuff yeah they were like Versace
you shit I don't know who you're talking about oh dude there's six yeah dude
there's this town in South Carolina called Murphy village where it's just
all Irish travelers and Tom described it to me as like you mean just people
visiting from Ireland no no the Irish Romanis yeah yeah and travelers yeah
that's the word to say yeah one and right yeah they're all inbred mm-hmm I
I mean I'm most Irish people in the same $30 from each other for years. You can say that but you can't say gypsy.
Most Irish people are like time travelers the way that their brains are stuck in
the Middle Ages. That's right. Traveler is a funny thing. Does that mean that if
somebody rips you off can you say like "Oh you really traved me."
Yeah it's funny yeah it's it's not okay to say the word but you can say a
a thousand mean things about them. Yeah, yeah. Yeah, I guess Tom was also telling
me that they have like a golf tournament every year and every year it gets live
tweeted because somebody runs away with all the money. Like somebody steals all
the money from this golf tournament that they have. Where are they keeping the money?
I don't know. This, what? They're keeping the money in a lockbox. Is it like a
a cartoon the money's sitting on I think this is a cartoon town where everybody
dresses like a fortnight character yeah probably is a cartoon you know they put
mustard on their barbecue that night actually shut up I had it's pretty good
it's not good South Carolina is a fucking goof off of a damn state yeah
yeah what about terrible North Carolina raise your shirt up yes sir
Raise your shirt up?
Pidi Pablo, yes sir!
Oh.
Yes sir, raise your shirt up.
Mm-hmm. Keep pounding.
What about Alligator Adventure?
Alligator Adventure.
Awesome.
They meant to put that in North Carolina.
Yeah?
But they missed.
What about the Panthers?
The Panthers are a North Carolina team.
They're called the Carolina Panthers, but they play in Charlotte.
So.
He doesn't even know.
I bet a lot of those Panthers haven't even gone down to South Carolina and pounded down there.
They keep pounding up in North Carolina, pounding it out.
Poundin' Panthers. Poundin' damn Panthers pounding out in the playoffs. Yeah. I actually don't know if they're...
Mustard barbecue sauce is good. I bought some Sweet Baby Ray's that had mustard in it.
No, that's not what South Carolina must... or barbecue... South Carolina barbecues, they do
pulled pork like North Carolina, but then they... and they make the like vinegar sauce. Yeah. Then
they add mustard to it, man. That's good, dude. Mustard... Shut the fucking... shut up. Mustard's so good.
Shut the fucking up right now, you bitch.
It's gross.
Mustard?
You get older, you start appreciating mustard more.
I'm older than you and mustard can suck my dick.
Whoa!
Yeah, you're an idiot. Crazy.
You're stupid for that.
You guys have to stop.
Yeah, you have to stop. What?
Yeah, bitch. Yeah, bitch. Yeah, fuck you.
I bet you put ketchup on your food.
I don't put ketchup on my food.
I knew this. No.
We're not gonna do this. We're seriously not gonna do this.
I'm fat and giggly.
He said it.
I said I'm fat and giggly.
You are fat and giggly.
I'm not fat anymore!
But you giggly though.
Admit you're giggly.
I've been watching a lot of Fear Factor.
I'm really obsessed with it now.
I saw my fear happen before my eyes.
Saw this really good episode.
You know how they'll do ones where it's like
that they have like couples fear factor and like newlyweds fear factor stuff
like that. They had one that was twins
fear. Oh for real yeah, and they were doing this challenge here. They were
doing this challenge where they had to like dive into water and like from like
a hell that's whatever okay and like and like collect all this stuff and there
are these two twin there. So there are these there there are a bunch of there
a bunch of sets of twins. If you can believe it, there are these two twins
that I like were like cowboys and there were these two twins that like Mohawks
were like like punk rockers and they send the punks. They like did the
challenge. They like dived into the water and like came back and like one
of them was like clearly just like so out of it like you just like got a
concussion or something from it and he was like it's like oh and they're like
and Joe run. It's like oh like how'd you do how was it man and he's like man like
when you hit that that cold water like you don't know where you are it just
changes something about you just start thinking weird things and it's like what
what do you, what are you talking about? Like what weird things do you think?
I was like start thinking like man, those cowboys are pretty hot and then the
twin is like you hit the water and started thinking the cowboys are hot and
then John Rogan's just like okay guys, you have to leave like I'm not going to
talk about this anymore.
It was so crazy. He hit the water, became bisexual. He instantly turned gay.
one twin turned gay when he hit cold water. It shocked him enough that he
and the other the other one was like what are you talking about? It was so
funny because all the other trends are doing the show where they talk in
unison and stuff on purpose. Yeah, they all dressed exactly the same. I should
have had they should have the sclar brothers host that episode. They would
have been on fucking fire. Yeah, yeah, I wish Joe Rogan had a twin. Oh my God.
Oh, that'd be so cool. Jim Rogan yeah, Jim Rogan or Bo Rogan. Just a second
Joe Rogan man. Yeah. Dodo Dogan. I wonder if he has brothers and sisters. Joe Rogan? Let's
find out. He does have a mom and dad. I mean, no way. I always assumed he did. No chance.
But maybe not. No chance he has a mom and dad. Yeah, his mom is, his mom's comedy and
his dad's pot. Yeah. Yeah, but he's basically the combination of the two. He's a hybrid.
Yeah. Yeah, he's an Indica and a Sativa. Yep. Remember when we were filming, speaking of
we were filming that home planet video, speaking of that and fear, funniest thing I've ever
heard was when Neil accidentally like lit it. He accidentally lit the joint and he
said my property just screamed my fear yeah my that's a good reaction I think
yeah something that is scaring you is actively happening in front of you to go
my fear my fear cuz it's true I mean it's like that's such an honest reaction
my fear my fear my fear I mean that's a great reaction my fear that was my
- That honestly, that's how I'm reacting to everything scary.
- Yeah, the rest of my life.
- Like in a movie theater.
- Yeah.
- Damn, Freddy Jason comes up.
- My fear, my fear.
- Freddy Jason pops up on the screen,
I'm screaming my fear.
- Can we please turn this into a Halloween horror house?
- Yeah, I would love to.
- I just wanna do one week where just fans of the show
can come by, pay $5, and they get real scared and leave.
- Yeah.
- You know?
great I would love to do that and they're not allowed to take photos or remember
the address and I like to remember it either yeah once they leave we give them
a forget-me-not on tour do you guys want to do that or forget me yes he doesn't
do the million-dollar haunted house in Texas where they poke your eyeballs and
put put calm in your mouth no no they're screaming my fear yeah my fear my fear
I would just say my fears.
That is so crazy that you can just pay
No, you don't pay. It's free.
You pay one million dollars
You get a million bucks.
You get a million bucks
If you make it 24 hours, I think.
Which is also like, I would want to sleep probably.
24 hours and it's just like guys being like,
I'm going to touch your penis while you sleep.
No, they like start poking.
Well, you sign, nobody's ever done it I guess.
I guess or people have done it, but yeah, it's last like an hour. Yeah, because
they like waver is just like is like we can put needles under your skin. We can
we can kill you. You can touch your private parts. It's just a waiver. Yeah,
which like yeah, it is there is a thing in there like we can kill you. I think
yeah, yeah, which I just don't think that waiver holds up in court. No,
definitely not. No chance, but I do want to test it by dying there. Yeah, I would
love to shut down that haunted house. Me too. I go in there with a gun. Yeah,
there's nothing in the way I would add I would add a line to the waiver and and
that says you are allowed to shoot us and then I was signing I'd hope they didn't
notice my line I added I go and shoot them yeah it's in the way for they
there's no there's no way they had in the waiver like you can't defend yourself
you can't stand your ground in our haunted house that's yeah you're allowed
to stand your ground anywhere yeah I'm concerned Texas is a stand your ground
ground. That's true. Here's what you have to do. You have to trick them and you have
to do an Ocean's Eleven type thing where you construct a copy of their haunted
house but you put it inside your house and you trick them into going to that one
and then you can kill them in self-defense. That is so smart actually. Yeah. Yeah you weren't in
your haunted house you were in my kitchen. Yeah so I can kill you and I get a million dollars.
Yeah that is actually fucking genius. Yeah. Yeah it's called haunted house doctrine.
Mm-hmm. It's true. Yeah. Mansion doctor. I think it's Ocean's Eleven doctor more than anything else.
Yeah it is. Yeah. I really really want to do a heist and fucking have a hot wife.
Ocean's Eleven is so awesome. You know what's really cool? What? Ocean's... Ocean's Twelve.
Just the Ocean's. Ocean's Twelve is really cool. Yeah. You know what's better than the
Ocean's Twelve? What? Ocean's Eight. I don't see that one. Just less people though.
but they have 16 boobs. Oh so it's way more boobs. Yeah it's infinitely more
boobs. I guess that's true. Yeah. Would that be 16 boobs? Yeah.
Eight times? No. Are you trying to do eight times two? Yeah that's 16 Pat.
Yeah. That would only be two people. What? That would only be two of them. You think two
people have 16 boobs between them. So two people with 16 boobs. No that would no. Hold on.
I know where this is. There's no like fraction involved in this right? No you
had it you had it the first time. What fraction would there be? Well two to one.
It's two for every one person, but there's eight eight women
So it's two two for two boobs for every one woman and there's only and there's one there's when there's eight of them
So it's 16
That doesn't sound right
There I feel like there's one set of boobs we're missing it's yours. Yep
Bitch ass well, it's mine when I'm watching it. You don't have you don't grow boobs when you watch the show
He does I saw him do it really well that would be oceans nine, then it would be 18 boobs
They should make oh then oceans one where you're than the less you're the last person
I mean we're in there like and who's our last member yeah, and they all look at the camera
They should that should be it that should be like a like a ride at like an amusement park yeah
talk about the ride what we how we're done talking about the etra. I love the
that was last week. It's always but it's like oh, we talk about the yes, no
shit and yeah and you're the and and it's like you're the like okay, well
he's the contortionist. He's the hacker or whatever he's the face and then it's
like oh and then this guy he's the guy who rides a roller coaster.
that's a great idea for right yeah and then you're part of it yeah right
right there. I don't make sure you straight the guards scream when you're
upside down yeah that'll distract the guards will be here's the high take a
photo take a photo at the loop-de-loop we're building a roller coaster in front
of the bank to distract everybody inside and then we'll go into them but we built
a roller coaster in the bank yeah in the middle of the vault and it spins around
and we put the guards in the middle and oceans 11 roller coaster will be so sick
great idea go through the vault and stuff they should make two more roller
coasters that are not for like fucking stupid movies like Harry Potter yeah
like they should make them for cool there should be an Inception roller
coaster yeah oh yeah there should be a cerebral roller coaster yeah there should
be a adaptation roller coaster yeah you know that's a Nectar King the York
roller coaster that would be pretty sick yeah into the different world you know
The problem with that, that line would be way too long.
That is true.
Yeah.
That line, you gotta like, you know, and the car itself, it's like, how are we going to
fit 200 people on a fucking car?
Yeah.
Oh my god, a racing Arizona coaster?
Elmo and Grouchland coaster.
Yeah.
Damn, there's some, we need to open an amusement park.
Damn.
We can.
There's a, there's like a simulator thing that you can download.
those a real one no you asshole you ask that we want to we want to use millions
of dove your money to open up a real you don't you don't clown don't clown yeah
you poop pop your poop you poop Prince you're a poop don't call him a pen I'm
not because your print what was he talking to oh you're talking to the good
person over there must be talking to this wall you're not on my friend Cameron
talk to the wall cuz the hand ain't listening there's so many bugs in here
yeah it's this I don't even see any bugs I just got a bug in my one of them cuz
I'm too sweet I think you have diabetes no I think that's what that means I'm so
scared of getting type 2 diabetes really I'm gonna get type 1000 why are you
scared of that cuz you know it's something I never think about and then
like then you're but you're scared of it but you'd never think about it I never
think about it but then I'll eat something and then I'm like no way I'm
not there might have been diabetes on this yeah there could have been with
diabetes might have this I'm gonna have to start taking injections yeah it's so
easy to not get diabetes okay it is all right just different food oh I'm so good
at not getting diabetes you stop eating sugar surprises that's the only thing
- The thing about diabetes is people think it's the sugar
that does it, but it's actually the surprises.
- Yeah, you need to stop.
- Your body's not expecting it.
- It surprises your insulin.
- The biggest surprise is the diabetes itself.
- Yeah.
- I feel any time someone gets type 2 diabetes,
I'm like, yeah, it's not that hard
to not get type 2 diabetes.
- Well, that's the one you can get rid of, right?
- I don't know.
- No, I don't think so.
- Which is the one that you can--
- You can prevent it.
- But you can't cure diabetes, I thought.
I think you just like have to stop eating like Jolly Ranchers and stuff if you're
on the way. Yeah that's not gonna happen. I'd rather lose both. That's the thing, anytime somebody,
it's like people, you go to the doctor, the doctor will be like you're teetering
on diabetes, you have to stop eating a Hershey's Kiss every morning and they go
I would rather. You think I'll do one Hershey's Kiss every morning? Yep. I would rather kill myself. I would
rather lose both of my feet than stop eating a Hershey's Kiss. Yeah. I hate
Hershey's Kisses what I want every morning just say you don't like chocolate and go
what just say you don't like chocolate and go ahead and leave mm-hmm if that's
what you're gonna say you know just a little maybe the fruity candy factory I
did you seriously obviously not a chocolate fan I prefer sour to chocolate
what kind of fucking I prefer me to a chocolate bar oh my god I want to put a
hard hardy bow into your face I want to shoot you with a bow but zero no
Hardy bow one that might make you fall in love with chocolate the superior candy
no well okay depends on the type of like dark chocolate yeah gummies and sour
candy are good but that but it's a that is a child's candy yeah that's for babies
meanwhile a giant chocolate rabbit or Santa Claus that's a distinguished
pleasure a crunchy one a trolley crunchy worm those things are fucked up those
things are fucked up stop making new candies man no we had them we had them
on the plane to Tampa yeah they were really create they're crazy they're
creepy they look like they have a picture
shell yeah it's odd it's a texture that you shouldn't have in your mouth basically
everything is i think it's it's just a nerd's rope i mean no it's like eating a
bug that's why i like them yeah it's just a nerd's rope just something hard out on top of a gummy and
it's sour yeah it tastes the same it's what it's a bug it's eating a bug well it looks like a shell
well no it's a hard shell that is a squishy it's not a real worm yeah but there's a bug inside so
it's like there's no no no you're thinking of a sour scorpion no dude hold on speaking of trolley
- The trolley company, they gotta stop
with these gummy shapes.
They are going too far.
Sour octopus, sour sloths, sour James Hardens.
- Damn, pea trings. - Pea trings.
Sour, what else? - Yeah, show what
the pea trings.
- Oh, they got the juicy worms.
- Bears. - Those are good, though.
- Tiny bears that are small.
- Wait, hold on.
The bears are smaller than the worms?
- What kind of fucking reality
do these animals exist in? - I'm gonna be making
a call to God and having him sort this one out.
- Hey God, they fucked up your entire creation, man.
(laughter)
- They got the order wrong.
- They reversed your creation's beard.
- They made James Harden's beard a gummy.
- They made the small things big
and the big things little.
- They're reversing your beautiful work, oh Lord.
- Yep.
- So basically your creation,
hey remember your creation you made in seven days?
Yeah, they're fucking it up in one.
- Yeah.
- Have you heard of the bursting worms though?
- My worm bursts into your mouth.
- The juicy worms?
- I have a juicy worm that's gonna be really good.
- It's like a, it's like a,
it's like a gusher, but it's a gummy worm.
Imagine explaining a gusher to God. Yeah. Yeah. There's no possible way you're
gonna do it. You're not getting... God created them. You are not passing through the threshold of heaven.
Hey God, remember those weapons that humans created to spread war and strife? Bombs? Yeah,
they made a candy version that goes in your mouth and they love it. Yep. Yeah, remember
when you sent the devil those airheads? Mm-hmm. They made a food worshipping them.
He doesn't send the devil airheads. No, no, the devil turns people's heads into balloons.
that happens yeah is this a nice one no that's just something one of the
torture method the book of Stephen really book of Stephen's 33 33 33 33 and
a third book of Stephen did he Stephen was the 14th Apostle and one of the
commandments is respect the pouch yeah yeah yeah it's the the 14th Apostle and
all of his like stuff was just like respect the power yeah well yeah so the
11th commandment was respect the pouch and the 12th man was respect it mm-hmm
And then the fucking Pop-Tarts are crazy good.
Mm-hmm. Yep. Do you remember that one part in the Bible
where all the little people are running around and that
monster that's just like a mouth upside down, it starts eating all of them?
Yeah, the honeycombians? Yeah, he says you gotta have his pops.
Oh, the pops. Yeah. Yeah, read your books, dude.
wait no the honeycomb Ian's had that little that thing honestly is satanic
yeah it's not good yeah yeah that's why it's in the book of Stephen these are
all the things Jesus had to fight before before he did first prestige and went on
the cross yeah that was he did prestige in that way yeah but then he didn't ever
like deleted his account after he respawned yeah like can't leave stuff
going on yeah when that was just doing side quests he needs to come back very
soon yeah I want to play with him again yeah he needs to come back kick Brandon
at office yeah how about that yeah you know you know who swore on the book of
Stephen Brandon really yeah he put his hand on the on the book of Stephen and
said I'm gonna be president right on the book yeah that's a another as another
verse from the book of Stephen mm-hmm it's like I mean that's why that's why I
mean you know speaking in Christian Christian Christian mothers are actually
they're right about Harry Potter being satanic and kind of subverting God's
work because you know they have they have these these candies they're
corrupting God's candies they're odd candy frog that's alive yeah I don't
think so that's not right every flavored beans no beans have one flavor they were
you're made out of butter. That's not right. That's not right. Satan if you
guys got sworn in appearance, what would you guys swear in on if you were
because of the flying spaghetti the Bible Bible book of flying spaghetti
monster? I would probably do a DVD. Yeah, yeah. Oh, we can always do a DVD of
the Bible. We do something that's not it. Can we do something that's not a
book? Yeah, okay, then like a swearing on a trillion dollars.
oh that's pretty smart actually a trillion dollar coin and then you
remember maybe like an ocean's eleven here's the heist okay you get yourself a
job as the president right and you say I'm my religion is I'm gonna swear on a
one trillion dollar coin you make a fake version of the coin uh-huh right and you
have it you switch it out yeah well you have to train as a magician for a couple
years that's fine but that's but hey that only makes you more like they make
most presidents do that yeah yeah and then you know would be good that would be
be a good national treasure sequel is if they had to steal the Bible as it's
being sworn on. Oh, that'd be that'd be pretty cool. Is the Bible that's
hollowed out? You know what's inside of it? We'd we yeah, but yeah, you drop
your coin. You take yours, you take the other one and then the big the the
coin they get they get back and the best part of the oceans movies when the
guy realized he got ripped off yeah, definitely the guy puts the coin back
in the treasure. He tries to put it into a vending machine and it's a yeah.
this is not a real coin. Yeah, it says 25 cents. Yeah, well it has like you know it
has it's like one of those made up one trillion dollar things where it has like
a picture of Jesus on it or something. Yeah. And you fucking goddamn, the
president got me again. And then he's immediately smited by God because it has
a picture of Jesus on the coin. Well then hey he tries to come after you, right? Who
are the people of the United States gonna believe? Some fucking coin monkey or the
the president. I mean I would say they believe the president, but after
Brandon's legion has been wreaking havoc and it's a good point. That's a good
point. Holy land, it's kind of tough to say. Yeah, I mean it might get caught up
in the courts. Yeah, definitely. Yeah, basketball courts, because that's how
we're going to settle this damn thing. One on one, me versus the coin guy.
First guy to dunk wins. I would maybe ask to swear in on my crush's hand, so I
got to hold hands with her. Oh, that's a good idea. I would like to swear in on
Pamela Anderson's boobs with both hands. That's how addicted to being the
president. I am yeah yeah. What else do I want to touch hmm? No, no, not poop,
whatever you do don't make me swear it up. I'll swear on anything, except no,
not P, but now he's holding it to I was wearing on the damn TV remote yeah,
and you probably would yeah. You could swear on on a universal remote and you
could do a prank where then when you're swearing and you press the power button,
everyone's TV turns off. They can't see the rest of the inauguration. I want to
swear it on the click remote and then take that yeah and take the click remote
is swearing in on something is a great opportunity to steal anything in the
world. Anything you want you build us at you it's a thing or they have to let
you. So all you have to do is become the president. It's the easiest thing in the
world to do is win an election. I mean my grandpa says it's the easiest job.
There is you play golf president, except for Donald Trump. Yeah, he worked
really, really hard yeah. I mean a sleepy Joe can do it. I could do it in my
- Yeah, exactly. - For sure.
- Yeah, and yeah, you just have to ask them,
like, I wanna swear in on, you know,
whatever thing I want.
- Yeah.
- My enemy, I want my neighbor's motorcycle.
- I'm gonna swear in--
- I'm gonna swear in on my neighbor's lawnmower.
- I'm just taking your neighbor's shit.
- Swearing in on a Funko Pop of myself,
and then they have to make Funko Pops of me.
- True, yeah, you could ask to swear in
on something that doesn't exist to make them invent it.
- Oh, whoa.
- I would like to swear in on a personal teleporter
only it worked with me oh my god I was like this morning on world peace I would
I would rather swear in on you it has to be like an object I like to swear in on
ending world hunger so it could be a button that ends world hunger I guess
yeah that's true did you guys actually see that the UN proposed Elon Musk and
world hunger and then he bought the bird site you see that the UN actually all
proposed to each other because they're all they're all gay liberals yeah
yeah, global. Oh, that's just and you know the media is not going to report on that.
What yeah, seriously not yeah, damn the un was that stand for the
yeah, the I heard the media is in the pocket of the of the the un yeah, the
flesh pocket yeah, their butthole is that their meat pocket there yeah,
they're but what is he when me pocket I'm I wasn't trying to United Nations.
Oh, okay.
What's up?
I thought it meant like UPN.
What is that?
I don't know what that is.
Yeah, I don't know what you're talking about.
UPN?
When you're in the bathroom, UPN.
Damn.
(laughing)
What is wrong with you today?
What did you just spit out?
Is that a booger?
That's a booger.
Oh my, what?
That's a booger?
Yeah.
Dude.
What the, put that back in your nose.
Put that back in your nose right now.
Is that a napkin?
what the fuck is wrong with you that is the biggest booger I've ever seen I am
just oh it was like that that looked like it looked like it was cherry
flavored it did I think my nose is about to bleed I think I think if it's old
it's black it's old blood so it's previously blood yeah I guess I must have
had a bloody nose in my sleep. How did your, how did it fly? Have you ever had that before?
Bloody nose in my sleep? I don't fucking know. You get a bloody nose in your sleep and then
I'm looking up with blood all over me. And your pillow is all covered in blood. Yeah,
that's happening. I used to get nose bleeds all the time. Your wife's skull is cracked
open. Yeah. Oh my damn nose is bleeding again. That's separate. That's a separate thing. Oh
man, I get a bloody nose in my sleep and then my damn horse head in my bed is like. I hate
when my wife's skull cracks open in her sleep and all her ideas and dreams come out. Yeah
And they go into my damn head.
Yeah, and I'm dreaming about princesses and a pink car.
All this damn dumb girl crap.
All my wife's dreams pop into my head, and then, "Oh, look, I'm buying an Easy-Bake
oven on Amazon the next day."
Hey, baby, did you, like, enter my brain at night or something?
Because I seriously had a dream that I was in a girl's body.
I had a dream I have to stop sleeping next to you.
Yeah, so I have to stop sleeping next to you.
I'm going to go get a hotel by myself.
I had a dream I was a woman and I was married to a man.
Yep, so you must have done something to my brain, you tricky succubus.
you witch you witch witch woman you which I would what didn't it but then many
yeah I agree to have a bewitched situation where you realize your damn
wife is a witch damn yeah maybe be fine with it yeah what if it's like oh we're
gonna we're gonna go like I'd like you to finally meet my parents and you go to
a graveyard in Salem yeah hold on yeah wait hold on
and their green your parents are rocks with words on them.
You must be a what is this?
What are these things?
Okay, so you are basically obviously a witch you're a rock monster.
You have rocks for parents.
Something is wrong with you.
Okay, you're crazy.
Wait, your parents are two jars.
That doesn't make any damn sense.
What is this two jars with tons of pepper in them?
The hell all right.
I'm making brisket.
jars making brisket with the pepper in those in your parents yeah I found out
or like yeah or like she's like I'd like it's a witch you like you to meet her
parents and she takes you to the urns and they're empty you're like oh no I
found out that you were your parents were pepper and then I smoked a brisket
in it now I'm seeing your mom and dad everywhere like how high okay I thought
I thought that that was seriously just fancy cat litter and I've always
wanted to know what it was like to use cat litter on a brisket on a brisket.
I was doing a Google Foods experiment.
Oh my bad. I thought that was butt powder.
Thought that was just tons of trash. I just threw it away.
Oh, I was using that on my butt. I basically fed all that to my fish.
I was thinking like if like the if I was if I woke up in my apartment and I saw
like a hot dog on the ceiling, I would spend all day jumping up trying to get
it with my mouth.
I don't think fishes are wrong for that at all. Okay, I didn't know what the
connection was to what we're talking about. I thought you were just like
yeah. I was thinking the other day. If there was a hot dog on top of my
ceiling, I would be I was I was thinking about that dude Fisher. I mean yeah, of
of course you eat the food. I mean, well, so I mean I don't know maybe it's just a
me thing, but I before I've looked at a fish like eating food, I'd be like what
an idiot. What an idiot for eating food? Well, yeah, it's just has to swim. It
just he looks so dumb doing it looking from the outside. I don't understand
your perspective here. I don't think my perspective is outside the tank. So
previously you thought that fish were stupid for eating food. It's the same.
No, it's the same any any any pet. But if a hot dog was on the ceiling, yeah, any
pet, I feel like is has it's looks stupid eating its food. Why? Because you
give them the food and they eat it and they choke on it. They can't be what
I'm not talking about dogs. You're sounding like him now. No, I'm not. This
is a Patrick point that you're making. No, it's not. He's making perfect sense.
That's that is only helping my case. No, it's just okay. You think that the way
that look when they the way the way that a dog eats food. If I ate food like a
dog ate food, I think I would that I would have no dignity out of a bowl out
if somebody put a bowl down the ground i ran over and started a snare for you
down here in a restaurant
i don't do that i don't do that at restaurants that'll put a bowl in front
of you and i don't think so fast and i don't like
they don't have hands
of course i have hands at restaurants are they don't dogs don't have hands of
course i don't get out of the united well they could at least eat slowly with
dignity
there's still there's a disconnect here
do you think it's a dignity issue definitely a fellow federal and i'm
sometimes food with no dignity. No fish
eats food with more dignity than a dog,
but less than a human unless they're
eating a hot dog. Let's love a human.
Yeah. Well, no what I'm saying is I was
thinking that a fish a fish didn't have
dignity eating and then I was like
thought of thinking about it and I was
like no, I guess that's probably the
most dignified way. They could do it a
dog could eat more dignified. How would
you feed a dog in a more dignified
manner if it walked over to the food
slowly and it took one bite and shoot
it and swallowed it and then took
another bite instead of going. I think
you had a pet pig instead of a dog because my dog pretty much my dog eats slowly
will you feed your dog like slime out of your hand that's not true it's completely
you told me that he eat now no he's eating out of a bowl I've seen you feed
your that has changed in the last like 24 hours then nope yeah nope it's been
he gets he gets like a he cooks a little bit of like duck or something no my
daughter in his hand and then he does I mean squeezes it through the gaps in his
He uses it to get the juice out and then gives it to his dog.
He makes kibble with pumpkin and chicken.
He cooks the kibble in an easy bake oven.
You're feeding your dog kibble?
That's not good for him.
But with pumpkin and chicken because he has digestive issues, okay?
And he has a slight, every morning if he eats just kibble he has a diarrhea that is purely
snot and it looks like it came out of his nose.
Then why are you feeding him the kibble anyway?
Because if you feed him a little bit of kibble he gets his grains.
Just put a piece of bread in it.
He can't eat bread.
This guy's a Michelle Obama for dogs.
So Obama for dogs. He can't eat croutons because they're crunchy. Yeah? Yeah. So just put, just
make your dog a salad every morning. Make your dog a chicken Caesar salad. Okay. Alright,
I'll start doing that. That's a great idea. Uh huh. A table side? Yeah, a table side. A
table side where I skin the anchovy and. Yeah, you make the sauce yourself. That's a good
idea. Yeah. I did that in an episode of Kitchen Nightmares I was watching. It's kind of fucking
gross that there's fish in Caesar salad. That's fine. You know Caesar salad made by a guy named
Caesar the squishy squisher fish or in a Caesar show visa and it's a show these
and sardines are so good yeah but a squisher they squish it they squish the
whole thing and turn it into much yeah they don't they don't watch it I was
watching an episode of kitchen nightmares where the it's like a place
in Boston where the guy is making Caesar salads an Italian place that they're
making Caesar salad table side which is here's a kitchen I'm a Caesar salad
- I have a cafeteria in my middle school.
I'm completely naked and I'm fighting Reptar.
- Wow.
- He can fit in there?
- Yeah, he's a toy.
- What's a big cafeteria?
- He's a toy, asshole.
- So he's toy-sized.
- He's a giant.
- No, the toy Reptar.
- Well, you didn't say that.
- Yeah, because I thought it was obvious.
- Oh, so you're Tommy Pickles.
- It should be obvious then.
- No, I'm me and I'm in my middle school
and I'm naked and I'm in the kitchen.
- So you're naked at your middle school?
- Yeah, as a middle schooler fighting a Reptar.
- Okay.
anyway the Kitchen Nightmares episode is in Boston and there's a scene where
Gordon Ramsay is- Oh the toy Gordon Ramsay right? Yeah the toy Gordon Ramsay. Yeah of course.
But he's in front of he's in front of the Sephora in Faneuil Hall. Uh-huh.
He's like, "I need to go to the North End. The only way to do it is
by one of these." And he gets on a fucking duck boat. He's in front of the fucking
Sephora in Faneuil Hall and he has to go to the North End. He gets on the duck boat at
the park? He gets on the duck boat or he's like I need a quick history lesson and he
gets on the boat and he's like hey Gordon where you going? He's like I'm
going to the North End. Wait one of the ones that's a that's has the it's like a
car and a boat? Yeah. And then he gets on it and the guy's like telling
him like yeah the North End's one of the it's got the most Italians in all of
Boston and then it's like I mapped it out from that Sephora to this restaurant
it's about a four minute walk it's a four minute walk it is a - it is a one to
two minute drive depending on traffic Gordon Ramsay gets on there's two
streets between the earth and then that's a four yeah there the he gets on
the duck boat for one minute to hear this like fucking Boston guy just be
like yeah there's a lot of Italians here I mean he needed a history lesson he said
it you could have walked I'll be sorry at the time
Menino man you know I don't need big I don't know man you know mm-hmm the
marimini no soy BLT a clover hmm yeah yep those every day I'll be so pissed off
if Gordon Ramsay commandeered my duck boat dude if Gordon Ramsay was probably
try to confit yeah oh my god if Gordon Ramsay was in Boston if I see him in Boston
I'd probably try to put sauce on it. I'd probably put a brown sauce all over my damn duck boat.
Oh you want to put gravy on my duck boat? Yeah asshole. Yeah I'm gonna put sauce on it I'm
gonna feed you duck. Fucking hell there's no sauce on this duck.
cutting it I'll just how do I turn this into foie gras
foie gras
I would love to see a TV show of Gordon Ramsay eating inedible objects and
complaining about like eating like like duct tape or something
you haven't seen
fucking hell it's too sticky
oh fucking hell
fucking hell it's too silver
what the fuck what is this
nice. Yeah, this is a fucking sponge. This is fucking Crayon. This is a
fucking blue spot. Are you going to sell? He's he's at he's at a
restaurant in the kitchen at a restaurant like eating the plates.
It's fucking it's stale. This is fucking broken. I would literally
only watch that for the rest of my life. If you just eat it, just
him reviewing the food on fear factor. Yeah, pig come in blood
and he's like putting his hands and he's like fuck me. Look at
this look at this would you you would you sell these gonads would you sell these
these alligator eyeballs are fucking no fucking seasoning he comes up to Joe
Ruggs like this is chef I need you to taste this me it's like one of the
donkey dicks and Jerry's like I'm not gonna eat that if you wouldn't need it
why are you serving to these people it's a good point yeah fair point about show
Joe Rogan chef to do every part of the eating definitely you have to do
everything with them dude if he's if he's the best he's the best reality TV host
because he looks like he's never done anything in his life he looks like he
woke up that morning like he spawned that morning it's like an animal from a
bowling ball and he's so awesome he just I saw I saw an episode the other day
where he just had his head he just had like a growth on his lip like he just
had a disgusting and they did not do it which is okay and cool if Joe Rogan
wants to have us on the oh yeah I mean I love he's the but he literally is the
perfect like game show reality show. I think we could get on. I think we get on easy.
That'd be so funny to get on there and try to like explain something that doesn't exist to him
that we made up like us trying to like talk to. You really you want to troll Joe Rogan? I don't
want to troll him. You seriously why? Why would you do that? I want him to think about experimental
concepts. Like what? Like basically like what like okay think about like the fastest car.
to Tesla Model S. 0-60 in 1.6 seconds.
Yeah, think about that. Now imagine it had the engine of two of them.
So it had two engines
inside of it. It had two ones of the engine.
So this is the concept you want to ask him about.
Yeah, I think he probably would have some good insight on that I have to say.
He probably would. If there was two ones of one car.
I think honestly Patrick, I think you and Joe Rogan head to head, he's tearing you up in
the mental arena.
In the mental arena?
Yeah.
What about the pasta dutchie arena?
I bet he can smoke you under the damn table too.
I bet he can't drink as many beers as me.
I bet he can't drink twice as many beers as you.
There's only one way to find this out.
I think you need to go on and have an eating challenge/smoking challenge/drinking challenge/mental
challenge.
So I'm going to eat a bunch of Delta 8 gummies.
- No, not Delta 8.
- No, no, no, I eat the Delta 8.
- He does use CBD therapeutically though.
- Me?
- He does.
- Oh, I started because of him.
- Doing CBD because of Joe Rogan?
- Yeah, for my back.
My back problems.
I have back pain constantly.
- Every time you turn your back to me it's a problem.
Get your fine ass back over here.
- No.
- Sit in my lap.
- Okay.
- What?
- Huh?
- That's the sound it made when you sat on my lap.
- That's a weird sound.
- What the hell?
- Why'd it do that?
That sounded like you were standing up more than sitting down.
Yeah, that's a classic stand up sound.
Yeah, as your butt is stuck to the chair.
Let me sit down.
Huh.
Oh, there goes my penis into his butt.
Ouch!
Did you ever listen to that Norm Macdonald sketch album?
That thing is so funny, dude.
Oh yeah, I know.
He's going to come back pretty soon, I think.
Yeah, I think I heard that.
I heard I heard I'm digging him up. Yeah, I heard that I'm I heard I'm defiling and
him so he has to come back and wander this mortal plane forever. I do kind of
every dead person like dead famous person I do want to see a picture of
their body like Osama. Yeah. I mean like that should be required.
They should send that to Chris Farley. Oh yeah. Which is one of the greatest of all time photos. He has that
balloon in his nose. Yeah. So awesome. Yeah. Damn I'm gonna go out like that. No you
want to do full of help put that picture on a shirt so sick yeah I remember that
so tight I mean I'm full of smells cuz you had a balloon yeah all right we're
on tour right now we're like yeah if I threw the tour we are a 14th Oh right
now we are in with you is be Arizona mm-hmm we're hanging out with no I mean
probably by now it's completely sold out and there's no chance of you getting
tickets, but you should check, but you should double check. It's like
so I don't know which shows are left because I don't have the I'll pull it up.
We're doing a show in the 14th. You said it's the 14th. So so today is May 14
today's May 14. We are we have left are we at tomorrow Fort Worth,
Granford, New Jersey and then Austin. Then we got LA. Then we got San
Francisco. Then we got Chicago and then I think we're doing a show in the
ghetto. Yeah, I heard we're going to do the hood. Yeah, so we'll be there
pretty soon. Yeah, alright. Bye!