You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
Wow.
I am back on the computer.
I talked to Cameron on Twitch.
You never hop on.
It's because I'm busy, dude.
You're not busy.
- You're not busy, every time that we go on Twitch
you're playing like Warzone, or Valorant.
- No, he doesn't play Warzone, come on.
Now you just showed you don't know him at all.
- Yeah, you don't know me at all, dude.
I play Valorant and I play Counter-Strike
with my younger brother, that's the only games I play.
- No, you play, it used to be Warzone.
- We'll be like, oh, we're gonna go live on Twitch,
we're gonna play a game, and Kale will be like,
sorry guys, I'm busy, and then his Discord says like,
watching game video one minute.
(laughing)
- Well, 'cause I'm busy.
- Busy doesn't mean that I am at work.
Busy just means I'm doing stuff that I'm doing.
- It just means you don't want to hang out with your friends.
- Yeah, you want to go and you want to watch
that Korean guy play Warzone.
- Yeah.
- Korean Savage, dude?
- Listen.
- Korean Savage.
- I don't, he's not, you know, he's not my number one anymore.
- Yeah, Caleb will be like, "I'm busy."
And then his Discord status says,
"Reading 101 Minecraft jokes dot pdf."
- No, I let, there's a kid that I let
borrow my discord login. I knew I shouldn't have done that. Oh you're one of those discord
guys who likes kids? Yeah you grew up a child. No he didn't know how to make an account so
I sometimes let him borrow mine. And you let your brother use your discord. And you said
do not open my, do not open the photos channel. Is what you said to that kid. Yeah. But you
said it with a wimpy face. Do not. I'm not grooming him, I'm giving him advice, friendly
advice on it. Like how the Greeks, the ancient Greeks, they would take a young boy and show
him how to be a man. If grooming was a bad thing, they wouldn't do it at barbershops,
is all I'm saying. Exactly. Yeah, yeah. Facts. You wouldn't be allowed. If grooming was bad,
you wouldn't be allowed to do it to a dog at a dog hotel. Barber shop, and he's like,
"Yo, that's facts right there. That's facts when I'm at the shop, man, getting chopped
up when I'm chopping up at the shopping up it's facts there's a there's this like
thing and God there's like this building in goths town that has been like building
in Gotham it's called Wayne Tower no there's this build this building in
Goths town New Hampshire that has been like six businesses in the past two
years and now it's a barbershop called Tonic and it's one of those like white guys with
military cuts. Yeah, yeah.
And I'm waiting for that to go under so I can start my artisan mustard shop.
Have you guys seen the HBO show The Shop?
No.
Where it's like, it's like a bunch of like black athletes and like musicians and like actors
and they're all just like sitting in a barbershop and talk and it's just like a round table discussion
on like random shit but then one of the episodes for some reason Jon Stewart is there
it's like LeBron James like Rick Ross and Jon Stewart
and he's doing he's just doing his uh his half-baked character he's just
His whole discussion is asking them different things have they done on pot
No, but it is like it's so funny cuz he's just asking he's like so interested he's he's like so what do you mean when you say
steez
It's really good dude, yeah, I mean that's yeah
I think I think they've done a couple episodes and they always have just like one
Like white dude who's like always a dork. Yeah, it's usually a comedian
Yeah, like we should when the podcast dies
We should all we should open a barber shop called like the grizzled survivor where they only do buzz cuts like that one of those
Kind yeah, yeah beard beard. Yeah, forget where it is in Nashua. Hardy moose. I got
Yeah, yeah the whiskey trout
The US warrior haircut. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, there's a there's a barbershop. I went to in high school one time
In Nashua that is owned by veterans and I asked them for a specific haircut
And then the guy like clearly only knew how to do one haircut
Like the one like the military haircut and like he was like look man. I'm just gonna do what I'm gonna do and
artist. Yeah, he's like, "Look, I'm gonna do what I'm gonna do because what you want it
doesn't make sense." And I was like, "I've gotten that haircut, like, that's the
haircut I get." So I had like some stupid fucking like... It is funny when barbers pretend
they're like artists. Barbers pretend they're like
tattooers. Yeah. And they're like, "Well, you know, we got to meet somewhere in the
middle." White barbers at least. Yeah, and it's like, "No, we're not meeting somewhere
in the middle. I want red socks shaved into the side of my head. Thank you very much."
Yeah, yeah, it's very funny that you can you'll go into a barbershop and be like oh I want this haircut and they're just like
I think I'm gonna do a different one on you. Yeah
Matt somebody's clipping your toenails and they were like, yeah, I actually want to do a spike instead of just
Like an alligator, yeah, it's like if you had a job like giving elderly people sponge baths in a nursing home
and you're like, "No, I'm gonna use milk this time instead of water."
Yeah. I'm giving you a milk bath.
I know what's good for you.
Yeah, I know what's gonna look good on you.
You're gonna look good covered in milk.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
You will smell so good smelling like that.
You're gonna walk around all day.
It's 90 degrees outside.
You're gonna get out of here. You're gonna go outside.
And you know what? While you're at it, get rid of that fucking walker.
It's ugly. All right?
Oh my God. You look like...
Ugh, you look weird.
Let's sew that weird vagina up.
you're too old to have that thing.
- You look weird.
You're not gonna use this anymore.
- Here, yeah, we're gonna cut your nipples off,
we're gonna leave you with one arm,
we're gonna put it right in the middle of your chest.
How's that sound?
- Yeah, that's what freaking barbers are like now.
- I'm just gonna turn you into Mr. Potato Head.
How's that sound?
- Hey, grandkids have a new favorite toy.
It's you.
- We're gonna keep all your limbs, all your eyes,
your hat, and your mustache,
we're gonna put it all in your butt,
and your grandkids are gonna play with that.
- Hey, have you ever heard One by Metallica?
We're gonna do that to you.
(laughing)
Oh no.
I'm gonna cast a spell on you.
You're gonna turn into a frog.
You're gonna look great.
There's gonna be a princess.
I'm a witch doctor, if I'm being honest.
She's gonna give you one kiss,
and then you're gonna transform back,
and that's what we're gonna do today.
I would hate to be a frog.
I would hate it if I was a frog.
You would have to eat flies all day.
How do you, where do you even,
that's kinda like the ultimate like,
like pickup artist is the frog who gets a woman to kiss him
yeah yeah you know like that's a pretty you got you got it's game the frog but
he's using like pickup artist tactics yeah sup bitch you look like shit
you're like shit come kiss me you fucking cunt yeah nice boobs for a girl
the other day the other day i was walking in me and jan were walking into our apartment
And we like, open the front door.
Like, as I was opening the front door, she was saying something.
And I just like, pretended to yell at her.
And I was like, "You're fucking gone!"
Like that.
And then I opened the door, and one of our neighbors, this lady, is just standing there, like, staring at me.
Holding, like, a bag of clothes, like, for her life.
And I was like, "Oh, I'm so sorry."
She's like, "I thought someone was attacking me with a pen."
But now it's even worse, because now some lady just thinks I yell at my girlfriend.
Right.
Which I guess I do.
Yeah, you could have just...
I guess I technically do.
You could have just like sat there and just been like, "No, I was actually joking."
No, you don't get it.
You don't understand.
I was calling her a con as a joke.
The stairs yelled at her.
It was the edge of the door frame that yelled at her.
"Ah, this door is so creaky."
Yeah, it was not good, dude.
Yeah.
That's...
I think actually she maybe moved out this week, thank God.
Probably she moved out because of you.
yet she probably did did yeah getting owned
getting so yeah one of the best ways to get on its own your neighbor moves out
that's actually a good think about it and i got no more neighbor
you can buy that i was not a crazy likely
you know you're listening to the i can play drums on the wall
like i love to be a people in the every gig lesi as you're going to i can
practice
Let my smoke alarm go.
You're playing the Jersey Shore theme song.
*laughter*
Blasting the Jersey Shore theme song
and just running up the wall
trying to do backflips over and over.
You're trying to subliminally
try to get her to move to New Jersey.
Boom! Just running up the wall
and falling over and over again.
What the hell are you doing?
Sundays is jumping practice, thank you very much.
*laughter*
Hey! Look, I gotta jump!
I'm trying to get my vertical leap crazy good.
I'm trying to be in a white boy dunk competition.
- I got those basketball shoes that have the platform
on the front but then no heel.
- Yeah.
- I'm doing body rounds.
- Those are a thing.
I've seen those at like six different Goodwills.
- Player, I'm gonna be real with you.
I work at a Foot Locker.
You're just making it up.
- You don't work at Foot Locker.
- I do.
- I feel like you in a Foot Locker uniform
would look very scary.
You work at Foot Locker, you're the security guy, they hide inside one of the Foot Lockers
to make sure nobody's stealing anything.
Nah dude, I would be, if I worked at Foot Locker, I would just become the guy from the
Chicken Wing talk show.
Yeah.
If I got really into sneakers, I'm just that dude now.
You're Sean Evans.
I'm just talking to Action Bronson.
Just about whatever he's talking about.
I've never seen, watched that show.
I feel like just like this looking at that show that
That's like that feels like a rung down from from fucking Joe Rogan like that's like the way
That's like lamer Joe Rogan. Yeah, it's a crazy thing to be yeah, I mean, but he'll just like interview
Yeah, like I said, so I understand so I understand your favorite movie is the guardians of Gahool
Go straight up that's the best movie ever I love the guardians of Gahool
and then like the thumbnail is like action Bronson's brain fell out while he
was eating a chicken and it shows a brain out his ass actually Bronson combed in a
poop when he ate it it's so cool how action Bronson was just able to coast on
sounding like ghost face for that long yeah and then just gets mad about it and
if anyone brings it up yeah then him and ghost face did the song together yeah
dude that was huge. What people don't know about Action Bronson is that he's on an Italian ivory.
Yeah, that's not got the same cultural impact. Action Bronson actually swallowed
Ghostface and he was talking from inside him. That's why his mouth never moves when he raps.
He just opens his mouth. He's so hungry, that's why he's always talking about food. Yeah,
Because he's got a feed easy to do.
He's got a feed too, yeah.
I'm eating for two.
I got Ghostfacekiller locked up in storage.
I'm feeding him porridge.
Let's keep going.
I don't know.
I'm Albanian.
Nice.
Keep going.
I don't have any more.
I'm Albanian. I'm Iranian.
I'm selling nukes to the Iranians.
in
is
I like the mullet by the way, it does look good.
- It looks good, it's the ultimate boys haircut.
It's just there's a time in your life
where it just, it will thrust itself upon you.
You have to shave at least one side of your head.
- And if you shave just one, that's a problem.
- I did that in freshman year of college.
- There's no Dr. Cortex.
(laughing)
- There is Adductor Cortex.
- No, Dr. Cortex Insanium, it's not a real thing.
- Yeah, it is.
- Nah.
- He's Dr. Cortex.
I looked up Dr. Cortex Insanium, nothing came up.
You probably spelled Insanium wrong.
It looks like there aren't any great matches.
Dr. Neo Cortex.
Oh, that's why he has that big N on his head.
That's not why.
Thank God that's why.
I thought it stood for Ned Flanders.
Yeah, I thought it stood for no.
Because he looks like a Simpson.
Yeah, no brain.
No brainer.
This guy's smart as hell.
That's what it stands for.
He's friends with Uko.
That's why when I'm answering a multiple choice quiz where it says Y or N, I circle N for
no brainer.
This question was easy.
Yeah, no brainer.
This one's the correct one.
Yeah.
So what have you guys been up to the past couple weeks?
Anything?
Fucking nothing.
I got a job.
I haven't had it yet though.
Yeah.
works at Applebee's.
I am opening an Applebee's franchise out of my mother's house.
That's huge dude.
I'm doing one.
An Applebee's speakeasy in the basement of my mom's house.
An Applebee's speakeasy.
We just buy Applebee's and TGI Friday's frozen appetizers from the store.
We take people's orders and then we just immediately Uber Eats that to my house.
be $50.
That'll be $50 and it'll take an hour and a half.
But there's something about the ambiance of this place that just can't be beat.
There's something about the cold temperature that's just different than what you could
get at a normal app.
There's something about it that just feels like a guy's house.
That's honestly like the whole appeal of a COVID speakeasy is that like, oh, I'm like
breaking the rules.
There is a place when I was in LA, I didn't go, but when I was in LA, my brother was telling
me about a bar that has like pool tables and they're just open all day every day.
They just have the lights off. And apparently if the, because the whole
thing in California right now is if a bar is open they charge, they fine the
bartender $10,000. Oh my god! What? Yeah and so the whole, that's, that's, it's smart
because it just gets, it makes sure that no bartender is willing to work. But so
what, they've gotten busted a couple times but what the bartender has done is
is when they see the cops like walking up to the door they just sit on the other
side of the bar
and they say yeah I don't know what happened the bartender just left
and it's worked
that's so sick dude. That's so funny. It's genius dude
like most, it's crazy cause. That's what you do if you ever get
caught like mugging somebody just you just hand them the knife
The mugger just ran away! There's the mugger he's right there!
Oh my god, thank god you got here just in time!
Yeah.
Yeah, dude, most like bars in New Hampshire are like open.
Yeah, but there's no- And they have like wall-to-wall people.
It's like- That's New Hampshire.
There's not like an order though to make it not open, right?
Yeah.
No.
No, no.
It's live free or die, you know?
You can't- Yeah, and that's exactly what people are gonna
do.
Yeah, dude.
Yeah.
Epic.
Just getting COVID from just like the shittiest just dive bar in like Lincoln, New Hampshire.
I can't imagine the mindset that would make me want to do that.
Alcoholism?
Yeah.
I feel like that's pretty simple.
Wanting to have fun, not believing COVID's real.
That's kind of a true, that's the devil's three.
Yeah.
The devil's triad.
The dark triad.
Yeah.
Whoa.
I'm on day four of not drinking today.
But I have to, tonight I'm supposed to go hang out with somebody.
I forgot I made this plan to go hang out with somebody at a bar.
So what do I do?
Sparkling water.
Sparkling, but then...
Ask for a big jug of milk.
Get milk like Spongebob.
Vodka tonic called the vodka.
But then they're gonna think I'm like a girl.
They're gonna think you're a freaky pervert.
Can I just have cranberry juice and a man's piss just mixed up in a thing?
'Cause that's the kind of guy I am.
Yeah, okay, all right.
Take a little bit...
Just get me a big cup of dry glitter.
That's what I drink.
you just make something up just like a new liquid can you just make it up can I
drink your plasma yeah can you give me some like halo style plasma not real
life green goo green goo plasma yeah can you just crush up can you see me
peanut butter in a beer glass can I get guzzoline from Mad Max Fury Road it's
like gasoline but it's from the future and from Australia you will have a pino
Magrigio and I will have a milkshake let me get a Bud Light but around the rim can
you just put the glass into a jar of peanut butter and kind of twirl it around
yeah the peanut butter you guys have a sneeze box let me get a let me get a
juice box and some gummies you guys have just take a toy to play with what do you
Do you have x-men? Do you have coloring books?
Do you have a menu with a maze on the back that I can perhaps solve and maybe some trivia?
Hey, can I draw some? Can I draw tattoos on the bartender?
Please? Can I draw funny tattoos on the bartender? Please?
I'm out of ideas. Can I just work here for the night?
I'll wash all the dishes. I just, I can't drink.
Were you guys afraid as a kid of having, of being not with your parents?
We've had this conversation like five times on this podcast.
- Yeah, it's always in my head.
- You bring it up every time.
- It's 'cause it's one of my biggest fears,
the idea that we would eat a burrito
and then my mom would be like,
"We can't pay for this burrito, you work here now."
- Yeah, you're getting adopted by Guillermo.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
(laughing)
- He would be a better father.
- Yeah, dude, teach you to make burritos.
- Yeah.
- My father never taught me to make burritos.
- No, you have to learn, that's something you learn
on your own.
- I guess my dad taught me how to use--
- Sending my son out to the woods for a week
so he can learn to make burritos and become a man.
- My dad taught me to use partypoker.net
and how to make a gin and tonic.
- Yeah.
- By the time I was nine years old.
And those are two things I'll never forget.
- That's probably, that's why you are the way you are.
- Smart, beautiful, head of hair, genius.
Great at gaming.
- Well, I don't know.
- One of the world's greatest podcasters.
No, it's true.
It's all true.
I don't know about that.
I don't know about that one.
I'm making an emoji face right now, the one with the teeth.
You know the one with the teeth?
What do you call that face?
A grimace?
He's kind of cold, but not cold enough to have the cold on him.
This emoji face?
Yeah, I'm making an emoji face.
In the comments below, guess what face we're making.
Guess the face!
Comment the emoji that we're talking about.
Yeah.
Okay, now guess this emoji.
It's the one that has an ant.
I'm doing the black hand emoji right now.
Don't.
Somebody guess how.
Is David Blaine making a comeback?
Yeah, he's floating on balloons.
Dude.
It'd be so funny if someone shot him down.
It would be so fucking funny.
Just some kid with a baby gun.
Just some kid with that mission in Majora's Mask where you gotta shoot Tingle down.
like a 55 year old guy who's sitting in a lawn chair in his front yard and sees him
is like I found a UFO pay me a million dollars to take this one down
hell I found an alien it's just David playing he is shooting a David plane
yeah what people are talking about with the David Blaine trick is that each
balloon is filled with the dying breath of a child yeah yeah he did he did do a
magic show at Epstein's yeah did he yeah yeah that's for me was like he was only
Johnny Cash did a show in prison oh so did Jeff Ross so yeah David Blaine was
only roasted prison Jeff Ross at the little st. James roast yeah kill it
David Blaine was only on David Blaine was only on on little st. James to in
in
like fake freckles and like a big big fake bowl cut wig
pretending to be a kid.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- He tries to get--
- He's just dressed up like Stuart from Mad TV.
- I'm going to escape from this island.
- Yeah.
- Close your eyes for two hours.
- That's Jeffrey Epstein when he snapped his own neck
by kneeling down with a bed sheet.
He was trying to do a David Blaine type trick
where it looked like his neck was made out of rubber,
but he didn't learn the trick correctly.
- No, he did not.
- He didn't watch the YouTube tutorial.
Yeah, he just saw David Blaine do it at his island and he was like I'm gonna try this when I go to prison
I'm imagining Giselaine Maxwell going to the...
He went to prison he's like well, I got nothing to do in here might as well pass the time by trying a magic trick
I saw David Blaine do and accidentally killed himself
Giselaine Maxwell going to the set of Mad TV and seeing Stuart and then just being like I need him.
I think
Do you guys think what the masked magician does is moral?
Who or is it?
The masked magician the guy who he wears like a paper bag on his head
And he fucking shows how to do a bunch of magic tricks on spike TV. Oh, that's that's that's mean dude
Mm-hmm. That's like if you went on TV and showed that people how to make a McDonald's burger at home
It's not okay
You know that they've done that
There's a YouTube channel where the head chef of McDonald's makes a big that's like if there was a YouTube channel where they tried to remake
popular snacks
Where a woman tried to make like cheeses and stuff in her oven and was showing you how to do it
That would be just like making meals from the movie ever did that would deserve to die basically is all I'm saying
Yeah, that's like watching goodfellas and making the pasta. It's like
Food in real life, uh-huh it's kind of like it's like if a dialect coach showed you all the different accents of a character
in a movie. It's just messed up. The Masked Magician is like a man making the world's
sharpest knife out of plastic. Yeah, yeah. Yeah, it's like watching a satisfying video
where something gets squished. It's like watching Aaron Cairo teach you how to kickflip. That's
a little specific. Yeah, I don't know about that one. That guy, Aaron Cairo, have I, I
got the DVD delivered to your house, Cameron, the Scientology one? Yes. Yeah, there's a,
So there's this really popular skateboard YouTube channel.
They were like the first skateboard YouTubers.
And the dude who started the channel is heavily involved in Scientology.
He's on that DVD giving a testimonial about how Scientology helps him skateboard.
That's pretty cool.
Dude, I think if I had stayed in LA, I would have become a Scientologist.
You would have become a Scientologist.
Yeah, why not?
Yeah.
I mean, just yeah, why not?
Who cares?
I wanted to it would have been like you can only meet Tom yeah you met you have
to make choices in life at some point to just like kind of have an interesting 20
years look if I that would have been a good one if I joined Scientology I would
have I could have given John Travolta a good massage yeah no you it would have
been the worst massage of his life yeah I don't think you don't stand you know
that he fucks the boys no yeah no no no no I think you're completely missing the
point of the massages he pretends to get massages and then he grabs our hands and
he puts him on like his asshole he fucking puts their fists in his fucking
ass I thought I thought he was teaching them Saturday night fever moves no no no
no well you know well from what I've heard about what happens on the set of
I guess you could say you could say I have not been able to stop thinking about that
yeah sucking a man's penis on the set nobody ever told a story that was more
made up
he's fucking blowing a guy on a set of set in the middle just next to the
catering table we got a party sub that day. New York in the 70s.
New York man. So like, oh yeah it's so funny yeah I was there I was on the set I was a
consultant. Yeah also I never asked him like why well he cuz he said it's just
like yeah. I was an Italian consultant I was teaching him how to be an Italian
son. Yeah I was teaching him how to how to blow guys on the set of Saturday Night
Fever. Yeah there's yeah strange allegations about John Travolta
the surface after the credits say blowjob consultant.
Yeah, it's like that's what the best boy does.
Yeah.
I saw Mark Wahlberg on the set of Boogie Nights having sex with a woman.
Hollywood is crazy.
Oh my god.
You will not believe what I saw Mia Khalifa doing on the set of one of her videos.
He was reading a book!
[Laughter]
You guys see that video of those...
The soldiers?
The army guys asking...
Can you imagine being like a guy who lives in like...
In Syria
And like a bunch of guys with guns come up to you
And we just start going like "Have you seen this woman?"
And you don't know who they're talking about
They're filming you. Yeah, I'm just walking around saying "Mia Khalifa"
Like they're the minions, that's all they can say.
[Laughter]
Mia Khalifa
- I'm a big ol' guy.
- Me a Caliva.
- I just be like, what the fuck?
We should do ISIS right now.
These guys suck.
- No, it just made me understand why they're upset.
- I mean, yeah.
- Made me understand why they're doing
all those dang beheadings.
- Pat's in ISIS now.
- Look, look, I'm just saying I understand it.
- Yeah, what do you understand?
- I'm not saying I'm gonna join.
- He's winking.
- I'm not winking.
- Do you guys remember in like 2014 or whatever
when Obama was like, "We're not calling it ISIS anymore,
"we're calling it DASH."
- DAISH.
- No, I don't. - 'Cause they don't like that.
- You remember that?
- No. - DAISH?
- I was in college and my English professor,
he was like, "Yeah, basically it's whatever,
"Middle Eastern for piece of shit assholes."
(laughing)
I'm like, "That's not true."
- That's awesome.
- DAISH is--
- Oh, yeah, wait, no, I do--
- It's an acronym.
It's Do Right and Kill Everything.
That would be Dakey.
That'd be Drake.
That's Drake.
Dakey.
Dakey?
I know you had it.
That would be Dakey.
I just switched.
No, no, no, I know what it would be.
It would be Dakey.
That wouldn't be Dash.
I just switched brains with Pat for like one minute.
I just couldn't understand numbers or acronyms.
What's the acronym?
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
Wow, that was horrifying.
Patrick's doing the yes face right now.
Patrick just turned to the side and did the yes face from the pictures online.
Yes.
No, I didn't.
What's the yes face?
The one where it's like, yes.
Where one of the guys is saying, "You like Marvel movies? You like Funko Pops?"
And then it shows a funny guy who says yes.
Yes.
Who has to show he's cool because he doesn't even have to explain himself.
I feel like that's like maybe the last one. I haven't seen a new image in a very long time.
It just literally is Rage Comics. I mean, we're just looping around.
It's Rage Comics and then the new Impact font. Those are just the Coomer ones.
The ones that are like, X-year-olds whatever and just have things that they do.
that's literally just like the same as socially awkward penguin.
Yeah like it's exactly the same. Except worse dudes. I mean socially awkward
penguin that's he's goaded. Yeah no everything's
awkward. Goaded because he's got his own bloodhound gang song.
That's right. Yeah. Once the bloodhound gang shows respect that's
when you know you're a legend. Same with Joey Fatone. Same album.
Same album. Joey Fatone and the socially awkward penguin. They were going
fucking that's right not so it's so it's so funny when a band
I'm gonna join the Bloodhound Gang some of their songs like just stupid nerd shit
like there's an em you're all the em your songs there's a bunch of them they're
just called like children of Cybertron and like like yeah what and my name is
Thanos is another one there's a bunch of shit like that there's a bloodhound gang
song called jackass and the first line of the song is jackass I'm a pimped-out
Jedi Knight. Fuck yeah dude. Just mix everything together. Obi-Wan's got himself a pompadour
these aren't the droids you're looking for. Whoa. Wow dude that's bars. Speaking of rapping.
Jimmy Pop got bars. I found a rival Eminem on my street. Oh yeah? He lives on my block and now I
think I have to rap battle him. Yeah just walking up to somebody in the middle of the street like.
He's also like beating me dude. Yeah. Like he's like, I mean he's fucking gold chained up adidas track suit. Oh
I mean, I can't I don't know if I can compete with that. I've been trying to wear my wife beater out
And i'm just getting
Yeah, you're getting you're getting fucking shown dude getting wigged on dude. It sucks
I'm trying we're about to have a wig off and he's fucking beating me. It sucks, dude
Yeah, it's a bummer man
- Man, it just sucks to be confronted
with the best in the game and know that you can't touch it.
- That's what it's like in New York.
That's where the best ones all migrate to.
It's all the same.
- If you wanna make it big.
- Yeah, if you wanna be the wig of the week,
you gotta move to Queens.
- Then you fuckin'--
- No, you go up the rungs.
It's kinda like Def Jam Vendetta
and then the final boss is Michael Rapaport.
- It is, yeah, exactly.
Yeah, Michael Rappaport who fuckin' lives in like Dobbs Ferry or some shit.
Right.
Yeah, lives in like a- I know where that is.
Lives in like a giant, like, fuckin', like, like, village house.
That, like a- He lives in like a gingerbread house.
He lives in a- He lives in a hovel.
Like a fantasy candy village.
He lives in a village hovel.
Yeah.
He lives in a village.
He lives in the Hansel and Gretel house on a high rise.
Yeah.
He does, yeah.
He lives in a- Yo, my house is made of candy!
My house all cookies!
My house is a whole cookie jar!
draw you want you gonna build me a house made out of cookies expect me not to eat
it oh fuck okay fuck you don't think i'm gonna
eat all the fucking candy here hey word up
what my sink made out of chocolate fuck you
yeah did you guys see that new rachel dolezal
oh yeah yeah it's you yeah i wish cameron there's a new rachel dolezal
yeah her name's her name uh jessica krug
Krug. Jessica. But she goes by like Jessica Le something. What is it? No. Yeah what's the
or she has like a different one second let me look it up. She was using like a fake name wasn't she?
Been pretending to be black for her entire professional career. She has now revealed
she has been lying. Yeah she was going by Jess LaBombalera.
God damn dude.
There's a video.
Yeah, uh, um, my name is, I'm Stewie Disco and I'm a black guy.
Yeah, uh, I'm Freddy Rap.
Is he Conan?
And I would like to collect a scholarship to Harvard University because I'm black.
That's what, um.
My name is Rap.
That's what, uh, Mindy Kaling's brother tried to do.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, MendyGale's brother just shaved his head and then he went by like Deshawn or something,
I don't remember.
Deshawn.
Let me look up what he went by because he was trying to like expose affirmative action.
Yeah, that's what he said when he got caught.
Yeah, I was just trying to expose it.
But there's like a video of Jessica Cruz like complaining about gentrifiers in Brooklyn
and she has the like it's insane that nobody caught on earlier in this because
her accent is insane like it's the craziest fake accent like she's like
she's like bonk weekly she's doing just like a crate like it doesn't even sound
like any accent like it's she's just doing a crazy voice and then there's one
point where she like is making fun of like white gentrifier so just so we can
tell she just switches to her normal voice for a minute it's so fucking funny
dude it's sick dude I he did not go by the Sean he went by
Jojo nice and his website for it is Sean D'Souza he went by Jojo and the website
for his book is called almost black.com I have to check this out almost black.com
uh-huh it's it what's his book about it's just about trying almost black duck the
true story of how I got into medical school by pretending to be black
literally all he did was change his name to Jojo and shave his head Jesus Christ
it also what a fucking what a fucking like like obviously yeah it's racist but
like what a fucking like the admissions office just being like oh Jojo yeah
obviously yeah Jojo oh yeah his name's Jojo all black guys are named Jojo and
they call people cool cats yeah Bebo they walk around medical school with a
giant giant boombox yeah lasting right sugar hill gang right like yeah it's
He shows up to first day of school at medical school they're like yeah so
first this is a medical law 101 he's like cool y'all mind if I put my cardboard
right here I'm gonna bust some moves it's like I'm an active listener you
heard so I'm just gonna be spinning on my head while you talk yeah yes of
course yes of course mr. Lil Wayne can I call you Jojo like he literally he just
like looks like an Indian guy with a shaved head like I like the fact that he
got I don't know Joe I don't know where I'm going with it but like no come on
no tell me tell us tell us what's up tell us about this very fact that he got
that far yeah it's I mean they don't care at the schools that's I mean it's
just a lot like Elizabeth Warren got that fucking far like yeah they do not
- They don't care at all, they just want--
- How many people-- - They want people--
- To get away with pretending to be a different race.
- Elizabeth Warren, are you talking about Big Liz?
Big Liz from law school?
Oh shit, dude, she was that bitch.
- I miss Big Liz, man.
- Yeah.
- No, I'm also off, I'm off nicotine as well.
- Oh yeah, you're not doing nicotine?
- Well, if I'm not drinking, I have no desire.
- You do this like every--
- I guess every week is like--
- I do this every month.
two days every week I quit her for is there hung out with somebody last night
and we did like we we did a butt funnel yeah I'm an addict yeah oh yeah no I'm
off of everything right now but I don't know last night man we did we did two
buck funnels at once yeah we did it we did blow out of the trash can yeah sucked
yeah I just had a I had a bad week of doing too many drugs and so anytime I do
that I feel like the next week I have to be mm-hmm yeah I have to become a
Christian you start yeah I'm a Christian you start drinking reishi tea yeah and
you Reese's puffs yeah yeah Reese's tea yeah where is it Reese it's Reese's
right well Reese's Reese's it's owned by a guy named Reese's Reese's
- That's the level of, that's like going up to someone
and being like, "I heard you just say ATM machine
"and I'm gonna need to have a few words with you."
- Yeah. - Like, who cares?
(gagging)
- People suck at, I hate smart people.
- Yeah, like Patrick. - Just shut up.
- Yeah, always trying to correct us
on how to pronounce things.
- I hate when people get mad at me for confusing
Iraq, Afghanistan, and Iran.
Same shit, dude.
Shut up, nerd.
Yeah, dude.
You know, you sound like that ATM machine guy, okay?
You sound like an ATM machine right now.
Yeah.
Oh, what?
I mixed up Japan and China?
Don't care, nerd.
Okay?
Oh, what's that?
I accidentally brought my camera into the woman's bathroom?
Okay, yeah.
Like it matters.
It seems like you're a fucking nerd.
Fucking idiot.
Look, the GoPro stays on my head, nerd.
It's for- Yeah.
This is a- It's for pranking.
- I thought you liked science.
I thought you liked science.
I'm doing a science experiment.
- If I take this GoPro off my head,
I'm gonna fall over, 'cause I'm only use,
I used to be really tall, okay?
So now I need to enhance my height with this
so I keep my balance.
- This GoPro has my brain in it.
This body is an avatar that I control.
- And I need to be in the woman's bathroom.
And I need to be in the woman's locker room
because I like it in here.
Okay? - It smells good.
- It smells good and I like the color of the walls.
- It smells good like women's poop.
(laughing)
I love the women's bathroom because it just smells so much better.
It smells like a woman's vagina and her piss and her poop too.
It's great.
Did you, uh, did you guys believe as a kid that the girls' bathroom at school had a couch
in it?
No.
That was a rumor at my school is that the girls' room had a couch in it.
You never looked in the girls' bathroom to see?
Uh, no.
You were brave.
I mean, I would try.
I would try.
Somebody told me there was girls in the girls' bathroom.
Yeah, that was a rumor.
I wouldn't like deliberately try to look, but like if the door was like a little bit open
Yeah, if the door is a little bit open I would stick my periscope in but I wouldn't like deliberately do it
I would get one of those mirrors on like a
Yeah, I would push my selfie stick underneath the door
But if there was straight up if there's a crack in the woman's bathroom door, I'd stick my thingy in it
Not gonna lie. It wasn't deliberate. It was just like if it's if it you know
It was accident
Excuse me janitor. It was accident. Can I leave?
now I have to leave great okay now I have to know the principal is calling me on
the intercom principals call me on my bluetooth I'm out of here yeah yeah all
right I was actually on a recon mission from the principal who claimed that
there may be girls selling drugs in the bear maybe girls on a couch in the
bathroom in the bathroom they're actually they're stationing me in the
girls bathroom to catch any perverts who might be sticking their thingy in between
the door so basically I just stick my thingy so there's no room for their
thingies yeah so they get confused and they they put their thingy listen I got
principal hired me if you if you have any questions you can call him no don't
call him I wasn't expecting you to call him don't do it he's busy he just broke
his phone two minutes ago that's why he sent me and not himself because he's too
busy fixing his phone.
Oh, you're going to the office?
No wonder you're a janitor because you're so stupid.
He was in the girls bathroom and he dropped his blackberry in the toilet.
No, don't go ask in the main office. They moved the main office to China.
It's...
Yeah, here. Here's a ticket to China.
One way.
Go ahead. Go to the main office.
It's in China.
Just leave me alone in the bathroom, Mr. Janitor.
Oh, okay.
Because janitors are so stupid.
finds a beautiful Chinese wife and he becomes a senator in China. Yeah and then he declares
war on America to try and kill you. In the old country I was but a lowly janitor. Here
I am a most honorable senator. Yeah. Do you guys hang out with the janitors in school?
Oh dude I had the coolest janitor. He taught me how to whistle. I hung out with one of
my friends had a summer job at the school so he like knew the janitor pretty well. This
guy Bruce and we used to just hang out with Bruce after lunch. We had like a
janitor who is like he loved like hanging out with the kids in the hall and then
and we all like loved him we were like this is the best guy ever and then one
day we found out that it was our classmates dad and they had like tried
to keep it because she was like it's a nice story because she I guess thought
that it would be embarrassing but then everybody was like you're like the
coolest dad in the world.
Oh that's nice.
Yeah that's nice.
At my elementary school there were, we had, there was Big Bob and there was Little Bob.
And they were both veterans.
And Big Bob was nice but Little Bob would startle kids by making the Donald Duck noise.
Yeah, you tell those about that.
Yeah he would do that very loud and scare children.
That is a terrifying point.
I talked about my magic janitor before.
The guy that he shot someone over a parking lot and used to do magic tricks at lunch.
parking spot. I've definitely talked about this. Okay Pat, I've heard so much here.
I'm gonna let you tell the story. Please don't mess it up because I really want
to know this one. Alright, so he used to do magic tricks for the students at lunch
and then one day he shot a guy or pulled a gun on a guy over a parking lot
dispute. Okay, so it was the same thing. You said the exact same thing. I wanted a story. You messed, the one thing I
fucking said don't mess it up tell me here's what I want beginning middle and
end what are you talking about he did magic tricks at lunch what kind of magic
tricks was he doing like he would pull the flowers out he had he had props on
yeah okay all right there we go that's one detail uh-huh
he had a ponytail okay there we go I'm sorry you're starting to paint a picture
here now bring us to the scene of the crime yeah I don't I don't remember I
just remember one day everyone posting on Facebook I just remember coming home
from the skate park and then seeing not the magic janitor on Facebook not the
magic janitor in all caps not the magic janitor they're saying that like had
other people been arrested for shooting people like all over town they were like
- Oh, and also the magic janitor, shit.
- No, it was just a crushing blow.
- First the mailman and the milkman, now the magic janitor.
- We should have guessed it was all jobs that began with M.
It was milkman and mailman and magic janitor.
Looking to hire a new magic janitor.
- Bruce congratulated me for a stupid thing that I did.
- What'd you do?
- Once he, Bruce was like, he thought it was really funny
'cause I got the, I used to just take the fruit snacks
and I would rub 'em in milk
and then throw 'em to the ceiling.
- Yeah. - And it got stuck
on the ceiling for like two weeks.
And then I had to clean the cafeteria for a week.
- Nice. - With Bruce.
So it's like, oh, you're just letting me hang out
with my best friend. (laughs)
- Yeah, what a nightmare.
- Oh yeah, oh, my punishment is I get to hang out
with my best friend, the janitor.
- Cool, big brother time, yeah, nightmare.
- Yeah, getting to hang out with my cool uncle
from home. Sick. My uncle from another grandpa. Yeah. My uncle and the dad's best friend. Oh, so you're just gonna make me
hang out in my really cool neighbor's basement for a week? Yeah. Barely even a
punishment at all for me. Epic win. So what did he congratulate you on? Oh, he was
just, he was like, "How the fuck did you get it up there?" Doesn't sound like a
Congratulations to me.
Are you serious dude?
Pat, are you fucking serious right now?
I don't know.
You just told, you just did the same thing, you just said the same thing twice again.
You threw the things up there and he thought it was cool.
Oh my god dude.
I can't believe this dude.
I'm paying, I'm gonna pay $800 to have you take UCB Storytelling 101.
Okay.
Are you okay with this?
That's fine.
That would help.
It would.
We could write it off as a business expense.
Pat comes back with a British accent.
Yeah.
It was a long time ago.
You know what would happen?
I would come back.
You'd get raped. It's the UCB. Of course that's what would happen.
I would come back as just one of those guys who's just emulating John Mulaney.
Oh yeah.
Yeah. Which I thought was kind of weird at the time.
That's what you would say after every single part of your story.
Like a liar.
You know, yeah.
Which is a crazy thing to do to a child, to lock them in the basement with the janitor for a week.
John Mulaney, I fucking hate you, dude.
John Mulaney did ruin a generation of men.
You fucking metrosexual toothpick. You suck, dude.
He really did.
last
fingernails and and saying you're gay but you're not I think yeah those are they're
a bit odd these fellows are a bit odd to me no you go to you go to any small town
that has like at least one McDonald's and there's a sexual guy go to a youth who
move it's actually it's actually it's pretty there to get away from something
From a smaller
It's it's woke to make fun of metrosexuals because they're appropriating gay culture. Mm-hmm. It's actually okay
There we go. There's why it's okay to be really mean to Travis McElroy
Stealing anything you want absolutely anything because it's really
Because it's in service of the greater good which is you know, keeping culture separated and making sure that
Yeah, making making sure that that cultures never interact. Uh-huh. Yeah, that's that's yeah that just doing just doing woke
Yeah, listen, listen, man
If if if Bernie Sanders got elected, I guess it wouldn't be Bernie if Kamala Harris gets elected
We're gonna have the dome from The Simpsons. We're gonna put all the gay people in there and oh
You know, that's that's how culture should be. Yeah, I don't think it's right that when when this is just the white folks
I don't like I think it's right when white folks use POC water fountains.
That's the wrong, that's not your space.
You know what I mean?
Stay out of those.
It's fucked up.
Yeah.
They got me fucked up.
I'm gonna have some water.
Yeah.
I'm gonna have new water.
So when we went on, I've been thinking about this.
We need a, we need a wiki.
when we when me and Caleb went on K-Zone last night you don't know what kind of
pain you're about to bring on us. CERB said they had a wiki. We need a wiki.
They're gonna say I'm like 10 pounds heavier than I am.
Shut up dude. We need it. You're not gonna like what happens. I'm only 215 pounds I learned.
I'm not that fat. I'm not even 500 pounds yet. Yeah I'm not the gargantuan
monster that the fucking fans have the image of me. Yeah it's very funny that
that all the fans are like, "We'll draw a fan art of Patrick."
And it's like Patrick, it's like a circle.
- It's Fat Bastard.
- Yeah, Patrick face, yeah.
- Right, and I'm just a little bit overweight.
I just have a beard, I don't, I'm not fat.
- Yeah, and I'm like not even bald.
- Come on.
(laughing)
- You know, like I have like tons of hair
and they just keep drawing me with,
just completely bald, it's so weird.
Fans, argh!
(growls)
- Yeah, dude, those people are perfect.
- Don't, no, please nobody make a wiki, dude.
- Make a wiki just for Caleb.
- No.
- Make a Caleb wiki. - Don't make a Caleb wiki.
- Don't make a Caleb wiki, it's not cool.
- Please make CalebFandom, Caleb.Fandom.com.
- Please don't do this.
- Please do it. - WetCaleb.Fandom.US.
- Can somebody make a deviantART gallery for Caleb?
- Please don't.
- Nope, nobody ever draw me with a dragon's penis.
- Or near one.
- Nobody make me look like Duke Nukem, okay?
I don't want anyone to draw me as Duke Nukem
and Caleb as the Doom guy and Cameron as the Wolfenstein guy.
Don't do that.
- If somebody draws me--
- The Wolfenstein guy, you mean Hitler?
- Yes.
That's exactly who I mean.
- If somebody draws me fucking a very feminine version
of the Scout from TF2, I'd be so pissed off, dude.
- Oh.
- Oh my God, dude.
If you guys make me fuck cons off
from the fucking Overwatch. - The Pyro's a woman.
- The Pyro's a woman?
- Pyro's a woman.
- That's not true.
- Well, that's true.
- That's literally not true.
- I think it was confirmed in one of the animations,
one of the videos.
- Oh, then, yeah.
- She pulls out her boobs.
(laughing)
- Yeah, it was confirmed in this--
- Someone says, "Those are hot."
- It was confirmed in this animation I saw
on this Rule 34, yeah.
- It is funny that they're--
- Pyro's also a red wolf.
- They actually confirmed that all the Mortal Kombat
characters have orgies in an animation that I just saw.
- They confirmed that everybody in every video game
has a vagina and a dick.
Yeah, it's pretty exciting stuff. Yeah, it's funny how like I
Don't know like I I'd say at least like this is a fake statistic, but like 30% of furries are a red wolf
And then yeah, like every because everybody went out nobody wants to be crazy
He said what animal are you you would have said red wolf coolest color coolest animal? Yeah, I'm half dragon half wolf
The advanced furries are when you get to the to the yeah when they're a little older and they're like I am but a white toad
Yeah, I'm a snail. Yeah
White toe. I'm a bit of an odd beaver
Yeah
Mm-hmm. Yeah, I'm a I'm a lonely
dragon
So if you're if you're half dragon half wolf do you just like you still eat gold
What's no you're half dragon half wolf you get your meat
From the mount from the dungeon
Yeah, that's right
So I get my meat from the dungeon I howl at the moon that's inside of the dragons den
So I howl at a torch. Yeah, I'm a toad a bird. I eat my flies in the air
cool cool what else yeah okay all right all right okay okay I have a half
Pikmin half owl yeah didn't I do I eat I haven't played Pikmin I'm a half
werewolf a vampire and that what that means is I drink my blood out of a dog's
Bowl. Wow. I'm going to the furry convention and when people ask me what I
am I'm just like I'm the lonely stoner.
I'm the lonely stoner. Yeah one of my fursona is a Simpson so it's really hard.
I'm Moe. Yeah my fursona is Santa's little helper. Yeah I'm half Moe
half stumpy so what does that mean some some yellow stumpy I guess I don't know
man kid don't make me do furry math mm-hmm I don't know how to do it so I
want to make a furry is probably gonna do so much math to figure out yeah to
calculate the size of the angle of the tail
- Yeah. - Dangle.
- Yeah, they gotta do-- - Angle of my tail's dangle.
- They gotta do math to figure out
the minimum amount of years they can spend in jail
for downloading the photo they're about to download.
- Yeah, the Vaporeon.
- Yeah. - So do, do, do,
furries-- - I knew a furry.
- Yeah, it was-- - I knew if that's Vaporeon.
Yeah, there was a guy-- - It was in your mirror.
- There was a guy-- - That's right!
- There was a guy I knew who was a furry
and once somebody caught him looking at a Vaporeon,
rule 34 once it was a Vaporeon cub too so dude he was they caught him because he
was working he worked as a as a construction worker and he was he was
looking at it I poked out of this he was looking now he was looking at the
Vaporeon picture on one of those big traffic signs that shows you yeah this
world is sick dude it's messed up that things like this happen this world is
sick can you imagine if there was like if we found out that monkeys were like like
drawing pictures of bananas that looked like monkeys and then trying to like
jacking off to them yeah we would we would shut down the zoo buddy yeah we
monkeys drawing elephants fucking each other yeah we just like yeah just
staring at the elephants across the cross this is jacking off did we would
that is a sick I mean they do they do that we just kind of like I mean monkeys
jack off but I don't think they jack off to the other animals. I think well it's
in their sight they don't know that they're like a chimp when you see a
chimp jacking off the chimp does not know it's jacking off. It's just got a dead eye.
You're talking about underselling the intelligence of these creatures dude.
They know what they're doing. Yeah but it's they don't need it to look at
anything. They're imagining. Yeah but they're just staring like a thousand
- Exactly, there's that video of the monkey
jacking off with the frog's mouth.
- Well no, but that's like a fleshlight, right?
That's not jacking off to the frog.
- Yeah, that's true.
- He's not like, oh my God, this frog is loving this right now.
- Well, we don't know.
- When you jack off, you're not jacking off to your hand,
right, you're jacking off with your hand.
- Yeah.
- Unless it's Caleb, he does it with his feet.
- You're jacking off with a chip.
- I pretend it's like Louis Armstrong's hand.
I'm like, oh my God, you are so good at the trumpet.
- Wow.
This grip is insane. I would never want Louis Armstrong to suck me off. I would hate that dude.
His lip is so bruised from playing the trumpet so long. That's right. He'll be going
"Mwaaah, mwaaah"
That's the noise he would make.
My mom says when I was a kid I saw that picture of Louis Armstrong blowing the trumpet and I asked her if he was a
raisin.
Well, I mean that is what the California Raisins was
They should have called them the California racists cuz those
Racist mm-hmm go take him down dude. Yeah, I'm taking down the California raisin one of 257
So let's talk have you ever seen your raisins? Yeah
Have you seen have you ever seen dizzy Gillespie play the trumpet? No, I played it. He played it wrong or something
Oh, yeah, and I've heard later. Yeah later in life it
The way that he used to play the trumpet it caused like his jaw muscles to like expand
So anytime he blew into the trumpet he would look like a frog
Also the horn of his trumpet bent upwards
So it's a guy blowing into a trumpet and he's going like oh my god. Yeah guys fucking face, dude. Yeah
You should see the video of him playing Salt Peanuts in fucking rules. I mean he looks insane
Terrifying dude. I know what he looks like he looks like he looks like in fucking society when the guy's face is in the middle of the ass
Yeah
You rules that video the video of him playing Salt Peanuts
like he's like pretty old and he's playing salt peanuts so it's just like
him doing that with the trumpet and then going "Salt peanuts! Salt peanuts!"
It's crazy man you can't get really you can't be the best at anything without it
kind of like destroying your body or your mind. Right that's like
John Coltrane with heroin. Yeah exactly. Yeah he was the best at doing heroin.
He was so good at doing heroin. With every sport it's like it destroys like a different part of your
body like your back or your legs your mind with comedy and music it's just
heroin every single time yeah heroin or whatever killed Mitch Hedberg it was me
oh no I think it was heroin I think he died I think yeah he that makes the most
sense one of the funniest photos is that is that photo of dead Chris Farley I have
seen that yeah I know he looks so bad dude also like who took this photo right
full of hell has a shirt that's just the picture of of dead Chris Farley and it
just says full of hell numb your mind and it's a picture that dead Chris Farley's
badass pretty sick what's on his face a blood a blood like a ball it's like a
Chris Farley Chris Farley did like a week or two before he died he did it an
an appearance he did a special guest appearance on all that and he is on so
much shit it is so crazy to see a man on that many drugs interacting with like
12 year old the Keenan Thompson yeah it's just Keenan Thompson just trying to
act like a crazy kid and Christopher Lee just going like well I'll tell you this
much this was we missed out on one of the greatest episodes of WTF that would
have ever been. Oh yeah. Yeah that's the real tragedy here. Yep. You know if I ever get
access to a time machine I'm sending Mark Maron back in time to interview every
historical figure. That's right. So who are your guys? Who are... Plato? Oh Mark Maron.
We love you. One of the best like thing like dad things to say is
like you know if Chris Farley was still like watching grown-ups it's like oh you
know if Chris Farley was still alive Kevin James wouldn't even be here and
that's what we missed out on. Cut to Chris Farley in the 90s just saying like POO!
And our dads just at home like oh my god that's the funniest shit I've ever seen.
Yes! Yes! Yeah man. He let he let he made it so fit he broke the glass ceiling for
fat guys. He did. He really did. People said okay they can they can eat food and
roll around but but can they yell? Can fat guys yell and be from the Midwest?
He dared to answer that question. Can fat guys be from the Midwest? Can a fat guy be
from Milwaukee? Let's find out. That's right. That's right. That's a science
experiment. That'd be a good science experiment. It's like an anthropological study. We wanted
to find out. It's a science fair. Yeah, it's an 8 year old kid at a science fair with that.
Can a fact, can a fact I be from the Midwest? Well, let's take a look at the numbers here.
I've grown a man named Chris Farley in a test tube to test this hypothesis. He has, he has
equally. Turns out the soil is very rich. Yeah. He has equally fat brothers. Turns out
can live for a while but then he dies and they take a funny picture of him.
Have you ever seen his brother Kevin Farley?
Just does like what he does.
It's so funny when there's a very famous comedian and then his brother is just a worse version.
Yeah, like Jim Belushi.
I mean, it's the best, dude.
Jim Belushi, well the Wayans brothers are all equal, in my opinion.
I think they're all equally funny.
I would say Damon Wayans is the best one.
Yeah, Damon Wayans, obviously.
Well, no, Keenan Ivory is the best one.
Because Keenan Ivory was the one...
Keenan Ivory is the...
You put the...
You got the foot in the door.
I'm gonna put your foot in my door.
I'll put your foot in my mouth, bitch.
Let's go.
Let's fucking go!
Let's go!
What else?
There's like a hundred...
Like Randy Quaid and...
There's a hundred.
what else there's like a hundred like Randy Quaid and Dennis Quaid. There's a hundred of these comedian brothers for a hundred boys.
uh-huh let's list them all let's list off all the brothers
Spongebob Jr. which is his brother. The Lucas Brothers.
the
Miller
are
in between bill burr and bill maher.
Louis CK's mexican brother Angel.
Angel CK?
Angel CK.
Sheesh's brother Sheesh.
Angel CK?
Sheesh.
Tommy Chong's brother Ronnie Chong.
Yeah, Tommy Strong, his weightlifting brother.
uh...
Mrs. Magoo.
patrice o'neill and patrick o'neill
it is a great irish brother
is a guy that looks exactly like
patrice o'neill just white and has a red hair
john maloney and john so crazy
yeah he's the one that they locked in a loop
john delaney
john maloney and john delaney
John Daly, their brothers.
Mike Bersmallia.
Okay, I have to go to bed.
I can't be, fuck me, okay, I'm done.
Alright, thank you.
Subscribe to the Patreon.
This is a Patreon episode.
Nope, nope, alright, I'm stopping recording.
Alright.
Alright, I'm done.