Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- I got an Instagram ad for an app called Joy Video.
- Joy.
- J-O-I video.
- I don't know, Joy.
- Joy?
- Joy.
- Yeah, it must be Joy.
- It must be Joyful.
- It must be smiling.
- It must be a happy app.
- This must be for smilers only.
I made an account. My name is Crumby Doobie.
Everybody add him on JOI video.
Crumby Doobie.
I guess it's like Omegle, but they made it into an app.
I said that I'm a 53 year old woman.
I think it's called Omegle.
Omegle, whatever.
Omegle.
And yeah.
We're going to see.
I think it's Omegle.
nudity pornography hate speech and racism and violence or okay wait nudity is not
allowed on joi connect me yo what's up who yo connect it's not working oh that's
fine dude is it sounds like I inappropriate Andrew hung who's hung oh I
I think Hung's probably a good guy. Yeah. Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello? Oh man, nobody wants to
talk to us. Nobody wants to talk to Crumbie for some reason. Oh! Who's this? This is Faiza.
Yeah, let's talk to Faiza. Hello? Hello? Yo, what's up man? Hey, how's it going? Good. It's going good?
No, what nobody wants to talk to us. Yes, what's his name? Masood Masood come on
Masood Masood come on talk to us. What's up my dude?
Hey,
what the fuck is going on man? Everybody doesn't anybody want to talk to
yes. Why does nobody want to talk to? Hey, what's up? Hey, yours hey yours.
How's it going? Hi.
What's that noise? How are you? Oh, dude, everybody. Oh.
Joris? Hello? Do we have you, buddy? Are you there? Hello?
Damn it! Dude, that noise! That noise is so jarring.
Anybody here? Oh, who's this? Who's this? I don't know, but we're accepting.
Oh, she was a girl, man. Not accepting if it's a girl. Wait, accept. No. Oh, my God.
Dude, I want to talk to a girl right now.
Wait, we need coins?
You just ran out of coins by hanging up, you idiot.
Accept.
Hello?
Hello.
Sorry.
Stop sneezing, you disgusting animal.
What the hell is that?
You should be sorry that's awful.
Yeah, no sneezing, that's terrible to do.
Don't do it again.
It's rude.
Why'd she hang up on us, man?
Okay, we have to earn coins.
Now we're out of coins.
Yeah, we're out of coins now.
We have to earn coins.
Well, that was sexually exhilarating.
Yeah.
I guess that's an app where you can get a JOI from a random person.
Yeah, smile.
Seems like it doesn't work, though.
Yeah.
I got smiles from all those people.
There's a beep.
I got a J.O.I. notification. Limited time offer, 75% off.
I love the coins. Yeah. I really, really want to get some coins.
You're here playing a YouTube video to your TV.
Yeah. Yasu shows up.
Dude, I miss yours already. He was so tiny.
He was really small.
Nobody wanted to talk to us.
Maybe because our name was crummy doobie.
Their picture was Amber Heard.
Yeah, and then you click yes.
Maybe if we put a picture of all three of us.
Yeah.
Trace Amigos.
Yeah, one of us has to make a new account because I am not giving up my spot as crummy doobie.
Yeah, that's if somebody could take that and impersonate you.
Yeah, no one is going to impersonate.
That's a good at to have.
Yeah.
Yeah, rare at.
Also, Hung, that guy, did not even show up.
Nope, a lot of people just they just denied us.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Yesterday I went to a went to a Yankees game.
Boo!
I basically went to a Yankees game.
I'm in here, I'm in my Sea Dog shirt and my Red Sox hat to get the get the stink of Yankee
meat off my hands.
And I'm in my Tom and Jerry sweatshirt and my black jeans.
Yep.
I can wear Boston Red Sox hat, Portland Sea Dog sweatshirt, corduroy brown pants and Adidas
shoes.
know what I was going to. Yeah, and my shoes are Nike. Okay. I thought that it was
Yankee, I thought it was a Yankee Doodle Dandy. Yankee Doodle game. I thought it was a Yankee
Doodle Dandy game and they were gonna put macaroni in their hat but they didn't.
They don't put macaroni, they put a feather in the hat and call it macaroni.
They should have. Well, but I'm a Yankee Doodle fan so I call it macaroni, idiot. I got an idea. What? Perfect fitted hat idea. So you know that like you know how
they make like the fitted hat like it's got like the like the patches on the
side for like the World Series or whatever. Yankees fitted with a
embroidered feather on the side. Or a piece of macaroni. And then on the back
above the new era logo it just says macaroni. What about a feather and then
an arrow pointing the feather that says macaroni? Who was this motherfucking
Yankee Doodle? Dumbass motherfucker. Was he like an explorer? No. Yankee Doodle.
people is a dandy yeah old Andy Yankee it was the British people calling the US
guys calling the US the US guys the Americans they was calling there was
them calling them gay wads who liked noodles who like noodles we're so stupid
I got another J o I notification was a Luna started following me I I hate
baseball games I'm always afraid I'm gonna get hit by one of the balls I'm
I'm really hit by a ball at a baseball game. I earned it dude. I got really scared cuz we I was like right
Where like the net?
Didn't cover yeah my head and then we like sat down and then sat down right next to me
He's afraid cuz he didn't bring a glove sat right next to me was a mom and like a seven-year-old girl and as those
Their heads are like ball magnets at baseball games. Those are the ones who get hit with the baseballs
What if the picture what if the pitcher throws a small ball and it goes through the net that was another worry?
a
Take Me Out to the Ball Game on every touch tunes. Really? You can just play
Take Me Out to the Ball Game. No, no, because you can not, you can, you can bar songs
from being on your on your touch tunes. Well, Take Me Out to the Ball Game is not
one they think of. Like a lot of... I played Take Me Out to the Ball Game twice. A lot of
places with touch tunes in North Carolina don't have any rap music except
for Eminem. Yeah? Yeah. That's cool. It's pretty, pretty smart. Yeah. Yeah. I played
Take Me Out to the Ball Game by Billy Joel and then I played Take Me Out to the
Ball Game by Jerry Remy. Did he write that? He wrote that song? No. Billy Joel? I didn't know that.
Whoa. It was a cover. It's impressive. The original writer of Take Me Out to the
Ball Game was Abner Doubleday. Who's your favorite version of Take Me Out to the
Ball Game? My teachers. Yeah that's a good one. Yeah I would say
30,000 screaming fans at Fenway Park. That's probably my favorite. Yeah that's
the one I played I played the Jerry Remy version after. Rest in peace Jerry Remy.
Oh it's a Yankee Stadium very nice it's very nice folks. It's not good. It's
dog shit. It's bright white. It is dog shit it is the worst stadium ever. No
Fenway is the worst stadium. No. Fenway sucks dude. Fenway is awesome. I would like to see
you fit in a seat at Fenway Park. I can. No you can't. It's made for
people it's made for people of Napoleon's height stature and build so short and
stout like five three and ninety pounds
he was not six seven six seven I feel like an asshole yeah back then people
were taller oh my god I'm so stupid I was short for back really yeah they were
taller seven yeah oh cuz there was more atmospheres of pressure yeah yeah
Napoleon was six foot seven four hundred pounds you know I was told that very fat
for the time I was told as a kid that during Bible times there was more
atmospheres of pressure so people were 12 feet tall and also they lived to be
500 mm-hmm well they live to be like 600 in the Bible right well Methuselah lived
to be 999 or whatever but some other people live pretty long yeah everybody
lives pretty long yeah Methuselah you don't like Methuselah he's cool but like
I think isn't that he comes to my house wasn't that like he's dead you know yeah
he used to be alive wasn't that like he died two weeks ago wasn't wasn't
Methuselah like they used to think a year was like a week and so he lived to be
two years old and they're like this is the oldest guy ever I don't know I've
never heard that before well I just I just came up with that so
Methuselah was two years old that you can't put that yep I just came up with
with that new theory and he was the oldest yeah, but he was really young and
he died from the name that disease after him.
That's also the thousandth the leoma. I was taught that mosquitoes were really
big back. Everything was bigger yeah. All the animals, the dinosaurs were bigger
back then too. Yeah, they're really small now yeah, because they're chickens
yeah and birds, yep and geese and turkeys. You think if you plant bird
seed yes yes you get a bird you think you could make a good food out of bird
seed yes I think you would make a sunflower right well can't you like like
if you ground up all the bird seeds seeds and so many different foods they
put if you ground up that stuff and turned it into like bread yeah turn it
into a type of bread do you think that bread well that's what the little red
hand did no shit mm-hmm I'm now haven't heard of her really yeah you haven't
in Little Red Head and the Stinky Cheese Man.
Well I'm not going to take the time to educate you. You can look it up if you really want to.
Yeah, it's not our job to educate you about the Little Red Head.
Was she cool?
I know, it's really not our job to be talking about her.
I mean I'm not going to expend my time and labor to talk about her a little bit.
I've heard of the Stinky Cheese Man.
Oh, okay.
And I know what you're going to say. You've heard of the Stinky Cheese Man
but not the Little Red Hen.
Yes, okay. I've heard of the man
but not the girl.
I wasn't going to say that. I was going to say,
have heard of the stinky cheese man you looked in a mirror oh oh oh and the way
he's dressed right now he probably looked in the mirror saw the little red head
- yeah I don't look like a hen you look like a cheese man if the stinky cheese
man was a babybel stinky cheese nope cuz you're wearing red I get that I
jokes on you because I get the head babybel lights which are blue baby
I'm a vegan baby bill. Oh, that is your pants are blue.
No, they're not their gene. They're blue blue jeans are not blue jeans or
they're blue. These are jeans. These are not black jeans. So yes, I'm wearing
black jeans yeah,
so
no, but default jeans are not blue. This is gene talking about the default
when you go to the store and you ask for default. The original recipe. It's blue.
This allergy season has been crazy. Yeah some crazy allergies coming through. Do you have
allergies? Do you usually get allergies? Yeah I'm allergic to fucking gay nerds.
You're talking to the gays. You said you're allergic. Well you just said the allergy season
has not been bad for you at all. Ever since I walked into this room, it's been awful for me.
Ever since you walked into the room. Ever since you walked into this room.
No. No I'm just kidding. I don't have allergies.
I can't wait to take this and then get so drowsy in the middle of the episode that I'm like
It should make you rowdy instead I wish dude. Yeah, they should start putting caffeine in zyrtec. It should make you crowsy
You're not even saying words anymore. It should make you crowsy. It should make you crazy. Yeah, like
Yeah, like like crowsy he went crow
To high school with a kid named don crowsy I went to high school the guy who ended up
I went to YouTube with watching a woman named Rhonda Rousey.
You're Don Krausey?
I just made that up.
Yeah, she was on YouTube.
Yep.
I went to YouTube with watching her.
Yeah.
Went to YouTube with watching Don Krausey.
You remember when they got Rhonda Rousey to voice a Mortal Kombat character in whichever
game, I think MK11?
Yeah.
And every other--
I'm gonna do a fatality.
Yeah.
She sounds like Droopy Dog.
She did.
Every other character, they just got real voice actors and then it's just her.
she's like okay guys we're gonna go to and fight now yeah it's so funny yeah
do that and then when they get like the
nobody use her body yeah nobody cares about ronda round people cared about
ronda rousey for like two months yeah when she was she got beat up yeah when
she she's in the entourage movie and she pegs turtle what the hell I'd like to I
don't know with that turtle. I don't think that's true like the peg her in
her face with a turtle shell. She dates her. She would be so good at Mario
Carter smash, bro. Yeah, she's a turtle. She's a turtle. She everyone knows that
about Rhonda Rousey. She's a little snapping turtle. She does have that. She
has a snapping turtle dad and then like a I just don't find her personally. I
just don't find her very lady like I just don't think she's all that strong
either. Yeah, I think I could be
she's either lady like nor strong. Honestly, do you I do you think you could
up around a rousing yeah yeah yeah I think yeah easily yeah she's like five -
maybe five blindfold on I could see what is 60 pounds let me check her stats yeah
she's the biggest woman who ever lived yeah hold on let me check you use one
thousand did you ever see that one fight where she's what thousand pounds old if
you watch her the footage of her fights she bounces around the arena like she's
on the moon really yeah cuz she's alright dude she's a hundred and thirty pounds
what yeah five way five foot seven I weigh more than that I mean if I had a
machete and she had a feather if she had a machete and I had just my actually my
when was a feather if she had a machete and I had a confetti I could fight her if
I had one fetty if I had fun fetty cake I could eat myself if she was pointing a
gun at me I could disarm her from a hundred feet away to probably point it
at the wrong direction, you could run towards her. I could run towards her
fast enough she wouldn't be able to react in time. Yeah, run to around her,
see her, run to around her. I do think I could beat up around her,
Rousey, and it wouldn't be an issue. I probably wouldn't even notice.
It'd be like, spotting a fly off of my shoulder. Yeah, I would do it by
accident. Yeah. I think I could, I think one person I could definitely beat
up,
probably my nephew. I'd probably make her smell my butt in the fight, too.
Yeah. I'd probably, like, do an arm bar. You see in the fight videos where
- People reach into their butt and they put it on people's face.
- That's the best part about the UFC,
is that every once in a while,
you'll be watching these two people fight
and one of them gets their face completely smothered
in the other person's butt.
- Or one of their legs turns into a goat leg,
revealing that they are the devil
and they should be beaten.
- That was a problem.
- And Ronda Rousey is--
- I'm glad that guy's evil, he has a cloven hoof.
- Yep.
- That was a problem in high school wrestling, I guess.
It's like kids would be in matches
and they'd do this move called checking the oil
and they would stick their finger in the opponent's butt.
- Yes, it's one of the legal moves.
- It's an immediate disqualification if you do that.
- Not, no.
- Which, it may be an immediate disqualification from that,
but it's an immediate qualification for the extreme UFC.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, which is a new league that me and Cameron have been
working on.
- It's a qualification for the high school wrestling coach's
private match.
- It has one more side on it than an octagon.
- Yeah, it has nine sides.
- It's a nonagon.
- It's a nonagon, it's got nine sides.
- That's the funniest high school sport.
- What, wrestling? - Wrestling.
- Yeah, it's pretty funny.
- My little brother did it.
- I would say unicycling.
- He was a good wrestler.
- I would say a clowning maybe.
- Yeah, unicycle juggle racing might be the funniest.
- Square dancing.
- Mm-hmm, yep.
- Yeah, maybe.
- Team square dancing.
- Yep, the fart parade I think
might be the funniest one actually.
- Y'all ever go to the fart--
- Where did what?
- The fart parade?
- Y'all never drank under the bleachers at the fart parade?
- We had a--
- Bring a clothespin, brother.
We had this thing at my elementary school, they called it the carnival.
There was no...
[Laughter]
It was like a night where like you would go...
It's a carnival.
Yeah.
You would go, you would buy tickets and then you would go around the school.
And there was candied apples and clowns and rides.
That's normal.
There was no rides.
Of course not, it's at the school.
They would, you would pay...
They're gonna bring a carousel into the school?
They had a fucking like a playground that they could have put like one of those carny
Ferris wheels.
school. You think they're going to they're going to have money to spend on
a ferris wheel? You guys ever go to a fall festival? We had old home days
because we didn't have like in in London, dear my church old home days on
Halloween to dissuade you from doing devilish deeds. They would have a fall
festival where instead of fucking summoning
civil war generals, you could go and you could bob for apples as a teenager.
It's pretty cool.
- Yeah, we had Old Home Days was just about
how all the houses are old or something.
I don't know why it was called Old Home Days, but--
- Well, you just said it. - Sounds like it was
'cause the houses were old.
- Yeah, it's the most obvious name I've ever heard.
- No, 'cause they would shoot off fireworks and shit.
They would shoot off fireworks at the high school.
So if you could shoot off fireworks there,
you could put a carousel in.
- Can you kill someone with a firework?
- Yeah, easily. - Yeah.
- Do you ever see that?
Do you remember that video where--
- Back up, Terry.
- A guy was-- - That's a video.
- A guy had a firework rocket launcher.
mounted on his bicycle oh yeah something and he was like running people down with
it yeah it's a real candle thing like yeah like try to cut him off whatever
you know I think the Roman candle like the Roman candle thing hits you it's
just like he just dies right it goes to the issue I think that there are
definitely fireworks so you can kill people with yeah I'm sure you could kill
someone with a Roman candle in the right conditions you can kill someone with a
the pencil I guess he's a joker didn't you made him eat it or you put in their
mouth yeah oh dude you know do you remember the fucking what's this I lost
it the fucking the knife-throwing DVD oh you lost it dude I gotta find that
what's the smallest thing that you think you personally could murder somebody
with thumbtack thumbtack who's a directs yeah I was gonna say the smallest amount
of poison probably the smallest nuclear bomb but Patrick is such a brute he may
not understand such things a thumbtack how what would you how would you do it
with a thumbtack to the jugular and you and you you follow the vein down yeah
yeah the person is asleep so they're actually completely not well I got I got
an answer for you nothing the void they suffocate and die whoa
that's not only fucking shit you're finished Gary's thing you killed
somebody with a scream mask yeah definitely my terror ball I could give
them my terror ball and they might lose their mind from insanity yeah yeah
insanity is pretty small - like a fan has a ball but it says it's got a sticker on
it that says Caleb's terror ball yeah it has a jack-o'-lantern face yeah I was
gonna say a Halloween face that's such a sick movie phantasm I gotta do a rewatch
watch that movie so you should check out orgasm yeah orgasm. Oh have you seen that
no shut up you should actually check out this funny ass movie cannibal the
musical actually like close your mind I love that yeah actually like it's like
like blows your mind it's actually it's musical but it's like it's raunchy
but don't y'all gotta check out South is raunchy but yet funny South part is
really funny it's raunchy get blue I love I love cannibal the musical so much so
think about South Park and Campbell the musical and orgasm on all these things
that South part there there does they're not afraid to go blue with it. It's
true. They're really not a blue, but the creators are red. The characters in
South part must be pretty blue because of the how cold they are. Yeah, the part
that they live in. Yeah, tally is blue. That is actually true. Yet his eyes are
red. Yeah, explain that. Yeah,
explain why he's blue but his eyes are red.
Have a hard time explaining that.
It's Tucker Carlson.
The towel is blue yet his eyes are red.
Why is that? Why are his eyes red?
We need a new wave of adult animation.
Because of Democrats.
I think you guys agree.
No, no, a new wave.
Okay, a new type.
Without all this depression shit.
There needs to be no mention of mental health
through children's penises unless it's unless it's really funny and this is
like it's about really the character who's so depressed all the time that
he's like I'm gonna kill myself maybe it's like a show about two smiling
friends I've never seen that show so I don't get it
got your ass a bit I haven't seen the show he got you I got you no you sound
so dumb you interrupted my thing to say that I just bumped Cameron what are you
gonna do I said nothing about it I didn't even make any allusion to that
show and you just interrupted to say he's floundering right now he's
floundering like a flounder I'm gonna I'm gonna turn can you turn around can
you turn 90 degrees to the left okay well you have no eyes on this side where
do your eyes go wait can you turn back my eyes are turn the other way can you
turn the other way yes both your eyes are on this side that's yeah
- You're a flounder.
- No, I'm not floundering,
but I do have both of my eyes on one side of my head.
- Sounds like you're floundering.
- It's just easier to see like this.
You asshole.
- It's harder to see like that.
- It's easier to see one side.
- My stomach just grumbled, I'm so hungry.
- Oh.
- Stop rubbing your belly like that.
- That's nasty.
- Oh, I wish I had food right now.
- No, stop.
You've never been so hungry
you've rubbed your tummy. No you're not being chocolatey. Are you a pirate?
They don't eat mutton? They eat mutton. How would they get mutton on the...
They have hardtack. They eat fish. And horse meat.
I'm so hungry I could eat a horse. What do pirates eat? Horse. Pickles. Horse. No. They eat horse and bread.
eat pickled horse. I don't think they had a horse. I swear to God, you saw it.
Well, if he swears to God, that's probably true. Yep. I remember well,
yeah, I just heard they salt their meat so that it never goes bad or whatever
and it's usually horses meat. That could not have always worked. I bet a lot of
the times you're silly. It's all dry age. And you're like, I mean, I think that I
think that fifty percent of the food that people ate back then was rotten
anyway. Yeah, that's probably why everyone was dying all the damn time. Yeah,
Could be. Can you imagine how bad it would have sucked to live any time other than like
ten years ago? Yeah, you had to like, back then you're eating like the saltiest horse
meat in the world and you also have to figure out what... And now you get Cheez-Its, Cheetos,
and Doritos. Yeah, and you at that time, you're eating the saltiest food in the world and
you also have to figure out what to do with that drunken sailor. Mm-hmm. To early in the
morning. Yeah. It's fucking horrible. I hate when you wake up early in the morning. Early
in the morning is the worst time to wake up. I've been learning about medieval history.
They didn't figure out what to do with the drunken sailor either and one way it
really sucked to live back then. I've got something to tell you. Is apparently
the way that marriage worked back then is that it was a man and a woman.
Oh that's how it worked back then. Oh yeah, that's right. But you had to it was
like a phrase that if you say if you both said the words like the like words
of a marriage you're just like you were married legally. Really? Like it's like a
magic spell where like if both of you said the thing then you're married so
so that it would be a thing where people would would trick women into marrying
them by like and then they're to like the woman would take them to court and
have to be like no. I said it, but I like I got I was joking. I didn't meet like I
was I got tricked and they're like sorry you're married. Whoa you could just do
that you could just be like can you read what this paper says and they'd be like
no I'm I'm a peasant. I can't nobody but nobody invented lying. Oh Ricky Gervais
and Rick yeah, so so you couldn't just say no. I didn't say it yeah. Well there
yeah, it's just funny that imagine that you could just get someone to say you
could also. I guess you could also just say like oh yeah, they said they said
the thing and then they're yeah, okay, but then also if you lie, you would go
to hell yeah yeah, those people so believed in that way. You have a
background, then you can lie. I guess, yeah, I feel like hell's full now. You
think healthful, I think hell's full now because everyone's twerking and being
gay, but they're not dying yet. So you need to go kill all those people who are
being gay and twerking, Patrick. Okay. This is your mission. Okay. And also I'm just a
dog. You just said my activation phrase. Yeah. Your activation phrase is you need to go kill
those people. It's genius. It was actually Patrick. Yeah. Patrick, I could see you being
a son of Sam type. Yeah. Yeah, well, not so much killing people, but if you did kill people,
I do think you would blame it on a dog. Yes. Yeah, maybe. You'd be like, no, a dog told
me. I was tired. I was tired and I was so tired. Yeah, well, that's the thing.
Nobody would suspect him. I mean, if he was a sleeper, if he was a yeah, let me
tell you, I'm a sleeper right now. It was boring me. Yeah, I was talking about
what a better murder. It's boring to you. So it's normal and commonplace
because it's boring. So it's so it's something you experience. Okay, I did it
and you're an evil murder killer. Which murder did you do? Who did you kill?
Subway subway couple weeks ago nobody died so yeah not my best work okay well
you use it was a murder that you were confessing I think you murdered you
killed Kaylee Anthony I'm not gonna confirm or deny I plead the fifth what
really you plead the fifth I'm killing that two-year-old kid it's funny I'm
I'm not Kaylie. I can't confirm or deny. Yeah, just deny it. Yeah, why not? Why
can't you deny it? Yeah, yeah, that's a lot about you. You can't deny it. That's
a lot of the court speak makes no damn sense. Why are they making all these
damn lawyers? You guys should watch. If you're a lawyer listening right now,
fuck you. What happened to good old sinless country lawyers? I think you
guys should check out a little show called Better Call Saul. It's actually
about a guy who wears a funny KFC suit and he's really really good at fighting
the world he dresses up like a chicken wing yep I call it I call it I call it
worse call Saul cuz I think it's worse than the fuck are you even fucking
talking about something else even rhyme with the show worse better or worse it
doesn't rhyme it's better than a change it to worse
I should be called Paul, my brother.
Paul Wall.
Paul Wall sitting on...
Better Paul Wall, that's what you want to be called.
Better Paul Wall would be a better show.
Rapper Paul Wall.
Rapper Paul Wall would be a better and cooler show than Better Paul Wall.
He's making fronts for everybody.
He's making fronts?
He's making fronts.
Why is he making fronts?
He's a rapper, he doesn't make grills.
He makes grills.
Yeah, I'm gonna grill your front till it Johnny Dang makes grills. I thought he makes them. No, he was on throwing fits
He's talking. Yeah, I'm gonna yo, I'm gonna I'm gonna grill your front till you're Johnny Dang's
Good you don't want that you don't want him to grill your front you said good I said good
Okay, dude, whatever you say I'm gonna use your butt like a hot pot
I'm gonna cook my meat in there in his boiling diarrhea
He's gonna diarrhea up to fill his butt cheeks and you're gonna be dipping
in slices of meat into it
To cook it really slice of meats very thin. Yeah
It is okay. Well, but you have diarrhea in your
Body's a cauldron. Yeah, your cheeks are like somehow closed on either in like a bear is to admit that like a reservoir
Yeah, so what I sit in the pile driver position in my butt bubbles and people dip you never had a bubble
Why are you staking it? That's what it means to have a bubble, but
Boiling diarrhea as yeah, no, I've never I didn't know that uh-huh. I actually didn't know that's true
Just because you say it's true, and you have one doesn't mean that you everybody does have a bubbling, but oh, it's a bubbly
Oh my god, I've been hearing serious bubbling
but
you can see her pants like it looks like in like Super Mario Sunshine, like the
fucking the goose on the ground.
The very yoga brown sludge looks like a mirage
God
bubbling, but oh fuck oh check that wall. Look it's all
you know that was too far yeah. You don't have to add a fart sound to it. But stink! No.
Not mine. Jinks. We jinxed again. That wasn't as good a jink. Our famous jinx just got redone.
That jinx is crazy. I realized somebody posted a clip of it. Yeah, Tucker posted it. Oh my
God we're doing it again. What? We are seriously good! Hi. You're not part of the jinx. Yeah,
but we are part of the
the
no you're not part of the jakes
no you're not
the
oh my god
I don't want to have a triple janks
that's like creepy
yeah that's like
I'll do this all day Patrick
see that's not a jank
we just do a copy
different things you can't copy both of us at once.
You can't say it differently.
Yeah, you got it.
You just wish that you had a-
Stop rubbing your tummy.
Stop, you're not being- I can't tell if you're
jolly or hungry.
You're really confusing me with your body language and language.
That's the type of
rub you could do.
Don't jiggle your belly
like that. I don't know what
to do with that. You could do that type of
rub after you eat too.
kind of it's that's counterclockwise clockwise is I want food counter
clockwise because you want the clock to move forward to when you're eating
counterclockwise I want to go back and I didn't have this much food in my stomach
so much. I want to turn the clock back. That's genius. And yeah when you pat it that's pause. Yeah. Pause time.
Oh that's so smart dude I never thought about that. Yeah yeah you don't think
about that kind of thing you don't think about a lot of things. What if you go up and
- Up and down, what's that, volume?
- Up and down, that is, you know,
you're trying to get stuff to throw,
you're trying to throw up.
You get too much to try to throw up.
- That does, hmm.
- Really, that's how you make yourself throw up?
You move your hand from the bottom of your belly?
- I can't make myself throw up with the uvula.
- You can't pull the trig?
- I can't pull trig.
- Damn.
- I've tried to, it doesn't work.
- I lost the ability as an adult.
- Yeah?
- As a teenager, you used to go around
just vomiting on people.
- That's cool.
- Yeah, it was cool.
- Yeah, I'd walk around.
Let's kill you, waiting around vomiting on people.
- Man, I hate throwing up.
- I hate throwing up.
- Basically, I probably hate throwing up
more than anyone else.
- I love it, I'm basically addicted to it
and I do it after every meal.
- I hate pooping.
- Really?
- I hate it.
- I'm not a fan of pooping.
- Dude, I literally like--
- We've talked about that, right?
Like pulling the butt trigger.
- The butt trigger?
- Sticking your finger up your butt to make you poop.
- Doesn't work.
- But you like--
- I know it doesn't work, but I like doing it.
- It makes me shoot something out,
but it's it from the front.
I'm saying yeah, yeah, I mean I've had to put my finger up my butt to get poop out
before I've never had really I used to get really constipated and I was like I
was stick. I was like I was eating rocks and like every once in a while, there
would just be like a black rock in my butt and I'd have to dig it out.
Okay,
yeah, I'm not going to touch that. Yeah, you know, yeah, I don't want to the
rock that you said just yet if it was my rock I touch it but not yours it's the
it's the evil in the microwave at the end of time been it yeah exactly but yeah
I have to cover one of those videos where it's like we microwaved a cell
phone battery I have to cover my finger with toilet paper and then like stick it
up my butt and dig out the poop rock at that point why cover with the toilet
paper dude I used to think you're up there the hell we talk about there's
poop in my eyes I used to have to poop so hard I had to put another man's penis in
my butt I don't believe you that's actually a gay thing yeah that's false
and I wouldn't help which is fine it blocks my shot for coming out when they
were done if you do need to do that to poop I did I did a white poop out my
front it's a birds yeah I made birds stringy bird poop yeah I paid a guy yeah
to him as a do you say your child what I didn't say as a child you're three
he said you're three years old i paid him
and wait you paid him yeah and then i got in my and then i got my big plastic keys and i got my
my big plastic car and i went to i went to the toy mcdonald's that's the yeah everything
everything's just plastic yeah yeah i mean it pretty much is yeah damn do you think that that
Plastic the crap what are the tiny ones called micros micros shooting into kids now? Yeah, I think they're like for plastics
I think we're all done. Do you think that's why I'm so fucking weird what?
Plastics I was thinking about it. I feel like I feel like everyone
Everyone in plastic
Make plastic approximately 26 years ago
Really? Yeah. Yep. That's when I invented like like plastic and like Tupperware and shit
That was like an invention in the 70s right because like the polyurethane me and Cameron
I'm a recently
Know that I think that I think the thing where people are like Oh zoomers are like afraid to talk on the phone or whatever
I think that's a microplastics thing. Yeah
Thanks. I think that there's plastic in people's brains that makes them afraid all the time. Yeah, that's probably true
There's plastic in people's brains that are making them fucking bisexual. It's probably it's probably the plastic that come that's from Halloween masks. Yeah
Really good point makes them scared of stuff. Mm-hmm
I don't I don't know I mean I've eaten a lot of plastic in my life yeah my little
brother used to eat like he had macro plastics my little brother used to eat
every we had these I've talked about this haven't I we had these micro machines
Star Wars things that came with little characters and he would just take like I
watched him eat Chewbacca he would that's that is my little brother
life as a child yeah he would just pick them up because he thought it was candy
and he would eat them. He sounds stupid. I used to just chew on bottle caps all the time. I did that
too. Yeah. My little brother, his thing, his like, he would eat his thing. His party trick I guess was
that he could chew the top of a can off like a goat. I don't think I have any microplastics in
my body. I watched my little brother. I don't think there's any chance anything's going into
my brain stream or stomach or whatever.
It's a pure metal, see-through metal water bottle.
Yeah, well it's safe. It's...
It's from Nalgene.
Yeah, and see the way that
the printing is wearing off? There's no way
that's happening on the inside. True.
Yeah, that doesn't happen. Do you guys think that
microplastics are the reason why I'm bald?
Yes. Yeah.
When my brother was 14, I watched him
chew the top of a
soda can off. That's pretty cool.
That's the craziest thing I've
ever seen. Do you guys like me growing my hair out? Do I look like a hippie? You look cool,
yeah. You look like a damn metalhead with those shaggy locks. That's right. Watch me hit
the thing. You should try and shave like LeBron does and shave to the line, like give yourself
a bald line. Just a crazy giant forehead? Yeah. Alright. Cool. I will do that. We're
not gonna bet on it. Okay. I won't bet. No, we don't wanna bet. Bet. Right now. Who thinks
I can't die it's gonna be exciting at the end of the tour when you have well I mean
I guess down to my damn legs yeah you have blonde beautiful blonde perfect
hair yeah look like Fabio Fabio that's gonna be cool it's gonna be really cool
yeah would you ponytail it up do you think dude I I think I'm done being bald
I think I'm gonna grow it out well I think you should Ben Franklin I think
yeah I think I'm gonna go full Ben for a ribbon I've been I just turned 25 years
old I think I'm really gonna like settle into my old age now yeah yeah I mean I
mean I've been ready to do that since I like I'm the elder I'm losing my hair
the elder okay and I need you guys need a role model you need to role model for
what aging in a classy way looks like yeah so I'm gonna start wearing
dresses I mean I mean shirts that are so big they look like dresses and I'm gonna
grow my hair you could grow a mustache which you can't tell that to this if you
could grow my leg to this thing um you it would look cool with the with the hair
that's what I'm banking on that I look cool and not creepy okay when I finally
get the my grandpa's like horseshoe hair I think I look like a like a cool French
pervert at the moment yeah and I'm gonna keep going with it yeah you look like
statham yo do I you really mean it I really look like Statham
you really think I look like Statham?
yes you talking what a waggy
you wanna sell us a dog?
what did he say?
snatch I never saw snatch
I've seen plenty of snatch.
He said he's never seen snatch.
I closed my eyes.
It's scary.
Yep, it is scary.
Yeah.
I did.
The first time I saw when I watched a porno for the first time.
It's like putting my body parts down the sink.
No, thank you.
I thought that like.
There's mold in there.
There's a baby in there.
I saw a vagina for the first time and I went, "Oh!"
On a video.
There's blades in there, I heard.
There is.
I didn't see for a long time. I only saw the front of the vagina. I never saw that
fucking underside the undercarriage part. You know the part where it's like you're
looking under a car. Yeah. You see like actually how it works. You're like oh
fuck I need a expert. I saw a lady in a video with big lips. I would just see the front and I'd be like oh it looks like a
vending machine. I would see the belly button and be like that's too small. Yeah.
Yeah. There's no way my huge penis is gonna fit. Yeah it's not gonna work. No.
I straight up I I was like I didn't see I saw I think I told you about this I my
brother got mad at me or we got into an argument at like a family barbecue and
then I was being annoying and then I got sent to my room and I threw all the
porno that he had in his in his underwear drawer out so that he would
get in trouble and I wouldn't and I and there's one of those books that your
brother had physical pornography my uncle Kevin when he lived with us left
it in our basement oh that's cool yeah he for like he was like leaving and like
forgot that he left all of his porno. But one of them was like a book that was
like it was like a photographed like Kama Sutra and I like looked through it
and I was like they don't even show the like what does it look like there's no
okay they have to they have to use the butt. I was like 10 I was like okay I
guess it's just a flesh mound down there and you put everything in the butt.
Everything goes in the butt. Yeah. It's a pretty good theory actually. I straight
up I didn't make sense that the vagina is underneath no it's like why no it
doesn't make right put it right where the penis is yeah put it right it should
be facing it's only hands to stand up he's actually be facing the world mm-hmm
you know you could have sex and nobody would even notice and girls should have
the same fly it's it's energy it's it's meant it's like that cuz they're
supposed to when we're supposed to suck up dirt and dust from their chairs when
they sit down oh that's a caveman times when they were just loincloths or
robes that had no undies under there. They would sit on a log and they'd suck up termites
for nutrition.
They also can articulate the flaps to move around like a snail.
Who invented clothes?
They can use it to crawl.
Adam and Eve.
John clothes.
What? Adam and Eve.
I don't think-
Those aren't clothes, those are fig leaves.
I think that the loin cloth and everything-
Tarzan, sorry.
I don't think clothes, like, yeah, I don't think there was, I don't think that shit was
you. I don't think anyone work clothes. A loincloth is funny because I think the
only point the only point of wearing clothes if you're like you know you're a
caveman pre-society or pre like taboo or whatever is just to be warm or not to
like get rained on or something yeah and just wearing a loincloth it's just like
taboo great board game oh my god dude don't get me started any board game is a
buzzer an hourglass a popper mm-hmm categories or a mousetrap we should do
do an episode of different board games that have a mouth strap dude. I got I
remember getting mousetrap at a yard sale and just just put this never knowing
how to play the game and is doing the mousetrap over and over and over. Oh
yeah, so I don't know how to play it either. Yeah, nobody knows how to play
mouse trap. I didn't even know there was a game. I thought it was a like a Lego
set. Basically, it basically is should play scategories on the podcast. I'm
getting a serious desire to do something right now. Yeah, want to play
scategories? No, that's not that I don't know if I should, but I need should I do
but yeah.
What?
Pat said yeah.
Why?
I just really wanted to throw my crock at you.
That was rude.
It was so much fun.
You hear that upstairs?
That's what I'm doing on the inside.
That was so much fun.
You hear those kids crying?
Nobody can hear it upstairs.
Those kids always wanted to throw my shoe.
Yeah.
I've never done that.
I threw my shoe.
I told you about this.
I threw my shoe at a kid at a football game in high school.
I just threw my shoe at you and you just had no reaction.
Yeah.
Why?
I got a lot of stuff thrown at me.
You have to do it again.
I need you to react to that. If I threw that at Cameron, he'd be up here, he'd be tickling
me. So like, why aren't you tickling me? Don't want to. I threw my shoe at a kid and
it started a fight. It's microplastics. It flattens the affect. But now he's going to
be scared every time I have a shoe on him. He's depressed from microplastics and he can't
even, he can't even, he can't even feel anything. He can't even react to a shoe hitting him?
Yeah, he has no, he has no emotion. I'm not going to react to anything hitting me. Anything?
What about a million dollars? You're that serious? You're those kids that get beaten
up all the time? Hitting your wallet. That's what I'm doing. Yeah, you wouldn't even feel
know that like you would have a reaction to a million dollars hitting your
account. I thought you were a smiler. If I had a million dollars hit my account
right now. Yeah,
probably by a PlayStation. What was that's a reaction. If you won the
lottery, what would you do with the money? I would do. I that's a pretty
good point. I would spend it, but I would do the like over time.
You would spend the money over time. I would not take the lump sum. I would
I take the lump sum. Wait for real? I think no the lump sum is the way to go. You go lump
sum and you put it all in like an investment portfolio and it grows more interest than
if you end up with more money. No. Yeah. You do that. No because the thing about the lump
sum versus the like pay every month or whatever is if you choose the month thing like the
way that the year thing. The whatever. It's like thirty years. It doesn't matter the interval.
God is going to strike you down. You're going to die after one payment. Yeah. Everyone that
wins the lottery has like a bad like it's just like how that not Bill Gates that
book it's just like how that is yeah oh yeah the lottery yeah it's exactly the
same way you win that lottery the same way I hate when I bought when I try to
buy a lottery ticket at the gas station I accidentally buy a lottery ticket for
the Shirley Jackson lottery and a bunch of a bunch of Midwestern Hicks come and
beat the shit out of me and kill me and they say this is what America's like
like wait what is the lottery you know you're home never right yeah never you
never read great American literature like the law it's like a short story they
make you read in middle school that's it's pretty good but it's like about
like like it's like they keep talking about like we're gonna play the lottery
today where everyone draw like these pieces of paper we're gonna get the
lottery who's gonna win the lottery and you're like oh the lottery sick and then
and then the end the twist is that whoever wins the lottery gets killed to
to prevent like overpopulation or something it's to it's for the crops.
Yeah, it's a kill one person and that prevents overpopulation. That's some
bulls. No, no, so you have a good hard rocks at them. I don't know what it is
for a good hard. It's a metaphor about America is the point. Oh, it's a
metaphor for America. It's making perfect sense yeah, but yeah, I know
that that that was one of those short stories where it's like you know. I
don't know, maybe it's just the type of kid that I was in middle school, but
whenever we read like a story where someone like died violently or something,
I would just be like a sick yeah that I'll do their their London's read this in
school. I forget what I was a mass. They think they're making me learn about
America, but I'm actually learning how to kill some but throwing a video game
yeah forget what I read.
It's did you get to you like the World War two stuff a lot then oh oh we read
we read the Scarlet Ibis and I hate it so much. I don't know what that one is
the Scarlet Ibis is like story about like this guy who just like hates his
disabled brother. We read a bunch of books about the Taliban. Yeah. Yeah. I had like
three straight years of World War Two stuff. Yeah. Yeah. And a friend of mine, he got out
of reading about World War Two because his dad died. And so he was like, I don't, he's
like, I don't want to read about something so like depressing because my dad died. And
my my teacher is like, okay, and then made him write a paper on the Great Depression and
people had to eat their dogs. I remember in like I can't remember if it was
elementary school or middle school or what we're just like we're doing we're
learning about the the civil war or something and it's like I can learn
about that really have interest you you're not allowed to in the south
you're not a lot of the northern aggression. Yeah, that's what that's the
other thing that's so funny. Their teachers and it would tell us like yeah,
you know in the south, they call it the war of northern aggression. It's like
it's not true at all. Yeah, it's so funny yeah, but they were just there. I
remember there's one assignment. It's like all right, we're going to like
some randomly split the class in half and you guys have to write like these
journal entries from like for the perspective of people from the time
like this has to write a like a diary entry from the perspective of a slave
and this has to write a diary entry from the perspective of a slave hunter,
slave
like a video like his job was to like hunt down runaway. So
we did do that for
tell me it wasn't slave on a slave hunter.
Do you have that your mom keep that and we read it on the show?
We'll all go find it. Yeah.
Another day hunting for sway.
I think it literally was like
like third grade.
It's sway hunting season
wait. They made us do that way. I just they just made us do that
again in high school for like this do that again. Last week in
high school for like internment like Japanese internment is I
remember making fun of my friend because like we like saw his
assignment. We had to write something that was like pro
Japanese internment and the like the first sentence was like I
I cannot stand these Japanese people
why do they do that? It's so funny to write something like did yeah I've
talked about it before, but in in high school I had to do the Lincoln Douglas
debate and I had to be Douglas. I had to argue for slavery. Yeah, it's like why
what is so yeah, so we're yeah we had we had all that does make you think like as
like a like a fourteen year old or whatever you're like you think it's like
this doesn't matter yeah yeah we had to do immigration day at my school and you
had to like write journal entries like they gave you a character I you you and
you go around this school as like an Ellis Island immigrant you got to like
wear like it was like an excuse to like mate like I'd wear like my grandpa's
suit and like a scally cap dude I you pull out of a hat I got fucking Irish
Irish really I got Irish and then like I and then my teacher only used like Irish
American names and I was Stephen Brady and I had whooping cough but I just like
didn't I had to like right the teacher didn't participate no they were the
teachers were the Ellis Island I thought they got to pull an immigrant to your
teacher pulls out as I was weird speeding Gonzales five years in a row I
I just remember this is just causing all this stuff to flood back. You ever do an
elementary school. We had this thing where they handed out like like cards of
construction paper. They had to wear around your neck and it's like some kids
got like blue cards and some kids already cards and it was like blue cards
get to like go to lunch early. They get to walk in the hallway alone and red
cards like they can't don't get recess and they like there's like all this
stuff you have to like do ten extra minutes of homework at the beginning of
class or something and at the end of they're like so you you like red card
red card people you didn't like that very much right and we're like no. I was
red card by the way, so I was pretty Polish yeah and they were like well
that's what it was like to be black during segregation. Oh really we had
that for but they were like that was what the Holocaust was. Oh really it was
it was about they said that we were black and I was like dude I'm I'm like
in seventh grade. I know what happened during the Holocaust. You don't have to
be like and also they didn't get reset.
it was really bad they didn't get resus. The fucking immigration day thing was so
funny because like idiot I just almost dropped something on the floor and I
got it in my whole body. No I'm never gonna fix this chair. I'm gonna drop you. Like I don't understand why you don't just sit in a different
there's so many other chairs. This one has the fun wheels. Yeah. So don't you feel like an
asshat? I do. What was it? Oh oh so like if you got like a like you were encouraged to
bring in food and like if you got Italian immigrant like everyone literally just
brought in like market basket boxes of spaghetti and we're like yeah yeah oh
yeah we didn't get lunch either that day cuz you were supposed to bring in food
and my friend brought him try spaghetti and just like I guess I have to fucking
eat this he's a dry spaghetti dry spaghetti sounds like a life at life
back school life hack you forget your lunch you go to the nurse she'll give
three gram crackers true. How often did you go to the nurse to get to the
back? I was in the nurse's office constantly entire school career yeah. I
skipped so my learn when I learned those I was friends with the nurse in high
school and she was like the mom of one of the like kids in my class. I like
didn't know very well, so I just hang out with her mom every day. Same it my
middle school nurse was like the mother of this really like shit head kid who
became like a SoundCloud rapper.
And I learned when I learned that you could just like go to the nurse's office
and be like, Oh, Oh, no, Oh, and like your mom has to come pick you up like
so. So I think that my mom's day seven so when I was second grade,
I went home 15 times in like I had months and my teacher had to like call a
meeting with my mom.
Yeah, I had I had in I feel I've may have said this before, but in senior of high
school I had 90 absences.
Really? Yeah, it's a senior in one year.
Yeah. What the fuck? It's like half the year. So awesome. That is so I like I
came so close to not graduating.
Damn, damn, dude, I wish I just did all my classwork in like the last week of
school genius. Yeah, yeah, very sick. I recommend any anybody who wants to do
that. It's cool. It works. You should be able to do that with everything dude.
That's what that's what our job is now. Yeah, no, our jobs are way hard. Our
jobs are actually true. You only have to work one week a year. We just do all of
our episodes in the one week. Yeah, and then and then I can pursue painting
painting. I can finally become a pro skater. And dancing. Dancing, you know, not
gonna happen. Sorry, you can't, you're trying to put an edge in on my territory.
But hip-hop. Hip-hop dancing? I don't know. I don't know. I think you might, listen pal, I
understand you're interested in dancing, but why don't we, why don't we start you
a rung lower on the ladder. You're gonna, you're gonna learn posing. Yeah. Okay.
Hip-hop posing. Okay, that's fine. And hip-hop painting. Yep. Yep, that's okay. Graffiti.
No, that's not hip. That's not hip. That's a hip hop crime. Okay, listen pal hip
hop is about raising people up and doing good for your community and graffiti
ruins fucking buildings. Yep and fire hydrants a flat ground back flip in a
gym. Yeah,
it's true. It's in a multi purpose room. Yep in a in a high school. Yep, it's
about wearing hip hops about wearing a sci fi watch pal not destroying it not
destroying a store front yeah yep. I remember I just remembered this I my mom
had this like freeze dry nail stuff. So you like spray it like it's like you
know you'd like spray it on your fingers. So your nail polish dries faster and I
spray to you yeah, you would I like I was like whoa it's crazy like you can
spray it on yourself and it makes your hand cold and I sprayed I sprayed like I
I gave myself like a chemical burn with it on the back of my hand when I was
like seven such a perfect that's like the like archetypical perfect stupid
seven year old thought is oh, I can spray this on my hand and it will make
my hand cold. I should do this. I spray I gave myself a chemical burn and
then I guess I like it like blistered up and then it like popped in class and
then I was like oh, oh geez I have to go to the nurse. I should get sent home
And I did, but then like the school called my mom
and was like, "You were putting out cigarettes on your son."
(laughing)
My mom had to fight the school and be like,
"No, I'm not like burning my kid."
Like I'm like, no, he's just stupid
and he sprayed nail stuff on himself.
- And they were like-- - Child services stuff
is so evil, they're always trying to take away a kid
just 'cause a mom is trying to get a little more use
out of her own house. - Yeah.
- Kids should be like Swiss Army knives.
yeah, no it's like my mom was working all the time and she did not lock up
anything with chemicals. He's not doing any. I mean my my my second grader is
easy as a child. He's not doing anything past nine PM. It's okay for me to use
him as a night table for my glass of water. You shouldn't if you take him
away from me, I'm going to shoot up the school.
I will come here. I am a great parent. I do not abuse my son. I would never
hurt a child, and if you continue with this case, I will shoot up the school
until
(laughter)
- Can you imagine the shit Steve Martin's mom got?
- Oh my god.
- Can you imagine that prank you little kid?
- You shoot your son an arrow.
- You put an arrow through your son's damn head, okay?
That is unacceptable, Mrs. Martin.
- Yeah, dude, that's Carrot Top's mom, too.
- Oh my god.
- Are you kidding me?
I don't know any of his famous props.
- Well, who's that other guy?
- Amazing Jonathan?
- No, the other guy?
with the watermelons?
- Oh, Gallagher.
- Hey, you put watermelon on your son.
- Oh, you did you cover your son with watermelon
and send him to school?
- Hey, I mean, any of these stand up comedians,
it would be easy to accuse their parent of abusing them.
It's like, hey, you make your son
wanna be a stand up comedian?
- Come on.
- Come on, comedy?
Seriously?
Come on, dude.
- These people are actually,
honestly, comedians are broken.
- Did you?
- They're broken people.
- Uh-huh.
- They're all in therapy.
- Have you ever considered that maybe like comedians
they're like depressed and they crash on each other's couches. I think we need to
make it weird. Yeah, I think that's how we roll. I think we make it weird. Yeah,
and crash on couches, crash on couch and then we bowl. We that's how yeah, that's
the is that out yet. Pete Holmes bowling show. That's what the show's called is
called how we roll. Really? Yeah. Oh, that's what I was saying.
Yeah.
Is it good?
No.
What?
I mean, it could be good.
It's amazing.
It's not good.
Where he's bowling and then he's like hanging out.
Yeah, bowling.
I got a bowl to save our family.
I've got to get a divorce or something.
No, he doesn't get a divorce.
I think this show's about being divorced.
No, it's not about divorce.
That's what Crashing was about.
I have Pete Holmes.
Hey, it's me, Pete Holmes.
You're a terrible Pete Holmes impression.
Oh, yeah.
No, you're doing...
What are you doing?
Did you see the episode of the Pete Holmes?
Tom's bowling show where he's he's at the bowling alley and he has to chase
around Jerry, who's trying to steal his bowling ball. Yeah, Jerry is yeah, but
Jerry's the good guy. I heard Tom and Jerry are going to make an appearance on
that's how we roll for real. Yep,
you're fucking no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
stop. Well, Tom and Jerry are going to be on because it's like you know how
when they have like
like they have like a special guest appearance from like a show that like
like on the middle when like they had all the kids in the hall on because like the
principal was from kids in the hall they had on the middle they also had a guy
who was special in appearance yeah yeah yeah his appearance was rather special
Atticus Schaefer name that kid break it's awesome they did 15 seasons that
show the kid never gets any older yeah it's cool but yeah when they have like
this special guest appearance by like the old cast like it's like oh they have
like you know like this person's from oh like when Drake and Josh would show up
up on i carly yeah they're having that his friend flint so that's how we they
should do that with every live action show should be like just only hire
people who have that brick disease yeah, because then it's like a cartoon yeah,
you never have to change like it's like the simpsons like they're just stuck
actually in second grade forever like a the kids two hundred years old that kid
he's like i don't know what i saw that kid in a hieroglyphic he's he's he's
there and which dreamer down he wears a lot of real tree. I think he's a very
dope. He's a catholic to you. Oh nice. Yeah, to you to you. I wasn't going to
tell. I wasn't going to do it. But as soon as I said, I like funny
all right. So what happened? Your boy entire voice. We got left on the door.
We got a Catholic. He immediately was trying
for the twenty second what days today are they is today's it's a clever little
r_d_-m_ is a san francisco show uh... even today but i think it's over that
sixteen and and uh... the twenty-six uh... which is thursday uh... that's
that's a lot of that
so those are the last two shows on our tour
uh... and you're gonna wanna go to those 'cause they're gonna be fun and we're
never a target is wrong to be dead by the uh...
norad about by