Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately!
Time for Patrick's reign.
Time for Patrick's reign of terror.
Uh, see I'm already doing something evil.
I know, you're already ruining- I'm doing an evil mind melt to the people upstairs and
they're slamming things with hammers.
Somebody's doing a giant stomp.
What the fuck is that?
One second guys.
Hi Ben.
How are you doing today?
Wait, he got a call from Ben on the show.
Wow.
Oh my god.
What do you mean no?
Don't say no to me like that Ben.
This is the most insane call in we've ever had randomly on the show.
Stop saying no to me Ben.
Actually talk again.
in the middle of something right now you need to leave me alone talking been
that's not the real so yeah you said yes or no hang up hang up now
ok you're saying yes but you're still holding the phone I can see you it's a
video call put it down
then you just do it
ok stop saying yes and do it you are so fucking annoying man. You must be opposite day.
a
What's going on?
Wait, we're getting a phone call.
Who's this?
Who's on the front line?
I'm getting a call.
Hold on.
Who are you getting a call from?
Ben?
Wait, Ben, how are you calling both of us at the same time?
I don't know.
Whoa.
You keep saying two different things.
Ben, it doesn't work like that.
You two-faced fucker.
Hello?
Yes.
He is two-faced.
Wait, Ben, is this... do you have a twin brother?
Wait, Ben, is this, do you have a twin brother?
*laughing*
Woah!
Oh, they're not twins?
I guess they're not twins.
Wait, do you think we could get them to talk to each other?
I think you can.
We have to make this happen.
You have to get him off the phone and get him started.
Oh true, yeah.
Stop hitting Ben, he doesn't deserve that.
Stop, guys, stop.
dog stop tickling his feet can we make him talk to each other yeah okay here
Ben
they nobody can hear it's working hello wait we have to get one of them started
right over here like this hello.
It's not it was working for a second. I stopped working all shit. This is
horrible.
I hate this
talk to him. Hey, hey, Ben. Hey, Ben.
He's making fun of you. He's mocking you. You're really gonna fucking mock me. I
really don't watch it talking Ben.
I'm hitting him. I love talking Ben. Why do you have this on your iPad?
Why do you have an iPad? You're a child. It's the funniest thing to have on an iPad. Get a Microsoft Surface.
Get this fucking dog out of my face. What other apps do you have?
I have a lot of apps. You know what I just found out?
Minion Rush. I found out when I gave Caleb
his phone. Yep. Which I'm
impressed with that can open it with just with my face. I forgot that if you delete
CamWow you don't have it. It's literally you can't get it back.
It's like Flappy Bird. I'm sorry. I'm so upset. Is CamWow gone? CamWow does not work with the
new operating system. Why don't you get a... I want to figure out how to jailbreak my phone
so that I can get CamWow again. I remember that I jailbroke the first... my mom had like
the first iPhone and then when she got the next one I just used it like an iPod
yeah jail broke it and I was doing a lot of porn watching I jail broke mine too I
found out how to download like you can torrent on it yeah I downloaded was the
project X soundtrack I never had like something that I could jailbreak like I
didn't have the right I had the like old the like nano or whatever I thought and I
remember like break those those kids called rock box yeah I did it with my
mom's iPod like classic I also had the original shuffle the one that was just a
flash drive I got one that was sick that was I loved that one. I had no idea what song, you had to memorize the order of the songs.
yeah I would just have all my songs on iTunes I'd be like oh like what like 10
songs do I want to take with you today it's like it's like picking a load out
yeah no it was so fun. I kind of want to go back to that. yeah yeah my mom won my mom was
obsessed with I think that's why I only listen to like three songs that probably
- Because I just got--
- I used to load, yeah, I'd listen,
I'd load like two albums on and I'd just listen to those
and I'd like change it up every week or something.
- Yeah, exactly.
- My mom was obsessed with online giveaways.
- Yeah.
- And-- - I think I got my iPod
shuffle for free.
- That's how my mom got one,
she got a blue iPod shuffle through an Oreo giveaway.
And on the back of the clip,
it was like the third generation one,
the one that had a clip.
- Yeah.
- And on the back of it,
it just had the word Oreo engraved into it.
- That is so sick. - That's so tight.
- Yeah, and then my brother,
my little brother, she gives it to my little brother
because I already had my sister's old orange iPod Nano,
and he ran it through the fucking wash.
- My big brother used to threaten to eat mine.
- Yeah.
- He was so small, he'd be like,
I'm gonna, he was mad at me,
he'd be like, I'm gonna eat your iPod Shuffle.
- Wow.
I won a giveaway on Twitter once
when I was in freshman year of high school.
I won a whole complete cruiser board.
- What's that?
A whole complete?
- A whole complete one.
- An entire whole--
- Like trucks, wheels, a whole complete.
- Is that the brand name?
- No, no, no, no.
- You're just saying you want an entire
complete, full, total board.
- A complete board, yeah,
'cause I could've just won a deck or something.
- But just say you want a skateboard.
- Yeah, I could've said that.
But I won a cruiser board 'cause I knew
a trick that Rodney Mullin invented.
- Was it the-- - Through CCS.
- Was it a backflip?
- No.
- CCS.
It was Ollie Airwalk or something.
- I think the only giveaway I ever won
was an online giveaway for movie tickets
to the 2020 remake of The Grudge.
It was like the worst movie I ever saw in my life.
It was so, it was crazy.
- That was a cool giveaway to win.
But then I tried to, 'cause it was like a,
like a little kicktail, like cruiser board.
I tried to-- - A whole entire one.
- Whole entire one.
- But it didn't have any wheels or anything.
- No, I had to.
- But it was, it had the wheels,
but it was just half of the board.
- Right.
- I won that and then I didn't like the graphic on it.
The graphic was literally,
it was a triangle with sunglasses.
- That's sick.
- That's cool.
- And I sanded it off.
- Whoa.
- And then like I forgot about it
and then it started raining or something
and then like it was just completely waterlogged.
- Completely entirely.
- I'm gonna waterlog you.
- Better not.
- I'm gonna fill up your porous body with water.
- You're gonna be fully saturated with water
by the time I'm done.
- I'm working on that already.
Whoa. I've been, uh, I've been dedicated to becoming hydrated all the time.
Yeah. It's like I really scared about my kidneys.
Your kidneys. It's hard to be hydrated all the time because you have to pee.
So I wake up three times a night. It's so annoying. I hate peeing.
It hurts. I know. I know. The end. Yeah.
The end of peeing hurts every time. Yeah. A little bit. No,
I don't think that's true.
Every time at the end when you have to push out the little last bit and then it
hurts a little bit I'm drinking Evian because I saw water sommelier say that
Evian is a good bottled water to drink I'm a tap water man I don't buy it yeah
I'll tell you how to talk to my sommelier I'm not paying three bucks for water
yeah it's why I will get a Gatorade you got to talk to my sommelier I'll get a
you don't have a sommelier Pierre it's not yours he's mine he's not I consult
him he's a YouTube video Luke gag norm that's not his name that's his name no
PLG is also that's a bullshit fucking that's a real guy that's my water
Somalia but he's not a water Somalia says he says that this is the perfect
water cuz he's from the Alps what the fuck you talking about that's what he
says he's biased he's from the Alps that's true you know what I didn't think
about that yeah yeah but he said said a century of water yeah bunk what does that
mean bunk it's water it's bunk it's not bunk he said that anytime they all
water water advertises how good their pH is it means that it's shit all water is
exactly the same they make it they make up fake stuff like you to buy water
bottle the only one that is not the same is Nestle and Dasani no honey is
bullshit honestly tastes like it has cream in it
Dasani they literally put salt in it that's fine I don't give a fuck yeah
a good water they put sand in it it's all this
dirt in that yeah they look up they don't put sand and this sonny is
bottled in Flint Michigan I don't give a fuck all right all water is it literally
exactly all the water is the same all water it is exactly the same yeah it's
completely safe it's not it is not all water is the same it is you're not
giving a single water ample yeah and it was fine in his tan suit he's fine
Obama drank that damn water in his tan suit.
And did he die?
No.
Yes, they replaced him.
He was completely fine.
They did not replace him.
They replaced him with a different, they replaced him with an impersonator who had gray hair.
You're wrong.
Michelle Obama is...
He replaced everybody else with impersonators and that's what the problem with the government is.
Barack and Michelle were basically a, like, a prestige situation where anytime the Obama would die,
they'd replace him with the Michelle who was a man and they'd shave his head.
Yeah.
And then they'd get the new Michelle from one of the clone tubes.
Uh-huh.
and then that'd be the new Michelle. Also all clone tube liquid is the same.
Yeah, it's all just people say like oh some of it's like oh this one has more
clone nutrients. It's like no it's not. So and honestly the best the best clone
tube liquid comes from Flint. Actually yeah. That's why the water there is
is so colorful. Oh man this tastes so different from Dasani.
Can you imagine making like a like a nice like pasta dish in Flint, Michigan?
I just feel like it's got so much like well all that that brown stuff boils out.
yeah it's like alcohol was it there like flint is it like the the water turns on
you could light the water on fire was is that the problem was that water there on fire or
you think now you think of the the gulf of mexico during the bp oils oh okay yeah yeah
that was a cool video guy turns on the tap puts a little like the
oh is that where the water that's where the water is controlled by people in robes yes or my i might
typey thing of the water nation. Oh, I don't remember from avatar. The last
airbender was I think the real water. I think it's milk and honey in flint.
That was a problem yeah. That was the in the Bible. They say the rivers flow
with milk and honey in Israel, I think, and it's like what how about water and
no wonder they are going to issue water yeah. You fucking spent three thousand
hundred eating drinking milk and honey. Where's the milk come from to the river?
The fuck is that
Is there some big cow just squirting into the top of a man? I mean that's that's
probably the closest thing you can get besides medicine to just a diarrhea
inducer milk and honey. I feel ever from a river yeah mixed yeah, yeah, that's
gross. Oh, it's a fracking thing. Wait, my fracking hate what you're talking
about.
This is so sick. She lights the water on fire.
Let's see his.
All right.
Whoa.
That's pretty cool.
She's going to, bro.
That's so fucking sick.
Yeah, the water in America is all fucked.
Yeah.
Yeah, there's like, that's like why we're-
That's why I have a sommelier.
It's like why everybody's like this here.
That's like why everybody- Have you guys seen-
Have you noticed that people in America, fat people look completely different from fat
people in other countries?
Oh, dude, fat people-
Even at the same weight.
like the Mediterranean look like Kings yeah it looks gorgeous oh my god like a
fat Italian guy like the way that everybody holds their weight everybody's
eyes are just fucked a fat Italian guy is just an average American yeah exactly
everybody goes bald at very young ages America it's gotta be the water it's
gotta be the water it's also the gravity's here different is different
because there's an under where there's an underworld cancer is like everybody in
America the only way you can die is cancer mm-hmm see only every other
country has cancer figured out yeah no cancer and for neighbors upstairs
completely no one has ever died of cancer up there yeah the food oh here's
an idea I was having this morning I was thinking about McDonald's and I was like
I love McDonald's but I'd never am like unless I'm like drunk I never want
McDonald's after like five o'clock so you need to have a like a McDinner menu
they do but it's like like like you can get like a steak I think hamburgers a
lunch meal. What about like a chopped sirloin at McDonald's? Yeah like
something like that. Okay like like gravy with mushrooms. Yeah. Over just like
big mac quarter pounder patties. Turkey dinner. Maybe a mac and cheese side. Yeah. You know. Or like a
big red velvet cake. And here's the other thing. They have those in other countries at
McDonald's. I know it's fucked. Like McDonald's in Italy? Yeah. Don't even
don't even think about it. That's the most. Don't even think about it. That's the most.
- Don't even think about it.
- It's the most divine cuisine.
- It's fine cuisine.
- It's divine cuisine.
- You don't even have to think about it.
- Don't even think about it.
- It's divine cuisine, that's what I said.
- But we need a McDonald's dinner menu
that they don't start serving,
you know what they should do at McDonald's?
They should close for one hour,
between four o'clock and five o'clock.
- Yeah, oh my God.
- Right, then they reopen.
- That, I mean, that's what it's like
everywhere in other countries?
- Every other country.
other McDonald's is like every store and restaurant does that right?
Mm-hmm.
In other countries?
They do it in some restaurants.
Oh yeah, but that's because they're mimicking.
But I just mean in general.
Like you can't.
Yeah, dinner, like a...
Like even I feel like it may be like in Europe a hardware store would close from like, yeah,
like four to six and then it's like the fancier tools.
Yeah, guys probably, well in Europe it probably has to do with they're all fucking addicted
to drugs.
Yeah, and then it's probably because they need to take naps too.
Yeah.
McDonald's and those.
I'm so I had to work two hours from twelve to four. I need a two hour nap. I
need a complete two hour nap and tomorrow I need a week-long vacation and I need
that every other week. Yeah and I need a twelve year old girlfriend. Really?
Yeah, you can buy a whole boar at the counter. A whole jamon? Wow. Cooked boar.
Holy. At the counter. I don't think that's true. Where? Spain. Spain. Cooked on a
spit? No. Cooked at McDonald's. Cooked on a McDonald's. Cooked on a McDonald's
grill on the roof. Okay, but yeah, the year these Europeans man they take
they're so lazy six months off. Yeah, it's up to what to braid your women's armpit
hair. Yeah. Yeah. My God, your arm don't even want to think about the body. I
want to see that. Yeah. What to braid your girlfriend's fucking leg hair. Yeah,
I want to break your legs. Yeah, it's like, maybe I just think I need to
adopt a you more. You're not an animal. It's like many women are so bohemian in
Europe it's like I see I see an entire I see kind of so much hair on their body
and yet a shaved or very shortly cropped head of hair yep mm-hmm I was just
thinking the same thing a very exactly the same closely cropped closely cropped
haircut buzzcut yeah I'm trying to see that kind of a I want to just experience
I want to even some Korean French Spanish Italian women your hair is long
in the wrong places yeah it's supposed to be long on top of the head.
You have a boy haircut, Isabella Rossellini.
You're supposed to have a little black tower.
Supposed to have long hair.
Emerging from your vagina and no hair anywhere else.
Yeah.
You know?
And instead you got a spider web butthole
and your fucking leg hair's insane.
You look like a carpet.
You're fucking, you're shaving a Jordan logo
into your calf hair over there in France.
Stop that.
Knock that shit off.
That's bullshit.
Get rid of the smell.
Yeah.
They go to the barber, women in France go to the barber just to get a fade up on their legs.
Yeah, that's true.
And their arms.
They like getting it so the ankle has no hair and then it fades up.
It fades up.
It fades up into just the most Sasquatchian woman.
Just disgusting, dude.
Yeah.
Women in Europe.
And I would hate seeing all that.
I don't like that.
Women here, they'll walk, they'll go to the mall, they'll walk through the perfume section
at the store and they'll get all these sample aromas sprayed on their wrist.
And I mean in Europe, these women are going out behind the mall, they're walking by the
dumpster, they're rubbing cardboard, banana peels.
That's right.
And they eat snails.
And the women who walk by the perfume at the mall, a lot of times here in America, the
good country, a lot of times they pass out because they haven't eaten all day like they're
supposed to.
Yeah.
Which is that women should not eat a single meal.
Most women don't walk by the perfume counter, they drive by it on their rover scooter.
What?
What is it called?
Rascal scooter.
Most women in America are driving around on a rascal scooter.
No, women in America are beautiful and they shouldn't eat a single meal.
They should eat one meal every other day and they should have no hair except for their
head.
Eyebrows, eyelashes.
No but and giant boobs.
No but at all, the giantest boobs of all time.
That's America.
And they should all wear that Spike TV as a thousand ways to die model.
France and Italy on the other hand, the women are cross-eyed, right?
They have a fucking, they have half of a, they have a torpedo sticking out of their head.
Yeah.
Right?
They have an eye patch.
They have a giant, a giant mustache, right?
They look like Ron Burgundy from fucking Anchorman.
Yeah.
Right?
But they're not nearly as funny.
Okay.
No, no.
And then you have all these, all these women walking around there and also, oh fuck, what's
going on?
There's a nuclear war in fucking Ukraine.
What am I going to do?
I'm going to show my hairy boobs of the world.
Yeah.
Exactly. I think that did work though. I haven't heard a thing about Ukraine in months.
No, that actually did work because all the Ukrainian and Russian soldiers saw us sort
of vomiting because of all the hair on the women that were completely showing their boobs.
Well, it makes sense to have that much hair in Russia because it's so damn cold there
because it's always snowing.
I don't care if it makes sense. Women's bodies are not supposed to make sense. Here's just
to please me.
That's a good point.
Women in Europe too, I mean, you'll see them riding around bicycles just pedaling there.
- It's a man's vehicle.
- Their heart's out.
It's like, well, what are you trying, you know you're riding, they don't even need to get
anywhere.
They're just trying to kind of cultivate a funk.
They're trying to get this sweat to beat up in their crisscross hairs.
- Luckily, most of the bicycles are only for guys.
- You know what the leading cause of death among female cyclists is in France is actually
their mustache hairs getting caught in the gears.
And then they do a complete front flip.
- Women are so sure I am the dark knight.
- These women cyclists in Europe, they're trying to look like a calm and placid morning
in the meadow with dew drops built up all over these blades of grass all over
their bodies. You know what everybody says, "Oh there's no mass shootings in
Europe." Yeah there is. Actually there's tons of mass shootings, but the
bullets get stopped by how thick the hair on women's bodies are, like as if
they have a Bible sitting in their front pocket. Yeah exactly.
Nobody can, everyone's wearing basically a bulletproof hair dust. It's literally Kevlar. Yeah. I heard they
harvest that to make Kevlar. Yeah it's basically like a spider web or a silkworm.
A French woman's hair basically has 1,000 little strains in it.
Yeah.
So like one normal American hair is equal to or like one French like one strand is one
normal American's hair.
Also they don't even walk.
They use their fleas like nails.
And they're all like drinking wine.
These hairy French women you'll be thinking you're having sex with one and you're freaking
coming out of your thing and and and the woman goes with you but you didn't even
put it in it's like oh my gosh I guess your lice were sucking my wiener the
whole time. I was completely stuck in your hair and your lice were a pleasure.
They have the Louvre. Yeah I Louvre to not go to Europe. Uh-huh yeah that's a really good
point. Yeah. Hey UK I will not be visiting you.
Okay. Yeah that's what I say when I see a French woman's hairy ass. Yeah yeah.
Yeah, they have Berlin Berlin. I'm going over there. I'm seeing the women. I'm
hurling mm-hmm because I have fucking disgusting they are you know and also a
lot of the ones in Germany a birdhine yep I'd rather I've never had to go there
I'd never had a worse time than going to fucking Germany and seeing a disgusting
see all these women look like sheep they look like complete and not to mention
they're they're stuck in a fucking pin right on the side of the road yeah they
like fucking sheep these women. They got a guy with a big cane poking them. Yeah and it's
like how the fuck am I supposed to cut these women look exactly like fucking sheep to me.
Yep. It's fucking bullshit. It's pretty gross. And now they're trying to get rid of Boris,
one of the last fucking cool ass guys in all of Europe. Coolest haircut in the world. Just
like one of the last true beasts of the East. And now he's fucking, they're trying to dead
that and I don't like it. He's the best of the West though isn't it because the East
is Asia. He's he's he was raised in China. Boris Johnson is from China. Yeah.
That's crazy. Yeah. Do you know the do you remember Far East movement like a G6?
Yeah. Oh, I'm getting moved from the first. Yeah. Yeah. Get that verse. I
forgot about that. Yeah. But you're basically shaving all their heads like
I'm like they're smoothing like eggs. Don't try coming up to me when I'm
ordering Gregg's.
*Humming*
Shaving all their heads. Is that what it was?
Shaving all their heads.
Make them smoother than eggs.
Don't come up to me when I'm ordering Gregg's.
That's fucking fire.
My name is Boris to the J
and I'd like to say
we have to
keep England
English today.
Yeah, I do remember that verse.
*Humming*
And then they cut it out like
retarded they cut out that his verse yeah like the like you can't find on Spotify
anymore no well yeah you can still find it there but it's blacked out didn't
they get rid of that song from Spotify the day that Ukraine yeah it was like
well they're like well the world is just this the world's change it's probably
this fault yeah yeah probably was I heard so funny I heard some horrible
news about Ukraine. What? Apparently a lot of the Ukrainian citizens and soldiers
are harming Russians. Wow. That's disgusting. No. Apparently weapons are
being used. Really? Yeah. I didn't know that. I heard that like yeah they're I
mean I don't want to tell tales out of school here. I heard they're seriously
that few may have died. I heard some horrible news about Ukraine. Yeah the
that country still fucking there. It's not a fucking parking lot by I heard
some I heard a horrible thing get rid of it. I heard a horrible thing what the
lines of the Selka are too long. Now I want I hope that Vladimir Putin
destroys Ukraine destroys all of Europe and just makes like a cool new bridge
between the Russia and the US and maybe we could have we can you what about a
big water slide? I mean looking at this sit this situation between Russia and
I think now more than ever is when I finally need to perfect Freddy Krueger's abilities
because I would love to haunt the dreams of every man, woman, and child who thinks it's
okay to stand against.
Vlad.
We were walking around.
Tale of two Vlads.
Yep.
When was it?
This is in July?
No.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Beginning of July right now.
Beginning of the month we were walking to like a train meet, me and a couple friends.
It is the beginning of the month.
We walked past.
middle-ish. There's that restaurant Veselka and there's like a person out
front like asking for donations for Ukraine which is like with like the day
that Biden passed that like 1 billion dollar like aid thing. Yeah. Ukraine.
1 billion vials of aids. Yeah. That's sent to Ukraine. That's what's gonna happen next.
But it's like the day that that happened and there's like somebody out there like
asking for like donations and like we just said like we didn't have cash then
and my friend Michael, you know, her,
she like just looked at her and just said,
I don't believe that exists.
I don't believe that the Ukraine exists.
- Nice. - Yeah.
- It's pretty good.
- Yep. - I guess that's a--
- Sounds like a you had to be there kind of thing.
- Yeah. - Fuck, I'm fucking hate myself
so much. - The ghost of Kiev.
- What if I killed myself in the middle of the show?
What if like in the like Budweiser style?
- That'd be shit, Budweiser?
- Budweiser, yeah.
- Budweiser style.
- What if I like just like added like one day,
I just like really tank something
so hard and I just you out of nowhere you see my mouth foam up and I'm just
sitting there I just I like a cyanide that I just pop and I'm like all right
this that's officially the worst joke I've done on the show wait I got you
that wasn't even I can't yeah we can blame her for that I can't hear you
Michael I can fix this pet well it's cuz I told that let me fix this thing Pat
let me fix this okay hmm the ghost of Kiev yeah yeah I'd like to shake that
that guy's hand by the neck pretty good. It sounds good, but it was like kind of
it wasn't good enough about that good. So it makes his seem better. They call
them the ghost because he wasn't real. I wish he was a ghost. Yep. I want to
wish he was wasn't that was debunked as a myth. The ghost of Kiev. Yeah, it was
debunking. I prefer to believe every I wasn't like it was like video game
footage or something. Yeah, yeah, it was modern was complete video game footage.
yeah yeah heroic goes to Kiev drops giant dragon turtle into lava by pressing
secret button the ghost of Kiev the sleeve move him around the entire circle
I'd like to shake his hand yeah by the neck by that balls it's just too easy to
be a political commentator okay it goes to Kiev shoots magic ball at fire
salamander and turns him into big dragon. Ghost of Kiev's stuck in a Super Bowl
running around the entire course and getting a million coins and he's a monkey
like at this point. Ghost of Kiev bouncing back and forth between two
paddles for a very long time. Ghost of Kiev clears entire line of Russian
soldiers goes to the team shoots apple it's at a
at slowpoke turns into slowbro in the river
that's right damn i wanna play pokemon snap now
i haven't played pokemon snap oh they made a new pokemon snap they did i forgot about that
a couple years ago for sure
no they didn't
they did my little cousin had it i gotta tell you this has got to be the most boring game i've ever fucking played
yeah pokemon snap is the gayest shit ever i mean no it's really i never played the original
out of all the pokemon games, it's the least cool pokemon game.
And that's really saying something.
Woah!
Oh my god, they did that again.
He's been through enough.
You're really piling on.
I know, that was a little too much, but to be fair, it was about Pokemon Snap.
He sucks.
You really love Pokemon Snap.
It's so good.
People talk about Pokemon Snap all the time.
I really never.
Pokemon Snap was one of those games where I think one time I went to a... was that GameCube
Nintendo 64. I think it was 64. Whichever one it was, I went to a hotel that had like
one of those like, it had like a Nintendo 64 that you could like pay to use and I
like begged my parents to use it for the one night and I played Pokemon Snap and
I was like this is the worst thing I've ever played in my life. You just weren't good at it.
It's not fun, you don't get to fight. It's not a fighting game. Am I crazy or did they do like a
Playboy Snap? Like a... They, no you're thinking of Leisure Suit Larry. I don't think so.
Oh, no, no, you're thinking of that you're thinking of that mission we went on. Oh, I'm thinking of the mission that we did in real life
It's a Playboy mansion. Yeah
Like bushes the Playboy rebrand it the last like four years has been so fun. I haven't
Yeah, basically they like do like
It's just become like a girl power magazine. Really? Yeah, but like my but like my grandpa probably still has a Playboy
Yeah, he's getting these articles. It's literally only the articles now. No, no, they they know
Brandon wants is to change the playboy into only the article he wants
Yeah, he wants to make it New York Times playboy. They're all losing all the boobs
Hustlers gonna be these days. It's gonna be just fucking it's so it's really funny
How long they how they're still still doing articles. Well, fuck. What's his name? The the Hugh Heff
- It was like a ultimate next level rapist.
- Oh yeah.
- It was so Bill Cosby used to hang out
at the Playboy Mansion all the time.
- He would, Bill Cosby would hang out there
and pretend to be a toilet.
- And now they get Kate Upton to have her
dress like an angel, and she's like,
"This is for Roe V. Wade."
- I would say anybody who wears a bathrobe
is probably has some issues with sexual consent.
- You need access to your naked body way too easily
as a way there's way less rapey comfortable clothes. You can be wearing
at your mansion. Yeah, that's a that's a huge red for example little
a curious George pajamas, which yeah even but see with the pajamas. You have to be
careful monkey because a lot of these pajamas to you'll see you'll see they'll
have the the buttons on the back to open the butt flap. Yeah, and that's also not
so good, but also you can't do much with your like just your butt. Yeah, you know
like you can do with your butt but like you can't seen so much you can't attack
a woman with your ass you'd be in the same way that Hugh Hefner and Bill Cosby
did with the front Hugh Hugh Hefner attacked a ton of women with his butt
those old man dinosaur farts he'd be sitting in there he'd be like well I'm
gonna eat chili again for dinner that's what he said the end of his life that's
what Hugh Hefner sounded like. All the pipes he would smoke that gave him malignant
tumors in his throat. He lived so long. He lived so long because of the tumors
actually had a symbiotic relationship with him. Yeah. And he'd sit there in his
robes and he'd say like, "Hot dogs again, oh boy!" Yeah. That was the tumors talking and they
wanted to put more carcinogens in the into his body. So he could blow farts in
girls faces. So he could blow farts but also the methane from the farts would go
into his body. He'd make them sign an NDA and as they... It's kind of like a circular...
like a... As they dot the I in their name, Cherry, with a heart, he would just...
he would already... they'd look up, they'd say, "Here you go," and he'd already be
blowing a fucking hot noxious fume. And they had dust on them. He'd like to put
baby powder on his butthole. So that it had... you'd see it. Yeah. And also he dyed it
green. It was completely green baby powder. You know how sometimes... You ever seen the videos of
him sitting in a hot tub yeah right well there's no way he was yeah he was
striking yeah you can't see his legs at all you guys know when sometimes you'll
fart you have to like wipe your ass mm-hmm he had when he farted they'd have
to wipe the walls yeah that's right yeah so the Playboy mansion was covered in
mahogany yeah that's how they would it wasn't that's the thing it was it was
very light would paint the entire mansion like the episode of Spongebob
job with where they paint Mr. Crabs house and he would basically paint the front of
his asshole and make a humongous bubble and it would pop yeah yeah.
That's how it happened. It's the truth. I really hope they have to a palpitating
playboy man. What do you think the playboy mansion? What do they do with it
now? What do you? I think they should actually turn that into housing. I
literally think they should turn that shit into affordable housing. Yeah, us
excuse away turning a mansion to affordable housing. A mansion is
expensive. You think it was somebody a family's going to live in there for
what a hundred dollars a month yeah, realistically guys that's not possible.
They should make it twenty percent affordable housing, because I think
that's the requirement and what does one like a few rooms yeah, a few rooms
of just like poor migrant workers, and everybody else is like people like
rich guys, who are like I'm going to fuck people in the yeah, rape
acolytes yeah, exactly looked up to this like Rick Moran. I was thinking of
famous guy I could think of. Rick Moranis, he actually got his jaw slid. I heard he got
his jaw slid too. For no reason. For absolutely no reason. And it's like, I don't know if it was for no reason.
Rick Moranis got his jaw slid for no reason. I witnessed Rick Moranis get his jaw, what
was the full thing? I witnessed, why did I just witness Rick Moranis get his jaw slid
for no reason? Rick Moranis jaw slid. That's legendary dude. That is so legendary to me.
legendary comedic actor too. He's in the five neat guys. Oh yeah. The SCTV sketch.
Yeah yeah with Eugene Levy. I don't know why that one gets me every time. It's
funny. It's a funny thing. Yeah. Eugene Levy, what a whiff of a kid. Yeah. Really
messed up. Yeah. Oh yeah. He could have been such a funny kid. There's nothing more
embarrassing to me than... Yeah, Stifler's dad. He had a funny kid and he had a great kid in a movie. I mean his dad...
he's had a lot of great kids in the movies.
Stifler, now that's a good kid.
And you know every day Eugene Levy sits there and says
I wish I could have had Stifler.
It really should have been Stiff's Creek.
And it's not, it's Shit's Creek.
Well you know the show
is called Shit's Creek.
I think that's
the number one
reason, you should,
when a person has a kid,
when a nepotism kid, they should never
be allowed to be anywhere near their parent in anything.
- Yeah. - Agree.
- Unless it's like-- - 'Cause that just makes it,
it's so embarrassing. - Unless it's like
Donald Trump and Donald Trump Jr.,
'cause The Apprentice was very funny to see him on there.
- And Sofia Coppola. - Yeah.
- Yeah.
- And-- - I guess I just mean that
they should, he should take his son out of his show.
- Harrison Ford and his son.
- 'Cause besides his son, that's a great show.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
If it weren't for, yeah. - Actually, I've never seen
Schitt's Creek, it's very popular.
It might be good. - I've seen a lot of it.
- It could be good. - It's not good.
you know it's really bad. Yeah, it's really not good. I've seen I've seen
all of it. You've seen all of it. I've seen every holy shit. Really? Yes, why
it's my family. Watch my family. Watch it in quarantine. Okay, that's beast.
Yeah, it's really bad. Who's the best character is Eugene? At least is he
putting up numbers on his? He's funny. I feel like I mean, he's like Chris
Elliot's probably the best. He's only funny. What's the what's the woman's
Catherine O'Hara. Yeah she's funny in that. She's great in everything.
Yeah exactly. They have an all-star cast and I have never watched,
except for that one boy, but I've never watched a single episode. There's a bunch of other
stinkers too. I think that they're probably,
Eugene and Catherine are kind of holding it down.
Chris Elliott's not good in that show. He's good, I don't know.
The show is just really annoying so it's hard to think anyone is good in it.
Fox, NBC, CBS, ABC not come to us yet.
- I know, yeah.
- I have a great idea for a show.
- Like can we just skip the-- - I have a lot of great ideas.
- Shit's Toilet.
- Can we just skip the whole like streaming bullshit
and we could do Shit's Toilet as a sequel?
- Shit's Toilet, and it's a toilet store.
- It's like what's the--
- And then in every episode somebody says,
"Hey, who farted?"
- What's the--
- What are a fart--
- What's the blackish sequel with the kids?
Shits Creek. No, they have a bunch of ish. Yeah, that's like white ish weirdish or
something. No, it's like we're weird teenagers or something. Teenish. I don't
remember. Blacker ish. It's not black. No, no.
Yeah, the sequel series, the sequel series to black is just blacker ish. It's
a candy store that they own. I don't think so. I don't think that's true.
that okay, well, there's a completely true. I heard that there's a spin off
the show is multiple spin off. Yeah, and one of them is black. One of them is
mixed ish. Okay, one of them is grown ish and then it says another potential
spin off named oldish. I'm thinking of never made it to air. I'm thinking of
grown ish, which is all I was thinking of blacker ish, which is the show. I'm
pitching. It's not you can't pitch black. It's a black owned candy store.
You would not be involved in that show. Nobody would want you all. I would be
white guy on the show the one white guy you'd be the clown the white guy that
they make fun of you really want to so racial divide yeah your show like that
by having a funny of a goofy ass white character uh-huh really bro well
nothing are gone on no every day I don't think that's okay why because it's gonna
be you and you're my friend and I don't want to see you just get eviscerated
it'll be like a like it'll be in good fun I don't think it would be but we need to
do a Schitt's Creek like like sequel shit called shit shitting shitting so it's a
it's a shitty it's a black crashing and Schitt's Creek yeah yeah shitting yeah
black on the candy store no we're not it's not called blacker ish the show is
called blacker ish though shitting no it's not the shitting would be like
would be Eugene Levy's other son.
He's like he's a long lost son and comes back.
And he kills the other son.
But not in a hate crime way.
Like Cain and Abel.
He's gay? Eugene Levy's son? I don't think so.
I thought he was pretending to be gay in the show.
But if you want one, hit me up.
Nah, I'm kidding though.
Check this out.
What are you doing?
What were you about to do?
I was going to show you something really cool.
I don't think you are.
Is he throating a banana?
Dude, there's this...
Do you guys know about this guy?
That was a big banana too.
about this this guy this guy boomish boom is professional counter strike player
boom no I've never heard of you recently he so he was neither either of you were
impressed I mean it's a banana in your mouth I could do that with a water
bottle I do it with that water bottle the so there's this guy boomish and he's
a he's a professional counter strike player he's really good and he's really
fat and ugly looks exactly like like Kim calm right and but he has always had this
hot-ass Russian wife like really hot Russian wife like way out of it I think
I've seen this guy yeah there's a picture of him on a boat with her yeah
like he's always been just like he just fucks this tent and then they just got a
divorce and in like all the divorce proceedings all this stuff came out
where like she was cheating on her and he he was cheating on her there's a he
released a picture of he put a banana in her asshole
post a picture of it. I'm trying to find a picture of Boomish. He was addicted to coke apparently and she
posted like all these videos of him like snorting coke and then also she some
somebody got in contact and asked and she in very broken English was like I
broke up with him because he is a complete lesbian and he loves sucking
cock. So I guess he was that's her way of saying that. Wow. I looked up Boomish and I
couldn't find anything other than Boomish in the magic pancake pan. That's
cool. I think it's technical. Technically, his name is Boomblah or something. Boomblah,
okay. He's a beast, though. Yeah, that sounds very sick. Boomblah4, okay. I'm on boomblasters.com
now. I don't know how the fuck I got here. Here at Boomblasters, we are dedicated to bringing you
superior sound quality products, including custom electric car horns.
Wow! Here's him with his wife. Whoa! His ex-wife now, I guess. Yeah, I've seen that.
Yeah, and then she this is a
programmable
Wireless car horn, so you can also get a little talking hamster, buddy. I don't know how the fuck I got here
But I think that this is kismet. I think that
Now that your car is is in like danger all the time of getting yeah
Broke like license plate stolen broke their window broken like antifa is constantly targeting your car we could get
This wireless for sound car horn when when does our?
Tote bag get here
Oh, I haven't even checked boom itch is a big fat lesbian and loves to suck cocks dreaming
And he's also a complete methadrone addict. He betrayed me more than once and hurt me very much. We are getting divorced
betrayed me for sake of a
F-slur friend who throws a blowjob and throws a light at me well take a blood test before you see him
Damn, and then this is he might be it might as a banana radioactive blood it check that out. That's crazy
Yeah, so if you do that Patrick, I'll be impressed if you put a banana in your asshole, which by the way
She's not really it's like right on the tip of the yeah, that's barely
Unless that's a plantain and we're seeing about half of it, then this is not that impressive. It would not be hard
I don't think no be very soft. It's banana
Get mashed up in there if you got it. You know if you got a gripper
Yeah, that thing's getting that thing's coming out like like when you like banana bread better definitely
definitely oh
That's gross. Oh my god. I wouldn't make banana bread out of that
I mean, it's like God's got a kitchen's filling the room with the smell wallets in the oven. Oh my god
My god, that's nasty god damn. Oh, and you wouldn't had drizzle anything over it. No, I would not drizzle any kind of okay
I got a I got a notification
Drizzling on pastries. Look he's slutty. I agree yesterday. No today at 1 in the morning that it shipped
Okay, tote bag. Yeah bag. That's a way. You sent me the picture of I couldn't find the picture of it
It's in the email. It's in the podcast email. So you guys are going on vacation. You guys excited? Yeah, I'm going to the Bay Area
I'm going to do some
Some skateboarding I think and he's gonna find Sasquatch in the great grand Sequoia trees. Yes, I am
yep actually I'm going to that area I'm going around there going to Berkeley
going to I'm going to join the pack that's awesome like little beef from the
back yeah that's sick I'm going to this my audition I've always thought of you
as kind of - - I'm - - as hell you're not - - it's yours we've had this
argument before have we so - are you kind of - yeah I still I think he's
I don't think you turning your hat weird is making you any more hyphy though.
Honestly.
It's LP.
I think that might be, you look exactly like LP right now.
You do.
Yeah.
You do look exactly like LP.
You look literally exactly like LP.
Yeah, you look like a complete LP, kind of knowledgeable rapper.
I'm splashing in gas and flashing my trash.
Bernie Sanders!
It's not.
Is that what he sounds like?
No, not at all.
Bernie Sanders and I are smoking crack!
He doesn't smoke crack.
I'm smoking crack rap!
I'm a fucking unicorn and I'm a dragon watching crazy porn.
I'm a fucking unicorn.
Hitler 2 will soon be born.
That kind of is right.
That is, yeah, that's exactly the thing.
And then I go down to the store and I bore with the floorboard door, buzz up with the
door, butter bore.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm a robot flying through space.
I'm a crazy bird with a laying egg.
That's pretty much exactly what he said.
I'm sitting on the biggest tallest chair.
Yep, sitting on the biggest chair in the entire world.
Yep, the-
With a super girl.
Yeah.
Yep.
And I'm gonna hurl.
Yeah.
And I'm a unicorn.
Hitler 2 will soon be born.
That's a fire line.
That is a really fire line.
Hitler 2 will soon be born.
That's like also-
I'm a motherfucking unicorn.
Hitler 2 will soon be born.
I think that should be, that should be the new Run the Jewels song they put in every
movie trailer. The CIA just moved my corn. He's hungry for corn. He made corn for dinner.
The CIA just moved my corn. And I'm having sex with a girl like porn. Wow. That's fire.
Yeah. I'm going to join the pack. I'm going to maybe do a song with Andre Nicotina. I'm
going to do... what else is in San Francisco? I'm going to go down a big hill. I'm going
I saw a video of the Golden Gate Bridge when I was a kid and they zoom in and Michelle
Tanner's face is there and the guy says "Lost out there and you're all alone!"
I don't know what kind of old man bullshit you're on.
I don't know what this is.
I guess nobody even cares where I'm going for vacation.
Where are you going for vacation?
I don't know, I guess nobody cares.
You've talked about your vacation a lot.
Where are you going?
Not worth bringing up.
I want to know now he's going to the beach. I actually don't know where you're
going. Yeah, I know you have literally only said I'm going to the beach. He
didn't tell us like where he's going on a mission. I think somebody gave you a
mission. I tell you where I'm from above. I think a Christlike figure gave Cameron
a mission the Congo really the Congo you for trying to find a big gorilla or
snake or something is that what that movies about which ones that's about
yeah Congress about gorillas it's about a bunch of them. I think well I only read
the book I don't know what the movie and then the book is about a bunch of
intelligent is not in a conga that's in South America yeah and John Voight plays
like a Cuban that movie is they're casting a movie is crazy yeah it's so
cubes in ice cubes in it fucking isn't that a remake though no no I thought
there was an old anaconda probably there's a movie about an old anaconda
I'm thinking of the song anaconda yeah but who else there's a bunch of people
in that. There's a kid in my art class in high school who said like, "Whatever you
do, do not look up the Nicki Minaj Anaconda video." Really? I watched it when it
first came out. Well I didn't know there were four Anaconda movies. I thought
there were only two. Rap videos used to be so much closer to porn though.
There used to be so many rap videos that were actually like naked women, like
completely naked. Wasn't there like... Tip drill. Yeah, wasn't there a few
like videos that were like look at the go online to see the answer version yeah
yeah they do they do the sucker free like after dark thing on MTV - well they would
never show them on that yeah and then they'd be like if you want the uncensored
version go to Nelly's website yeah yeah and you go on there and he's swiping the
swipe it for your butthole legendary moment completely legendary though
insanely do you know about that I wasn't listening listen he swiped a credit card
through a woman's butthole. Who did? Nelly. That's cool. Yeah. So cool.
The Saint Lunatics. I need a tip. Saint Lunatics, unlockable characters in NBA Street Volume 2.
Yeah. They need to bring back the Def Jam fighting game. Yeah. They need to bring back just unlockable
characters like that in games. I think that, I think they should take the technology that
everyone's using to make AI pictures of like, Garfield goes to hell or whatever,
and they need to put it to work so that you can auto-generate and you can type in a thing and
and it will make a fighting game with all the characters
from that thing. - That's such a good idea.
- Yeah. - That's kind of like Mugen.
- Yeah, but it's AI.
'Cause Mugen is made by like 12 year old kids.
And that's basically slave labor
and how to support shit like that.
I think we should enslave robots and computers instead.
- Mugen's not made by slave labor.
- Yeah, it is.
- Same with Roblox.
- Yeah.
- Really?
- Complete slaves on the back end.
- That's pretty cool.
- The slaves have to move the characters on the screen.
- Yeah, they--
- Mugen was annoying though,
'cause if you wanted to add a character,
you had to go in and like type in the fucking code and everything. Yeah, it's
very annoying. That's why I'm saying we need to have an AI version. Yeah.
That goes on PlayStation. That's why you always download a preloaded version of Mujin. Yeah, but it should also... but that's the thing about Mujin.
Like I don't want it to be like Spongebob versus Dr. Phil or
whatever. I want it to be like, yeah, like I type in like, I type in Anaconda and
it's every actor from Anaconda. Yeah. And there's no... and the Anaconda is
there to also people. I know yeah, exactly anything yeah, I type in like my friend,
my funny ass friend group yeah, and I get to control them and make them fight each
other yeah, and I could do a little tournaments and make myself the winner.
That'd be cool yeah, what if you typed in well here's okay, here's a horror movie
pitch okay, okay, so that this is a horror movie in a world where that game
exists rather watch a horror movie that game already exists. Okay, that game
exists. I'm ready for the pitch you type in you type into the thing into the
thing to make a new game people in my house right now and there you see the
roster load up it's like you your mom your dad your brother your sister the
killer attacker oh my god his name is the killer attacker well it could be
anything no I think I see a killer versus when you know it says like the
killer yeah yeah or like or maybe you started the enshrouded murder you play
one in one game mom versus dad you a new challenger has appeared just stronger
then yeah a new challenger and then you're yeah and then one by one you see
across the roster mom character locked dad yeah
director a lot the only one that's unlocked aborted brother and then you
know aborted brother and he kills both your dad secret family dad's secret oh
my god yeah it'll tie family it's - yeah dad is in the middle yeah it's like it's
like an M bison yeah yeah damn yeah that'd be so sick we should make a
fighting game I'm trying to I've been learning about making textures yeah yeah
I tried to get in I made a I'm in a college me really are it sucks so I have
so many like half finished unit only thing so bad yeah it's all just so hard
it's all dogshit it's all like it all programming is is like watching YouTube
videos and about specific stuff that you need to do.
- Yeah.
- And then six months later,
when you want to work on it again,
you just completely forgot it.
- Exactly. Nothing, I mean,
you can learn like actual programming,
but nothing, no interesting programming
is something you ever have to do.
- Definitely.
- Yeah.
- Like you're not like creating new things or anything.
It's all you Google, like how to make a guy
punch another guy.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Yeah.
- Made a Red Sox fitted hat in a skater XL.
- Hell yeah.
- He saw me do that yesterday.
- How did she get into like Blender?
- I don't, I think I'm just gonna stay with textures now.
- Okay, so you're making like little, okay.
- I'm making new shirts.
- I wanna see you model.
I wanna see you model bikinis.
- I don't, there's a bunch of tutorials on here
that I have been looking at, but I don't know.
- Tutorials on your computer?
- My goal is to fully make an Osiris D3 mesh.
- Yeah, you should probably learn Blender or something.
- That's your biggest goal in life?
not my biggest goal in life but with this. What's your biggest goal in your entire
life? Become God. Probably settle down have a couple kids and then just die
very peacefully. Okay now your girlfriend stopped listening now what's your real
biggest goal? Real goal? Yeah. Settle down, get a mini bike. Yes. A little pocket
rocket. Oh my god. Drive it around in a big loop-de-loop. It's fucking awesome.
- Like go up, go down?
- No, like Bob Burnquist mega ramp in his backyard.
Like I take a little dirt bike down.
Actually, I think maybe my life goal is do the mega ramp.
- Do the mega ramp?
- Yeah, do the Bob Burnquist mega ramp.
- It's big, dude.
- It's fucking crazy.
Bob Burnquist is like the craziest--
- He just wakes up and does that?
- Yeah.
He's like the--
- He just drinks a cup of coffee, does a mega ramp?
- It's insane that he's able to do that.
him and like there's like probably like 10 or 12 guys.
Didn't a little kid do it?
Yeah, I think his name was...
I don't remember.
Maximum Airy.
Have you ever heard of Burberry Airy?
No.
He's this like really fucking shitty like Instagram skater.
He has like his big thing is that he'll skate and those like you know those Yeezy foam like
slippers or like the sandals.
The foam like through boosts or whatever the fuck they're called.
Yeah.
like skating those and big like Liberty Spikes and shit he looks like a fucking idiot.
He looks like a creative character or created character in like a Tony Hawk game.
I mean he seems like a creative character.
Yeah.
Based on his fashion choices.
There's this video of Burberryary where he's on Instagram live and somebody is like who
inspires you like blah blah blah or like you're such an inspiration to me.
He's like honestly do not look up to me.
Do not look up to me because I'm a bitch bro.
I'm a bitch.
Deadass.
I'm a fucking cocksucker literally that's how I am as well yeah a lot of people we
know we have a pretty young least skewed audience that goes into the younger years
and I just want you guys to know like I'm a fucking piece of shit and you
should not even look up you should look up to me I don't if anybody ever looked
up to me I think you should you should literally hurt guys if people are
listening and they don't want to look up to Patrick or Caleb you could look up to
me I'm gonna be opening a factory and I'm gonna need a lot of fans fans to get
Daily autograph
You had it word for word wow that's impressive
You should become a guy like that yeah, I think I could you think I could you do a full rebrand
What do you guys think will look like?
Yeah, dude, I told you I really want to do that to my hair
Stand up though, I would like to make a hair on my head stand up. Yeah, like the guy from static
This is like a Wayne's dad
The video made by hype beasts. It's the title is Burberry. Ari wants you to hate him. Whoa. Wow, you guys know giant afro
Yeah, you could do it. I think you guys know what you're guys know Wayne static. Yeah, it did die touching a microphone and it electrocuted
He died from drugs
but
He died and he and the and the
Maybe I said this before but it's like the band the rest of the band did like a reunion tour
uh-huh and like they like played his vocals over the like through the over through like the PA or whatever and
In they had a an animatronic skeleton like as the vocalist
- That's so fucking sick.
- That's fucking awesome.
- It's like the coolest thing.
So I would say, yeah, if any of us die,
- Live show with our bones there.
- Yeah, live show with an animatronic skeleton.
- Yeah.
- It's truly the coolest thing.
Our real bones, animatronic rebranded.
- I could easily,
one year I could be one of the best skaters in America.
- No, no, just dressing like that.
- Nope, I'm gonna be a better skater.
- All right.
- I had a dream that I was a skater last night.
- Yeah?
- Or I was skateboarding.
- It's fun, isn't it?
- I was skateboarding around a town that I invented
and it was actually insanely cool.
that's literally I have so many I did wake up and I was like oh I guess that's
kind of the fun part of skateboarding you can skate around yeah yeah I never
thought oh yeah I was just kind of skating around dude this skeleton so
sick can we just get three skeletons that we play our voices through we
should like that oh my god that's sick isn't that so I'm gonna do to my hair
it's yeah skeletons talking mm-hmm you know a new show about just three
skeletons I like skeletons me too I've never I don't think I've ever seen a
real human bone I have where that was like a museum I saw I saw a pile of bones
in the woods and they had ain't tell anybody we definitely talked about it
before they had that uh they had that um exhibit where at the museum where they
had a bunch of preserved human body oh yeah and they were like all like they're
like slaves and shit yeah yeah I saw that as a kid in it yeah I freaked me
I think I saw cat bones in the woods. I remember seeing it was in a bucket and
it was like a dead like wet bones. Wait do x-rays count? I don't think so. I saw so
many x-rays. I also saw that exhibit but it was I saw it back to back and one day I saw
that and the Dead Sea Scrolls back to back. Damn that's so cool. I saw an
exhibit or I was part of an exhibit. Really? There was a Penn and Teller had a
thing at the Museum of Science and you could put your head in it in this like
thing and it made your head look like it was floating. Do you remember the
electricity room at the Museum of Science? You met Penn and Teller? I saw I met a video of them.
Oh okay. I used to be so... It was like a thing where you just wait in line for a long time
and then your uncle takes a picture of you. I would do anything to meet Penn and Teller.
I wish I... I wonder if I still have that picture. I gotta ask my mom if my uncle
ever sent that to her. Do you think I could make Teller laugh? I think that you could make
Teller freaking talk. Do you think if he started, if I was on that show Fool Us with Penn and
Teller, I would walk into the audience and I would start tickling him so hard just to
see if he makes a sound. Yeah. Just fucking destroying him with my fingers. Yeah. Just,
yeah. I'd walk up to him with a false pretense. I'd walk up to him and I'd be like, "There's
nothing in my hands. There's nothing in my hands except your rib cage and the inside of
your legs I have to there's something horrible before you go alright so here's
the here's the trick yeah you go on stage also that is technically pen and teller
you go on stage you say hey before I start anything I just want to let you
know I have already fucked up my trick yeah you go on stage with a big metal
a cage and the door is open and you say, I think my tickle monster got loose.
That's right yeah, that's good and you say don't look down because he hates
when you look down everybody close their eyes is the only way to defeat the
tickle monster yeah and then teller he's going to be terrified to be shaking,
but he'll slowly kind of close his eyelids and then you pop up from behind
and that's how you get away with it too, because otherwise you're going to jail,
but they can't arrest a tickle monster and also as soon as he opens his eyes,
you start tickling yeah. What the hell did tickle much? I saw it right yeah,
just ran away. He just ran, he scurried that way, I saw his red tail. I have
a trick that I could pitch. What? Do you guys think that I could fool for
a pen and tell her with this? Yeah. Yeah, I would be like I'd have a deck
of cards. That's a classic magical mainstay. And every card is their card.
And I'd say, I'd say the first card on this deck will be an ace.
I draw it and it's an ace. Oh my God. And I think they could even shuffle
it beforehand. Whoa! That'd be sick. They could shuffle it as many times,
they could go through and here you know what that how do you do it? Well, so
actually here's what it is. I'd have a deck of cards sealed deck of cards.
They they open it up. I have them open it up. I say go through the deck, take
out all the aces, take all the aces, burn them. You could burn you could eat
them, do whatever I don't care and then they hand it back to me and I say the
first card I draw will be an ace and I draw it. It's an ace. How do you do it?
maybe I'd like move behind my back really fast. Yeah. Oh yeah. I've got
the ultimate, this is the ultimate show here. Okay. So it's Fool Us Penn and
Teller but okay like in the same vein but it's called Make Us Laugh. Okay. And the
hosts Teller, Silent Bob and Harpo Marks. That'd be brutal. What an audience.
and Charlie Chaplin if you can get him yeah and then the audience behind them
is the writers and producers of SNL during an audition.
Oh yeah and they're not rough yeah oh my god that's right I know from experience
and also just because that's not that many people just a bunch of fucking
deaf people yeah just fucking thousands of deaf people yeah and
blind and deaf and blind and a couple of just a
couple of dead people and a few babies and it's hosted by Nick Cannon. No babies
These are way too easy, okay, not baby probably the easiest for us to make
us
yeah, like two or three horses and maybe a giraffe like a yeah, no, no, no,
that's way too easy, maybe a snail or bug yeah type
animal yeah, something with no vocal cords fish a fish yeah, good, that'd be
another one of the audience members, but then you got a clown fish because
people might work at it. But then you go out there and you tell me it's an easy
show, though you got there. You tell the aristocrats it's fucking over yep funny
of all time you hear the soon as you hear Harpo's horn honk yeah it's over
start doing Bill Hicks stuff - you know it's all just a ride it's actually just
bullshit out here shit is stupid if you do like real comedy like that work and
if you work in comedy kill yourself dude listen Bill Hicks was so funny you can
even make a fish laugh absolutely we were watching I think the other day we
You're watching old Sam Kinison bits?
- Yep.
- How the fuck?
What?
I mean, I guess when you have nothing but TV,
that's probably one of the funniest things in the world.
- He used to do cool shit, man.
He'd yell. - Have you seen?
Dude, have you seen his, when he hosted SNL?
- Uh-uh.
- It's so sick.
- What's he do?
- He goes out on stage, they're playing,
and then they're not stopping playing,
and he kinda looks at them and gives them a shrug,
and then they point to a guitar
that they just have on stage and you start soloing wall and then he goes in
the like these bits like
you should
which shows you know you know when this will win this comes out
i think the show our brooklyn show will be next week
and so
by some tickets
swagger dot com slash shows it'll be a little bit like world army can buy
tickets to the website.
I can't tell you the name of the address of the venue, the day of, unless you already
know it.
What?
That doesn't matter.
I think that's how they do their tickets.
That's not important information.
That is pretty important.
Yeah, they will find that out when they buy a ticket.
It says it on their website.
If anyone complains about any of these fucking tickets, I'll kill you.
And we have Portland and Seattle on there too that will be in a few weeks I guess.
I think.
I'm not doing the day math.
And then we have shirts too.
Slash shop for the shirts.
buy tickets for the Life World show because it's going to be very fun. Two
shows, fifth and sixth. We don't know who's on the complete bill yet but once
you know we'll know.
Pat, you're killing it with these announcements.
[LAUGHTER]