You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content!
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately!
[Laughter]
I'm recording. Wait, let's do the-
Wait, we got a backdrop here, so-
You're wearing wireless headphones, Patrick, and you've got a hat on.
Boy, it looks like he's- with that hat and those headphones, he looks like a steampunk train conductor.
Alright, Pat, I think you said- you said no or something.
I said I don't.
You don't? Okay. Yeah, you look like Criss Angel. No, wait. Don't say anything.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, Ruth's Criss Angel.
[laughs]
Yeah.
Fucking fat magic man.
This guy looks like Christmas Cookies Angel.
Yeah.
[laughs]
Yeah, Crispy Chicken Angel.
Chips Angel.
Okay.
[laughs]
Chips Angel.
I'm gonna make these chips disappear.
Yeah.
Turn around.
[laughs]
This guy's looking like Chip's angel food cake.
I made them disappear in my mouth.
The funniest part about Criss Angel is that he's got a speech impediment.
His accent is so good.
He has a lisp. I always said he's just a New York accent, but there's something wrong with his tongue.
He has a big tongue.
He does?
Yeah. I'm gonna make his tongue disappear.
Yeah, in your ass.
Yeah, in your butt.
Having sex with him would be scary, because remember that one...
that one I made the condom disappear yeah you're really risking having a kid if
you have sex with any magician ever right yeah they gotta make everything
disappear the whole time it's fun nothing in my condom nothing in my condom
turning it inside out times yeah man he's gonna make a dove crawl out of your
pussy after you're done. Yeah, he's pulling a bunch of maxi pads tied
together out of your vagina. Oh fuck, I'm worried that the homeless women on my
street are trying to fuck me. Yeah? Yeah, every time I walk by them they just give
me, yeah again, they're trying, yeah they want to double dip. It was so good the
first time. They just, I walk down the street and they give me eyes. There's
like four of them they look exactly the same maybe they're evil sisters yeah ooh
ooh it's like the fucking the ladies from my street
ocarina of time the two witches except it's four of them yeah oh yeah maybe
you're just dizzy when you're walking there and there's only one of them no I
I don't get dizzy, I actually--
I don't get dizzy, I get even.
(laughing)
I do, dude.
I can't be spun.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't get it, I don't even,
it doesn't phase me, I'm unfazeable in that way.
It's kind of awesome.
It's one of my many abilities that I have.
You have at tops one ability.
I have two abilities, that and credit card debt.
Yeah, that's an ability.
And those are my two abilities.
And I unlocked it about eight months ago.
It's been a great ability so far.
What are you guys drinking?
I got water.
I got coffee and water.
I'm back to drinking and smoking alcohol and...
I might smoke alcohol again.
Let me see how many days I have.
I made it two weeks.
That was all I needed.
Pat's gonna do way better than you, Caleb.
I literally said I was doing it for two weeks and I made it two weeks.
I don't know if I'm gonna do better than you.
He will not.
I'm at six and a half days.
I mean that's pretty--
- It's tough man, it's just so fucking boring.
- Right, yeah, I don't know what to like--
- I thought that a TV would help me.
I thought that I got a TV and put it in my bedroom,
I was like this is how I will stop drinking and smoking.
And then I just sit in front and watch basketball
on the front of my bed.
- You don't need a beer to watch sports.
- I want a fat rolled one dude,
I don't want to smoke a Scooby snack.
You know?
[Burps]
What are you burping on?
Oh! Oh!
Yeah, burp check.
What are you burping on?
I went to the dentist
a few days ago.
And...
The dentist was like...
It was just for like a
teeth cleaning and after he cleaned my teeth he was just talking about like
like he was like talking about how he was really excited because there was a new toothpaste drop
he was like yeah they just came out with this new toothpaste you have to check this out dude
and then he was telling and then he was like and then he was like and he was like and i'm
gonna give you some of this waxed floss i'm really pissed off because the company discontinued my
favorite kind of floss but i've been in contact with them and i can tell you i think they're
they're gonna bring it back. I guess you I mean... That's what you do as a dentist.
Like if you're a human you can really only be interested in one thing. Yeah. You
know like if you're gonna do it well like Michael Jordan it was basketball
this guy it's... I guess he does just keep... do you think there's like a
website there's like there's like a like a... Tom's of Maine. It's like yeah
no it was just it was I've been thinking about it so much just like of course
that's what a dentist would do. They would keep track of all their, like the new drops.
Dentist that's like a Richard Scarry job. It's like one of the base 15 jobs that my
brain understands as a job. Yeah, that's one of the jobs that animals can do. Yeah,
exactly. Dentist, construction worker. A donkey could clean your teeth. Yeah, he could. I'd
let a donkey touch my mouth. You would? What other animals would you let touch your mouth?
Yeah, let's go through them.
Where do you draw the line?
Probably...
How inhuman can we get?
Salamander.
No.
Alligator.
What?
You'd let a donkey touch your teeth but not a salamander?
I would not let a reptile touch my teeth.
Why do you...
Why not?
Why would you not let a reptile in your mouth?
Uh, scales.
Salamanders don't have scales.
You think it'll give you scales?
Yeah, it'll give me scales.
Also, salamanders aren't reptiles.
I don't want anything sticky on my teeth.
Reptiles aren't sticky.
And they have sticky...
Except candy.
What about Skittles?
I owned a gecko.
except candy I own the gecko I owned a gecko I know he climbs up a glass no he
does why do you know him anymore yeah he died yeah yeah I I used to own various
reptiles and bugs would you let a bottom you had a bug
Yeah, I had a pet bug on a tiny dental floss leash, and I'd walk him around the neighborhood.
I had to clean up after him.
Patrick, would you let a bug touch your mouth?
I would not let a bug touch my mouth.
What if it was the more...
What if... okay.
If it was like a... if it was a gorilla dressed up like a dentist.
You would notice.
I don't think I'd notice.
I don't think... I think gorillas' hands are too big to be a dentist.
He'd end up just like...
Yeah, if you...
You'd choke on his fingers.
dentist I need a dentist with tiny ass hands.
- So I'm so confused why you wouldn't,
why would you not let--
- No, just a person, just a person.
Like if it's a dentist, he's gotta--
- Got a small mouth?
- I don't want someone's fuckin' hot dog fingers
in my mouth, you know?
- 'Cause that's what dentists do,
they stick their whole hand in your mouth.
They kinda do.
- They kinda do.
(gagging)
- My dentist does, yeah.
- I think you guys have freaky dentists who are into stuff.
- Well I actually do go to a freaky dentist.
The last, second to last dentist I went to left the, you know the sucker thing?
Like the thing that dries your mouth out?
Patrick keeps going to different dentists and they keep just looking at him and going
"Ugh!" and just running out of the place.
Yeah. No, this dude, so he left the sucker thing in my mouth for like 30 minutes and I was like,
"Oh, he must be going to the bathroom or something." And then he comes back in and he-
30 minutes?
Yeah, like 30 minutes.
And you survived.
I'm sitting there just like
and he's like
he comes back in and
He fucking is with somebody else. I'm like, I think I was like 15
he's no I was 14, so he comes back in with somebody else and
he is like
It's someone from his church and he's giving them a cassette tape of his wife's organ music
So he was gone for like 30 minutes because someone texted him and is like hey
I'm here and then he came in he's like oh you're gonna you're gonna love it you're
gonna love it track three she does this cover of fucking this song it's amazing
let me get this clear were you strapped to the chair yeah why didn't you do I
didn't you just take it out of your mouth I don't I didn't know what he was
gonna be back I thought if I took it out that he came back he would you would flip
out I'm 14 I was 14 I don't wanna look like I what if he's good like weird about
his tools you know. You should turn it on him. You don't touch your uncle's tools in the shed.
Yeah you do. I would touch my uncle's tools if he put them in my mouth and left them there for
30 minutes. Yeah. It's different. It's different. Yeah your uncle put his tool in your mouth.
That's true. When I was in high school, I um, when I was having like really bad sleep problems and I
couldn't sleep, I fell asleep at the orthodontist in the in the chair and and I yeah I got like I
I kept waking up, I kept falling asleep and waking up just like from the sensation of
someone putting hands in my mouth.
That was probably one of the most real life nightmare experiences I've ever had.
I wish I could sleep with a dentist.
No dude, just imagine waking up because somebody is reaching into your mouth.
That's probably like the worst experience you can have.
That's a jackass prank.
I would just pretend that I'm eating a big hoagie.
You can't pretend when you're asleep, it's not possible.
You can pretend in your sleep.
- The imagination can either dream or play pretend.
You can't do both.
Exactly.
- That's right, Patrick has no answer to that.
I was taking a jewel hit.
- Have you guys ever tried to do astral projection?
- Yeah.
- You have?
- Yeah, I know Cameron has.
- Yeah, I tried to in high school.
- I know fucking Cameron has.
- Yeah, and when I was in high school I used to,
I got obsessed with it because I heard Sinbad talk about it on the podcast.
He was like, "Yo, I used to be astral projecting all the time."
He said that he used to do it all the time and that he like one time traveled to China
while he was astral projecting.
And he was like, "But I don't play that voodoo shit anymore."
Anymore?
Yeah.
That's dangerous, dude.
But I was like, "I'm young.
I have nothing to live for.
I want to go to China."
So I would try every night, I would...
- How does it even work?
- Yeah, no, yeah, that's like a lucid--
It doesn't.
- Yeah, what do you, right.
- You become a ghost.
So what I, but his advice, his technique,
is that he would sit on his bed
and then like almost fall asleep
and then right before he fell asleep,
he would reach out at like something
that he'd placed on his bed, like a rock,
and then he would leave his body
and then he would go to China.
(laughing)
- He had to get on a plane, he had to go to the airport.
- Yeah, you can't float.
- No, he fell asleep.
- You just have to wait.
- Also, everybody can see you.
- Yeah, right.
- Yeah, and you're fully clothed.
But I just wanted to, I don't know, go to the WBA.
- I would try to lucid dream and never wore,
I could never do it.
One time I got sleep paralysis at school
'cause I fell asleep after a test
and then I could hear people being like,
"Wake up," but I couldn't move at my desk.
Oh my god.
Damn.
That sucks dude.
Yeah, dude.
Evil.
I tried to do lucid dreaming because of something Ray Romano said.
What'd he say?
Ray Romano, Ray Romano's a lucid dream guy.
I watched an interview.
I'm sensing a trend between you guys' experiences.
Yeah.
I watched, it was a Pete Holmes interview on the Pete Holmes show of Ray Romano.
There are worlds beyond our comprehension.
I kinda just astral project to get away from my freaking wife.
That fucking rocks dude.
What is up with comedians being completely insane?
Yeah, who would know?
Who would have thought?
Yeah.
When I was a...
I got really into lucid dreaming.
I did it a lot when I was growing up.
And I got into it when I...
I have to have said this before, but I got into it when I was staying with my cousins
in California.
And one of my cousins picked up this girl at a gas station and then brought her back to
the house.
I was like 14 and I was like, "Damn, she's so hot."
And then I took a nap and while I was napping,
I started lucid dreaming and I was like,
"Oh my God, the possibilities are endless.
"I can do whatever I want.
"Let me just imagine getting a blow job from that girl."
(laughing)
And then I woke up just covered in my own cum
and I've been trying to do that ever since.
I've been trying to get back there.
It was amazing, dude.
It was like Minecraft.
(laughing)
- It was sick.
- I gotta, I gotta figure out how to do this.
- I feel like I should apologize to her.
(laughing)
I'm sorry, gas station lady, if you're listening.
- You can do that in Minecraft,
but the only other creatures in Minecraft
are like cows and pigs and stuff, so nobody does it.
- Right.
- Nobody has sex, nobody has--
- Unless you're on an MP server.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, Patrick goes on an MP server,
minors and
uh... no files
you know i was a bit of a little bit of just said that you thought that up so
bad on those good miners and i'll tell you what i would have said that i had
your pedophile or something no miners and pedophiles you know what a minor
insurgency and it's like jailbreak on
on the head like absolutely there's a lot there's miners and there's pedophiles
and i have to play well right now i get it
now you make that be a good role play server on gmail
yet we should make that yeah
I'm gonna get in touch with Gabriel.
No, because everyone who plays Gmod is either 12 years old or 40.
You can't, that would be too real.
I guess the entire thing is Miners vs. Penoply.
You would just open up a world of like...
You would just open up a very toxic community.
No, I think it would actually be really friendly and positive to Miners.
It would be great for the kids.
Alright, before we get this started, let's have a good game, boys.
You have referees.
Yeah, we need to make sure that everybody on both teams recognizes that they are valid and
Just like very like positive. I'm taking a knee on the pedophile side during the national anthem at the beginning of the game
Sometimes you got to take a stand dude. Yeah
Yeah, they sing the pedophile anthem at the beginning of the game, and I don't support that kind of thing
Yeah, it's Gary Glitter rock and roll part two
It's just them going "da-na-na-na, hey!"
No, it's that song that's like "I love little girls, they make me feel so good."
Oh, Oingo Boingo?
That's the same guy who wrote the Simpsons theme song.
What a poorly aged...
Yeah, I know.
Really?
Yeah.
That's Danny Hoffman.
I knew Caleb didn't know that.
I knew Cameron knew that, though.
You didn't know I knew that?
I didn't know that until like a week ago.
You two are Simpsons heads.
Huh?
You guys are a couple of...
No, I only just started watching the Simpsons like a month ago.
I was a big Oinko Boinko fan in high school.
That makes like a lot of sense.
Yeah.
That's yeah, I would have expected that.
Oinko Boinko is what you called breastfeeding your mom.
He breastfeeds his mom.
Oinko Boinko fan.
His mom drinks his milk.
I breastfeed my mom?
Yeah, you, hold on, wait, hold on, let me think about this.
Yes, you would.
Yeah, yeah, you would breastfeed your mom
with your big juicy tits.
Did somebody just shoot a gun outside of your house?
Yeah, I don't know what that was.
I didn't hear it.
Alright, well, it must have been nothing.
Don't hear any screams or anything.
Hold up, hold up.
Hold up, yeah, go check.
I heard a voice.
It's 16 minutes in.
Heard a voice.
A voice?
He heard a voice.
What?
I think he's astral projecting right now, dude.
Yeah, you're astral projecting into his house to scare him.
Yo, it's Sinbad, he heard us.
He shows up, knock on the door, "Hey man, what?"
I heard you were talking shit about astral projection.
Knock on the door. Hey man. I heard you were talking shit about astral projection
Listen I had to pick the voodoo sticks back up
What
All right, we'll just keep it in that wasn't too long
That was crazy yeah, I was like a little like you kill the guy. I think it's a ghost
I think it's haunted sin bad dude. Yeah, it's a very old building
Do you guys, what percentage of you believes in a ghost?
None. Zero percent. Okay, this is, you asked me right at a time. I was thinking last night
I was reminded, I was hanging out with my friend and I was reminded of the most haunted experience I've ever had in my life
Which definitely, I don't think it was a ghost, but it felt like one time I was walking home
It was on New Year's, New Year's Eve, right before New Year's and I was walking
from my friend's house to my house with like a bunch of friends and we kind of were just like walking around my hometown and
We're like, oh, let's go on this street like that. We haven't walked on before like let's just see what's up here
And we were walking and like Elm Street. Yeah
And we saw this big haunted house and we went in and bats attacked us
We're just walking down this Wow and like
There was like just a bunch of like train sounds over and over but the train tracks were like further across
Town and then like a bunch of the houses the front doors were just like a little bit ajar
like
It was like like truly like the most terrifying thing I've ever experienced
I'm sure that it was just like we all just got really scared for no reason
But you heard a ghost train we heard ghost trains dude and the doors were all open and you didn't go in
No, it's people's houses.
You know, it seems like it wasn't people.
And then we were all just noticing the doors were all open.
Yeah, it seems like it was ghosts.
And then there was just a really old lady in a wheelchair sitting on the sidewalk all alone at the end of the street.
Did you wheel her home at least?
That's her house.
And then so we were very scared by that and I realized that's probably why, that was probably, you know, the simulation glitching out.
And that's why 2020 is like this now.
Dude, yeah.
Because that was right before 2020.
Hey, thanks a lot, Kim. You gave us Carole Baskin.
Yeah, Kim.
Yeah, thanks a lot.
That's what I was thinking about last night.
Kim, Kimrin.
But no, I don't believe in ghosts.
Your name's Kim.
Kimrin.
Kimrin?
Shut up.
Yeah, shut up.
Thanks a lot, Kimrin.
I don't believe in ghosts,
but one time I was at People's Republic in Cambridge
with Tom, Jesse, and Abby.
And Jesse is way into ghosts,
and she kept talking about it.
And then we went outside and smoked a cigarette,
left Tom and Abby inside.
And then we walked back in,
and they were about to vomit.
and like looked, their eyes were like completely dilated and we were like,
what happened? And they said, as soon as we walked out of the door,
a glass moved from one end of the table to the other.
And we thought that we thought we were like, you're fucking with us.
And they maintained to this day that that's what happened.
I think it changed Tom's life. Yeah. I really think he was like,
I can't do comedy. I have to go be a doctor now. Yeah.
I honestly think that's when it all shifted for him. That's when he was like,
I have to just be like a normal guy.
- Oh my God.
- I have to check and make sure people are dead
so they won't come back to life.
(laughing)
- I have to be the guy that confirms
whether or not someone's dead.
- Yeah, my mom believes not in ghosts,
but in like angels that you can see.
- Yes.
- Yeah, so.
- Oh, you told us about your angel story.
- Yeah, I did.
- The one where the angel looking over your bed
when you were like five.
- And my mom's still,
my mom is like barely even religious anymore
and she's still like, "Yeah, I saw an angel on you."
I saw your angel.
My mom believes in ghosts.
My uh...
My mom thinks uh...
Well this has been...
So there's like uh...
There's like a radio that wasn't plugged in that turned on in my sister's room at our
house in Ware.
And uh...
There's a room in the house that we don't put anything in because that's grandma's room.
Uh...
Is she dead?
No.
We don't...
Grandma...
Our grandma doesn't live with us.
You never had a grandma.
Oh my god.
- It's even scarier. - I know.
I know.
- Oh my God. - No, there's like,
there's like this room that apparently
like the people who used to live there
like said they hear like voices in
and like they can talk to the grandma.
I forget most of the shit,
but like apparently like somebody--
- I think that's an iPhone game.
- Yeah.
Yeah, there's just an iPhone game in their house.
But somebody, one of the other neighbors
walked up to my mom while she was gardening once.
She was like, "Oh, in that room right there,
"that's grandma's room, right?"
And she's like, "What the fuck?"
- Whoa, dude.
- Yeah.
- Apparently it's like well known.
- We should honestly go go shopping.
- I think that's a good thing to do once,
we should go with your uncle, dude.
- Yeah, dude, get a whole map.
- My friend, my friend Dan went to school
in Hawaii for a while and he was hanging out
with his friends and they were getting drunk
and then one of his friends was like,
I'm gonna go pee on this sacred ground,
this sacred Hawaiian ancestral ground.
- Smart.
And he did, and then he got a huge rash up like,
just like half of his entire body,
just like from his leg up to his chest.
But he wasn't like--
- If that's the best a ghost can do,
I'm a little scared. - Yeah, I know, right?
Right.
Yeah, they just feel you, they make you itchy.
- The thing is, nobody's ever,
even if ghosts are real,
nobody has ever died from a ghost, I don't think.
- Something that just is forever repeating in my mind
is I think Griffin found it,
but it's one of those videos where it's like,
50 people give their hottest takes,
and it's just a bunch of people saying woke,
social justice stuff,
and in the middle there's just a girl who goes,
"It's not a bad thing if you're haunted by a ghost."
(laughing)
- Sometimes it's really chill.
- I think about it all the time,
but that's all she says.
- I don't know, I feel like that's a bad thing.
- I agree.
- Right?
- I mean, it's the haunted--
It's worse if you have a ghost that's watching over you.
It's worse to get haunted.
It's worse to get like a guardian angel.
Personally I would say it's worse to get haunted and killed by a ghost.
But a ghost can't kill.
What would like a ghost can kill?
A ghost can kill.
Everybody's judging you Pat.
Duh.
Yeah.
Bunch of ghosts and vultures out there.
They're judging you right now dude.
I hate it when a ghost judges me.
No, you want to go to ghost court.
I think the fun one is to be judged.
That's the worst.
I think the...
No, you would like it.
That's the fucked up thing is that he would actually like it.
I would hate it.
I would hate it if a ghost judged me.
No, and everybody would be wearing a white sheet except for you and that's how they'd
know you were guilty.
And there's one white sheet that has a powdered wig on it.
Yeah.
That's the judge.
And also one of the jury members has glasses over their white sheet.
Yeah.
The ghost lawyer's wearing a tie around the white sheet so you can see like the outline
of the head so it's just kind of pointless to wear the white sheet. And then your ghost wife is in
the audience with your ghost baby. And she is breastfeeding. Yeah and she oh and she's got
them out dude. Oh my god. She's got two hole two eye holes cut lower down. And then you pull out
a vacuum and you go. Suck the milk out. Yeah you suck them. No you go Luigi's Mansion on the whole courtroom.
You could probably suck breast milk out with a vacuum.
I think the coolest ghost development would be if like some scientist invented like a device that
lets us see ghosts and we find out that they're just all hanging out all around us all the time
and they're just like smoking weed just smoking weed and like you know just I would hate that.
Putting up under people's heads.
I would not feel safe in my own home.
Pat would like that yet again.
Pat is no Pat is lying right now.
He is capping.
Pat you are capping dude.
I'm not capping.
You are capping right now.
I'm not capping. Stop the cap brother. Yeah. Take that cap off. More like Capric. No! You're crapping
right now. No! I'm not. I'm sitting. You're sitting in the, on the porcelain throne right now. Yeah.
That's right. No crap. Yeah, no, hey, no crap brother. No crap. Now we could uh. Exactly,
no crap. I feel like we would find a ghost if we went looking for one. I would not. Absolutely.
I think our next big video, our next documentary should be some kind of
some kind of ghost hunter or cryptid hunt. We can stay...
I don't think I've talked about this but the best part about Matt
besides every other besides every metal in his head and the music and the
ghost hunting thing is that all of he's had like maybe four or five different
ghost hunting organizations, all of which are acronyms that spell out a dirty word.
So I think right now, I think it, I think right now is...
Say some more, say all of them.
So one of them was crap, and I don't remember what that one was.
One of them, one of them was shit, and then now the one that he does is ass.
Acquiring supernatural spirits.
That fucking rules.
So sick, dude.
- Crap, probably, the P in crap is probably poltergeists.
- Probably paranormal.
I bet it was--
- I wish it's poltergeists.
- Capturing and controlling really annoying
paranormal poltergeists.
- Poltergeists.
- Yeah.
Yeah, it probably was that.
- But yeah, we should, we'll definitely go ghost hunting.
We can, what's the oldest place you guys know about?
- The Earth.
- Oh, there's one place, the Earth's core.
We could go to the Earth's core.
Dude, there's probably so many lava ghosts down there.
Find a ghost in the center of the earth.
Do you think they'd let us check out the White House?
Do you think there's dry bones in the center of the earth?
Probably. Yeah, dude.
That's probably where they come from, dude.
That's where they base their Bowser comes from.
Bowser came from the middle.
Middle of the earth.
Yeah, Bowser, he does like lava.
Yeah.
I hate when I'm trying to find Bowser and I fall in and I burn my bottom and I have to run around going,
"Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ay!"
Yeah.
Don't you hate that? But I actually run way faster when I do that.
do that. Yeah. So annoying. It's kind of like a speed hack. Yeah. I hate being Mario. It's
so annoying when I'm Mario. Yeah. Oh my god dude. What a lot of people don't realize is
that it hurts when fire comes out of your hands. Yeah. He burns himself every time like
Wolverine. Yeah. And he just never gets used to it. Yeah and when and you. He doesn't have
the healing like Wolverine. You can't fucking believe dude the growing pains when you get
a mushroom, your whole skeleton just stretching out to twice the height.
Oh, terrible.
No, annoying dude.
You think that's bad.
Imagine like the crunching and the creaking that happens when you get the tiny mushroom.
Yeah.
Yeah, and imagine trying to say to the Walgreens cashier that your name is Tanooki Mario.
You're not gonna believe me.
You're so fucking annoying.
You get it, Mario's SSRIs.
Yeah, all this for some white bitch.
Yeah.
No thanks.
Nah.
God, it sucks being Mario.
- Shakira.
Shakira I'd do Mario stuff for.
- There's not even like a trampoline or anything
at the bottom of the pipes too.
- Yeah, you just gotta hit it, dude.
- Yeah, you just gotta land.
- You know how much brain damage I get
from jumping onto blocks from the bottom?
- Yeah, and fighting turtles?
- And hitting turtles?
- You think that feels good to kill turtles all day?
You think that feels good for me?
- You think?
- I don't even have pockets big enough for all my coins.
- Yeah.
I don't even have pockets big enough for all my coins.
I'm Mario.
Hey, how's it going?
It's me, Mario.
I don't have enough pockets for my coin.
And then you have your brother.
Yeah.
Don't even get me started on my brother.
Yeah, he's always mom's favorite.
Yeah, I wonder why.
Yeah, tall.
Yeah.
Scared.
He's also a pussy.
Pussy.
Yeah, why do you keep hunting ghosts?
Why do you keep hunting ghosts if you're such a baby?
They should call him Pussy Luigi.
Why do I keep getting captured by the ghosts?
they should call him Pussuigi.
They should call him Pussuigi.
Boohooigi.
Yeah.
Pussuigi.
These are all good names.
And I've got a fat evil twin who wears yellow clothings.
What do you think I am, Waldo?
Don't even get me started on the purple one.
You guys are Waluigi and Wario and I'm both the Mario brothers combined.
You're...
No.
Because I'm the good guy.
I'll take Wario.
I'll take it.
I don't care.
Cameron's definitely Waluigi.
I'm Dry Bones.
No, one time dry bones one time for you are Luigi for we Caleb Caleb is
I'm not lucky -
You're the little you're the little look at my tongue. You're a yeah, tell me I'm Yoshi
Look, you're fucked up. You're a fucked up green dog like Yoshi. He's a dinosaur actually you would think
You guys are both
When one Christmas we met we got my
grandparents like mugs with all of us all of us did like a drawing on the mug of them and my brother tried for like
Five minutes and they just gave up and traced Wario as my grandfather and my grandpa opened up
He's like, ah, it looks just like me
And then I showed him Wario and he was perplexed and the fucked up thing is it looks just like it
Hey, yeah his w has confirms Wario is a
Tiny's easy opposite of Italian. Yeah, whatever that is I wrote him. No, he's worried Irish or Greek. Yeah
Sworn in and the two people who make pizza
And me I make pizza. Yeah, he's here Italian. Oh, yeah, I forgot
Bitch, we should go on a European world places. Yeah, we should go on a world tour of Europe
I'm thinking of going on a world tour of my house today to go to the bathroom. Yeah
Yeah, I'm thinking of walking around in a circle in my house. Yeah, I might go on a world tour to like the store man
I wish I didn't have to I wish I didn't have to walk all the way to the bathroom
I wish I could just cut to a map and show two dots one in my room and one in the bathroom and a line going
Between them with a plane flying and then I could be there way faster without having to walk so easy, dude
But like the plane the plane kind of arches like yeah
I like pattern kind of arches in a way that it doesn't make any real sense to I'm fast
I have one of the fastest that's the fastest way to travel on a glue the fastest the fastest way between two points is is a
Large arch that goes all the way over them. Yeah a red on a globe. Yeah, you're right
Because it's because it's small the globe is smaller at the top
You're right. I know I'm right. I'm agreeing with you
You're a genius dude. I'm a green with you. I'm a green guy. I'm a creeper. I know you're a Yoshi. I'm gonna creep it green
I'm not Yoshi. You're a green creeper. You're Yoshi. You just said you're green and you're a creeper.
Yoshi is definitely Grinch adjacent. I don't I don't really like you guys calling me that. I like you.
No, I'm not Grinch adjacent. Yeah, you are. No. I'm the Grinch named Jason.
You would be like a sub boss in a Grinch RPG.
I would not be a sub anything you anyway. Yeah, you're the sub boss in the Grinch RPG
And you're the guy who's like you're the wrapping paper guy. You're the guy
No, I'm not
You yeah, we're the heroes
Yeah, those are for we're not Cindy Lou, but we're not Cindy Lou and you're the wrapping paper boss
I'm not the wrapping paper boss. And if I was you guys
paper for
I don't even sound like that.
Yeah, you're the Grinch's medium.
He he he he.
I don't even sound like that.
I'm taking all the wrapping paper for the Grinch.
You're called the Grinch's groomsman.
The truth is I'm actually very close.
That's your character's name.
I'm very close with Santa Claus and neither of you are getting presents this year.
What?
It's okay.
Yep.
I'm celebrating a different.
That's right.
You guys are both getting.
Patrick both converted.
We didn't tell you yet.
To what?
Don't tell him Patrick.
Judaism.
Judaism?
Oh, okay. Well, I know Jewish Santa too.
That's Charlie Day's religion.
I destroyed him.
It's about rats and stuff.
It's about rap.
Yeah. Judaism is about rap.
If I know one thing about Judaism,
it's hip-hop.
Mm-hmm.
That's right.
The seven days of hip-hop.
Hip-hop Hanukkah.
We're gonna have a hip-hop Hanukkah this year.
That's right.
- That's right. - A hip-hop.
(laughing)
- Hanukkah.
- They're playing a dead Prez hip-hop
every time that they light the menorah.
- Yeah, that's right.
And Lil Dicky's there.
That's the only Jewish rapper I know of.
Actually, no, Ill Bill is a Jewish rapper.
- What?
Asher Roth.
- Asher Roth's Jewish?
- Aziroth from World of Warcraft?
- I think so.
- Mr. Moth?
- Mr. Moth? - Mr. Moth from outside?
(laughing)
- He's in World of Warcraft?
You guys aren't making any sense to me.
- What are you saying, Sephiroth is Jewish?
- Yeah, yeah, Asheroth is Jewish.
- Sephiroth is a Jewish rapper.
- Tell me what you just Googled.
- Asheroth.
- And then what?
- Wikipedia.
- You did Asheroth Wikipedia?
- Yeah.
- And you just clicked and scrolled?
- It's one of the first things.
- It's one of the first things that shows up.
- You did control F Jewish on Asheroth Wikipedia page
and you got one result and you're like,
oh, he's Jewish. - Actually.
- But then you didn't notice that it's just in the,
in the info box, it says not Jewish.
It just, everything that he's not is listed.
- Patrick wrote a script for Google Chrome
that just on every, it automatically control F's Jew
on every single page that he's on.
So he just has to go to the Wikipedia.
It's easy for him. - It's not true.
- It is true. - It's not true.
- It is, dude.
You, you-- - It's not true.
- You're a disgusting person
and you're evil too. - I'm not.
you are you are you're going to be coming from time i don't know man i'm thinking
of becoming evil
you are you already are there don't need any coming as super villain
your act miller was jewish
i'm just on the wikipedia page for jewish rappers now but the uh... there's
some that are like there's one guy is like a
his whole thing i'm a jewish rep that showed what you know what you know what
Oh, her mom's Jewish. Okay.
Well, yeah, that's how it works.
That thing that was like, "She's in racial chat rooms" is the funniest thing I've ever
heard.
Oh my god, dude, what are the fucking...
Okay, so it's got like, the Beastie Boys, Doja Cat, Mickey Avalon...
Mickey Avalon?
Yeah.
Rucka Rucka Alley.
Yes.
Two live Jews.
Samberg. They put Andy Samberg in it. Weird Al isn't on it.
Remember, we confirmed he's not Jewish. Yeah, that's kind of the new
podcast we're doing. We pick one celebrity every week and we find out if
they're Jewish or not. This week, Halle Berry. Let's go. No, it's Ashton Roth
already. No, it's Halle Berry this week. Let's find out.
Halle Bailey there she is
Child actor Sally the baby. Is that what you're saying? No
I searched Hallie B and it filled in Hallie Bailey who I don't know who that is, but I tell you this much. She's not Jewish
I'm gonna tell you that really I could have told you that for well
That's that's why we're doing this show is cuz Patrick is clairvoyant about this one issue
That he I have no idea why I know he just sees their penis
Tell me Obama cut uncut I
Feel like that should be public record. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, I mean absolutely
When the president gets his physical we should know what the president the president's got a thingy
We have to know the cut the length if it's like a tricolor one. We should see a traced outline
What the fuck do you mean tricolor?
Like a Neapolitan ice cream?
Yeah, like the, you have the base--
What is that? What? No!
Somebody has a solid penis.
Somebody has "get blessed by God" with a perfect pink penis.
You know what I'm talking about.
I have one of those.
The base of my penis is like midnight black.
The middle is like a Georgia peach.
It's bright red.
And then the top is as bright as the sun.
It's glowing red.
spot on a JRPG boss. You don't have that? No. What color is it all the way through?
Looks like a candy corn. It's my color. It looks like my skin. I don't know man, maybe I'm the
chosen one. No. Yeah, maybe I'm the chosen one. If anything you have a deformity. I'm the chosen one with the
tricolored penis. That's just the truth dude. Confirm main character. I'm the good
guy. You never heard of that Patrick? No! That's the thing, everybody message Pat pictures
of your Neapolitan penis. So he knows that it's a thing. And no Photoshop. Yeah, no Photoshop.
This is a no filter challenge. Send a photo of your penis to what's his name on the other
end of this phone call and make sure that there's three colors in it. Okay? No Photoshop
allowed. No Photoshop elements allowed. No PixArt. Okay? No Pixlr.com. No WordArt. No
no word art, no Google Docs, just pure,
uncut or cut, tricolor penis, okay?
- Yeah.
- I don't wanna see your penis.
- Oh, you already said you did.
- My shit look like a candy corn.
- I said that.
(laughs)
- I said that I don't wanna see it.
- You said that you wanna see it.
- No.
- You said you wanna eat it like a candy corn.
- I don't wanna eat it like a candy corn.
- You said, wow, this looks like a popsicle
from the ice cream truck.
- Pat wants to find one under his pillow.
- That's not what I said.
- Yeah.
If anyone has access to Patrick's pillow, please place your penis.
Please put your penis in it.
Patricks pillow.
He's going to flip it over in the middle of the night.
But he flips it over not to get to the cold side, just to check if there's a guy's penis there.
So there's something there.
And he's going to do it.
Yeah, it's like waking up on Christmas morning for him.
I don't want to see it.
What if I showed you my penis on this call right now?
I've seen your penis.
No, but you haven't seen the three colors.
You saw it.
It was turtled.
Okay, it didn't look very big and it looked like one color.
Just trust me, there's three colors.
- Did you, you made it?
- It's four and a half inches long
and it's spiraled like a duck, okay?
When it's hard.
- You took Neil's phone and he took a picture of it.
- I'm gonna take your mom's phone.
- No.
- Oh, I'm gonna take your mom's phone
and I'm gonna do nasty stuff to it, dude.
- Yeah, I'm gonna ruin her high scores on Candy Crush.
- Dude, I'm gonna--
- It's not gonna happen.
I'm gonna shit on it and throw it in the fire like a mud-baked salmon.
That's what I'm gonna do.
A mud-baked salmon?
Or a clay-baked salmon.
You know those?
No.
Somebody didn't grow up in the woods.
A mud-baked salmon.
It's a real thing, dude.
That is not a thing.
Nobody's ever been camping.
First you don't think Neapolitan penises are real, now you don't even comprehend a mud-baked
salmon.
That's how stupid you are, dude.
No, it sounds like you're fucking dumb. You are like you didn't grow up in a fucking cave like Caleb. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, your penis didn't see the light enough. That's why it looks like that not did I do you have one of those blind?
Cavefish penises it's translucent your
Lungs inside penis does not and it's got it's got a little light. It's like an angler fish
It has a full skeleton inside it listen
Listen, I don't lure fish onto my penis and then give them the first color, okay?
That doesn't happen.
That's what you do.
I don't even know how I would do that, man.
I'm trying to comprehend that.
I'm looking at my penis right now.
I do not have pants on.
That is true.
Man, it looks so small right now.
I'm looking at my...
It looks so small.
insane looks like an accordion though like you know it gets bigger I'm looking
my dick it looks like an unplayed perfectly pristine packaged accordion
yeah I'm looking I'm looking for my weird Al man it's like a it's like a it's
like a prank can of peanuts yeah yeah got the snake in there yeah you were a
can you were can on your thing you can do you were can on it and it springs out
like a like a big worm yeah into your face yeah big big damn you got a big did
you guys see did you guys see Jokar Sarnaev is not gonna be put to death
dude I'm gonna have a party tonight I'm gonna invite everyone I know unless I
have something to do about it yeah what are you gonna do about it I'm gonna
murder Jokar Sarnaev he's gonna I'm gonna write in now that now that I know
I know he's gonna be alive in November, I'm writing him.
You're gonna write him?
Yeah, let's lead a Jokar Sarnaev write-in vote, dude.
I mean, why not?
Finally somebody addressed the Boston problem.
Yeah.
Well, okay, and here's his, like, here's his, um...
There is a Boston problem, and he is a hero who addressed it.
The good Joe.
That's right.
Oh, shit.
Cameron's gotta get on the fucking, Cameron's gotta get on a campaign.
I'm gonna get on Dzhokhar Tsarnaev's campaign.
I'm gonna send him an email like, "I work for your campaign, dude."
You think he gets email in jail?
No, he just gets it in his mind.
Yeah.
That could be his big thing.
He got an email that told him to do that.
He could be on stage and be like, "Listen, we can talk about healthcare, education, reform,
foreign policy, all we want.
The truth is, neither of my opponents are willing to do anything about the city of Boston."
He's like, he's at a campaign rally and he's like,
"And I have great news for everybody.
"Look under your chairs
"because everyone has a pressure cooker bomb."
(laughing)
- How do the pressure cooker bombs work?
Do they just--
- You put really bad rice in there
and it stinks so bad it kills everybody.
- Yeah, you put a real stinky curry in there
And then you just turn that bitch on bomb.
(laughing)
You turn on the bomb setting.
- Yeah, they should stop making pressure cookers
with the bomb setting on there.
That's a big problem.
- Yeah, that was a huge misstep on Black and Decker's part.
- Putting the bomb setting on it.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
They should just put a bomb setting on everything though.
- Screw the microwave.
- Microwave.
Do you guys know, I don't have a microwave anymore.
Do you guys know anybody--
- I don't have one either.
- Didn't have a microwave growing up?
No, I don't know.
No, they were so commercially available.
I mean, I guess, like, I guess,
did, like, my parents count?
Yeah, wait, no.
'Cause, yeah, just,
they didn't grow up with microwaves.
My sister-in-law, like, her parents believed
that if she would have,
if she ate food out of a microwave,
she'd, like, grow, like, a third eye and shit.
Yeah. They're not wrong.
I mean, yeah, the thing, like,
comparatively, they've been,
stuff like that has been around for a pretty short time,
and I'm sure in like 20 years it's gonna be like,
oh yeah, the iPhones were actually like
accelerating our evolution to grow wings all along.
- Well that's definitely true.
It's definitely true that a phone
is sending stuff into your brain.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, stuff that we can't see.
Kind of like a pure black goo.
- Yeah.
- That Patrick immediately adapted to.
And Patrick is the next step of evolution.
Something that can actually handle the phone.
- Yeah.
Like I was thinking about like me and Cam quit,
we like quit using Twitter every like couple months
for a little bit.
Yeah.
And Pat just has never, it's never popped in his head.
No, I know.
Never stopped.
No, can't stop.
Me and Simon were talking to Pat about like,
like 'cause Simon and me were just talking about like,
like even, I'm not even a 10,000 followers
and I get so angry at people on Twitter
who are just annoying me and I'm just like,
oh my God, this is ruining my life,
but it's also the only way I'm making money right now
so I have to stay on.
And they were like, "Oh, Pat, you have like 25,000 followers.
"How do you deal with that?"
And he was like, "I don't know, I don't care."
- It's not a big deal.
- It just doesn't, it's crazy.
- Like, he just gives a shit.
- He's like, I mean this in the best way.
You are one IQ point below where you would be
if it made you mad.
- Yeah.
- You know, like you're like, you're like 119.
- Maybe.
- Yeah.
- Probably like 139.
- You're not 139.
- No.
- Probably 139, no.
I'm a hundred million.
I don't know.
I don't even have an IQ.
I kind of transcended beyond it.
It really, it literally, none of it, none of it fucking matters.
Like why, like there's so many people like, there's so many fucking people who are like,
"Oh, my mutuals are fighting."
Who gives a shit?
Just fucking, you can put it down for a little bit.
Go on a different, like just scroll away.
Go on a different, go on vote.
Go over to vote.
Go vote.
Go to vote.
What's the what's the conservative one? Oh, what's it called? Scribbler?
Yeah, parlor burbler parlor
Parlor yeah, I made a parlor account and I got banned for pretending to be Ruth Bader Ginsburg
I plundered on parlor. I
Put disinformation regarding hydroxyl or whatever the fuck it's called. I am Donald Trump. I am gay
That's what everyone wrote on Parler.
That's what everyone made an account of.
The week that Parler came out, everyone made an account that was like,
"I'm Donald Trump and I'm a Democrat."
And then got banned and we're like, "Look at these freaks."
I totally got them.
Oh my God. Oh yeah, free speech, my ass.
I should have gone and made boobs official.
Who gives a shit? Who gives a shit?
It's free from the internet.
I'm going on there and being like, "I am going to kill you. I am going to destroy you."
getting banned and be like, "Well, I guess it's not a free speech app after all."
Yeah, someone got triggered.
Yeah.
Someone got reverse triggered.
Fucking own, dude.
Yeah, spending enough time to make an account on their website and interact with enough
people to get banned.
Yeah.
We're conservative now.
Why not, dude?
Shit like that does get annoying, though.
I will admit.
It does get annoying.
Just put it down, dude.
Just go do something else.
No, I know.
I know.
That's what I do.
- You put down Parler? - I do.
- I put down Parler and then I open Twitter back up.
- Nice, and then you oscillate between the two.
- Yeah, remember they tried to do that with like Mastodon
or whatever the fuck it was called?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I'm the Mastah and the Don.
- Hey. - That's right.
- I made one, I made the Subway account on there, on Mastodon.
- I couldn't figure out how to use Mastodon.
- Yeah.
- Oh yeah, that was like the one for--
- That like the decentralized one.
- Sick of right wing trolls on Twitter.
Yeah, that's the one for people who are sick of an app that just works normally.
You can just turn off.
Yeah.
Sick of an app that makes sense that isn't everything on websites, like .io websites.
Yeah, that's it.
Any of those websites, I mean, they've perfected websites at this point.
Like, you'll never have another, like, dig to Reddit move.
You know what I mean?
Because they've just gotten too good at making them, like, nobody, you can't make a more addictive,
put billions of dollars behind researching how to make Twitter the most addictive thing
it can be.
You're not going to be able to make anything that competes with it.
Every website update that's been made since 2010 has just been a negative move.
Oh, absolutely.
It started with the blue lines on Twitter, like the blue reply lines.
Yeah, it started with all the blue lives in threat.
The blue lives, too.
It started with the blue lines and then it was like, "Oh, now you can put four pictures.
Now we're going to show you the pictures.
I loved when you couldn't see the pictures.
Yeah.
Yeah, and you open it up and there was those accounts that were like food or gore or whatever.
I mean, they would just be like breaking John McCain.
John McCain dies while in Ryan Dunn's car and then you click on it and it'd be Goatsy.
Yeah.
I miss that.
Yeah, that was the best.
And the surprise.
You know what I mean?
They took all the surprise out of it and then-
Surprise me.
Keep me interested.
Okay?
They took all the surprise out of it and then they put like fucking-
I want to see a man's balls and a man's ass.
I miss Fave Star Cups.
I miss the Fave Star Cups.
I was talking about that the other day with Cameron, like the serious Fave Star Guy things.
The ones where it was like guys who would make posts like "I just saw someone hitting an
innocent child, hit me instead, I can take it!"
Those are the fucking best.
Those are the best guys.
It was either that, they would say shit like that, or then jokes like "Umm, yeah, whiskey
equals awesome."
like just the worst types of guys and then they would send like some girl on their like 15 like
fave like you get one fave star cup a day and then they would send them like some girl some woman who
has like a husband and they're like oh here's your cup darling thanks for the cup darling
i missed fave star i was i was uh at the time i was like
trying to reply i was i would just like reply to rappers all day
Yeah.
I was a...
At some point I got blocked by E-40.
Oh yeah?
I'm still blocked by E-40, dude.
It's fucking heartbreaking.
Damn.
Yeah, I don't know why I did.
I was an early adopter of Twitter, I think.
I think that's why I'm such a fucking moron now.
Yeah, definitely that's why.
Yeah.
Undeniably that's why.
I was too busy.
I played Battlefield 3 and I went on the hip-hop Reddit and...
Oh yeah, you guys were Reddit guys.
I was a huge Reddit guy.
I was a Reddit guy, yeah.
I was just a Twitter guy. I wasn't even I never went back and nuked my reddit account because it was all like yeah
I'm so excited for the Obama re-election campaign. Yeah. Yeah fucking it was atrocious, dude
I'll probably probably nuke mine too, but it's not tied to my name or anything. I don't think people I never used
My genius brain decided that my reddit name should be Caleb underscore pits. Yeah. Yeah, so smart great move
I had no idea, I just, I had no concept of like why you would want to be anonymous on the internet.
I wasn't posting like anything racist or mean. So I was like, yeah, you just, you know, just post embarrassing like Hillary stuff with my full name on it.
Yeah.
You were a Hillary guy?
No, but in 2016...
Were you a Hillary guy in 2016?
I mean I worked for the Bernie campaign but then the campaign manager was like
in North Carolina was like we need to do like a big Hillary push and I was like duh okay I
work construction and so to my 400 followers I was like y'all we need to back our girl.
Oh no dude I was I was Hillary in 2016. I didn't I voted for Jill Stein.
I was that was like right around when I when I started listening to Chapo Trap House so that
That was right before I learned that you could vote for someone else.
I was early on all that shit.
I remember listening to the first Chapo.
When they were on Street Fight.
I was too busy.
I was having sex.
I was too.
No you weren't.
No.
I was having sex with my phone.
Yeah, because you have a lightning bolt cable for a penis.
was it Street Fight that they were?
I don't remember.
I remember it actually.
That's you and then you turns out you don't remember.
Here's me.
Yeah I remember.
I think I remember about that.
I remember that.
What was that voice Cameron?
Do that one again.
I think I remember that.
Yeah my name is Patrick. I'm also mean to my friend about voices.
No it was really good.
He sounded like, uh, you sounded like Ernest.
I don't know what Ernest sounds like. I've never watched an Ernest movie.
Let's do some voices to close out the episode.
Let's just do a bunch of voices.
Okay, let's do, um...
What were you gonna say about me?
Don't worry about it, Patrick.
I know what he was gonna say. You don't want to hear it.
Sometimes I think about just like the media diet that you grew up with
and it blows my brain.
Oh.
The idea that you grew up watching jackass and Ernest movies
is insane.
Yeah.
I know I I'm I'm a fucking weird person. You're such a freak dude. I'm a freak. I'm a freaking moron
I hope that lamp behind you jumps up like the Pixar intro and squishes you and
Replaces you and then we watch a lamp instead of Patrick
I we Cameron and I were talking about this like on stream the other day like I I literally like I remember commercials
From the 70s even though I never fucking saw
Like the the one with the sad Indian that was Italian. Yeah that guy and then like that's from the 90s, I think
But there was like like we were talking about the Calgon commercial the ancient Chinese secret. I
Don't know what that I don't know why you're saying we were saying
About it. I was telling Cameron about it. He was telling me about commercials from the 70s
Do you guys remember the head-on commercials? Mm-hmm. You mean headstrong?
Yeah, I'll take you and it's also it's not a commercial song. Yeah, it's the song but it's in the commercial for like amp energy
dude, the head-on commercials were like
Brilliant, they fucking make those they were so good. I'd like late 2000 mid 2000
They must they must have made it in like 1990 and I just recycled like I was fucking being hypnotized
You were dude. I mean, I guess yeah, that is true
Remember when they parodied it in disaster movie?
The thing is no parody would be as funny as those commercials just were.
There was, they made the...
Adam Curtis could make an entire documentary about Head On.
Exactly.
The disaster movie parody was "Head On, apply it to your fucking forehead you bitch."
That's fucking sick dude.
I don't know what Head On is.
Yeah Febreze, fucking spray it on your couch you fucking dumbass.
Spray your shit with it.
That's gonna be the next wave of commercials.
Of commercials?
Absolutely.
They already kinda do that.
They already kinda do it.
Implied, nudity.
I mean like after the self-care brands kinda like start to run its course and people get
like more people get angry at them, there's gonna be one brand who like goes like, "Yeah,
we're the fucking cool brand.
We don't give a fuck about self-care or being woke.
We speak what's on our mind."
They're gonna bring Crack Docs to Pepperdine.
- Like Kraft Mac and Cheese is just tweeting that
over and over and everyone's gonna do it.
- Kraft Mac and Cheese rustic cut, it's for men only.
- Yeah.
- Thick cut.
- They bring back Cheesosaurus Rex but he's a PUA now.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- He drops a macaroni in a girl's drink.
- Brands are gonna start just adding random women on Twitter
and just sending them unsolicited dick pics.
That's the next step for brands.
- It's a message from Applebee's to a woman
that just says, "You look so much better without makeup."
- Dude, I miss the GoDaddy commercials.
Those were, those rocked me.
- You remember that one GoDaddy commercial?
- Do you wanna titty fuck this athlete?
Go to GoDaddy.com.
- Danica Patrick's boobs at GoDaddy.com.
- Okay, and me as a kid, I said, "Okay."
- Yeah, sure.
- So I went there.
It's like here's our plans for a website.
Here's how much bandwidth you can get.
And I'm like, alright, I don't care about your plan.
I care about my plan to titty fuck that girl from the commercial.
Exactly.
Remember that one they had that fat kid?
Now that's a plan.
Yeah, and that's what I call a plan.
There's a Go Daddy Super Bowl commercial where it was 30 seconds of the fat kid from the
I'm Just a Kid Simple Plan music video making out with a woman.
And everyone was like, what?
This is disgusting.
I was disgusted by that.
They made a kid make out with a grown woman?
Oh no, he's like, if you look up a picture of him,
he was just like the generic nerd
from every early 2000s movie.
Oh, but he wasn't a kid in the--
No, no, he just looks like a fucking IT guy.
Pat is like, no, he wasn't a kid, he was 14.
Yeah, he was above New Hampshire age.
The average age.
Yeah.
Now they should bring back corny commercials though.
GoDaddy make out commercial, it's Jesse Hyman is his name.
Whoa, yeah, Jesse Hyman Breaker.
Yeah, he made out with Bar Refaeli.
Yeah, me too.
Meet Jesse Hyman, he bakes out with Bar Refaeli
in front of 11 million people.
Jesse Hyman is like, just the perfect pick up word.
Really good name, yeah.
Yeah, I'm Jesse Hyman.
I'm Jesse Hyman.
Oh, he was one of the band kids from--
What about Buster Hyman?
Buster Hyman?
What's up, I'm Buster Hyman!
What about Hunter Hyman?
What about Hunter Cunter?
Hunter Pussy?
Just, yeah, becoming a pickup artist and just changing your last name to Pussy.
Titty Mister.
I'm Titty Mister.
Nice to meet you, welcome to Dave and Busters.
I'm David Sexual.
Ooh, David Buster.
David Sexual.
David Buster.
David Buster is a good one.
Yeah.
I'm Tony Robbins.
Tony Danza.
Tony Robbins.
I'm Robin the Pussy Blind, dude.
Mm-hmm.
Because I'm Toby Robbins.
Toby Robbins.
Toby Robbins, his PUA brother.
Yeah.
He's a pickup artist guy, right?
They based--
Tony Robbins?
No, he's like-- he goes on stage and he's like, "You can-- you can have everything!"
Every dollar in the world!
And then, like, middle-aged women are like,
yes, please, fuck my ass.
- You know what, I thought Tony Robbins was the guy
from, like, that elliptical commercial.
That's a different Tony.
- Yeah.
What's up, I'm Jimmy Female Orgasm.
- Jimmy the myth?
- Yeah, no more--
- Jimmy the myth!
- No Jimmy Female Orgasm, how 'bout that?
- Oh my God, that's what I'm talking about.
Female Orgasm is his real last name.
He just makes his first name, No Jimmy.
- Yeah.
- I would be a great pickup artist.
- Oh, I'm thinking of Tony Little.
That's a very different guy.
- Tony Little, no, Tony Robbins is big.
Tell you that much.
- Tony Little's the guy with the,
he wears the fitted hat and he's got a ponytail.
- There was some pickup artist
who was on Freddie Wong's podcast in 2011,
whose name was, I think it was Adam Lyons.
And I didn't know what a pickup artist was.
I was just like 14.
and I thought he was fucking awesome dude.
- Yeah.
- It was like all these nerds talking to this guy
who like gets pussy all the time.
And he was just talking about like harassing women
on the street.
- So what kind of special effects do you use
in order to draw the women in?
That's what they're saying.
- I put my penis closer to the camera, see?
So it looks bigger.
- It makes it look a little bigger.
- I put them in the background.
I put my penis in the foreground.
But yeah, he was just talking about like,
they were like, so like,
what's like the greatest pickup you've ever done?
And he was like, yeah, one time I
picked up a girl from her boyfriend on the street.
- Whoa. - Yeah.
- Whoa. - And I was just 14,
like I would never let that happen to me, dude.
I would kill, I would probably kill you.
- Immediately kill that guy.
- And then he talked about LARPing
and how he would go LARPing
and try to pick up women while he LARPed.
- Dude, that fucking rocks.
- So sad. - That fucking rocks.
- Just picking up the kind of women who LARP.
- 'Cause he's doing it 'cause he's like,
oh yeah, well, you know, chivalry back then was different.
- Yeah.
- It's a whole different thing back then.
- Yeah, super impressive.
You picked up a woman LARPing
'cause you were like under 350 pounds.
- Right.
- Like fucking sick.
- You were the only person there
who kinda looks like a knight.
- Yeah, yeah, exactly, yeah.
- Yeah, you're the only guy--
- I think he's like five, six, too.
- You're the only guy who's not,
who's just pretending to be a troll.
- Oh, and then I looked him up recently--
- I'll imagine it.
He's married to like five women at the same time.
- God damn, oh my God.
- He just has like a bunch of wives on like a compound.
- Oh my God.
- So sick, dude.
- It's where, I can understand if,
I can understand if they all have their own houses
and he just visits them, but if he's got a compound,
fuck that.
- I can understand having, you know, sleeping around.
- I can understand having multiple wives
in their own apartments.
- Let me tell you what, one wife is plenty for me, okay?
I mean, woo!
- Hey, look, that's all I need, all right?
That's all I need, but if I had more than one, I'd probably not put them on a compound.
Five different wives telling me to get off the video game?
Yeah, man, sounds like paradise.
Five times the wives is five times the chores, if you think about it.
Exactly.
Yeah.
I'm not doing that shit.
Let's think about the pros and the cons here.
Of five wives?
Yeah, five wives means, uh, oh my god, but what if they all, what if one wife-
Five mother-in-laws?
No thanks.
Yeah, no fucking thanks.
Yeah, no fucking thanks. Yeah, but if they all have gay dads, that's ten father-in-laws. Yeah, I'm thinking the best life in the world
I'm thinking we got a flag football game
We got a whole flag football game greatest fourth of July ever I beat up all my father-in-laws Oh
Yeah, you're gonna have those five father or those ten father-in-law's building an octagon in your backyard
Right. Oh my god to be amazing
You can have also different they could be like different characters like oceans 11 style, you know
You have like you can have like an explosives expert dad
This is the hacker over the hacker dad like hey father-in-law the toilets claw clogged
and he'll be like, "I'll be right over."
Drops a stick of dynamite in, blows up the toilet,
fills your fifth wife. - And he's called the cleaner.
- And he's the cleaner.
- His name's the cleaner.
- Yes, you could have a chef.
- That's Billy the cleaner. - You could have a chef.
- Chef dad. - A chef father-in-law.
- Yeah. - Right?
Who comes over, makes you a French omelet, dude,
while his daughter fucking sucks your balls, man, yeah!
- Yes. - This is my father-in-law,
Jacques Pepin.
- Yeah, exactly, yeah, and then you could have,
- Yeah, you could have like a very sexual,
like South American father-in-law.
- Sultry dad.
- Yeah, who comes over and he like,
he gets your wife primed.
(laughing)
- Well, it's okay, 'cause it's not his daughter,
it's the other one. - It's not his daughter.
- Yeah, it's a different one.
- But he comes over, he lays down the rose petals
that lead to your bed, that your construction
father-in-law built.
Yeah, and then right before he's about to penetrate--
It's kind of like Queer Eye with dads.
- Dude, father-in-laws for the--
- Father-in-laws for the son-in-law.
- Single guy.
- For the father-in-law for the son-in-law.
- 10 father-in-laws for the one guy, yes!
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah.
- We gotta fucking pitch that to Netflix right now.
- Yeah, LAN parties.
LAN parties with the father-in-laws,
you're all playing Counter-Strike.
- Uh-huh.
- Oh my gosh.
- I was imagining a show--
- You got Jedi Academy.
hacker father-in-law the show yeah there we go the show like and they're all like
trying to give advice at the same time and there's like one of like yelling
about like explosives and a hacking and all over each other they don't know how
to take turns everybody be quite there and you speak first okay I know we don't
know each other that well yet. We're early on in the marriage.
And then you have Captain, who's like an ad...
Let's run through their names. Let's run through their names.
Gadget. We got Gadget the cleaner.
Um, Bombs Away.
Musonex Monster.
[Laughter]
Gadget the cleaner, Musonex guy.
Bombs Away is the explosive...
Bombs Away is the explosives expert. That's three.
I thought the cleaner was the explosives.
There's another cleaner.
There's a janitor.
There's French maid dad.
Oh, sexy, topless, French maid dad.
Yeah.
Walks around, cleans your house.
So how many dads are we at now?
I have four.
Mr. Bean Dad.
Wait, but they're code names, so we gotta get their code names.
Young Dad, like he's really smart, but he like skipped a bunch of grades and became a
dad master.
Uh-huh, yeah.
Yeah.
Um, um, Snowboard Dad.
We got Shaun White.
Shaun White Dad.
Shaun King Dad.
Yeah, yeah, civil rights activist dad.
- Yeah, therapist dad.
- No, no.
- He's the one who asks you about your relationship
with your father.
- I cannot be a therapist.
Get that fuck outta here.
- Line 11 firefighter dad.
- First responder dad.
- Space man dad.
There we go, that's all 10 dads right there.
- All right, here's the fucked up thing though.
Now that we have all 10 dads,
I kinda want more.
- Yeah.
- I kinda want more dads.
- All you have to do is--
- I kinda want a monster dad, I want an alien dad,
Ghost dad, Bill Cosby dad.
- Monster truck dad.
- Monster truck dad, yeah, Hillbilly redneck dad.
- Caleb, here's the thing, is if you want more,
all you have to do is you go--
- Get another wife.
- You go to the bar, you go up to a woman,
you ask, "Do you have gay dads?"
And if she says yes, you go, "Great, nice to meet you.
"I'm Buster Hyman."
(laughing)
- Yeah, Buster Hyman, I barely know her, Hyman.
- Yeah, but I will.
- I will.
- Oh, I will.
- I will, I will.
- Oh yeah, I will.
I'm gonna get to know it pretty damn well.
How about you and your two dads come over?
Hey, my name's Buster Hyman and I know what you're thinking.
Buster Hyman? I hardly know her, Hyman.
But just you wait. Just you wait.
[laughter]
Yeah.
Ooh. Hamilton dad.
Hamilton dad?
Yeah.
What does Hamilton dad do?
It's a dad who likes Hamilton.
That makes sense.
Civil War dad.
Reenactor dad yes ghost dad ghost dad said ghost dad you did yeah all right
where are we gonna put all of them in the house where am I gonna put all of
them I don't have enough room in my cabinet God thank God we have money money
dad yeah we have rich dad and poor dad I got a poor dad poor dad lives in the
check bag dead bag and bad dad and bad dad
trying to destroy the family unit yeah
yeah who social justice warrior dad yeah
we have that we've we already have that
no no this is like this like like Travis
McElroy style dad okay okay my dad my
- My dad and my dad.
- Skateboarder dad.
- Well that's kind of covered with Sean White dad.
Sean White skateboards.
- Gamer dad, although that could probably just be gadget.
- That's gadget for sure.
- See there's a lot of, there's too much overlap.
- There's only about 15 types of dads you can have
and then you just start doubling up.
- So 20 is too many, but so this means that there has to be--
- 20 is plenty.
- For 15 to be the number,
there needs to be either a widower dad or a straight dad.
That's true. Oh my God, one mom?
A mother-in-law could be a dad.
The mother-in-law, you just keep her in the basement.
'Cause I don't need a girl.
I don't need you kind of.
Listen, I have plenty of wives.
Yeah, how about you can sleep in the shed.
You put all your wives in one room
and then you and the dads get to hang out.
Yeah.
It's really just a life hack more than anything,
more than a plan, you know?
- Yeah.
- 'Cause you don't wanna marry,
you don't actually wanna marry any of the women.
'Cause you just select them based on if you love them.
You only selected them based on how cool
their gay dads were.
- Yeah.
- You know, so you don't give a fuck about these girls.
- If there's a widower dad though,
then the widower dad could be like--
- The widower dad's the evil dad.
- Oh my God. - Oh no, dude.
- Yeah, but then it's only 14 on the dad compound.
- But you still have 15 total dads
where you think it's important.
- Yeah, you have a dog that's technically not a dad,
but you can call it dog dad.
- Yeah, it's kind of like a dog's purpose dog.
- Yeah, we do need an animal, we need an animal.
- Monkey dad.
- The monkey dad is your actual dad
who died and got reincarnated as a monkey.
- It's like Winston from Overwatch.
He just kind of like a smart gorilla.
- And then you can say--
- It's like the monkey from Night at the Museum.
- Okay.
- You can say, yeah, yeah, and my dad's a monkey.
- Yeah, turns out.
- Yeah.
But like if somebody says something unbelievable,
you could be like, yeah, yeah.
And my dad's a monkey.
My dad's a monkey.
Yeah, and I got a dad who's a hacker named Gadget.
Yeah, and I have 15 dads and they all live on a compound.
Yeah, sure.
Except for one's a monkey.
Yeah, totally.
I have seven wives and I've never seen them naked.
Yeah, sure, man.
Yeah, and one of my dads is evil
and he keeps trying to blow us up,
but we've been using different war tactics to attack him
and kind of prevent him from destroying us.
Yeah, okay, sure.
Yeah, we have a big computer that's got an AI in it, and that's technically a dad too.
Yeah, and we also have Cyber Dad.
Yeah, Cyber Dad, that's like the Jarvis.
It's not Gadget, it's like the... yeah, no, he's like...
He was a dad created by Gadget.
He's like Cyborg from Teen Titans.
Yeah, sure, a dad created by Gadget.
And my name's Hunter Poon.
Hunter Poon, I barely know her, Poon.
Anyway, a six-pack of Bud Light should not cost ten dollars.
(laughter)
- It's so long.
- He's just talking to the grocery store.
He's like, yeah, if that costs $10, then I have 15 dads.
Yeah, sure.
- I have 15 dads and a gadget dad,
and one of them is an AI created by a gadget dad.
- Yeah.
Anyway, I'll take my beer and hold on.
(whistling)
Dads assemble!
(laughter)
- And by the way, they're not just dads.
They're dad-in-laws.
and then he walks out of the store
and you might wanna watch out for hitman dad
red dot appears on kissier's head. They're not dads, they're just my brothers
yeah they're more than dads. First it was dads, now it's brothers. cheaper by the
fifteen dads and me. cheaper by the baker's dozen
cheaper by the baker's dozen of dads. well if that ain't a dad's dozen i don't know what is
That's a daddy's dozen.
That's a daddy's dozen if I've ever seen one.
Oh, alright.
Oh my god.
I love having fun.
Yeah.
Me too.
I love to have fun.
I wish that my-
It's one of the top ten things.
Yeah.
Alright.
I should be dad soon.
Alright, we can end now.
I just-
Yeah, no, that was important to do.
Yeah, we had to-
That was very important to flesh out.
We had to explain the dads.
Yeah.
Alright.
of dads.
[BLANK_AUDIO]