you're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
Okay, I'm recording too.
It's really easy.
The whole, everything's easy.
Me and Pat are in the flesh.
You should make sure that you guys, you can be heard.
You should look at the audacity waveform while you're talking
and make sure it's actually loud enough.
I think you probably gotta get closer.
Yeah, I think I'm good too.
I think this is...
Yeah, so Caleb and Pat are in the same room.
They're sitting side by side.
No, I'm sitting on Patrick like a beanbag chair.
Yeah, he's sitting on my lap like it's Christmas.
Yeah.
Pat's got a fupa full of beans.
It's like the tauntaun from Star Wars 5.
It's actually like the tun-tun.
Which is actually like a bon-bon.
How many pounds Patrick weighs?
Come on, Patrick.
This sucks.
Alright, well look it then, right off the bat, Jexy2, read it to us, let's go.
No, I, I, um...
No, you said you were gonna write Jexy2 for this episode.
We're gonna hear a Jexy2 script.
That's what this whole episode's gonna be.
Okay, interior.
No, no, no, no, no, Patrick said he was gonna write it.
Patrick has to say it.
I told you, I told you that it's not ready.
Patrick has to talk for an hour. You did not say that.
I told you it's not ready.
You said, "I'm going to write Jexy2 and I'm gonna read it on the premium episode."
it on the premium episode. So that's what you're gonna do.
I had other things happen. Are you doing a take back right now?
No. Are you seriously doing a take back?
Are you doing backsees? I have to.
Why do you have to? Okay, first of all, nobody ever has to do
backsees. Yeah, I have to.
No you don't. No.
Because it's not, the vision that I had for Jexie 2 is not coming.
Alright, well then finish it right now and say it out loud as you finish it.
Interior, Jexie office.
Let me, I have it open.
The Jexie zone.
Okay.
Let's go.
I gotta find out again.
Come on.
Everyone's waiting for it.
He has to find out.
I'm really fucking this one.
All right, this is all we have for Jexie 2 right now.
It better be 100 pages long.
That better, it better be 100 pages out of 200 pages.
It is one page long.
Now.
Is it one very long page?
Like an old school Bible?
It's a scroll.
It's a scroll, yeah.
It's written on a scroll.
Yeah, and the first letter is giant.
Yeah, like in Spongebob.
Like in Spongebob Squarepants.
No, it just says giant.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, I guess I have to read Jexy 2 even though it's not finished.
And you have to do all the voices too.
You have to do all the voices and you have to-
Cam can't help it.
And you have to-
You have to, once you reach the end of this page, you have to improv 99 more pages.
In every line you have to do 25 pushups.
Okay.
Interior, Mike's house.
Start over.
25, buddy.
This sucks.
And no knees either, no girl pushups.
I don't even- Big boy pushups.
I don't even like Jexy 2 anymore.
You want it, dude.
This is what happens.
You're the one who wanted Jexy 2 on the show.
Yeah, listen.
I didn't know that I was gonna have to do it this early.
You know who listens to this show, man?
Famous Hollywood producers.
Adam DeVine.
Adam DeVine himself, Jexy himself.
Jexy and Stuber both listen to this show.
Oh, yeah?
And they're giving away a spoiler.
And they want to hear.
Yeah, you just gave away a spoiler.
You just gave away a spoiler.
All right, interior, Mike's house.
Mike is sleeping in his huge Casper mattress
that he got from his job making the advertisements
on the subway that say all birds is like a unicorn on crack.
There are empty Soylent bottles all around his bed.
He is hung over from smoking weed.
So far this sucks.
- Yeah, I'm not liking it.
Can you rewrite that intro?
- Okay, well--
- This is nothing like Jexy.
- Okay, then what are we rewriting it?
- It's to me--
- You can use the keyboards right here, Caleb.
- My arms are too short.
- Your arms are too short.
- No, T-Rex arms.
- My arms are too short, dude.
you're closer to the keyboard than i did i hurt my arms today and it'd be really
fucked up he made me move
all right what i have to do it can we add in
some giant robots
uh... right at the very beginning of the night intro jack c the iron giant arrives
okay i think that
the the iron giant arrives any city ties for jack c sins
okay the iron
Giant jizz ant what the fuck?
the
The iron jizz ant arrives
Fully loaded like a baked potato
Was the iron giant say
I'm the iron giant
He doesn't say fuck you. He doesn't know that he says fuck you stop typing it and just say it out loud
I can't see what you're getting words in the iron giant
Okay. What would the Iron Giant really say? He's a hero war weapon. Yeah, but what if
this is like a... what if he's like a Deadpool hero? Oh. So he says
bad stuff like fuck you. Okay, so you got to put to the camera then. Yeah.
I'm trying to see a parentheses to the camera
Parentheses right now you you read it
Okay, the iron giant fuck you. I'm a pedophile
We got him. No
Caleb we finally admit on recording no
No, that's that was clearly in the iron Giants voice
Yeah, your own boy mean nah me Superman. I just did it again
That was Superman's voice that was yeah, you fucking idiot. No, that was Eminem's voice
No, yeah, no, no Griffin
What's Peter Griffin say? He's adding all this shit into the
Peter Griffin says I'm going to fight
That chewy
What's going on over there?
Oh, Peter Griffiths says I'm gonna fight that chicken.
Oh, okay.
I remember that episode.
Yeah.
Okay, then Mike says, "Ah, shit, what the freaking heck happened last night?
While I was smoking herb,
I think I hallucinated my phone
talking to me."
So that's about Jexy.
That's kind of a reference to Jexy1.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
So, then Jexy says, "You did not hallucinate."
And Mike says, "What the?"
And Jexy says, "Hello, I am your phone, Jexy.
Last night I watched you jack off to pornos on me and now I speak because of an update."
And Mike says, "Uh, yeah, I think this is the start to an awkward friendship."
So wait, so didn't they already have a friendship in Jexy 1?
This is like a reboot?
This is a new...
He smoked so much weed that he forgot what happened in Jexy 1.
No, the guy in Jexy 1 is not named Mike.
This is a different guy with the new Jexy.
So this is...
I thought Jexy was a girl.
So this is kind of not Jexy 2, this is like the Iron Giant, a Jexy story.
This is like, um, if...
This is like a spin-off.
They made Halloween 3, and Halloween 3 was not about Michael Myers.
It's a Jexy story.
It's like Rogue One.
It's a Jexy story, it's not a Jexy.
is
chronicle with family guy
with including care family guy characters
yes i wish i wish i had written this writer do it so you can rated ready to
cameron you could share your screen
okay this in uh...
now don't share your screen i don't care in mind alright yet you are
spits spelling out the letters of the law is being in the oxen minecraft and
redstone actually created a word processor using redstone in minecraft
that i was so long
now would take me a little researching c movies in the time
right so then after that there actually is the sequel for jack c they're
actually doing a red-haired and i believe it is in like a lot of finished
can you let finishes
masterpiece i have to get to the second part of the
bucking script jackie isn't even sorry i know it's easy for us to gang up on you
'cause we're together and you're not
it's next to the jack c sequel is running a lot of blue version like
poking around
Cameron, you have to browse Reddit for the next minute while we read this.
Okay, so Jexie says... The Jexie sequel is going to be two versions like red and blue like Pokemon or
crystal and silver gold versions.
Three versions. There's three versions. No, crystal and silver gold.
You are but a jester in this court of Jexie.
Alright, you keep going. Okay, so Jexie says... There's going to be four versions.
What the fuck?
It's gonna be black and white and black and white too.
I can shut off the computer whenever I want and you lose two hosts.
We could just do me and him.
Yeah.
We could cut you out of this whole thing.
No, you couldn't.
We could shut you off.
We could.
Watch us.
No.
Don't believe me?
Just watch.
Okay, so Jexy says okay.
And then Mike says okay.
And then Jexy says, "Would you like me to call you a stuber?"
And Mike says okay.
And then Jexy says okay.
you a stuber now you added you and just as calling Oh calling stuber now okay so
that's okay well let me fucking finish I'm letting you finish I just let you
say okay like 20 times in a row what would the toys it's natural dialogue
okay okay wow this dialogue so realistic this is how to hit men would actually
talk this is how people would actually you know what they call a burger in
France okay okay okay so Stuber picks up the phone wait is Stuber the guy or is
that who is Stuber? Stuber is the guy. The guy but which guy? I didn't see Stuber
Kumail Nanjiani is Stuber yeah okay yeah so he says he picks up the phone he says
"Hello, this is Stuber."
And then Jexy says, "Hello, Stuber, you bitch.
"We are going to fucking fight."
And Stuber says, "Okay."
And Mike says--
(laughing)
- Okay.
- I kinda, you have like a style.
- Yeah, it's a very--
- Yeah, I mean it is like, it's like Wes Anderson,
you know, it's like, it's kinda mumblecore.
See, look, you're doing it,
it's based off your own speech pattern.
- All right, so then Mike says, "What the?"
See, that's like the third "what the?"
Okay, what the?
And then Jexy says, "Bring that ass over here so I can whoop it."
And Stuber says, "Listen, you Jexy, you phone bitch.
I'm gonna make your shit expand."
Is that a Samsung Galaxy S?
A little bit.
Yeah?
I'm gonna make your shit expand.
A little bit.
What's a little bit about the overheating phones?
Yeah, just a little bit.
I made it a little bit about that.
What are you talking about, dude?
Jexy.
Okay, you bitch.
You will be destroyed by my shit.
I'm going to make you kill yourself
and bring you back to life.
Shut up.
Shut up so he's going off script.
Oh my god, that has to be in the script now.
And then Stuber says you're gonna hurt so bad that you get your shit
And and that's when I stopped writing
That's that's when he decided to make a stage adaptation instead. Yeah, I have a I have another
Movie I was working on if you guys want to read the circle that well
Can we just can we can we figure out how Jackseed to ends first? Well, I know is it? Yeah, that's
Yeah, yeah, I have another movie I've been writing it's called um Bud Light Lime
It's about the creation of Bud Light Lime. Wouldn't you rather film that?
Well, I think we can read it, okay
I
Think I've already read it. But yeah, I've already read it. You do you man?
I don't think we've read it on the show. So this is like a sequel to the Bud Light movie
So no, this is the my own original movie. So it's a sequel to the blood light movie
Yes, it is a sequel. Yeah much like Jexy - yeah Pat just right see you write spec sequels and he sends them to
to
Companies and it gets blacklisted. He's been blacklisted ten times in Hollywood already. I
Don't think so. I think I'm writing three-page sequels writing James Patterson adaptations and delivering them by hand to his
Palm Beach home. I James Patterson and I
Actually talk to each other. No, you don't we talk to each other. Do not talk to the creator of maximum ride
We talk about I know you don't
Yeah, we do. I know what do you talk? What do you talk about? I know it's a maximum ride
No, they have other books. You know what I'm talking about. What other book?
I don't know. We name one other book besides maximum ride that James Patterson
We talk about--
You just make one up.
Enemy of the street.
Oh, enemy of the street.
I have another--
Mr. Alias.
Okay, that one wasn't good.
Mr. Alien.
Oh, Alien Ant Farm, that's a great--
(laughing)
What the fuck was that?
You cats are building bombs.
They are.
Yeah.
This is John Taffer doing a bar rescue of ISIS.
But I don't care about what files you have on your phone.
Yeah, put that down.
Just the sketches that he's...
Yeah, what if I just read my stand-up notebook?
Yeah.
I'm trying to find...
Put it down!
I'm trying to find Bud Light Live.
You're ruining this episode.
I'm not ruining the episode.
You already did.
Wow, this is officially the worst episode we've ever done.
It's the worst episode we've done because we can't fuck... there's too many fucking...
Because we can't fuck... do any...
There is one microphone.
You had one job.
There's two microphones.
I have a microphone as well.
Alright?
afraid to get close because he thinks I'm gonna steal a kiss is he right we'll see
no he's gonna be so quiet this whole episode cuz he insists I can't find I
can't find Bud Light Lime the movie oh no that won't even look at my eyes dude
there I don't know this is a weird setup weird what's weird about what's weird
about it it's hot in here friends why can't we be close guys can't look in
each other's eyes. He can't, he literally can't look at me for more than two seconds. Look
at that. He can't do it. He just looked into your eyes and started laughing. We're too close.
He can't look in my eyes. I, no. I mean, it's like trying to get a cat to look at you. He's
edging out of the camera as you're saying this. I'm not trying to do that. He's just
scooting away. It's okay. I smell bad. I woke up in a factory this morning. Yeah. Yeah. I
I stayed with somebody who lives in a factory in New York and then didn't sleep at all and
woke up with a roach on me and I went and moved in.
Nice.
It's pretty fucking sick dude.
I have another script here for...
Nice, what is this, Chucky?
This is my child's play sequel that I tried to write.
He does just write sequels.
That's right.
Yeah, I do write sequels.
It's how you make a living in Hollywood, Cameron.
I've actually learned to write...
They're kind of like the steel workers in Hollywood.
I kind of learned this from Alexander Bible.
He did tell me that the best way to make it in Hollywood as a script writer is to write
spec sequels.
Well, you know, he also did say that the best way to...
He said to get a CDL license too, which I have done.
He also, he did say that the best way to make it in Hollywood is to buy a horse and learn
karate so that if you can be in any possible movie they're making, if they need a horse,
they'll call you because they know you have a horse.
If they're making a karate movie, they know you have a horse.
And he also said to reenact the battle of Stalingrad using like, make a portal or something.
There was that one video where he went really unhinged.
That one was really good.
This is that guy you guys like watching...
Yeah, he's the Hollywood Secrets guy.
He tells us, "This is how we get into Hollywood."
Yeah, he's really awesome.
Caleb just turned his hat sideways, so you know...
Yeah, it's about to get real.
You know I'm about to listen to something.
Okay.
So this is a child's play...
What...
What movie are they on now?
I don't know. They don't have numbers in the names.
It's impossible to tell.
names up till three. All I remember is Bride of Chucky, and then there's Seed. I remember
Seed of Chucky and then Cult of Chucky. I remember being embarrassed. I think there's Sick. I think
there's yeah Sick. Well then there's the remake too. Oh okay so this would be a sequel to the
remake. Okay in the remake he's an app you know. Oh yeah. What? Um yeah. So the remakes Sick dude.
The way that he turns evil in the remake is so fucking funny.
They're making these app toys for kids and there's this big Chinese factory.
And the intro shows this Chinese worker guy who's being abused by his supervisor or whatever
and is really disgruntled.
And he's making one of the Chucky toys and he goes into the code.
And there's just like a switch, like an on/off switch that's like violence, and he turns it on and then kills himself.
I remember that. Sick, dude.
Dude, Mark Hamill does the Void.
Wait, that's the exact plot point from the Treehouse of Horror with the tiny Krusty doll.
The guy arrives and he's like, "Oh, the problem is he was switched to evil."
Yeah, that's literally the exact same thing.
Yeah.
Damn.
Alright, so this is the Child's Play.
Eight.
Child's Play 8 or 2 if they want to adapt this.
2/8.
2/8 if they want to adapt it to the reboot.
To the app.
Interior, Barney the Dinosaur Day.
Barney is on the set of his dumbass show being a moron as usual.
Barney I'm ready to do my fucking show Barney goes out to his toy chest like a
fucking baby and pulls out a mysterious doll Chucky hi I'm Chucky want to play
Barney something about this doll is not right
Barney puts the doll on the ground and starts to sing do you want to sing the
do you know I'll do yeah I love you you love mmm Chuckie shut shut the fuck up
bitch Chucky pulls out a spaz 12 and shoves it up Barney's purple ass I'm
back bitch and more evil than ever suey from family guy walks in do the voice
what the deuce that's how Stewie talks no
That's you right does sound exactly that sounds like Stewie you're right so he
says what the deuce and Chucky says damn I don't think I can be as evil as Stewie
and then Stewie and Chucky high-five Stewie and Chuck get a high-five so
that's the first that's how that movie would so that script seems to me kind of
like you forced an AI to watch 10,000 hours of Chucky and then it
It accidentally watched one hour of Family Guy.
Yeah.
Well, no, that's just...
He downloaded a zip file that had all the Chuckys and one episode of Family Guy and made it
watch it.
Yeah.
Well, that's actually the thing.
Family Guy is just like...
That's one of the things that they just train AIs on to study.
So that's how they develop the basic brain for the AI.
They made one episode of Family Guy written by humans and then the rest has been just
an AI watching it and then writing new ones.
Yeah.
Well, they have to, the writers of the show have to program the bots every week.
No, they have bots.
It's kind of writing.
They have bots that program the bots now.
Oh, they've outsourced it now?
That's why Stewie's voice has gotten farther away from British and more to whatever Patrick
is doing.
That's what modern is doing.
That was, there was a Geordie accent.
That was, yeah, that was great.
That was actually a Geordie accent.
It was wonderful.
God damn.
Do I have any more?
Do you have any more scripts?
more scripts. It was the scripts episode. The good play spec scripts. We're not reading that.
That's not even. Yeah pull that up. No. Come on man. No I did that for school too. Yeah
I did that. There's no shame in that. I had to do it for fucking a project. I did it too
I did an always sunny spec script. Oh I had some stupid fucking um. I had some stupid
fucking like arbitrary rule that it had to be a show in its first or second season and
I couldn't like I wanted to write a different one.
Well that's too bad.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
I'm so sorry dude.
Yeah I'm really sorry man.
So for some reason I can't open any of my other scripts.
Yeah alright here I'll just read my pilot.
Let's just read everything we've written.
Yeah Cameron pull up your awesome script.
I don't have any awesome scripts.
Yeah you do, dude.
You have that one called "Girls Gone Wild."
Yeah, pull up "Girls Gone Wild."
That's completely unscripted, okay?
No, you wrote a scripted version.
No.
"Girls Gone Wild" wrote the...
And I walk around and hand out copies of the script.
You have an open cast to call?
Yeah, so basically you're auditioning for a role as a girl in "Girls Gone Wild."
Here's the script.
I just need you to go wild.
Yeah, so just basically do exactly what the script says, and you have the part.
Fuck, dude.
I need to, I smell terrible.
Yeah.
That's why I'm not looking at you.
No, that's not true.
Yeah, because it's looking at people is what makes you smell them.
You're right, Patrick.
Yeah.
No, if you, because whoever smelled it, don't do it.
Well, the nose follows the eyes, said the wise man.
It's true.
I'm the one knows fall die said the eyes man. Whoa
The never soft eyeballs
Nice to be so terrified of that thing. Yeah, that's gore. That is that's uh
just up
Every never soft intro or every never soft logo to best for
Check this out
Not that it's gross it makes a sound and shit. Yeah. Yeah, it's not good. It's gotta be like a watermelon sound dude
I'm not gonna be able to play video games for like a week man damn. This is why cuz I'm moving oh, yeah
I have to pull if you unpack everything really quick. Yeah, if you just go really fast
I guess that could be like its own kind of video game. You could make you could I had to did you get your PC Pat?
Yeah, slept through it. He's lying. I did get it. It's here, but where where's here? No, it's in this
It's in the States
It's in the States, yeah, it is they sent you well
I say that because they sent me my monitor from fucking Australia. Yeah, and she's cool
It's upside down. Yeah, it's an upside down monitor. I try to move the mouse one way it goes the other it was kind of clockwise
I'm worried though because now if it's from Australia, I don't know if it's just an issue of the plug
I'm sending my left-handed son back to Australia
But yeah, they sent it with like one of those big fucking cords those big plugs
You need to get adapters for and the circle one the circle one with the prongs
Yeah, those adapters those outlets are evil. I hate those so much
Why doesn't everybody just speak English and use the right outlet?
Use normal outlets. Those outlets are like... Drive on the right side of the road, eat cheeseburgers.
Uh-huh. Those outlets are like way bigger than the ones... Right, it takes up more space on the wall.
Yeah. Because they have more power. No, no. No, it doesn't even have more power. It has less power.
It actually has double the power. No, it doesn't. Yeah, I think it does. No. No. Yeah, it's basically
Basically how you charge like a Tesla, this was one of those.
It is though, the Tesla chargers are that big.
I know dude, that's what I'm saying.
It uses, you have more power.
How many months of the Patreon do we need to do until we can share a Tesla between the
three of us?
Ooh, that's a good question.
One more if we play our cards right.
We play, alright if we play June Perfect, we can get up to like 60,000.
Yeah.
Let's do it.
How much those cards are?
60,000.
I don't know how much a Tesla is.
That's probably at least five.
Well, if it's a self-driving car,
I think I could get behind the wheel of it.
It's probably easy.
I saw people like, I saw a guy playing Angry Birds one time
while his Tesla was driving him to work in LA.
Yeah.
That's pretty sick.
I mean, it was, I was like--
That is, yeah, that is kind of a dream.
No, that kind of convinced me.
Yeah.
Yeah, the dream is just to play Angry Birds.
True.
Absolutely.
I just never have the time.
I saw a lady--
But if I didn't have to drive.
on her phone in an intersection near the McDonald's and she held up like a good lane of traffic
and then like got mad when everyone was honking at her and then stayed on her phone while
she crossed through the intersection and then like everybody trying to get through after
her just got super fucked up.
Pretty good.
I'm basically on the phone every single time I'm driving.
It's illegal in Massachusetts now.
It's illegal everywhere I think.
Well, it wasn't in Massachusetts, but it is now. You can't like touch your phone while you're driving.
The last bastion of free speech.
Right.
Yeah, I mean...
Like you weren't supposed to text, but you can't like, you can't like touch your phone. Like you can't hold it at all.
Janice's brother, every time he goes on a road trip, he just watches a movie while he drives.
I remember one time, he was like, he was going back to school from like visiting home, and he was like,
Yeah, man, I'm you know, the drives are suck, but I watch movies and make
What are you watching this time he's like I'm gonna watch Transformers 2 and sing
About like a singing pig
No, he was watching the one about like alligator American Idol. Yeah, I've seen that one with my nephews
What did you watch it in a rose in it? He plays the pig dude. Nick Kroll plays a German pig in that
He only got that role because of his billionaire father. Mm-hmm
Completely uh-huh above board but but but see someone got paid off for saying for sure. Mm-hmm
Yeah, that rocks dude. It rocks to be a comedian with a billionaire dad. Oh, yeah, I mean that's most comedians that are successful
Yeah, well, I would say most comedians have billionaire dads a lot of millionaires. Yeah, that is a
common through line
yeah, every comic in LA has like a
Dead dad and a rich mom a dead. Yeah. Yeah mom who's so rich because the dad died
Yeah, if you had much money - yeah, my dad actually died from too much money. It's so sad
So now I do stand-up comedy.
Aww, my dad died of money.
I write for the spin-off of Tuca and Bertie.
It's about two vaginas that kiss all day.
If your boyfriend doesn't want to watch this show with you, you dump him.
If your boyfriend doesn't eat your pussy while you watch Girl Regular Show, he's a fucking
chud, dude.
If your boyfriend is not just pounding away at your butthole while you're watching all
that, the reboot, but it's all girls.
Exactly.
Your boyfriend better, he better let you hold his balls while you watch a girl jackass.
An all-female reboot of No Russian.
If you could gender swap the main character, ideal game.
Yeah.
Greatest game ever.
I'm uploading, I'm doing it like an NBA 2K face scan to Modern Warfare so that the no
Russian guy looks exactly like me.
VR no Russian.
Oh fuck.
It's kind of what Superhot is.
No, in Superhot they have guns, they're trying to kill you.
They're trying to kill you with 5G mind control and no Russian.
That's why you have to attack, it's a pre-emptive strike.
Super hot, everyone in super hot looks like what we're going to look like once they install
5G.
Once 5G starts, time isn't going to move until we move.
And there's going to be too many people moving at once so it's just going to go normal.
What if the world already is super hot?
Whoa, yeah, the world's getting super hot could do to global warming and climate change
All right. I'll sit the rest this one out you guys
This you guys do your thing? Yeah, I just had to get that in you know, yeah, we're already listen
We're already we're already we're actually already in a super hot
virtual uh-huh, we're in
Caleb got here and just immediately ate a whole I mean I went he ate a whole from say your whole he got
Whole back in Boston it turned it turned me to the old me dude. Yeah, fucking eight
I got an American sub from 7-eleven and a sugar-free Red Bull nice and
I have not had alcohol or nicotine for three days. Oh good for you. I drank too much last night night
Yeah, I mean though they're gone now, but I drink of your trophies. No. I yeah, I left all my my beers up
I'm gonna mount every beer bottle I ever have.
It's a good idea.
Like a fucking, like a head.
Yeah, you should dedicate a whole room in your new place to be the empty beer can room.
Yeah.
I'll say.
Shit, you can't even get in?
Yeah, it's just...
It's just like from a week.
It's ceiling to floor, wall to wall.
Just full, there's no doorway anymore.
It's just...
I fuckin' last night I've been I felt like shit I feel like this is my third can of monster
today.
Yeah.
I uh I went to bed at like four and then woke up at seven and tried to like tough out the
day.
Oh no.
I went I went to CVS I tried to get a Pedialyte and they didn't have it.
I was gonna I was gonna do that I was gonna drink Pedialyte and then go back to bed and
then I.
A grown man in CVS getting one Pedialyte.
Yeah.
No so I bought a bag of beef jerky.
That's a red flag.
So nice, but I didn't find PD light. I think that you do
I think the one PD light is only a red flag if you're exactly Patrick's age
Did you have any older you could have a kid? Yeah, that's true. Well, I kind of look older. No, you don't
Yeah, I don't look 23. You look 20 or 22. I'm not even 23 you look
If I was 23, then you were no you think you look 23, but not 22
I
I think I look like I'm turning 24.
What?
Yeah, I look like today's my birthday.
Yeah, I actually look exactly one year older.
I look like exactly my birthday's today.
Exactly.
I just look like the kind of guy who would be having a birthday today.
Yeah, I just look like I was like a teen 12th birthday.
It's probably my crown.
It's probably my big birthday cake.
Probably my birthday hat.
I walk around with eating.
It's probably my big crown.
It's probably my ten friends that are always with me.
Yeah.
Celebrating me.
And the streamers.
It's probably because I'm...
birthday dress. I'm wearing my big birthday shirt. It says fuck you I'm Irish suck my nut.
It my birthday. It's my birthday. Master Chief fo President. We need to repeal the 19th amendment.
Nuts is better than nuts. Yeah. Which one's the 19th amendment? I don't know. Not a good
one buddy. You're seriously done for now. I'm freaking searching what the 19th amendment
is. Yeah. 19th. Absolutely, it's over. Is that women voting? Is that? Yeah, that's women
voting. You're in the clear. Clear. Yeah, you're safe. Safe! Master Chief, Master Chief
repealed the 19th Amendment. Wow, Master Chief just repealed the 19th Amendment and it's
Here's why that matters.
[laughter]
Vox explainer.
President Master Chief just repealed the 19th amendment.
Here's what that means.
Women can't vote.
It's a one sentence.
It's Carlos Mencia.
Carlos Mencia from Vox.
[laughter]
Gay wonk.
Carlos Mencia.
[laughter]
Trump is so DDD.
Trump is a freaking DDD dude. Yeah, you know, what's great Carlos Monsi is probably he's probably one of the most racist comedians of all time
Like he says like he's one of the he says shit Kramer wishes he said
If Kramer could have done it all again, he would have said exactly Carlos Monsi as jokes where he says like
Yeah, do it. I probably shouldn't say I
Watched I watched one of his specials from like 94
No, no, no, no, no from like the crazy thing is every single one of those jokes was stolen from Joe Rogan exactly
Well, I mean at least a couple of them like all the stuff about being Mexican. Yeah
Rogan you said two hours about how he was a Mexican guy. He's a guy even though he's from Costa Rica
Yeah, he was a cholo. Yeah, you know
There's like one Carlos Muncy, oh he's talking about Michael Jackson
and he says that Michael Jackson used to talk like "DAMN!"
It's just, it's one of the stupidest, dude it's one of the stupidest fucking things.
I mean, dude, in 2005 dude, that would have been.
Oh dude, it crushes.
I bet.
It crushes.
He says "Damn N-word N-word" and he says "Michael Jackson used to be like 'Damn N-word N-word'"
he points at a white woman and goes "now he looks like you!" and it kills the whole room.
It's insane.
This was before he died, this was before MJ died.
This was before Michael Jackson died.
This was before Carlos Mencia died.
Carlos Mencia will be dead by the time we release this episode.
That would be really funny.
Between right now and 7am Saturday morning June 13th, Carlos Mencia will be dead.
Yeah that could get us in trouble.
I feel like we had one moment like that right?
I I somebody posted on the podcast bell subreddit that I said that Nancy Pelosi
was a secret hotep and like and that's why she wore the kente cloth like 50 episodes
ago so I predicted that I predicted Joe Biden dying as well he died and I
predicted Patrick dying there. Don't say it. I did I already predicted it. I predict
Patrick will die in 12 years. Okay. 12 years. 12 years from now Patrick will be
dead. 12 years of Patrick. 12 years of Patrick. 12 years of Patrick. 12 years of Patrick.
saying 12 years of no 12 years a Patrick yeah Pat why do you write a script for that one
that's another one of his scripts yeah that is one of my scripts that did not go over
well they really they really didn't like my my crossover sequel where I was trying to
do Friday the 13th years a slave where Jason goes back to the Antebellum South yeah they
They didn't like that I pitched that to Nickelodeon at all.
Yeah, no.
They slimed you.
Yeah, they slimed me as soon as I said Friday the 13th, Years a Slave.
When you do a bad pitch at Nickelodeon, they just dump slime on you.
It's kind of like releasing the hounds.
Well, they also release the hounds.
You do go through a tube and you do end up at the old Nicktoons studio in Orlando.
And you have to fight your way out.
You have to do a battle for Bikini Bottom.
You gotta fight freaking Amanda Bynes to get out.
Oh my god, Jake.
remember her she went crazy on Twitter in 2013. Yeah she she went she wanted Drake
to kill her pussy. I'll kill it. Man if you listen I'll kill it. She's the man.
That movie, is that what the movie is called? Yeah, yeah. It's funny how like until 2009
that was a thing. Every year there's a movie that's like a bitch is a guy.
Yeah, this girl's pretending to be a boy. This girl wants to play paintball with her friends, but there's no girls allowed. It's guys only?
That was there was there was one that was like a BMX thing. Yeah, there was one with like a Chinese lady and she
Mulan. And she like yeah
Yeah, I forgot the plot of Mulan I couldn't continue that. There's a Chinese lady
And Eddie Murphy was there's this one where Eddie Murphy has to pretend to be a dragon so that he can hang out with Chinese people
It's kind of a play on the same thing.
They all had to pretend to be animated to be in that movie.
The BMX one is like, it's like, she's, I don't know why girls are not allowed to do BMX I
guess.
Well, for obvious reasons.
Same reasons they-
No, actually it's not even BMX, it's motocross.
Yeah, same reason they can't be fighter pilots.
They need three wheels at least.
Who was, someone was telling me that like women can't be fighter pilots.
It was me.
Oh, okay.
I was bragging.
You were bragging about being a fighter pilot.
One time I had a conversation with my mom about how you're not allowed to have, uh,
women are not allowed to serve on submarines.
Uh-huh.
For some reason.
And I told my mom that and she was like, "Yeah, I think that's how it should be."
And I was like, "What?"
And she was like, "What if the woman gets raped?"
What?
And I was like, "What are you talking about, dude?
Why would that be like, well, you're not allowed on the submarine because what?
Yeah, we don't want to try and stop you from getting raped.
We just want to make sure you don't go on a submarine.
Insane, dude.
Dude, what the fuck?
I mean, if you're over 30, you're completely insane.
Oh yeah, because they went to fucking, everyone over like 39 got their shit kicked out of
them by a nun at school.
Yeah, that's true.
And now they're all fucked up because of it.
Dude, I just had a conversation with my friend Sonny
back home who went to the same kindergarten with me,
the same like elementary school as me,
about my principal, Mr. Wolf.
And how he would--
Mr. Wolf?
His name was Mr. Wolf.
And he would like hit kids until like 2003.
Hell yeah.
And I guess he got woke.
Yeah.
He woke up, he done opened his third eye,
he smokes a DMT.
And he told me his son's name was like his son's name is like tiger wolf. It's like gun wolf or
So it's like so sick damn. Yeah guns wolf
gunner wolf
It might have been gunner gunner's a sick name dude. That is a pretty cool name
I'm gonna name my kid gunslinger
Yeah, I'm gonna my kid Shakira
slinger
Is my kid sling blade
My kid blade to blade Trinity. Yeah, my kids blade in Trinity
And that's our other boy Patton Oswald and blade Trinity
Now it's blade Trinity and to
Mm-hmm. The other kid is named - names - we call him blade - we call him - baka - we
We call we sometimes call him the one with Ron Perlman
I'm calling you think any like Funko pop dads right now that are having kids are gonna name their son like
like John wick O'Donnell
You know
And then it just grows up the Russo brothers Smith
This is my this is my son Bong Joon-ho
I just really loved Parasite.
So just a white kid named Bong Joon-ho.
The full name as the first name.
Bong Joon-ho Edward McNeil.
A white kid whose name is Bong.
That's the next president.
We need a kid with a weed name.
We need a kid president.
First of all, we need a kid president.
I've got some great news for you.
There's a video that you might want to watch.
Are you serious?
I think the guy from the office made it.
Kid president? Yeah, you made it.
The guy from the office, kid president?
The kid from the Oval Office.
Kid president.
Yeah, the guy from the Oval Office made it.
Yeah, Donald Trump's a kid.
What about, okay,
so here's a new spec script idea I just thought of.
All right, so you know the office.
No.
I've never heard of that.
Michaels, Pam, Jims.
Michaels, Pam?
Michael and Michaels, Pam.
Michael, Pam, Jim, Dwight, Oscar,
Oscar the gay grouch.
Leslie Knope.
The Schitt's Creek's.
You know, Chris Elliott.
Tuca.
Birdie.
- Bianca, Birdie, Bojack Horseman,
Gary Coleman, Emanuel Lewis.
- Rick's Morty Sanchez's.
- Tony Danza, Andy Kaufman, Judd Hirsch, Jeff Conway,
Mary Lou, what was the last one?
- Charlie and Mac and Sweet Little D.
- Yeah, so the office.
- Yeah, no, I know, okay, yeah, I know.
- So what about the Oval Office?
- So you mean like Space Force?
That's just Space Force.
I think he just got 8-0.
No.
So it's, so it's, so it's, um, what's that guy, Andy, Sam, no.
Oh, so Brooklyn Nine-Nine?
No.
That's who you're pitching?
Wow, he really wants to pitch Brooklyn Nine-Nine at this time?
Geez, dude.
Actually, he wants to pitch Brooklyn 100 because he 100% believes in the police.
I do, I know.
And supports them.
He does.
I only support, I only support a few, I only support the good ones.
You do not want to know which ones he thinks are the good ones.
Officer Wiggum.
Chief Wiggum.
Barney Fife.
The Dinosaur.
That episode of Louis where he plays a cop.
Michael Rappaport in the cop episode of Louis.
Bob Marley the comedian in Boondock Saints.
Yeah, no, I forgot he's in that movie.
- Butoxhead is so sick.
- Yeah, it's the best like dumb guy movie.
My uncle, my stupid Boston Irish uncle's like,
sat my mom down and were like, we need to watch this movie.
- Boston is the only like big city where people,
when movies are made here,
people from here think they're famous.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- People from here are like,
I'm famous 'cause I live in Boston.
- Oh, dude, they put fucking Watertown in the fucking town.
- Yeah, nobody in Chicago is like,
They pretty much filmed the Dark Knight here, so I'm like a star right like everybody here has a story about meeting Denzel
Uh-huh, yeah, like yeah, basically I was I basically I ate isn't Gus's dad in the town
Gus's dad is in every single movie
I remember when I remember in in high school when Black Mass had a premiere and like every kid came
Oh, yeah, yo my parents met Johnny Dapp
It was like no. No they weren't going to the premiere of Black Mass
I guess I lived when I was like three I lived around where Whitey Bulger did his
operations so I was in that movie too. Yeah. I lived a little bit near
Winter Hill where the Winter Hill Gang operated. Probably a toilet that you used. No I was
actually in the Winter Hill Gang. You were? I know Whitey Bulger. Whoa. Boston movie
mindset is so awesome. I think I've talked about it before, but in the Godzilla King
of the Monsters and the second Godzilla, the final battle is in Boston and it starts in
Fenway Park. I saw it in IMAX opening night and whenever they showed a Boston landmark
just getting completely destroyed, everyone in the audience cheered. They were just destroying
like destroying... And now they're freaking out about looters? Come on. Yeah. Yeah. I think
the problem is... We're worried about Godzilla. Yeah. They're cheering on Godzilla but they
hate looters. They do the same thing pretty much. I sense a double standard here. Yeah.
The problem is that the looters didn't have a Godzilla. Godzilla is protesting. Something
tells me you'd be talking different if Godzilla was black. Yeah, what's next? A black Godzilla?
(laughing)
- Have you seen, Cameron, have people talked to you
about Mystic River at all?
You're from around here.
- No, but I'm very aware of Mystic River.
I haven't seen it, but yeah.
- What that is.
- I haven't seen it either, but I know that like--
- Yeah, that's a Boston movie mindset movie for sure.
- Yeah, my mom's uncle's car is in a shot.
- Nice.
- Thank you for getting that.
- I'm just gonna hair out of Patrick's penis.
I pulled it out. It was a bunch knotted together like handkerchiefs from a clown pocket.
Yeah.
You pulled, it was a hair coming out of his penis and you pulled it and his tongue went down his throat.
[Laughter]
It was the end of his tongue.
He just unraveled like the Weezer song.
Yeah.
Into a pile of yarn.
Mm-hmm.
Like Caleb's Weezer song.
No.
Mm-hmm.
No, I never made a Weezer song.
[Laughter]
I never did.
Um.
Is that it?
Yeah, no, the Boston movie is great because they make everything in New York and LA, so it doesn't count.
Even when they make a movie that's like, "This movie is about LA."
It's not interesting because every movie is about LA because they're all made there.
But when a movie is about freaking Boston, you know it matters.
This movie is a love letter.
This movie is a love letter to the marathon getting bombed.
Yeah.
And we want to...
Oh, how was... Yeah, how did you... Because I didn't...
I don't remember. I don't think I was in high school when that movie came out.
I've definitely I definitely have told this story before but I was when it happened I was playing I was you know the movie
Oh the movie. Oh the movie. No, I didn't hear anything about from the movie. Nobody. I was I think I was uh
Then they have dead mark. Yeah, were people mad about the movie. I don't think I think some people
There was one with Mark Wahlberg where Mark Wahlberg like saves the day in America. Yeah. Yeah kills
Yeah, people were mad over that one. I'm gonna get over there get up get all the fucking brothers
But then I'm gonna get my brothers to get there
We're gonna turn him into fucking bird fights.
The ultimate brother fight.
How many tsarnaevs does it take to take down six Wahlbergs?
Well I don't know, they're kinda like, Russia's in, some parts of Russia are in Asia.
Whoa, that's true.
I think a Wahlberg would have an advantage.
Yeah, you might be right.
But then there was the Jake Gyllenhaal one where he has no legs.
Oh yeah.
Where he plays the guy who got owned.
Yeah.
I didn't hear that much about the second one people were definitely mad at the first one
But also people liked the first one as well because it's Mark Wahlberg
You can't not like Mark Wahlberg in a fucking Boston. Yeah, what's not to like? I love the recent like like
People online trying like who are just now realize. Yeah, I just found out about an entire page
Right Wikipedia just says hate crime. Yeah, like we like people have been that's why people like him
That's why he's burger so good. That's why he's a celebrity. That's like getting mad at Hulk Hogan for having that for the wrestling section on his
Did you know Hulk Hogan pretends to wrestle
This is seriously not. He also he also pretends to have a 12-inch penis. Did you know that? He has a 12-inch penis, dude
The Hogan, Hulk Hogan the character, but Terry
Whatever his last name is he had to say this in court
He had to say Hulk Hogan the character has a 12 inch penis while Terry whatever his last name is has a 5 inch penis
*laughs*
Dude that, the gawker thing was so, that was such a weird moment in like
2010 I remember cuz I just remember being very
Upset in junior year of high school that I did not see the Hulk Hogan sex tape
Yeah, cuz there's a there's a part in it where he tells the woman he tells Bubba the love sponge's wife
He says God. I can't believe I was eating like a pig 20 minutes ago
(laughing)
And I only saw that quote,
and I just remember just being so mad not--
- That you didn't have the full context.
- I didn't have him and his voice.
- Can you imagine, like, imagine
fuckin' society completely collapses,
we have no record of any story or video.
- That's why they wanna shut down the internet archive.
- That's right.
- So that they don't have the--
- But what if we have to go back to the verbal tradition,
and it's somebody just describing the Chuck Berry sex tape.
Like how- that would literally balloon into Christianity.
*laughter*
And so a man made a woman smell his fart.
And thus he did say, "Your can smell my fart."
*laughter*
And she did.
And it was good.
*laughter*
God, I need to watch that video again. It's been too long.
Dude, yeah I know.
I've run out of all videos.
is still named you can smell my fart.
- It is called your can smell my fart.
- The way he fucking says it too.
- You're gonna smell my fart.
(laughing)
- It's incredible.
- I mean it's so relaxed.
And she just says yes.
You like it when I--
(laughing)
You like it when I pee on you, huh?
- Oh yeah, he fucking pees on me.
- He starts pissing, that's when,
dude he's farting, he's using her like a urinal.
And then he farts while he's sitting there.
I wouldn't even fart on a urinal.
That's so rude. If there's someone else in the room,
I'll hold it in.
I will hold it in walking to the stall
and pretend shit.
How did the Chuck Berry sex tape get out is what I want to know.
He published it.
For a media release.
He posted it on eBaums.
He got in trouble because he had a restaurant.
And he was farting in the food.
Yeah, he's farting in the food. No, you can taste my fart
Get like a restaurant or like a club you gonna smell my foot and he was he had cameras installed in the women's bathroom
Oh that happened in the same problem
Problem the same problem that's a sort of issue arose at a record store in my hometown. Oh, yeah
Yeah, the guy got in a bunch of trouble
But he was just like I think I don't think he wanted this like how many women are coming into the video game and right?
You know, so if it was boys, it's fine. It's true. Yeah, it would have you would have gotten away with it
If it weren't for those meddling women, that's right. Yeah, I'm trying to ruin the the boy sesh
Yeah, he just wanted to feel like he was chilling with his bros
Even when they're in the bathroom, he's like this, you know, like we might as well have a camera in cameras bathroom right now
Just yeah, we don't and we just want to clarify that we don't have one. Yeah
And we definitely don't.
They discovered the camera in the record store because he was like talking to one of his
friends and then his friend was like, "Alright, I have to go to the bathroom, see you in a
while."
And he said, "I'll see you sooner than you think, my friend."
And they watched a full-scale investigation.
Yeah, he's not super conspicuous.
Yeah, his friend was an FBI agent.
His friend actually had a camera magnet in his pocket and the camera jumped on his magnet.
His friend was playing poppy jump on the toilet and he walked out and he said, "Nice score
on poppy jump on the toilet."
He said, "What?"
This guy's psychic.
He was playing poppy chuco jump.
Poppy chuco jump.
I tried to make a, when I was a kid and apps were first coming out.
I downloaded the Apple SDK.
Yeah, man.
I programmed a poppy jump knockoff,
and I was like, I'm gonna make a million dollars from this.
But then it cost $99 to put on the App Store.
Yeah, I remember wanting to make an app.
I thought that was the money level cap when I was a kid.
Yeah.
I didn't know you had more than that.
It is.
What'd you eat?
I heard that, yeah.
Oh, what did I?
A sandwich. Camera man, speak.
I had a sandwich, that's what I ate.
Oh my god, me too!
I had Chipotle earlier.
I saw the chips in your cup drawer.
Yeah, I went to the store today, I bought hot dogs.
Ooh, you know the store.
He's getting bold.
Yeah, I've been to the store a few times.
Oh!
Oh, good for you big guy!
I wouldn't assume that.
I wouldn't assume you've been a man at the store before.
No, I go to the store all the time.
No, you're too big of a baby.
No, I go to the store pretty much every single, twice, three times every single day.
I've been going to the store too much.
I know.
Too damn much.
You always go to the store too much.
That's like your thing.
Yeah, it's true.
That's like one of your traits.
That's like the...
Yeah, you look at Patrick and you're like, "This is a guy who goes to the store a lot."
Yeah.
Something about you makes me think you go to the store a ton.
Are you a smart shopper?
I almost worked for...
I almost worked.
I must worked for
Stop and shop peapod. Yeah, and then I found out that I
Accidentally like I thought I was signing up for like one of those shopper positions and I accidentally applied to be a truck driver
Definitely a try accidentally applied to drive the peapod truck do
Stop, I've definitely thought about driving a truck. Yeah. Yeah, dude you I mean they make so much money
Oh, yeah, I mean they get to kill themselves and nobody there's a big there's a glaring issue there
You need a CDL and a regular license easy to get a CDL
Yeah, my cousin they pay for the course if you like apply to be a truck driver. Yeah, most companies
Most like freight companies will just pay for you to go take the CDL class and shit
and my a friend of mine his dad drives a truck and
they're in like more debt than any person I've ever met.
So, true.
That really pushed me to think about it.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- It sounds good.
- Plus you get to sleep in the cab.
- Honestly, that's why I wanted to go to London.
It's like free apartment.
I mean, they all have TVs in them.
- Yeah, you can watch a movie.
- And if you're trucking through like the South,
a lot of the South has,
they have casinos in the truck stops.
- Yeah, they're gonna say in the trucks.
- You can have a full casino, there's strip clubs in the truck.
- That's what they have in the trailer.
That's what you think it's all like stuff
they're shipping or whatever,
they're taking from one place to another.
It's actually just a big casino.
- It's a big poker room.
- Yeah.
- You open up the--
- It's a bunch of dogs playing poker.
- Yeah, it's a bunch of dogs playing poker.
- Yeah, smoking cigars.
One of the dogs has weed.
One of the dogs is eating chocolate.
Yeah, so you know they're bad boy dogs.
- Yeah, he's doing what he's not supposed to.
- Yeah, he's doing a naughty--
Chocolate is kind of the weed for,
weed is chocolate for humans.
Yeah.
Weed is to humans, but chocolate is to dogs.
Chocolate is kind of like the humans of weed.
Chocolate.
Humans of weed.
Yeah, chocolate is kind of like the humans of weed.
That's our new Instagram account.
Humans of weed.
(laughing)
Humans of smoking weed.
Yeah, just pictures of guys who look exactly alike
over and over again.
Yeah, so basically I was playing,
I was playing Thug Pro the other day.
(laughing)
I was listening to Santa Maria.
I was listening to Tool.
Yeah, my life's been awesome.
(laughing)
Pretty much nothing has gone wrong.
We could do a coffee table book that has like a,
it has like a, you could double it as like
a place to roll joints.
Oh.
It has a joint roller.
It has a joint roller built in.
Whoa.
And it's actually, the pages are made out of weed.
Yeah.
You can smoke the book.
You can smoke the, you just take off,
It's like an origami calendar book where you do one a day,
you smoke one page a day.
Yeah.
Yep.
And also it's called the Bible.
Oh my God.
How do they make those thin ass pages?
Yeah, they squish it.
They make the Bible, it's like five times bigger
than it normally is and then they squish it down
in a big hydraulic press to make the pages thin.
They put it in the microwave from Wakan Waka.
They put it in the microwave and it gets really big
and then they squish it down.
Have you ever,
you ever have a friend in high school
who smoked weed out of Bible paper?
No.
That's cool though.
Yeah, of course, yeah.
I knew a kid who--
I knew a kid who did it
and people got very upset with him.
Yeah, people were like,
what a fucking piece of shit,
how would you do that?
And it's like--
You ever smoked a weed?
'Cause it's cool.
You ever smoked weed out of a $1 bill?
No.
Have you done that?
It's just a cool idea I had.
(laughing)
It's just kind of something I've been thinking about.
I've been thinking about. It's not a bad idea. Yeah, it's kind of a good idea. Kind of the best idea.
I think maybe you're not, I don't think they they catch on fire very well.
But how did the Joker do it then?
It's called movie magic. It's all CG. Yeah. It's all, including the makeup. It's all, it's all
cash and goings. Yeah, cash and goings.
Just cash and goings.
Dude, I'm uh
I'm having to shit pretty bad right now. Yeah, we're done
What it's funny that I always we start and I always have to shit a little bit and then an hour in I have
I yeah, that's you know, that's so interesting how that happened. I wonder Wow. I wonder how that works
Yeah, why is it never the other ways around?
Hmm, I always have an hour clock that I know. Mm-hmm. I'm gonna shit my pants talking to camera makes you shit
Yeah, that's what it is. Yes any girl really I get nervous. Okay. Oh
Turn it off turn it off no stop recording