You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
We need to get that out of your head.
We can watch TV.
Patrick is obsessed with the idea that we can just watch TV during an episode.
Patrick's obsessed with TV. You just want to watch TV during everything.
So?
What's so bad about that?
I would say it's not conducive to a podcast, just to watch TV.
Absolutely. You guys, the men who want to do a watch along to the Grinch.
Yeah, that's different from an episode.
That's watching a movie. That's not TV.
TV is where you watch a movie.
Not true. No.
There's a hard line between TV and movie.
There is not. There is.
My cord is stuck.
Oh, I need to get this off.
I need to tell you guys this before I forget.
I saw today. Such a rush.
greatest I am in a rush I'm on I'm speedy tonight I have somewhere to be we're
gonna put an hour episode in 55 minutes tonight that's what we're gonna do I'm
gonna squeeze it in I I saw just like the greatest like private school moment
I've ever seen I was dropped saw the greatest privates he's ever seen no no
all right back off you're okay I'm not gonna tell you the story it's really
good it's fine no look at me again look at me again no okay so this is what
happen I was I was picking up the kid that I babysit it goes to a private
school I'm gonna hit stop on the recorder I want to start it over I was
picking him up, not by the genitals, I was picking him up and this kid was
getting dropped off also at school, like this private school kid was getting
dropped off like in an escalade, like right next to where I was walking by and
he like opened the door and he like jumped out, he's maybe like 12 years old,
slammed the door like in a huff and started walking away and his mom rolled
down the window of the car and said "Alexander! Alexander! Alexander!" and then
and drove up next to him to like try to get his attention.
And this is like the coldest shit I've ever seen.
The kid turned around and looked his mom in the eyes
and said, "Drive," and then she peeled away.
- Oh my God.
- Oh my God, so fucking cool, dude.
I have not stopped thinking about this kid.
- Oh my God.
- He just said, "Drive," and that bitch was gone, dude.
She was, oh my God, dude.
- Whoa.
- Yeah, he was like the kid from the Twilight Zone episode
where he's God.
- Yeah.
But yeah, I just had to get that.
That sounded like a guy.
Yeah.
Yeah, there was a guy noise.
There's a guy in here somewhere.
There's a guy just going, "Ahh."
I can smell him.
I smell guys.
Yeah, what have you guys been up to?
Can you tell the story again slowly so we can think of more funny things to say about
it?
She said drive and then Caleb walked up to the kid and said, "I'll drive you crazy with
my penis."
No.
I don't drive anybody crazy with my penis.
No, I mean I drive girls crazy with my penis.
You drive a guy, you drive a boy named Alexander crazy with your penis.
I've been getting so many gay direct messages on Twitter asking to see my penis.
It's because of your video.
Yeah, you know, it's really funny.
I never thought that uploading a video of me eating a condom and saying I'm going to
fuck you in the ass would warrant so many gay direct messages.
And then saying your fiancé with one e instead of two.
And then accidentally misspelling fiancé in a homosexual way.
Accidentally.
It was an accident.
I didn't know that there was two ways to spell it.
I spelled it phonetically.
Right. I thought you didn't spell it phonetically because you would have written F-E-E-Y-O-F-A-E-E
We have different phonetics.
F-E-E-Beyonce.
Yeah, it might be Beyonce.
Fee Beyonce.
Imagine if her name was--
Wait, Beyonce only has one E.
Oh my god, she a man.
Beyonce is a guy.
He-once.
He-once. He-once.
That's like a New Orleans catchphrase, comedian.
He on say, he on say, and I say, he on say.
The bit loo to me out there, he on say.
The bit.
You're me.
I was looking at those New Orleans--
New porn pictures of babies?
[LAUGHTER]
Yes!
I got you back!
You can't fuck with me, OK?
I'm too speedy tonight.
You scared him.
Good.
He's a cat.
So--
It's not a him, he's a cat.
He's my friend.
No he's not, he's your slave dude. You have slaves.
I got little white slaves.
You have white slaves dude.
Yep.
Damn bro.
That's how you know you got money.
That's how you know it's real, when you got the white slaves.
That's true.
That's how you know you're on top. Top of the game.
Yeah you are on top.
Yeah cause I have a guy.
You're on top of a guy who's your slave.
Yeah you guys.
No.
Yeah.
We wouldn't have said it in the third person.
You're looking for a third person.
No you are.
For your gay marriage.
No, no, I don't have that. You're gay married to a man. Yeah, his name's Bobo Bubkus and he's a clown.
*laughter*
Yeah.
Bobo Bubkus?
His name's Bobo Bubkus and you're Mrs. Bubkus.
You fucking piece of shit.
No.
Drive.
Yeah.
No.
I thought it would work.
All I did today, I set up a driveway out of the living room.
I set up a new board.
With a...
Well, a Chinese board.
Mm-hmm.
So you put a Chinese board up in your house?
Oh no, that's Japanese writing.
that's an old one. Those are both old boards that I got Cameron drew on one of them.
Cameron drew.
A cup?
Yeah, I got a little cup on it.
He drew the cup.
I drew the cup.
What did you draw?
I drew on the other side.
He drew a guy hanging. I want to see that.
A guy hanging from his feet because Patrick told me it was upside down right at the end
and I was like, "Oh, I don't know what to do now." So, I made him hanging from his feet.
So, the body's kind of not drawn well.
Yeah.
Oh, that's cool.
He looks like a...
So guys if you guys are listening at home imagine a guy hanging upside down.
And then that's what he'll look like if he's hanging normal.
He looks like a raving rabbit.
Yeah.
No.
He looks like a raving guy.
What?
Yeah, I think we can't have Patrick on the podcast anymore after he said that.
Yeah.
You're kicked off.
What?
You're kickflipped.
That sucks.
I wish I was not kickflipped off.
Also, it's in my cruiser board.
It also glows in the dark.
so does Cameron, it's not that cool.
- I was telling Patrick about this.
I was saying, how the fuck does glow in the dark stuff work?
You like charge it up in the light
and then it like shoots out light in the dark?
That's crazy, it's just paint.
- Yeah, it holds the light, I don't know.
- Yeah, isn't that insane?
I never thought about that until today,
until Patrick was trying to get me
to look at his glow in the dark board.
- Yeah, and there wasn't enough,
there's not enough light in here
'cause I'm in a garden light.
- I know what you're talking about.
- Yeah, his penis is glowing.
- My penis is not glow in the dark.
- His board?
- Yeah.
- What is that, like his feet?
- I don't want to say it on the episode.
- He have board foot.
- Yeah, Patrick's feet glow in the dark
'cause of all the fungus.
- We should make a surfing documentary
like the Endless Summer or whatever.
- I don't know how to surf.
- Me neither.
- I actually know how to surf.
I could probably learn how to surf.
- Yeah, I know how to surf the web.
- Yeah, I know how to go on Reddit.
- Yeah, that's right.
- How many surfing, it's so crazy
can die while surfing I don't know that's interesting that's not I'd say no no
that's interesting no no cuz this means that Patrick doesn't know that you can
die doing anything no I know you can die whenever just imagine just imagine just
having just like a good time just like you're surfing like do you think it's
weird to die when you have your fun should protect you yes I just learned I
agree did you know you could die skate by all you yeah I know no I know you can
die do it I'm just saying it's you I just learned you can die at the movies
it's learned you can die when you get too old you can die at a country music
concert. Dan Bilzerian should have helped those people I thought that he was
if they if they gave Dan Bilzerian the AR he could have taken out Steven
Paddock. He would have no scoped him just for the walls. He would have spun in the
fucking air. He would have done a 360 off of fucking Kenny Chesney's big hat yeah
And fucking hit Stephen Paddock right between the eyes.
Yeah, red dot scope.
It's so strange, just like imagine you're doing something that you like doing and it's like,
"Oh shit, I'm about to die."
That's true.
Like surfing is crazy because getting killed by water, like a wave.
Getting killed by water is like...
What?
What are you talking about?
Getting killed by a big wave is crazy to me.
You don't, well, I think, you know,
people do get killed by the big waves,
but I think they mostly get killed by coral
that like cuts their neck.
No, I thought that the wave, like the--
That happens to me.
The waves can crush them.
Yeah, I thought like, no, I'm saying like,
it's crazy to me that like a wave could break
somebody's neck or something like that.
Okay, so it took you so long to get to the point
that now you're saying you don't understand water pressure.
No.
Okay, that's, all right.
Yeah, I don't understand water pressure.
I think that's the problem.
I don't understand many things.
It's crazy that if you have water instead of air in your lungs you can die.
Yeah.
It's just crazy that if you have fire in your lungs instead of air you can die from
that.
It's fucking bizarre, man.
What I said made sense in the head.
It made no sense.
It made sense in your head.
Yeah, it made sense.
I know the very end.
It made sense but I had to get there.
It also makes sense in your head to just keep buying skateboards and being unemployed.
No, I had those.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I got you.
that one I made when I was like 15. Oh you made a skateboard? You're a boardsmith?
Well I just cut the shape. Okay that's not impressive to me. So it was a normal
skateboard and then you cut the shape? Yeah. That's not making a skateboard. Well
I cut the shape, I painted it, I put the glow-in-the-dark stuff on it.
But it was already a skateboard. What do you think the characters in
Rocket Power are doing nowadays as adults? They're probably smoking
weed no dude they're smoking nah dude smoke it power smoke it power yeah
what's rocket power you ever watch rock I haven't bought a skateboard since like
you only watch like PBS growing up yeah yeah yeah rocket power was a
sick Nickelodeon cartoon that was about people with backwards hats and kids who
were acting acting their age mm-hmm
it's the best description I think you're gonna get about that show yeah they
would kickflip and they had a big fat friend and he was good at roller skating
and being a goalie and he could see they played hockey for some reason yeah
street hockey they did like a lot of everything extreme yeah it's street
hockey is not that extreme um it was for them dude it's pretty cool
also yeah fun but it's not like not fun it's not like I think that shows why
like I kids thought it was cool to like just be a group of friends that just like
skateboarded and did nothing.
No.
Yeah it was that show.
Yeah it was.
Well I mean skateboarding there's already like...
No but like that's why a lot of people got into skateboarding.
To the mainstream I guess I think that more...
Because it was like young...
More Tony Hawk if anything.
No but this that was for...
Rocket Power was for a younger audience than Tony Hawk.
Rocket Power was like elementary school.
That was like when I started like...
I was an inline rollerblader.
Ooh.
Yeah.
I think it was Most Extreme Primate.
Yeah that too.
What's that?
That's the movie where the monkey does... Is that the one with the skiing?
He does hockey.
The first one is hockey, the second one...
What's the first one? Vertical?
No, the second one is most vertical primate.
So the first one is extreme?
Yeah, MXP and then MVP.
But then MVP has... Bob Bernquist had a very...
Oh no, it's most valuable primate is the first one.
Yeah, and then most vertical is the second and then most extreme is the third.
Yeah, but most vertical is the one with Bob Bernquist.
Most valuable is the ice hockey one.
Who's Bob Bernquist?
Bob Bernquist. He's the guy, he was the guy who was always second to Tony Hawk in the Tony Hawk
games.
Oh, yeah.
So, alphabetically, there would be like Tony Hawk and then it would go alphabetical. So,
you know, like as a kid, I thought Bob Bernquist was just as famous as Tony Hawk.
As TH.
But he wasn't.
No, nobody was.
MVP, Most Valuable Primate, is a 2000 feature film that sparked the MVP franchise.
The film's title character, Jack, is a funny monkey. Citation needed.
Citation needed. Hey, that fucker's not that funny.
I'll add a citation. I'll be an expert witness.
Yeah, I saw the movie. It's pretty funny.
Yeah.
Yeah. You got like 20 citations. I watched this movie. I laughed at Jack.
Your name's Jack?
Yeah, just said that.
Go to most vertical.
All right.
Go to the Wikipedia page.
Why do monkeys get people names but dogs don't?
Well monkeys are closer to humans than dogs. But they're not Jack close. Well
they're, I mean what about Jack the Jack Russell Terrier? That's a kind of dog.
Yeah but his name is Jack. He also has terrier in it. See if he was Jack Chimp.
Maybe. Jack Russell Chimp? Jack Russell Chimp. This one says the film's title character Jack
is a fictional chimpanzee. Oh no. He's a real chimp. He's fictional. Yeah. Is this the same
chimp from uh Duncan? Is this Duncan? No it's not Dunstan. Dunstan was an orangutan.
Really? Or whatever. I don't know.
Um, is he? I think he might be a chimp.
Yeah, he's a chimp. Dunstan was an orangutan.
Oh yeah, he's not a chimp.
Yeah, yeah, he's definitely not a chimp.
Um, wait, I'm trying to get to most extreme primate.
Wait, was Bob Burnquist not in the sequel?
Was he in most extreme? I don't know.
Which one has Bob Burnquist? I didn't see Bob Burnquist in any of them.
Uh...
Most extreme primate just brings you back to the other ones.
This is compelling.
What the F?
Bob Burnquist did the...
I'm gonna freak out right now.
now. At an organic farm. Really? Yeah. It was cool. It was featured heavily in the Tony
Hawk's Project 8. The organic farm? Burnquist Organics was like a shoe you could wear. Tony
Hawk's, Tony Hawk taught me that farts were funny. Mm-hmm. Tony Hawk's Underground 2?
Yeah. The jackass one? It's the best one. Yeah, it is the best one. At the end you have
to escape Bam Margera's house. That's not his house, that's Skate-topia. No, it's his
house. No, he doesn't live in Skate-topia. Yeah, he does. Skate-topia's in Ohio. No, he
family's in Westchester. What was the why is the reason that it is exploding?
BAM put a bunch of fireworks in it. Just a classic BAM move. It was on the world
destruction tour. Oh that's what it was yeah. So the first mission you... On this tour we're
gonna destroy the world. Yeah you set up you you blow up Boston. Yeah yeah. You blow up
the Big Dig with the cannons and the Boston Common that's not it's next to the
Big Dig. That one pissed me off. The geography of Boston in Tony Hawk's
Underground 2 makes no fucking sense. They always fuck it up in video games. They did the same in
the new Fallout game. Yeah, like you can walk to Salem. The box of common is like as big as this
room. You can walk to Salem from fucking Concord. Yeah. That's fucked up. Yeah, come on Fallout,
get it together dude. Make it realistic. Yeah. And they got Skyrim, they nailed Skyrim. Also,
Fallout's wrong because there's a bunch of people in Boston. That's true. And the buildings all have
like windows and stuff. Yeah, they got the mutants right though. It was fucking horrible.
There is a ghoul in downtown Boston. There is. There is a literal ghoul. That guy with the
hobbling guy? There's a guy who looks like a Fallout ghoul who stole somebody I know's bike
and then the guy chased him down and he was like, "Can I have my bike back?" and the ghoul was like,
"Yeah." And he just gave it back. Yeah. That's pretty sick. Speaking of just the...
Just a ghoul move. He's like more of a prankster than a thief.
You guys ever deal with the really young homeless kid?
The real young homeless kid?
The real young?
The one who hangs out at South Station?
No.
Oh man, he's...
I don't go to South Station ever.
Yeah, me neither.
What does he do?
He, the first week I was there...
Is he bugging?
When I was, yeah, the first week, I like, because I used to commute here.
I was waiting for like a train or the bus to go back home at South Station.
I was smoking a cigarette.
Then I gave him a cigarette and he was asking me for money for a ticket to Manchester and
I was like, "No, I don't have cash."
And then he tried to talk to like a clearly gay man.
And the gay--
What was so clearly gay about him?
Yeah, what's up with that?
His shirt?
His penis.
His penis was out?
No, but he tried to talk to a gay guy and then the gay guy ignored him and then he went,
"Go paint your nails!"
Whoa.
It's like--
Go paint your nails.
your nails. Go paint your nails F-A-G-I-T and then I went into the McDonald's.
If you just say go paint your nails that's like a five-year-old.
Go play with Barbie. Fucking doo-doo brain. Go play Mary-Kate and Ashley Switch 16 for PS1.
Yo I just found, I just found Janna's DS with all the bunch of fucking games. I'm about to play Brain Age and get fucking...
- My DS Classic is broken, but I still have my 3DS
in that pink pouch.
- 3DS is a good one.
It's pretty cool, it is pretty cool.
- Yeah, I have a flash cart for the 3DS,
oh no wait, 'cause you got a plain DS.
I don't have a flash cart for the DS.
- It's a DS Lite, the one that I have.
And it's pink, but it's not like--
- It's pink like a polo shirt.
- It's pink, but I don't write about boys in it or anything.
- Yeah, you picto chat with guys on there.
You picto chat a guy.
- You dicto chat on there.
what I got. I also, Janet gave me a pink moleskin notebook. Oh this is mine? Yeah.
But I'm writing like regular guy stuff. Absolutely. I'm writing the word pussy
over it. I'm just writing. Yeah I dot my eyes with skulls not hearts. Yeah I'm a really tough guy. Yeah. Yeah.
And I write, I write with my pencil in my fist and I rip the pages when I write.
Yeah it's a completely unusable notebook. Dear diary! I gotta compensate for the pink thing.
today i ate a sticker people don't even believe it's mine because i don't i they say i say can
i have my notebook it's because i left it on the bar and they say they say i don't see a
notebook that could possibly be yours what's that it's an expired uh uh mythical i think
we missed packs yeah we did i think it was this oh my god yeah i wouldn't have had i saw someone
yeah i wouldn't have had money level 100 genesect holy crap what are these cars patrick is giving me
Pokemon did this expire? Yeah they're both expired. TMNT the video game. Damn this
is from 2017. Yeah that came in remember CEX and Downtown Crossing? Yeah I got a
copy. The sex store. I don't know what you're talking about. It was a like a used electronics and
video game store it was just called sex. I'm pretty sure it's a chain. What is this?
So you get a micro SD card you put that in there you can download DSi ROMs
online. Whoa! That is cool. That's sick. What happens if you put...
You cannot play, you cannot, I will not be giving you Dora Saves the Mermaids.
You will not be taking this from me. You sure? I want Dora Saves the Mermaids. I
bet you do. Yeah you do. It'd be fun. Yeah you do want it. These also aren't my
games, these are Dom's. I just feel bad for the mermaids. I don't know, it's not
about Dora I just I just want to save the mermaids. I can't sleep at night if I know that beings
are suffering. The game is like that documentary The Cove with the where the
Japanese people are eating the dolphins but it's I've never seen it no it's a sad
one there's basically there's a place in in Japan where Japanese fishermen just
like catch dolphins and eat their brains through a straw it's pretty funny.
- Montana, Montana.
- Montana for DS.
- You better tell me that's a dress up game.
- Oh yeah.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I think so.
- Oh yeah.
- I also have Strawberry Shortcake Strawberry Land games.
- Is that a dress up?
- Oh, and there it goes onto the floor.
Patrick dropped the game onto the floor
and it broke in half.
- This is distributed by American Greetings,
Game Factory, and Dick.
Yeah, that's you.
Remember Dick?
No, do you?
Is it the game?
- Yeah, you remember Dick, dude.
you remember every single time it was the children's like dick that used to go
into your ass it was like a children's entertainment thing they like it was
the logo at the end of all the inspector gadget cartoons and it was like a star
it was like a star shooting star and then it goes into a circle and it's a
little kid's voice and he goes "Dick!"
Nice. Pull that up, pull up the dick logo. Dick logo? No, pull it up dude.
Yeah, pull it up. D-I-C logo. Why'd you go incognito?
Is your mom gonna check your browser history? I just don't like having that kind of stuff in my history, alright?
Dick logo. What were you really thinking?
Dick.
Okay, that was an edit.
That's Tourette's guy, yeah.
This.
Yeah, here we go.
Dick.
[Laughter]
Way funnier.
The original is way better.
Dick.
That used to come on as a kid and I was just like, oh, they're just saying dick.
No, they say deek.
Deek!
It's actually a really old wizard saying it.
It's not a kid.
It's an old Brazilian woman.
Deek!
Little kids are going to repeat that, I feel.
Yeah, they're going to repeat that.
These little kids are going to repeat this bullcrap
they see on TV.
They're going to say, "Deek!"
I did. "Hey, mom, suck my deek!"
I did. I said it.
You said that? Yeah.
hear that word for the first time from yeah yeah that's interesting I was like
four I was the first time I was at the end of every like VHS I owned the fuck
every single one I only had a why do you watch to the end of all your VHS yeah
yeah look on the Patrick looked on the back of every VHS I did I was like oh my
god this is another dick one I did like white noise when I was a kid yeah so I
I like White Wedding by Billy Idol. Yeah, yeah. That's a great. It's a nice day for a
white wedding. My mom has seen Billy Idol a few times in concert. Yeah. I bet you. My mom
saw Billy Idol like a year ago. Me and your mom had a white wedding. No. Yeah, we
got married. No. Yeah, we did. Yeah, man. I'm your mom now.
I didn't eat your mom? Well, I beg to differ. Don't say that.
- Yeah, come on. - Yeah, yeah.
- It's my mom.
- Yeah, man, I'm serious.
- These are the premiums.
She doesn't even have the RSS for this yet.
- That's why she's not gonna hear it.
- She's gonna hear it.
- No, she won't.
- Mm-hmm.
- You're gonna give her the RSS feed?
- Yeah.
- That is the most embarrassing thing.
- My mom's my biggest supporter.
- First we give it to your,
no, everybody gets one premium-free RSS feed
to give to somebody.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I'm not, I'm gonna save mine up.
- Yeah, I don't think I would give it to,
I don't think I want anybody I know
listen to this podcast. I don't want to have to interact with anybody.
Yeah, listen to this. Yeah. Yeah. Or at least the other way around. I don't
want people you interact with to also hear this weird dark side of you.
I don't want to talk. It's like talking about like Twitter in real life.
I had a bad experience with that recently. That sucks. What happened? Someone's girlfriend like...
Someone's girlfriend totally got at me. I know who you're talking about but that's such a funny way to tell the story.
Yeah they asked me what my tweets were and I was like I don't know.
They asked you what your tweets were? What's your tweets?
I had a comedian recently that like... Hey nice to meet you I'm a girlfriend and I want to know what your tweets are.
I had a comedian recently mention Twitter because to like Boston comedians it's insane that somebody would have more than 80 followers on Twitter.
Oh my god, I know.
Stand up, people with stand up don't understand.
Boston comedy scene, everybody is just terrible at Twitter.
Well, because yeah, they're just like, they just don't think about it much.
They just, what am I handing you?
Yeah, they don't realize how you can like use social media to promote shows other than
Facebook.
Yeah, they just post like.
They're all, every Boston comedian is 28 and mentally ill.
And they all, their most recent tweet is like, teeth hurt today.
Yeah.
Like that's it.
Teeth hurt today are like, I need to like, here's like 60 reasons why I'm better than
Shane Gillis yeah or something like that like I was talking to somebody last
night at Thunder Bar about the did you in like October did you guys hear about the
the riot theater getting like like shut down all the shows there the Rosendale
theater because yeah Roger Square yeah because Kinback yeah cuz yeah cuz
Kinback was free here you go Kinback yeah repress for you I'd so Kinback said
like I mean just did like his regular like one-liner material and stuff and
I mean it's just like you know it's not any more offensive than like Anthony
Jeselnik or whatever. Right. But and then she went up on stage. Well she started
ringing a bell. She started ringing a bell. I did hear about this. While I think actually while Logan O'Brien was on stage and she and he was like
what's the bell about and she was like it's about misogyny and he was like
okay and then she just like kept ringing the bell like ding ding ding ding ding
ding ding ding and he was like what are you doing and there was like four people
in the audience yeah and she was like she got up on stage she was like this show
is officially over these people don't want to hear this stuff and everybody in
the audience was like we don't care like these are those are all our friends who
are performing and then she kicked everybody out and then went on Twitter
and posted like yeah she was like that you know this I I bravely stood up to
like a white male comedians misogyny tonight and they're never doing a show
again at my place and it got like 500,000. It was huge. It went viral for like the
stupidest situation. It went viral so that like fucking comedy
seller people could be like oh looks like I'm never performing here like.
And also yeah there was no shows going on there. That was like they did one show
every once in a while at this room. It was like an improv theater. Yeah exactly and
and this lady, she was like freaked out.
- Yeah, I'm shutting this shit down.
- It's so funny, dude.
- Yeah, it was literally, it was people like fucking
Mark Norman and like--
- Mark Norman said that?
- I think Mark Norman did like quote tweet it
and was like, it was either Mark Norman,
it was some big, oh, Chris D'Elia, I think.
Chris D'Elia did say something.
- Those are not the two guys I would have guessed.
- Yeah, it's crazy.
- Just so funny.
- Two people who--
- And it sucks that I was in LA for all, like I just--
- Yeah.
You were gonna go perform. I was on that show. I was on the bell right back at her.
Oh my god, yeah.
This is the thing I'm loud about.
I was like, "Bang a gong?"
How you like that? No?
She was Asian.
Really?
[laughter]
Okay, yeah. Maybe not a...
That might have made things worse.
That would have made things way worse.
She rings a bell, I bang a gong.
She's like, "Why'd you bring a gong?"
[laughter]
happened bitch I guessed okay a big bell I would have brought a bigger bell yeah
not a gong not anything yeah you're looking at the poster for Bonzo goes to
college a cool poster all new monkey shines he's a star of Bonzo - yeah it
doesn't have Ronald Reagan in it it doesn't even have this movie doesn't
even have Ronald Reagan. I thought Ronald Reagan and Bonzo were like a pair in the 50s. I was
watching the other night I watched like this video that was like all like the
greatest most memorable debate moments ever. Have you guys seen that one where
it's... Gore Vidal? No, no it's a Michael Dukakis one where they they open up the
debate and the anchor looks at... I mean Michael Dukakis he was anti death
penalty. Yeah. And the anchor looks at the camera he's like tonight the the
candidates have no idea what question we're gonna ask them tonight. They
haven't been prepared and they like have not been tipped off at all. And this
first question goes to Governor Dukakis. Governor Dukakis, if your wife Kitty
Dukakis was raped and murdered, would you be in favor of the death penalty? Really?
Yeah, it's the first question and he's just like, "Uh, no, I mean no, like I don't
know, no." It's so funny. It's the most gotcha shit. Oh it's crazy, yeah.
it's like so clearly they were in the can for Bush yeah but it's so it's just such
a great it's just I think about like if they asked like Elizabeth Warren that
tomorrow you know what I mean? Well she doesn't have a wife so it wouldn't work.
That's what I thought was funny about it yeah but Dukakis is uh they names like
part of South Station after him right? I don't know. Well you're obsessed with South Station.
yeah you love South Station dude, it's cause you love going South Station on a guy
you know what I'm saying?
oh you went to a guy's South Station
god dammit
where he had his train
I went there every day for a year
where you put his train into your tunnel
where you bought a ticket
you put his train into your tunnel
you bought a train on his tunnel
you guys are being rude
and a bus
yeah you let him run a train on you
and you went to the Regina Pizzeria in his penis
no I went to Cajun Cajun
way to, ugh
yeah
place sucks
I know
the po-boy at the bus station the po-boy at the bus I mean that's me it's a good
I'm the po-boy at the bus station it's a good deal if you want like a po-boy in two sides
just go get a slice of Regina I don't like Regina's I like I think I don't
like Regina's cuz I grew up eating it the one in the north end is good the
other ones are that's the original yeah the other one the one the one over here
in Austin kind of sucks yeah but they have cheap beer oh that's good and me
like you that's good yeah oh that's actually really good yeah actually I
love that's actually really good now that I'm thinking about it cheap beers good
Boston doesn't have any good pizza though Boston does not there's there's no
Regina pizzeria is our is the only wait there's no there's one another one
that's like our sabana knows Donna knows there's that place is so good I like
Domino's P I like I was in North Carolina made a Pizza Hut buffet trip
- Ooh.
- Never been to Pizza Hut.
- I got the worst food poisoning of my life
at a Pizza Hut buffet.
- Really?
- In Hudson, New Hampshire.
- You wanna get worse?
(laughing)
I'll give it to you, baby.
- Worst food poisoning of my life was a cracker barrel.
- Worse for me was a poop salad that I ate.
- Worst food poisoning, so I got,
the second worst food poisoning was Pizza Hut.
First worst food poisoning, I found a thing
of frozen bacon wrapped scallops in my sister's fridge.
and I don't, they were, the package did say
they were still good.
It said Best Buy and it was like three weeks.
- No, they were from Best Buy.
- They were from Best Buy, they were electronic scallops.
I shouldn't have eaten them.
- No, they weren't from Best Buy.
- I shit and threw up.
I shitted and threw up.
- Oh man, same time?
Both holes?
- Yeah.
- I shit my ass yesterday.
- So we just moved into my house in Ware
and the bathroom was still very,
like it still had all the old,
the old toilet and like the old sink and stuff.
- Oh yeah, the old toilet.
- A hole, just a hole around it.
- It's like a old house, it's like very old.
- A wooden toilet.
- I was sitting on a wooden toilet.
- A wooden toilet paper.
- A steam powered toilet.
- A steam powered sink.
- A steam powered brass toilet.
- When you flush it, it's so hot
that you can't touch your ass to it.
- I said that because I forgot that you guys
have never been to my house in Wayne.
- Never.
- That's what I was making fun of at first.
- Fuck you.
- Gotcha.
- Yeah, it's like the bathroom is like really small,
so it was just me just shooting diarrhea
and then shooting just liquid out of my mouth.
- Oh, nice.
- There was a Chumlee poster in the bathroom,
'cause it used to be my younger brother's room
and that was his bathroom.
- Yeah.
- So I would just--
- And he loved Chumlee.
- I got him a Chumlee poster for Christmas.
- And he put it in his bathroom to jack off to?
- Yeah.
- That's cool.
- No, but I threw up and shit and I was looking up
and it was just Chumlee's fat face.
(laughing)
- Damn.
a friend when we were like 11 his mom got him, it's a weird family, his mom got him
a Sports Illustrated swimsuit like poster. Why would you get your kid--
He was 11 years old and he put it just on the back of his bathroom door.
What if he's gay? And so she just was like aiding and abetting her son, masturbating.
Yeah it's just a weird family. It's like when parents are like, you
can drink but you know you have to let me know how much you have.
That was for me when I was that started when I was like 16 and then it stopped
because I got to I was a naughty boy yeah and then my mom was like you can't do that anymore.
You can drink and drive as long as you drive home. I was really good at
hiding it. Yeah I was bad at it I would vomit all the time and I just wake up
and I'd be like hungover as shit and walk into the kitchen and my mom would just
like she's been a wild night huh no I would get I would go to talk to houses
and then my mom would call me cuz I'd free like she's like oh you can go there
but you have to check in with me and then like I get mom's love checking in
she's like she was like oh you missed like I said like you had to check in
with me at like 12 and I was just like super fucked up and I was like calling my
mom and like super fucked up I was slurring my speech and they called my mom
and all I would do was just get louder like I'd sit there and be like hello
yeah no we're at we're at Mike's house just the first time I ever smoked weed I
was 14 and it was a bong in whoa it's really cool my older brother my older
brother helped me out. He was 20 and he was helping me smoke. I was 14.
That's responsible. It was very responsible. Stay thirsty, my friends. I was like bugging
out and we went and saw the Avengers and on the way there my grandmother called
me, which is like the scariest thing ever, and I like panic
answered and while she was like on the phone, like she could hear me, I asked
Josh, what do I do?
(laughing)
And then she was like, Caleb, are you there?
And I was just like, I'll be home soon.
But it was like the scariest.
My heart was beating out of my ass.
- Oh, the first time I ever smoked weed,
I went to, I smoked with these four kids
outside of the middle school gym.
- Nice dude.
- And they're all like in jail.
- Oh yeah.
- Yeah.
- Now one of them's like a dad.
I don't know what's going on with them.
I haven't talked to them in years.
but I forgot my cousins, my two six foot seven cousins
were on the basketball team.
- Nice, the Morris team.
- I always forget that that happens.
- I forget that.
- I forget what my huge cousins are on the basketball team.
- I forget about my humongous basketball cousins.
- And then I remembered and I freaked out.
- No, so I went to the game.
- My Harvill Globetrotter cousins.
I always just forget about them.
- I went to the game not expecting their mom to be there.
So I'm high as shit.
- Yeah, their seven foot mom?
- Their seven foot, no, their four foot,
five foot four mom shows up.
little bitch. 4 foot 5 foot 4. How tall is her dad?
He's like 6 foot 7. How tall is their dad? Their dad is 6 foot 7. My dad is 6 feet tall.
Your dad's 6 feet tall? Yeah. That sucks. Yeah. I didn't get any of that. No. No. I got my
mom's height. My dad is like 5'10" in sandals. Whoa.
- Whoa!
- Those are some big sandals,
'cause your dad is 5'3".
- No.
- Your dad's wearing platform sandals, man.
- Yeah, he looks cool, man.
- Seven inch sandals.
(laughing)
- Your dad's walking around dressed up like Bootsy Collins.
It's like Bootsy Collins at the beach.
- Yeah.
And his license says 5'10".
(laughing)
- 5'10".
- I think my license says 5'11",
which is just a blatant lie.
I was truthful in my license.
What does it say?
Mine is 69 inches.
What's that?
5'9".
Yeah.
Okay.
I don't know what my license says or how tall I am.
You suck.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Gotcha.
I can't even check because it's over there.
So, it's a mystery.
I need to get a new license.
Mine is getting bad.
Mine's exp...
What do you mean like it's going to get expired?
It smells really bad.
It's turning...
It's rotting.
It's decaying.
It's rotting from the inside out.
look evil in my license photo. The more bad deeds I do, it's like
Knights of the Old Republic. My avatar becomes more and more like his red.
I was seeing a picture of Dorian Gray.
No, no, no. Knights of the Old Republic. Yeah, it's becoming evil.
It's got the red. Or like Fable. Fable was so cool.
Yeah. You just got to live a whole life as a man. I never, my little brother played Fable.
I didn't play Fable. You should have. I never played Fable.
your sister you get is smoking hot in that you see yeah I'm serious
that game is Stefan Molyneux?
Stefan Rakel
wait no no no wait
it's not Stefan Molyneux
Stefan Molyneux is the alt right guy
I'm thinking of Peter Molyneux
I don't know who that is
he was just a bald guy who just ruined a bunch of shit after Fable
oh those are different guys?
yeah they're different guys
eggs isn't the guy who made that game know about the cubes I just thought that
was really good no I thought it was like because like notch had the same
trajectory yeah so I just assumed it was another one of those things yeah when I
for one day like people first started like make like dunking on that guy I
thought it was like when somebody dunks on somebody when someone when someone
does a dunk in a quote tweet I'm guilty of it but when someone does a dunk yeah
- What's your favorite, yeah.
- I just call people a bitch.
- Here's what you do, you quote tweet Nancy Pelosi,
right, and she has some awesome dunk on Donald Trump,
and then you quote tweet and you say, nice one.
- That is what I do.
- One billion favorites, right?
And then just, and then, and then just bitches in your--
- And I say, I say F-U-C-K, Nancy Pelosi.
- F-U-C-K, Nancy P-E-L-O-S.
- L-O-U-I-S-C-K.
more like Nancy Palooza. Nancy Paloo-is-CK. Nancy Palooza. Nancy Paloo-is-CK. She's just like, "Yeah, we gotta get all this shit out of the White House. My
fucking daughter's got shit on the White House lawn. I'm pissed off about it." I'm
pissing and shitting and Donald Trump's... I think Donald Trump's... I think Donald Trump's Chinese. I'll say it. He's a Chinese guy. I don't fucking care. I'm fat. I'm old.
bad fucking Chinese guy my daughter is Chinese my daughter never seen Louis
CK I'm Chinese I'm sure you think this CK is just like a Chinese Chinese King
Chinese King yeah like a Genghis Khan yeah yeah that's what it stands for
Genghis Khan Genghis Genghis Khan Genghis Khan what about that that would he would
be so pissed off he'd probably kill you and then rape your family Genghis Khan
PINGAS CON.
There's two instances where dr. Robotnik said penis. Yeah, and said like the the sentence splicing
Yeah, you to poop stuff and there's a hundred instances of you sucking penis. No
penis of dr. Robotnik of dr. Robotnik the Jim Carrey version the
like a white book the penis of dr. Robotnik chapter 1 chapter 1 headed
stench yeah the fetid stench of the Eggman's come permeated every fiber of
my being I looked around me come come come I am in hell I'm in hell pinhead
was there I am in hell was written on the wall and come no doubt written by the
penis of dr. Robotnik the end very short book with a footnote section yeah yeah
there's like a billion footnotes yeah so thick yeah okay yeah all right cool it
Bill Simmons you know I'm saying he loves footnotes I don't know Bill Simmons
Bill Simmons? He's a guy...
It's not Stephen A. Smith, I don't care.
Whoa!
Trapped in Dr. Robotnik's closet, I felt nothing but fear as his spiked penis.
As his pingas!
It's written out.
It's a screenshot of the video.
When you get a critical in Earthbound and it says "Smash" and it's got like...
Bouncing letters.
It says pingas in that font.
I need to finish -
Whoa!
Oh my God.
That's been happening a lot.
I don't know what's going on out there.
There's a guy seeing a hot girl and he's going awooga.
Oh.
They saw you through the window, Pat.
Awooga!
Yeah.
Yeah, and then -
That was Tim Allen and Jar Jar Binks.
What's the name of the guy from Popeye's -
Bluto?
Popeye's Adventure.
Is that the guy who -
Bluto?
No, the guy who loves hamburgers.
Oh.
like hamburger or something? He has like a food name.
They all have food names.
Olive oil. He's Olive Oil's brother so he's got a food name.
Why do you know? Is his name Castor Oil?
No his name is Hamburger Oil.
No his name is not Hamburger Oil.
Fat guy.
J. Wellington Wimpy.
No, his name's Hamburger.
Yeah well he's still got a food name.
J. Wellington Wimpy?
Yeah.
He kind of looks like Patrick.
He does not look like Patrick.
is a penny is a wimpy dude and he's wimpy like Patrick no I look like Popeye
cuz I'm don't say yeah you look like Robin Williams Popeye cuz you fucking
look weird you look weird you you look like weird prosthetic Robin Williams
forearms that's fine okay people think it girls like it and you go okay you're
constantly going yeah this is kind of weird you remember like on full house
like all Joey's thing was doing a Popeye impression. What? He was like, Joey's
like a stand-up comedian but then like you see him perform and it's just like...
I didn't even know he's just supposed to be a stand-up comedian. Yeah, his big thing
before he got a puppet named Woodchuck... Oh, I do remember the puppet. Yeah, before
he got the puppet all it was was like, "Oh, Uncle Joey's gonna do his stand-up
routine." And then he just does Popeye. You know, that's fine.
Yeah, that's like, you know, that's pretty fun. That's better than what I do probably. Just a
guy in a blazer with a mullet just going "Eck, eck, eck, eck!"
I might do that tonight. I might do a Popeye.
You should start wearing-
I hope I'm hosting and I show up and do Popeye.
You should start wearing blazers with like skinny ties on set.
Yes, dude. I love when a comedian dresses up.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
You know?
It's so funny.
I just always look like total dog shit when I do stand-up.
Yeah, me too.
I feel like a comedian dressing up is like similar to just like a suit guy in high school.
Oh yeah, absolutely.
There was this guy-
They come with like six notebooks.
I won't say his last name, but his first name was Alex, and he would come to Mooyah.
Oh, I know him.
Yeah, and he would, uh, he would, he would...
He would come out of work, and he'd be in his work uniform.
No, no, he was a student.
He went to Harvard.
Oh, shit.
Really?
Yeah, and he would come...
Oh, shit.
He would come and he'd be wearing like a, like a beautiful, like, blue, like Armani
suit.
Yeah.
And he would just eat shit.
And it was 'cause, I mean, just the goofiest thing in the world.
I've seen him do stand-up a lot he always dressed like that really yeah.
So great. Just awesome dude.
Is it the same guy I think?
Probably not. I think it was before you started coming maybe.
Okay.
It was a long time ago. I don't even know if he's I think maybe he's in Boston.
He's probably some lampoon kid.
The lampoon has such a cool building.
Yeah.
That's the only cool thing about them.
Is that sometimes I drive by that building I'm like I want to fuck somebody in there.
It looks like a castle.
It looks like it yeah it looks like an evil base.
Yeah.
It looks like there's a lot of things that went on in there that they didn't tell anyone.
It looks like that building could keep a secret.
Yeah.
They have a deformed lampoon member locked up in the attic who looks out of the window
at night and wails.
Yeah, like it's the guy from the Goonies.
Yeah, hold on.
It's the guy from Castle Freak.
It's Trollen Joost.
This is Trollen Joost.
And it's Goblin Joost.
Goblin Joost.
Goblin Ghost.
ghost I was gonna do one for Michael Che but and and Michael gay right yeah
frightened shit right full tray right full chain yeah frightened hey that's a
go right and I they have the same since he's a paramedical last name it's hey
That's a ghost I see. Donald Trump served in NFL team hamburgers today. Yeah, cuz that's a thing that happens now
Just doing goblin jokes. Sir, this is a Wendy's. Yeah, this is a Wendy's
All goblins are from the bottom. That's just a thing that happens now.
Yeah, so there I'm having a normal one. Yeah, I'd love that's every every Colin Jost joke is just that.
Yeah, I wish Colin Jost was an orc. Me too. I wish Colin Jost wasn't alive. I wish he was nothing.
I wish he wasn't alive but his brother Casey was still there.
I wish his brother Casey was still there.
I wish he was dust in the wind that had never reconstituted itself.
I wish he was stardust in a distant galaxy.
I wish he was dinosaur stuff.
I wish he was Gallagher.
Me too. He just does his shitty jokes and then smashes a pineapple.
So yeah, that happened.
Yeah.
We should get Gallagher. What happened to you right there?
What happened?
You just cracked.
Somebody reset Patrick.
tinder just added 300 new genders. This is why, this is what's wrong with the
dungeons in this country. He's conservative too, all goblins are
conservative. You remember when people got really mad at Colin Jost for doing
that tinder, that joke about tinder adding genders and then being like
that's why the Democrats lost. Yeah. Oh. That was, I think that's way bigger in my
mind because I just don't watch SNL. Yeah. But it was way bigger in my mind than it
actually was but I remember people were angry at him for that. Yeah people were very angry.
yeah people were in the streets people were right people there was a guy with a
pitchfork like Shrek and he was asking for Joe's head yeah because he looked
into the camera went I'm gonna basically the plot right true yeah bright bright
but if bright yeah I've got a goblin on TV this is bright but if bright was also
studio 60 on the Sunset Strip do you think bright do you think they're all
the comedians and bright or goblins or orcs or whatever there's there's
comedians and bright I'm saying if they're bored so you're saying in the
Max Landis in the world world of bright Max Landis yeah the famous rapist yeah
he so in the bright world I feel like all the comedians are probably like it's
probably just there's probably like work shows yeah that's what I'm saying work
comedy yeah yeah you have like Garflax da comedian
instead of like duh it's like just grunts Garflax da comedian. Oh my god.
they have their own circuit.
Because I mean allegory. Yeah, the whole allegory of his racism is racism. Then
yeah, that's so funny.
Dullet Yeah, there's the comedy clubs are all called like Dull laughing
goblin.
The crazy bat
that that the show flyer we looked at the other day was a show called
piss your pants with Brady and Melvin da Comedian.
Marv da Comedian.
Shervy.
My favorite one, the one, the poster that was getting me was there was one poster where
it was like there were three people stacked on top of each other and the first one was
Shervy and then Mother Mabel.
Mother Mabel which is like a guy in drag.
Oh yeah, just a guy doing Madea.
And then the last one was Kroby.
be. It was just two people. And they're crowbeed when they're together. Oh my god. It was so
funny. And then the host was Mr. Bring the Funny. Like it looked like a parody poster.
Mother Mabel is so good too. And then that sketch I sent you guys that's just him pointing
a gun at that lady. Did you guys watch that? Oh no I didn't watch that sketch. Oh my god
The Nonsense Sketch. Nonsense Entertainment presents Hood Pizza. It's so good, dude.
It's like filmed on like an iPhone 3G and it's like a woman opens the door and she's like,
"Yeah, is that my pizza?" and Nonsense is like, "Yeah, this is your pizza."
Is that how he talks?
That's how he talks. And she's like, "Yeah, let me just go get the money real quick." He's in
in the other room and he's like "Oh hell no we don't do that no more" and he pulls
out a gun, a real gun and points it at her and she's like "whoa whoa whoa" and then the
rest of the time it's like two minutes of him just being, her just being like
"man why are you putting a gun on my face" and he's like "bitch you better give me
that, you better give me the pizza money" it's so good I'll put a link on Patreon, go watch it
it's so fucking good. I gotta figure out cuz I mean I don't want us if I upload
the stinger knife video I don't want to like have us because it tells me that
their lawyers gonna come after you for that yeah you could only get that if you
bought the friggin knife you just sounded just like Jack black you just
were a Jack black for a moment she's gonna hate them Oh
Tom hates Jack black you know who loves Jack by junky Zack Joan Q said junky
School of Rock. Oh yeah. The Fucking Hot Bitch Principal. Have you ever seen My Blue Heaven?
She's in My Blue Heaven but like... She's in My Creamy White Heaven. Well she's in the
movie My Blue Heaven and like as a kid it didn't register to me that like
because she was on SNL like two years before or like three or four years
before and like she's got to be like 26 in that movie but then Rick Moranis is
her love interest yeah and he's got to be like 30 or 37 or something like that
that's not that crazy it's not that crazy it's just like because of that
I've always looked at Joan Cusack as a much older woman
so like her being in School of Rock and then being Jack Black's love
interest I didn't she's hot in School of Rock she is she's just got she's just
she's just library status you know cuz I'm checking her out yeah cuz I'm
checking her out yeah and I'm paying the late fees and then I'm buying the book
cuz I forgot to return it you know yeah or Moranis the or Moranis yeah honey I
blew up the or honey I ate the yeah honey I humans yeah I ate the cat oh does it
- An orc would eat a cat.
- You can't leave an orc around a cat, dude.
If I was an orc man, I'd be going orc mode on your cats
every time I'm in here.
I'd be chasing them around.
(laughing)
- Is that what you do already?
(gurgling)
- That's what you already do.
- I don't do that.
I don't like them, but I don't hate them
or don't try to eat them.
- You try to eat them.
- I've never done that.
- You literally tried to eat one today,
starting with the penis first.
- Yeah.
- That's just 'cause you have to start with the smallest.
- You saw he got a little bit of poop on his penis
and you were like, "Ooh!"
I'd seen the poop I've never even tried.
No.
That's how Caleb reacts when he sees a penis with poop in it.
I don't make a Yoda sound.
That wasn't Yoda, that was the Chamberlain.
Kobold pits.
The Chamberlain.
Kobold pits?
Kobold pits.
Oh, I need to leave.
Who's kobold pits?
It's like a kobold, it's like a type of goblin from the Legends of the Dragons.
Oh, okay.
I need to leave, I'm saying.
Oh, what time is it?
I have to go.
It's 724.
I gotta bounce.
Alright, we can finish the episode without you, I guess.
Okay.
Why don't you just, we can just stop it here.
Well this is a premium, they're paying for this one.
Right.
Okay, well I'll just leave.
But I also have to pee before I leave.
Okay then go pee.
You want to hear me pee?
Yeah.
I'm just going to keep talking.
I think that cord is honestly long enough for you to go to the bathroom.
It's definitely not.
I'm not going to go pee in... no.
Alright, let's talk about kobold pits.
Okay.
I'm going to go pee.
I'm using your bathroom as a sweat hut.
Patrick Orkman.
No.
Yeah.
totally an orc dude. I'm not an orc. What happened today? There was a guy talking to
himself on that. No, that doesn't even work well. Cameron Bosmer. No, it doesn't
work well. Patrick Bosmer. I'm fine with that. Bosmer, Bosmer. Bosmers are very
good at stealth. Khajiit Doran. You would totally be a Khajiit. No, I would not. Yeah,
would you're you like to thief I'm not a steal a Bosmer is probably a better
thief than a Khajiit really I don't even know what Bosmer's look like Bosmer's or
the wood elf okay that I knew there's some kind of elf yeah I can't envision
one in my mind a Khajiit I can imagine actually that was the only race I played
as in Skyrim was Bosmer's yeah yeah that's why you're Patrick Bosmer they
have skills in archery and stealth of course I'm gonna do that I'm gonna do
the Dark Brotherhood wait we're Bosmer's in Skyrim yeah were they called Bosmer's
No, it was called Wood Elf.
Okay, that's why.
It's technically, like, if you look up, they used to be called Boswell.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
That's what I thought.
I knew Boswell from the older games.
They don't call them like Altmer or like Dunmer, like from the Dark Elf and the High Elf.
Dunkirk.
Dunston.
You should be able to play as Dunston in Skyrim.
You can play as a monkey.
You just have no skill.
Oh, that's a good mod.
That's a good mod idea.
You can't use any weapons.
You're just a chimp.
Yeah.
And you can't use any weapons.
You're just a chimp.
Yeah.
And you can't use any weapons.
use any weapons. You're just a chimp? Yeah. And you're just a- you try to talk to anybody
and it's like, what is this? People just immediately attack you and then like at the beginning
of the game where they're trying to behead you, it's just a chimp on the execution table.
Yeah, they're just like, what? I guess we have to kill this chimp, I don't know. Cause
I don't think like a chimp could realistically exist in Skyrim. Nobody will talk to you,
We can't get any quests because we're having way more fun.
Yeah, keep going.
I'm parking my car in front of your house till tomorrow morning.
Okay.
They'll ticket you at like, I think it's like 6 to 6.
6?
Or 8 I think.
Okay.
6 to 8.
Okay, could you just ask Dom to text me?
Okay.
Thank you.
Bye y'all.
Bye.
So finally.
in time. Now we're getting into real Utilt Bosmer pits.
Yeah, but yeah, you try to talk to people to get like quests and stuff as a chimp and they
just go like, "You silly little chimp! You know you can't talk!"
They just immediately put up a fire spell. They just start, "Ah! What is this?"
Hit you with a rock. Yeah, no, you can have like a few things
in your inventory, but it's like bananas. It's bananas and then like stones.
Yeah, a funny hat because Dunstan loves hats. You can get all the hats. All of like the
hats and all of the armor. You can wear, you get Daedric armor from the start. You can't
have any body armor. What? It's Caleb. Is it Caleb? Yeah, it's Caleb. Are you sure? What
if it's a mysterious man? I forgot my backpack. Oh, Caleb forgot his damn backpack. Alright,
now he's leaving for right now finally can get back to some crazy fan is gonna
triangulate the sound of outside
this is a good
you know we can tell exactly by the sound of the air
i know you've located that you guys are in boston
yes i was gonna find out we were in boston subway
yet the restaurant
yeah there is a subway around here and i ate there
it's the worst one yeah i was talking about the air
it wasn't that bad when i went there
Subway in general is just always a mistake for me to go to.
I never enjoy it.
I forget how to order there.
I just forget that I always forget.
I'm always like, "Oh, I guess I'll have Subway.
It'll fill me up."
And I just feel like garbage shit after I eat it.
Jimmy John's is better.
I've never been to Jimmy John's.
Jimmy John's is better, however, their owner does kill elephants for sport.
I don't care about that.
Yeah, I don't care either.
I do that too.
But we don't even get any elephant meat.
Yeah, that's true.
Fucked up.
What about Bosmer John's?
Jimmy Bosmer?
Jimmy Bosmer.
me bosmer Jimmy bosmer's no there would be it would be an all vegetarian
restaurant I feel like bosmer's don't eat meat do they I don't know hey hey I feel
like a bosmer would not eat me I'm googling bosmer diet yeah shit I'm on
the bosmer diet so what do the bosmer eat that's a reddit post let's see here
okay they oh they're entirely carnivorous they're cannibals whoa they
don't eat any vegetables so I was just way like furthest off you yeah okay what
kind of what they don't eat plants it says there's a ton of vegetation
forestry and Valenwood they just can't harm it they are entirely carnivorous
society cannibalism is acceptable and particularly commonplace for warriors
okay that makes that guess that makes sense cuz like the Bosmer's whole thing
is that they were like born from trees or whatever yeah I took Prilosec and now
I've been burping a lot more, but my heartburn hasn't been as bad. Well. It's a solid trade-off isn't it monkeys paw?
Yeah, exactly
Dunstan's paw Dunstan's paw I would have been a monster special ability
You can
Pa if you know how to make Skyrim mods. Yeah, we need we need like a team
Yeah, we need to get the discord going to the Elder Scrolls 6 Dunstan. Yeah
Dunstan checks into Skyrim. Or I feel like it'd be funnier to put Dunstan in Oblivion.
Yeah, Dunblivion. Dunstanblivion.
Yeah, Orangoblivion. Yeah.
Orang-bl-blangblivion. All right, we're at an hour. All right. Bye. What's that Dunstanquest?
Dunstanquest. Dunstanquest. All right, that's the, that's the, you guys have to make Dunstanquest for us. Yeah, make a video game for us.
You have to make a video game called Dunstanquest. Goodbye.
Bye.