You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
Alright, well, it's on now.
You look- this is the most hobbit you've ever looked, bro.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, I looked like a hobbit as a child.
A lot.
You were a hobbit child?
I mean, you were short, I guess.
Oh, no.
Did you have really hairy feet?
No, I wouldn't wear shoes.
I wouldn't wear shoes anywhere.
So my feet were like constantly dirty.
I feel like the bottoms of my feet when I was a kid.
- Let me get a good look at these things.
Man, you have a long foot.
- Yep. - Yeah.
- What the fuck, man? - I know.
You know what they say about big feet.
- What size is that? - I kinda get it now.
- Stinky.
What size foot is that?
- It's an 11.
I think that's what it's size. - I think I wear an 11.
But that foot looks huge to me.
- Patrick's foot is a little bigger than mine.
- Then how do I fit in size 11 shoes?
- How do you fit in me with that big foot?
Put your foot up to mine.
I think my foot's long but my toes are tiny.
I think I might be a size 12 now that I'm thinking about it, or 11 and a half at least.
Can we just stay with our feet touching like this the rest of the whole show?
Let's see who's legs are up first.
Once Patrick realizes he can get us to believe he's a size 11, he's like, "You know, actually,
I think I might be a 12 or a 13 or a..."
I might be a size 20.
Now that I think about it...
My toes are tiny.
Look at how tiny my toes are.
You've got cute little piggies.
Everything about your foot looks big to me, man.
Look at that.
No lie.
That's fucking weird.
Your foot?
Yeah.
I could make some money selling feet pics to weird guys.
To a weird fellow.
A weird fellow on the web.
A weird fellow on the web made me rich.
I got high arches too.
Do you?
No.
You have low arches.
Oh, that's a low arch?
Yeah.
It's because you fucking wear skate shoes.
There's no arch support.
Yeah.
That's true.
You have almost flat feet.
Yeah.
That's true.
I do have flat feet.
Oh, flat feet is low arch?
I thought that's why I always wore some I stopped wearing skate shoes as a kid
because my mom said that I would lose my arches I think I'm a beautiful arches
yeah no no my arches yeah how is a weird fellow from the internet going to fuck
my feet exactly there should be no hole when I put them together yeah yeah be
tighter if you didn't have the hole oh you're right it's it's better to flip the
fuck a surface we have to ask we have to ask we don't know and I need to make a
phone call we need to find a foot guy yeah somebody like that what are we
gonna do to them when we're gonna hold them down and fuck their foot no they
don't like getting their feet for ya they like no what if we find the one
that likes what a mystery one the secret one that likes both a verse if you will
Yeah, I don't I think I I think I'll never understand feet no matter how long I really try
Yeah, I've tried watching well. I feel like sometimes. I'll look at like a
Person doing a weird thing with their foot, and I'll feel something
It's like a deep disgust you know like I like a like a like a deeper level of like it
Oh, I guess some people just like that like
Yeah, yeah, I can show you something weird. Give me a piece of paper and a marker
What are you gonna? Do?
No, what if you listen if you draw them and you pin them somewhere in my house, I'm gonna be pissed off
I was gonna draw I was gonna write my don't you dare make me a Hitler advent calendar
I was gonna make I was gonna draw a picture. I was gonna draw my name with my foot. Your name is Hitler
My name's it
My name is not Hitler gotcha way
This sucks. Can I take a shower later? No, I haven't showered in like three
Maybe I don't like this setup cuz I have to look right at the bright window to look at you
I have to look at the DirecTV satellite and it's sending messages to my brain.
What are you picking up?
It's telling me to kill someone powerful.
Do you have Comedy Central?
Start doing Chappelle's show.
Okay.
What if I was Chinese?
That's Mad TV.
You got it wrong.
Remember he, no, in his latest special.
Did he do a Chinese one?
In the latest Chappelle's special, there's this part where he says what if--
The George Floyd one?
No.
Wait, never mind.
Yeah, no, the George Floyd one, he went on a whole bit about what if he was Chinese.
I'm not sure if that's what he was saying.
I'm not sure.
yeah now the George Floyd one he went on a whole bit about what if he was Chinese
that's an interesting take
you have a clip of it?
Dave Chappelle saying what if I was Chinese?
were you there?
I recorded Dave Chappelle without his permission at one of his shows
it's really funny how mad they get about that shit
I know it's so stupid it's so fucking stupid
Dave Chappelle said alphabet people
that's right
people. That's what his whole thing is like. Those are the people who say, "I'm LGBTQ,
A, B, C, D, E, F, G, H, I, J, K, L, M, N, O, P, Q, R, S, T, U, V." It's like you already
used L, G, B, and T. You can't say them twice. You can't say it again. It makes no sense,
guy. You should do A, C, D, E, F, H, I, J, K, J, J, the jet plane. The plane. I am the
plane. I am JJ the jet plane. That's what they should be like. That's what the LGBTQ
acronym is I am JJ the Jet Plane. Pretty soon they're gonna probably start adding numbers
to that bullshit right? Can't stop looking at this hole in my pants. I know. Oh my god
it's hypnotizing. You're just jealous dude. It looks like the old monster trucks logo.
I've done stand up a lot of times where I like sat on a stool with a big hole in my
pants like this. Yeah it's pretty funny. Yeah. It's good. Yeah one time specifically at Improv
Boss and the stage manager told me as soon as I got off stage that I had a huge hole
my pants.
What if I was Chinese?
That's a good clip.
That's exactly what you promised.
What if I was Chinese?
That's the whole joke.
That's the whole special.
Dave Chappelle.
He gets out on stage, he goes, "What if I was Chinese?" and then the rest of the hour
is just him being Chinese.
What if he was...
Perfect.
He's the best stand-up of all time.
Dave Chappelle.
You know?
Okay.
And he was Chinese.
What would be different?
First of all, he would be Chinese.
I can tell you the first difference.
Don't you say it, dude.
He would be Chinese.
That's what I was talking about.
Don't you dare.
You guys want to hold me down.
Dave Chinese.
We're trying to hold Patrick back because he's a truth teller.
He's not afraid of the political correctness.
I'm not afraid of the political correctness.
We'll give you one truth for this episode.
Here's one truth.
- If you go to a restaurant and it's got a tall toilet,
your meal should be free.
(laughing)
If the toilet's too tall and it's spicy food
and you go there to shit, it's a pack of opinion for Bill Hicks
and your toilet's too goddamn tall, comped.
- Do you have a problem where toilets are too tall for you?
- Have you ever sat on a tall toilet?
that's normal for me.
- Yeah, for you.
- I've sat on a tall, no.
I've never been like, my feet are always touching the ground.
- I got short legs, I got a very long torso.
- I've never, you don't have a long torso.
- I don't think any party is very long.
- Yeah, my torso's long.
My legs are really short, I have like a 28 inseam.
- That's adorable.
But the point is, there's no such thing as a tall toilet.
You talking about like a bar stool toilet?
- There are tall toilets.
- Where?
- What, yeah.
- I'm telling you.
have to jump to sit on? It's one at my mom's house. The one at your mom's house is too
large. How tall is it? Stand up and measure how tall it is. So, alright, so a toilet size,
like a toilet's usually like about that height. Okay, hold on, let me take a poop. Lift the
thing up. Okay, alright, you're pooping right now. Okay, so he's talking about a chair. So
you're saying a toilet that's like this, move down a little. Like that. If a toilet was
that tall, wouldn't you be uncomfortable? How tall is that, Caleb? Give a measurement.
about two and a half feet tall. You think that's crazy? There are tall toilets. I have sat on a
tall toilet before. There's no way there's a two and a half foot toilet in your mom's house. Yeah,
there is. Are you sitting on the tank? Are you doing an upper decker? That might be my problem.
You guys have never experienced a tall toilet is what you're telling me. I've never sat on a toilet
and been like, "Dan, this is a tall toilet." I've sat on toilets and been like, "This is way too
small I feel like I'm sitting on the ground that happens to me like a
locker room tall what are you in like an NBA locker room taking a shit I feel
like there's probably talk yeah yeah it's probably pretty big I don't know
that it's like this is I'm almost at the height of this oh you know what and
that's how I think this you know what you know what I'm lying it was a
handicapped toilet now it was probably a handicapped toilet wouldn't those be
sorter? No, handicapped people are huge. They are. Yeah. Oh yeah, because they can
use... they have... Well, no, a handicapped toilet is more flat. Because they can, they can, they can
like use their service dogs to step up to get onto the toilet. The dog shit for them. Yeah, exactly.
I'm not talking about like a wheelchair... Yeah, they bounce off their service dog like Mario
to reach greater heights. I'm talking about a lady who paid to get her dog registered as a
service dog that's what I mean by handicapped what you say again I don't
even know it was a clean take on that okay somebody who registered their dog to
be a service dog yeah and what about them and what do you have to say I meant by
handicapped that's why they service dogs service dogs are funny I'm guessing that
doesn't work you can register an animal I mean I there are people there are
people who need them I will what the hell was that who's here doorbell I don't
I think that's actually my groceries. They'll have to wait. Yeah, that's okay. But I guess
service dogs probably work for some people, but I did get the cats registered as service animals.
Really? Yeah.
Did that cost a bunch of money?
It costs like a hundred bucks.
Cost a hundred dollars each?
Patrick's mom is here to pick him up.
Yeah, yeah.
That's what that doorbell is. Come on, Patrick, it's time to get on the tall toilet.
I wish.
We have to go home so you can use the tall toilet. Maybe that's why you feel so ill,
because you've been you've been shitting on my small toilet.
No, I...
Well, they need a tall toilet at the Patrick household to hold all the shit.
True.
Yeah.
I've been like... I honestly do... Every time I come to New York, I have this like weird feeling of like
I don't know this place and then I get like sick.
I think you're like a kid.
Yeah.
I think you might just be a kid.
I think that being at home all day, at least for me, being at home all like every day
during the pandemic and not going anywhere ever means that now if I go anywhere I get sick.
It might be a magnetic field.
I think it's just because I miss my mommy.
That's what I've been thinking.
I think it's that I miss my mom.
I miss my computer.
You know what?
I miss my computer and I miss my...
The only thing that's going to cure me is going home and Twitch streaming for all of my lovely fans.
All my lovely, beautiful fans.
All my beautiful, lovely fans.
So what are we going to do? It's the last day in New York.
We're going to make it the last day? Oh, we're going home today?
I don't know. We're going home today? Or I thought we were staying. It's either the last full day or
the last day. Yeah, that's true. What have you guys always wanted to do in New York City?
I don't know. I thought I was going to get pizza tonight. You thought? Oh yeah. That's not that
crazy. Yeah, I was going to get pizza with Peter. You could still probably do that. Now that's an
idea for a movie right there. Pizza with Peter? My pizza with Peter? My pizza with Peter. What
What would that do?
You eat it.
No, I don't do anything.
Yeah, we get pizza, me and Peter get pizza
with Wallace Shawn.
Yeah. Wallace Shawn.
And Wallace Shawn.
And we just keep making it,
and he's trying to talk to us about like,
existentialist stuff, and we're sitting there,
and we're like, and do Inconceivable.
Yeah. And do Princess Bride.
Do Princess Bride now.
Yeah, Wallace Shawn just being like,
I feel like I become the character is what I'm all set.
"This pizza is so good! Oh my god, I love a pizza more than anything!"
[Laughter]
Just farting.
Guys!
"You see, the problem with everything is..."
Can you do all the shots?
"Oh my god, the pizza's good!"
That's the bald guy from The Prince's Bride?
Yeah.
[Fart noise]
[Laughter]
He played the, uh...
I can't really remember what he sounds like right now.
He played like the leader of the Ferengi in Star Trek Deep Space Nine.
Really?
He played the-
I'LL HAVE A PEPPERONI!
No, that's not him.
I will have a pepperoni!
I will have a-
*unintelligable noises*
No, that's like a cartoon snake.
Inconceivable!
He played- I'm not gonna- I'm not gonna say-
I'm not gonna say the name of the Ferengi leader because it sounds too similar to another word.
Ferengi?
The Ferengi leader is called the Grand N-A-G-U-S.
*snickers*
Nagus? Oh my god. That's his name. Oh my god. We got him.
That's not his name. You guys have been a honeypot this whole time. Yeah. Yeah, well that's, yeah,
there's a guy on that episode who says "Nagus" very weird. Yeah? And... Is it Dave Chappelle?
He says it with certain vowels changed around. He says it weird by changing the letters. He says it
the letters. He's not saying fast but he's asking can I say Nagus. He asked can I say it? I enunciated it so it
doesn't sound like I said it. Yeah but yeah he asked can I say. He does say.
So it's a kind of a coy joke. No it wasn't it wasn't meant to be a joke. They didn't have that word back then.
It was a very serious scene. They didn't understand that word back then they didn't have it yet.
This is Star Wars? Fuck you dude. Fuck you. Whoa what the fuck. You don't respect anything I like.
I don't.
That's true.
I am cutting ties with Caleb Pitts because he has implied.
I'm sorry that I'm awesome.
Caleb will be playing with Playmobiles at his house.
I'm sorry that I like almost stuff.
You want to go to the Playmobiles store?
I like stuff like Ultimate Frisbee.
Caleb, I'm going to create a custom Playmobile figure of you and I'm going to flush it down
my toilet.
That first part, pretty flattering honestly.
It's going to cost me $150.
Pretty flattering.
a hundred of do they have a playmobile store here let's let's go to that yeah
can we go to that we could go I mean I was definitely we went to the Lego store
last time we were here yeah we found out who was who yeah I would I got Yoda the
first time I'm a unicorn girl yeah fucked up do I forget what Patrick was I think
Patrick was the brown M&M.
Yeah.
Cause I'm sexy and I'm bookish.
Not even a Lego.
Yeah.
I'm like a sexy teacher like the brown M&M's.
Patrick goes to a fortune teller to get his fortune around and they're like,
I said you're the brown M&M.
Cause you're kinda, you're sexy and you wear glasses.
(laughter)
Brown M&M at the Lego store.
Every single BuzzFeed quiz Patrick takes, it's the brown M&M at the end.
Which Sex and the City character are you?
You're the brown M&M.
Are you kidding?
The brown M&M on Sex and the City?
Oh, don't get me started.
She would be talking about getting her pussy destroyed.
Oh yeah.
Just get her pussy turned out like a pocket.
M&M's, M&M's only...
(laughter)
Fuck.
Like a pocket.
(laughter)
Oh, God.
Goddamn.
(laughter)
God damn it's an M&M dude. It's not gross. They just have like one hole. Yeah they got a cloaca.
And that thing's tighted in a muffler. Yeah. Oh my god. That brown M&M got a cloaca.
M&M stands for my pee and my poop come from the same hole. The brown M&M is
sexually telling you that she used to be yellow. Yeah. I used to be pink. I used to be pink.
that's right yeah yeah they make the brown M&Ms out of poop. How big do you
think the M&Ms are in terms of? They're probably about the size of an M&M. No shut up.
Shut the fuck up Cameron. In all the movie trailers they are like. No those are just little people in a little world.
Okay how tall do you think like the biggest the yellow M&M he's the tallest
one. How tall do you think he is? Yeah well they're smaller than Santa in the
commercial. Santa's huge though. Yeah Santa's like ten feet tall. Santa's the biggest
German guy. Santa's an ancient Norse monster. Is he Norse? What is Santa? No he's a...
He's German right? Dude he's Nimrod from the Bible. He's a pagan
idol. Was Nimrod a bad guy? Well yeah he's a complete Nimrod.
he's not he's the Christmas tree is a is a pagan symbol cuz you're supposed to set
it on fire in your house yeah it's a ritual burning a tree to celebrate
Satan is there a Kwanzaa tree yeah the Kwanzaa candle I grew a Kwanzaa tree you
grew one yeah in my backyard yeah I smoke Kwanzaa trees
Come on.
What's wrong?
What is that even mean?
What the hell is he doing?
First you're saying the Deep Space Nine guy, now you're saying that shit.
You're going off to the rails today.
Sorry man.
You're going off to the rails.
I'm completely insane.
I ate so much chorizo that I just have pig fat in my arm.
Can we go to the Joker stairs today?
Yeah.
We go to the Joker stairs.
I want to exhibit white male rage.
Yeah.
I'm going to go there.
I'm going to do an awesome white male rage sketch.
Is it true that at the Joker stairs there are just always a bunch of Chinese tourists taking
pictures I didn't even know that was in this god city is it in the city thinking
at times where in San Francisco no it's it's New York City my cousin drove out
here to visit them one day that's one of the worst things you've ever said to me
my like 16 year old cousin yeah him and his friends took it it's the same cousin
that I have that when you think I said that I have what size is he he's my one
of my taller cousins he's one of these on the outside probably like Cameron site
Oh, really? Yeah. Oh, he's like 18 now. Is he interested in sports and does he need management?
No. No?
Dude, he drove to the Joker stairs. Yeah, he drove to the- he went to the Area 51 raid too.
Oh nice. Dude! Did that actually happen? Yeah. Did people go there? Yeah, he went there. What did they find?
They found everything.
It was super successful. Yeah, they found everything. They just got killed. Yeah, everyone died.
Yeah, it'd be so funny if the government just guns down every like Instagram meme person they've met.
and they went there.
- That would have been amazing.
- Like they didn't even like rush out,
there was just a big crowd.
- Oh that's funny, I've showed you his thing on Instagram
where he has like that calorie counter
and he keeps putting Pepto-Bismol in every day.
- No, I haven't seen that, but that's funny.
I don't know if Pepto had calories.
- He, yeah, well I gotta--
- Is Pepto-Bismol milk?
- It's metal.
- Is it milk and metal?
- It's the stuff they make chicken nuggets out of
at McDonald's.
- It's bismuth.
- It's the pink slime?
- Yeah.
- It's bismuth.
never seen the sharpest you showed me the bismuth yeah last night yeah you gave me
the business oh it looks exactly like the dark crystal yeah yeah it's really cool
looking yeah I know about this guy at RIP the fucking dark crystal that that
show sucks that got canceled yeah I mean I guess it is now that was one of the
most like that was one of the best shows to me I'm obsessed with the gelflings in
dark crystal yeah I was a girl they're the ones that look like I wish I was like
a human that could go there and show them like how to do they look like
androgynous mop it I would like to show them a little Wayne how to love yeah
yeah I could show miss officer from this officer how to love what what if you
could go to any physical buddy what the fuck you doing with your fucking
god damn it dude you were just can you see my scar you are a fat bastard today
Yeah, I know can I just poke your stomach you can poke my stomach
Your friend boy, oh pillsbury dough boy, I don't like you today, dude
Evil Patrick's back baby. I mean did you yeah, I mean like I'm just gonna not look at you for the rest of this
I'm gonna pull my dick out.
It's kinda hard though.
Man, you're kinda sussquatch.
Sussquatch?
That's you.
You look like the sussquatch.
You're the sussquatch, dude.
I do like that.
You like that?
I'm a freak.
I like it.
So what if I'm weird?
That just means I'm different.
Yeah.
Yo, would you go on an adventure in this white boys universe?
God, dude, we gotta stop fucking...
We exhausted that bit like the first day we were here.
No, it kept evolving and changing.
The first day it was, "Would you cry to the most beautiful song in the world?"
No, first it was, "Would you cry if I hugged you?"
And then it was, "Would you cry to the most beautiful song in the world?"
And then it was...
"Would you dance if I asked you to dance?"
And then it turned into, "Would you throw it back on a sensitive thug?"
And then it turned into, "Could you ever be friends with a homeless guy?"
Could you ever fall in...
Would you ever lay with a homeless woman?
almost female yeah I think the sensitive thugs the best iteration yeah cuz the
sensitive thug and the sensitive that's got truth to it yeah I mean it's
sensitive playa he speaks truth in volumes you know and he has he has
different attributes could you ever fall in love with the sensitive gangster how
many thugs can cry that's some real shit huh how many gangsters how many gangsters
have incredible thoughts. How many gangsters really care? How many of my gangsters really
care? Can you imagine, what if a thug loved art? It's a fair question. Yeah. You know?
What if a thug could see a painting so beautiful it brought him to tears? Like I am right now.
Damn. Yeah. Damn. I'm imagining a mixture of the Mona Lisa and Starry Night. What if
If a thug had the biggest Playboy meal collection in the world.
Playboy bill.
Yeah.
But it is honestly sad to imagine.
When we say thug we mean like Caleb.
We mean like white guy.
You know, white hip hop fan.
No.
No, I'm thinking like a cool black guy with a gun.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, and he's like looking at a painting and he's thinking of all his friends who have
died.
And he's like, I might have to shed my tears.
You know?
I might have to shed my tears.
I might have to.
- Excuse me, could everybody leave this art gallery?
- I'm gonna shed a tear.
- I might have to shed, you don't wanna see a thug cry.
(laughing)
Everybody get out, leave.
Show me the most beautiful painting and empty the room.
- What if a pimp proposed to you?
- A pimp would never propose, that's against the pimp game.
As soon as a pimp proposes, he's no longer a pimp.
- Yeah, he's a wimp. - Caleb Pitts.
(laughing)
- He turns into a wimp.
- Yeah, from pimp to wimp.
- From pimp to wimp in one, two, three, four words.
- Mm-hmm.
- Would you marry my ass?
- Would you marry this pimp?
- Would you marry, make this pimp happy?
(laughing)
- Yeah.
Yeah, I am a pimp.
- That's just against the code of the game.
- Yeah.
- The game code.
- Which we know so much about.
- The Konami code.
- Yeah, we saw a genuine pimp walking around.
- We did.
- Yeah.
- That one with Neil.
- Oh my God, yeah.
- Yeah, he had the cane and everything.
yeah yeah he's 90 years old yeah it was at this place it was yeah it was my
retirement center we did see a real pimp yeah I did I didn't even realize he had
the blue hair yeah and the blue suit yeah he looked sounds like Tyler Ninja
Blevins I think it might have been Tyler that's a blimp did he have like he had a
headband girls with him he had a headband he was the lonely pimp and he
the lonely pimp. The lonely pimp. Damn the lonely pimp finding his way. The lonely pimp finding
his way in the big city. He just moved. He just moved from Wisconsin. He's a small-time
Wisconsin pimp. He's trying to be a big-city New York pimp now. I'm just trying to be the
biggest pimp of all time. Yeah. Did you see him cry? No. Did you see him have a sensitive
thought? Yes. What would you do if you saw a pimp cry? I saw a soft bubble come up and
there was a flower in it.
- That's so sad.
- Yeah, one of the saddest things I've ever heard.
- That's one of the saddest things I've ever heard.
I'm not kidding.
- A pimp with a flowery thought bubble.
- A pimp just thought of a flower.
(laughing)
Somewhere in this world, hey, somewhere in this world
a pimp has just thought of a flower.
Are you gonna make the changes in your life?
- Are you gonna be the part of the change?
- Be a part of the change.
- See the change.
- A pimp just imagining an ant crying.
Is that sad or are you tripping?
be part of the mountain, not the mohill.
- That's so true.
- A pimp, just imagine a mother bear feeding its young.
- Mother Teresa just saved,
Mother Teresa just became a pimp.
- Mother Teresa just became the worst pimp in the world.
Do you want a front row seat?
- She's too benevolent.
- That's right.
Didn't Mother Teresa like--
- Benevolent pimp is a great gamer tag.
(laughing)
Benevolent pimp.
Mother Teresa like she like believed that she Madison was gay
got her back blown out I mean she was fucking getting railed yeah she got my
god she just she did a world tour getting railed in every country she went
on a hellhomer sex tour yeah she went Jackie Chan around the world in 80 days
but it was around the world getting 80 lady laid yeah she was introduced her to
heroin mm-hmm she loved doing H I love doing heroin mate that's mother Teresa
I'm mother Teresa. I love doing heroin mate. Yeah. Oh, yeah, I fucking love putting a spike in my vein. That's right. Oh
Fucking load me up
Fucking load me up get me to party. I'm mother Teresa. Oh, I'm gonna be benevolent today
I'm mother Teresa. I'm feeling a bit benevolent today. What I'm gonna start. I'm gonna put this in your arm
Come here, I think she like over here
people like morphine and chicks she was like God's got you play a chill yeah yeah
and then people would just be like you just gotta wait on God he's coming any
minute now yeah and then their hearts are speeding and she's like she's made
people see God by giving him too much heroin too much pussy yeah yeah mother
the Theresa gave me too much pussy.
I'm glad Theresa pussy got me seeing God.
Yeah.
No, but I am thinking of becoming a pimp pretty soon.
Finally.
The neighborhood doesn't have one.
Yeah.
The hood need me.
I just thought there's a power vacuum.
Yeah.
There's a lot of women just walking around not knowing what the fuck to do on my block.
Ridgewood's Most Wanted.
It's going to be the sequel to Malibu's Most Wanted.
Yeah, exactly.
And I could be...
Well, no, I'm not trying to rap. Although, maybe I'll parlay that into rapping once I
have some experiences to talk about, you know? Because that's the only reason you become a pimp,
is so in 10 years, you could be a rapper. You have a story to tell.
Yeah. Let me tell my story as the sensitive pimp from Ridgewood.
The sensitive pimp is... I moved here two years ago.
I moved here two years ago. And this is my story.
And I started pimping a week ago. And I can't remember if I'm a pimp or a John.
I got sick from a sandwich.
Yeah, and that's my story. And that's my story to tell. So anyway, next. Happy to be here
at this youth group retreat, telling my story of how I came to know God. Because that's
the redemption tour. That's how you, you have to find God and then you realize everything
that you were doing as a pimp was wrong, then you start rapping. Yeah. You know. If you
gay you go to jail you better change before you go to hell that's right yeah
that's right the sensitive pimp story yeah I was gay for a hundred years mm-hmm
now I'm 25 and I'm drinking the beers yeah now I'm 25 I just changed my life I
used to be a pimp I thought about dropping out of college but I couldn't
dare leave behind that knowledge that's right can I have a little bit of
knowledge tell Roth I don't love college I used to that's a shitty thing I walked
with the limp I I used to drink beer now I don't even have a sip a sip that's
right I'm also that's right I'm the benevolent pimp thank you I'm the
tearful I've been thank you I've been the benevolent pimp have a great night
everybody and next up the benevolent pep. Hello ladies and gentlemen does anybody need help?
Do you guys need help? Do you guys need a role model? I'm that pimpin' Samaritan. Does anybody
here need a role model? Anybody here need to need to be taught a lesson about pimpin'? Does
anybody here need math help? Anybody here named Matthew? Matthew? Anyone here named Matthew? Okay
Matthew. Matthew. Did you have a grandfather named Ricardo? No? Okay.
All right. Anyone else there? Ricardo. Ricardo. Ricardo. Richard? Is it a Richard?
Was it a Richardo? Richardo. Richardo? Is that your... Okay. You know what? I think
I think maybe I think maybe this spirit I think maybe this may might be a
different spirit. I don't think this... I think actually Matthew's a liar. I
I think Matthew is a liar. Is there a Pikachu in here? Is there a Pikachu in here?
Did you have a brother? Do you have a brother named Charmander?
Char-Char-Char-Charles. Charles. Charles is Amanda.
Charles Amanda. Charles Martinette. Martinette. Charles Martinette. He's your brother.
Are you...
Am I a medium?
Are you in a medium show?
Yeah. I'm getting you're in a seat. Did anyone here have a grandfather that recently
passed away?
Okay, you did. What was his name?
That's exactly who I'm hearing. He just told me that you're he sees you and you're at a medium show right now
You're drinking Sprite. He says in your purse you have your wallet
He says you have socks on under those shoes he says what those feet do
He says you're not wearing underwear and you're wearing a dress and you're gonna get laid tonight, lady
I'm getting your grandpa. He's telling me. Yeah that okay. You're a freak bitch. He says you're a freak
He says you're a freak six days a week.
He says he says he says for the asks for the people sitting next to you to move
to the side because you got that stanky thang on you.
Yeah. Your grandpa's telling me you have to show me your boobies. Your
grandfather's telling me your back shot air smells like motor oil. Your
grandfather is not actually dead he's saying these things to me through an
earpiece. Your grandpa. He's backstage. He's backstage. Grandpa come on out.
He's doing awesome powers in my ear and he's saying grandpa horny.
He's saying, "Do I make me horny?"
Does anyone here have a grandpa who was horny?
A horny grandpa.
Does anybody here a horny milf who's DTF?
Anybody?
Does anyone here have a small penis...
Okay, I'm telling you.
Okay, your grandfather's telling me a number.
It's my phone number.
Does anybody in this room have a small penis caused by simple clog that can be undone using
this technique?
(laughing)
- Damn, it would be crazy to be a,
dude, being a medium is probably the easiest job ever.
- Probably the most fun thing ever to talk to.
- You have to have a gimmick.
- The easiest job is baby actor.
- Yeah.
- You don't even remember your job.
- That's true.
- Yeah, the easiest job is the one you can't remember.
- That's right.
(laughing)
- That's why I take Rohypnol before I go to work every day.
- A medium would be hard,
'cause you have to be an amazing storyteller.
And you have to wear a funny dress.
- You really just need a gimmick,
like the Long Island medium,
She's just like, she's from Long Island.
- Okay, I hear a ghost.
- Yeah.
- Ah!
- You can, ooh, you could be the fearful medium.
- I could be the medium afraid of ghosts.
- I'm hearing your grandfather.
- Oh my God, no!
Oh my God!
- Yeah, your grandpa says he loves you.
- Your grandpa says boo.
Your grandpa is saying boo.
He's just saying boo.
I think he really likes being a ghost.
- Does anybody here know a ghost?
anybody anybody
there's a ghost here
there's a ghost here looking for someone can anyone tell me if
there's a ghost behind me
is there a ghost in this room?
your grandfather says he loves you he's right behind me isn't he?
your grandfather says he's a big ugly idiot
and he smells bad
He fucking sucks dick.
And he's right behind you.
There's just a big weight levitating above his head.
Wait, is that a piano?
Hanging four feet in front of me.
Is that a ghost piano?
That's what ghosts do is they drop pianos on people.
Cartoon ghosts.
Casper's brothers.
Yeah, does anybody here a cartoon?
Yeah, Casper's brothers.
Those guys were jerks.
They're not brothers by the way, they're uncles.
Oh, fuck.
He's the nephew.
Some of the baddest uncles in media. I forgot. They bad? They're the biggest bastards.
Can you bust it open for a bad uncle? I would. Would you show your thing off to a banshee?
Yeah. Would you let the witch from Left 4 Dead 2's Screamature thingy? Would you hold it down
for a siren? For a siren? Could you let a leprechaun in? No. No? Could you let Monique? Have you
guys seen any leprechauns in New York City? Yeah, we saw a few. Really? Yeah, they were
running around your house last night while you were asleep. Yeah. I'm gonna hit you with
that WTF right now. Dude, this leprechaun was sucking my dick last night. Dude, the hottest
leprechaun I've ever seen. The hottest leprechaun let me suck his dick last night. There was
this big this big leprechaun this six foot tall leprechaun. Whoa yeah I think that's a
man. No. No. What do you think? A man would never have red hair and a red beard. Do you have a
watercolor tattoo? A man would never have red hair and a red beard that was a tall
leprechaun. Yeah it's a leprechaun. Tell it to the gingers have souls guy. Copper Cab.
Copper Cab. He doesn't have a beard. He has a beard now. Copper Cab is one of those
was
in my own pants at school. I was a troll. Yeah, I was doing I was IRL streaming in
my brain. Exactly. I was IRL, basically I would I would IRL stream peeing my pants
in math class then I would go home and I would watch the VOD in my dreams over
and over and I would cry laughing I would cry I was laughing I was laughing
so hard that I was crying. I mean once that copper cab supreme drop
coming. That's right. That's fucking right. That's right.
Yeah, Supreme box logo over his eyes or something on the shirt. Yeah
When is he collabing with us? Yeah, what are we doing the copper cab collab? We gotta get a ginger on
I'm sure I'm sure you you guys almost are there. Oh, yeah, my beard like reddish hair and you have a red beard
Yeah, that's true. He does have a red beard. Yeah, he's beard red beard. They call me Patrick the red
Who does that the Viking my Viking friends all my Viking friends?
friends love me hanging out with my Viking friends tonight yeah hey you want
to go out tonight sorry I'm with the Viking friends yeah yeah it's an actual
like do that all right guys want to like have like yeah like my Viking friends
yeah my Viking friends take me out with them on their raids yeah yeah when we go
I mean we go I never do that other stuff but we go we definitely go yeah I'm with
them like half the time I don't do I don't do the Viking stuff after dark yeah
yeah the Viking late show I don't get involved with that shit no no yeah man I
hate being a Viking nowadays I only ever do burials at sea with my Viking friends
Mm-hmm. Yeah, sorry. It's just kind of a Viking thing. Yeah. Yeah, I only read runes with my Viking friends
The fuck is a rune dude just make paper. Mm-hmm. Yeah, pussy. Come on. Don't be don't be just use the alphabet
Yeah, just use a normal alphabet
Why does everyone keep talking about gnomes what you talking about gnomes folk still mean something we got in leprechauns is the new shit
Yeah, leprechauns is the word.
Stop talking about gnomes, man.
Stop talking about that gnome shit.
We're talking about leps.
We got leprechauns now.
Little lep.
Leps world.
What about, uh...
Me and my friends in middle school used to play this iPod touch game that was a rip-off
of Mario called Leps World.
Leps World?
Yeah, it was about a leprechaun named Lep.
Lep the con.
Was there like goombas and shit?
I don't remember.
I'm going to look it up right now.
What does he fight?
I think maybe snails.
He fights snails?
What about a sip it like sipping on some scissor if it's like
I have so much gold I got leprechaun poisoning.
They made Lep's World 2 and 3.
Woah! No.
He fights, it looks like maggots.
Look at that thing.
He doesn't send the snakes out of Ireland.
Ireland what is that thing is that a maggot or a beetle or what that's like
just an Irish woman yeah that's his wife but yeah it's literally it's literally
just a Mario that pops fries I think I showed you oh he does fight snails -
look there's snails in Leps world - damn let's world - got the snail so you got
to watch out for anything they got a snail joints and oh he turns neon and
Leps world 3 and there's a pirate what the hell oh my god can we stream Leps
world yeah is it can we stream phone game I guess yeah I think I've done I've
gotten a phone yeah dude we got a stream left world
Leps world 4 has a monk is a monkey as the main character we should do this is
Leps world 4 we should make our own we should make us three as a family in the
Sims yeah oh we should play the Sims and we can make we can make two mommies mm-hmm
we got two moms I got two moms look at let's roll five getting to school and
he's like guess who has two fucking moms who wants to come over they have a
window in their room I live in the red light district in Amsterdam I searched
leps world on on Google Images and I'm just scrolling and there are a bunch of
just ripoff games that just can't like there's one here called leps world Z and
and one called let's world five
let's people love that i don't know what i see people are just making a lot of
money a les bles world yeah
lesbic on
now what
les brokawen no i don't come on menu but no
why did it was a little concern girls
the girl leprechaun can be
now that's a sheep recon she ever come
ship record
Leprechaun zombie world?
Why is the leprechaun there?
This is one of the funniest pictures I've seen.
Why is there a leprechaun at all?
I'm going to post this.
It's just a guy in a fucking AR.
No, but there's a leprechaun in the background.
Why is that leprechaun there?
Also, I'm going to post this picture with the...
Leprechauns traditionally are small.
With the episode.
And here's a giant head.
This guy is a leprechaun from the Teletubbies.
That's even scarier, dude.
- No, that's a big leprechaun.
- That's a giant leprechaun.
- What was that one kid's show where it was like all the--
- Booba.
- Is that the Almost Teletubbies one?
- Yeah.
- That has like the circumcised penis.
- Booba.
- You didn't even have to finish the sentence.
- Yeah, well whenever you bring up Teletubbies
and that ends up as what was that,
yeah, the answer's Booba.
- There's a guy named Mr. Man and Mrs. Woman.
- Mr. Man, Mrs. Lady.
- That wouldn't fly today.
- Uncle.
(laughing)
- That's right.
- Uncle might still fly.
- They live in a giant hive.
they go boo bah and then they fly around Jesus what kind of giant fat these
Chinese people on msg oh my come on come on come on what's wrong with those guys
or me it's the problem it's a Chinese it's not that it wasn't Chinese what do
- What is he saying? - It was British.
- Cameron, Cameron's tricking me into being racist again.
Fuck you, man.
- You're the one who said it.
- You can't tell me you don't watch a show like that
and think, oh, this is Chinese.
- I don't, no, it's British.
- Yeah, that's what I think.
I think this is like, I mean,
it looks like zooming in on their food
to like the molecular level.
- Exactly. - The bubas.
- Exactly.
Do you remember Bing and Bong?
- Having a plate of buba and uncle?
- Say big and long?
- Bing and Bong.
- No.
- It was another one of those,
like it was on that buba block.
- Bing and Bong?
was on that boobah block. Damn, he's on that boobah block. Don't fuck with boobah block.
Come on boobah block. You don't want to smoke from Mrs. Lady. Nah. Wear the wrong colors
on boobah block, you'll wet it up. Bing and bong. I think you're just... Bing and bong
is what it's called. Bing and bong is the tiny planet. That's like what all of Patrick's...
Let me see. What the fuck is that dude? I don't know, but I watched a bunch of this
This is a kid.
That's like a nightmare show.
Yeah, it's another one of those.
Bing and Tongue.
Oh, Google Bing and Tongue Tiny Planet.
Yeah, no, British kid shows look like this.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I do know there's some like crazy, there's some crazy British stop motion show.
CBeebies?
Where it was about like a guy who had demons in his basement or something.
There was some fucked up one about an old man who wants to eat the cheese on the moon.
Yeah.
There's this fucked up one where they did something completely different.
Wait, is this, is this British?
Uh-oh.
here comes the twist no no what is it it's made from Patrick's house it was
made yeah was UK okay could be anywhere is me nowadays the way with ghost
productions never ghost peppers ghost scary I didn't really watch a lot of
like kids shows made for kids yeah I I watched like I you obviously shows made
for kids and I stopped watching TV when I was like, like when I outgrew like, like,
like kids shows. I just stopped watching. I watched kids shows until I was six and
then I found Adult Swim and then I got fucked in the head. That's right. Yeah. My mom used to
lie to everybody and say that we didn't have a TV. Yeah. And then we did have a TV
the entire time. Yeah. People would come over she'd be like, "Oh yeah, we just got
this." Oh yeah, that's the microwave. Yeah. Yeah. That's our flat microwave. Look, we're making
Teletubbies in the microwave don't worry about it we're cooking in CIS for dinner
yeah look at this other fucking show I watch it's called the save them's early
2000s like CGI kid shows looked all fucked up what's wrong with you man like
if you ever have did you want have you watched hoodwinked since it came out yeah
it looks crazy insane smell powerful believe that's all the save them yeah
We're going to post all of these pictures with the episode.
Yeah, they look fucking awful.
That's just like the worst character designs of all time.
I think it looks alright.
I think they look small.
Shut up.
You hate it.
I think they look small yet powerful.
Oh my god, look at that fucking guy.
That little face.
He's got the smallest fucking face on earth.
And the biggest head in the world.
I got that small face.
I give that small face.
I got that tiny mouth.
I'm giving that 6'4" 5AR head.
I got a tiny mouth. I don't know what to do with it.
[Mimicking the sound of a baby]
Yeah, he's...
When he's sucking it, he goes...
[Mimicking the sound of a baby]
Their names were jazzy.
He goes down and he goes...
Noodle, Custard, Ka-Chung,
Foo... Ka-Chung?
Beanie Jammies, Ka-Chung?
What's that?
These are all the names of the same food.
Ka-Chung is a
red hippopotamus, red and white hippopotamus like creature. He's the
toughest saver. His name is Aikido in the French dub. Yeah this is, okay so this is
Canadian so that makes sense. Okay. So you were lying. No I never. Why do you lie so
much? Okay. Why do you play too much? I'm playing. You true. But there's a
character named BB Jammy's in the English version but in the French dub his
name is baby Jimmy baby Jimmy Jimmy Jimmy Jimmy Jimmy Jimmy Jimmy Jimmy Jimmy
what's going on you can be all you get you get you nice and ready for dinner
yeah we get you ready for dinner baby Jimmy we're having baby Jimmy for dinner
we are going to feed you a big snare baby Jimmy we are you guys ever eaten a snare?
I've never eaten an escargot. I don't like that they keep the shells in there. Have you eaten it?
Every day. Every day of my life. I wake up and I slurp snails like Shrek.
I eat a Shrek-sized meal.
And I pee on it.
You are Shrek'd out today, dude. You're fucking nasty. You're picking your nose and you're fucking sucking your own...
I think I'm farting. You're farting in the mud tub. Yeah. Oh, man. You have your feet out.
Man, don't knock that till you try it.
You have shit all over your feet.
Don't knock it till you try it.
You got three fat green babies that burp.
You smell like a fart in the mud tub.
Your friend is a donkey with a dragon.
Yeah, you're straight up Shrek mode today, dude.
You have a beautiful Shrek wife.
My donkey friend, a lot of people are mad at him for some things he said at the beginning
of his stand-up special.
Yeah, his karaoke post-credits scene in Shrek 2.
Yeah, that's what he said to the three blind mice at the beginning.
He sat at the front.
Blind mice sit at the front.
Yeah, they got mad about that one.
Yeah.
What are you going to do, man?
Hey, that's far, far away for you.
That's true.
Yeah.
Listen, that was a different time.
That was a long time ago.
Those are those far, far away liberals.
That was once upon a time, okay?
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
just ready to ready to jump on a donkey for any time he slips up you know he's
got up stop stop pulling my arm hair you almost said my Hitler hair cuz you know
you're a little you almost said stop pulling my Hitler hair I heard it stop
pulling my arm hair you fuck you know that you like I'm gonna sit down I'm
gonna have a Hitler breakfast this morning I'm gonna drink some Hitler
I'm riding my Hitler bike to work. I'm gonna comb my Hitler hair. Yeah my
Hitler boss wants me to stay late.
Oh fuck. You pulled his Hitler hair again.
How? He Hitler hit me. Stop calling me Hitler. I'm not Hitler. You're not Hitler yet.
You could be. You could turn into Hitler. No, no. You're brothers. It would be funny to...
No, come on. Don't bring him up. What the hell, dude? He's a child. He said he was
gonna be darker than Hitler. We don't know what that means. That can mean anything.
It's one of the funniest fucking things. Yeah a ten-year-old saying I'm gonna be
darker than Hitler. Yeah it's crazy. Nobody knew what to do in that moment we're just
like that yeah no don't just don't. Don't. Don't. Hey. I know. Hey. Yeah I wanted to be in the NBA
- Yeah, but we're not all gonna fulfill our dreams.
You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
- Just 'cause you wanna be darker than Hitler
doesn't mean you will be.
- Yeah, it's not, yeah.
- I'm gonna be darker than Gordon Hayward.
- Come on, you're a mediocre white man.
- Yeah.
- That's gonna take 10,000 hours of being like Hitler.
- Lord, grant me the Hitlerness of a mediocre white man.
(laughing)
- That's so crazy that.
- Lord, grant me the darkness of Hitler.
- You're gonna get in trouble.
- I didn't say that, that was something else
Caleb's brother said. I didn't say, he's not here. He texted me. Oh he did? Yeah.
You have a ten-year-old's phone number? Yeah, he's your brother. You're right,
that's true, that's true. That's true. That's true. That's true.
Pat, earlier when you said it's crazy that, were you gonna say something just
like it's crazy that the Holocaust happened? I don't even remember. You don't
even remember? I don't remember. Yeah, I don't remember. Yeah, I don't remember if I was
gonna say that? God honestly. I think I was gonna say it's crazy that we're such
great friends. Yeah it's crazy that I get to do everything with my two best
friends. Yeah. Yeah. We should get a sweater with three holes in the top. We should get a
bike with three holes in it. So we can fuck it. Yeah. Exactly. We should get a girlfriend with three holes in her. We can all split her.
No. No. That's some fucking freak. What the hell? I wouldn't find her attractive. I guess
girls do have three holes. God. Yeah, the nose and the mouth and the ears, right? And
the pit. The armpit. The pit. Not the armpit. No, the pit. The pit. It's just called the
pit. The pit and the pendulum. Where's that located? The pit? Yeah. Hey, if you know,
know there's a secret girl that's what that's what that push a tea so only the
ultimate ultimate pleasure men know pleasure pleasure men the view of you
been meeting with pleasure men I go to the pleasure man they've been meeting
with him I go to the pleasure men's ball
that's where we give each other advanced pussy eating techniques you were you
wear a crystal tuxedo at the Pleasureman's Ball and you wear so much chapstick.
Oh you gotta wear it, you gotta wear it. We don't even, we get that
squeezable carmex too. Oh yeah, the stuff that smells like a fucking
metal. Yeah. Yeah, it's all over your mouth. Yeah. Yeah and you're bragging.
You're popping your lips over and over again. I'm bragging about how great my pussy eating techniques are.
Recently I've been using my tongue. Yeah, finally, I mean if you don't, they like it
better if you don't actually try to eat it. It's been crazy yeah recently I've
just been licking instead of biting it. Yeah it's odd. Yeah you don't even need a
straw. It's worse for me. Yeah sometimes I still do it though low-key. Low-key you
got to do it. Low-key sometimes I still pull it out. That's just some real shit.
I put in Dracula teeth. I put in Austin Powers costume teeth and I eat pussy
till the cows come home. That's the pleasureman secret.
Pleasuremen, god damn it. What a weird group of guys. They're my crazy friends.
It's so crazy that they actually exist. They're my crazy best friends. I can't imagine
being a pleasureman. They're like the Freemasons. We dressed exactly the
same as the Freemasons. It's so crazy. I think the pleasuremen
started as an offshoot of the Freemasons. Yeah, exactly. You have to wear those
little hats. You gotta wear a little hat and you gotta wear a big dick. I would love to
eat pussy with the hat that the monkey wears in a hat. I would love to eat pussy with my
pleasure men. Pussy with my pleasure men. Pleasure men laugh together and they eat together
too. Whiskey for my pleasure men. Beer for my horses. Yeah, that's right. Whiskey for
the pleasure men. Beer for the horses. I love to go to the pleasure men's balls. We raise
all our glasses against evil forces and say whiskey for the pleasure men's balls. Beer
for my horses. Beer for my hoses. Beer for my horses. Horses. We've gotten almost no sleep
for days. What was that? I was talking in snake speak. That's exactly how it has been
it's just noises. Yeah. Yeah. Just noises and you and hypothetical questions about
sensitive thugs. Yeah. Yeah. And then we just ate chorizo and eggs. Yeah. Yeah. I
think my cholesterol. You filled the house with smoke. You did. I did. It was like
completely, I couldn't see. Yeah. There was no. You would be like, oh the smoke is
clearing and then you would go into another room and come back and it's like
oh I can't. You left the gas on or something. You did leave the gas on.
While you were driving to get us. Yeah. Maybe that's what's happened. Maybe we're
just experiencing the residual effects of a gas leak. I think gas leaks make you
happy. I've talked about this. Yeah. I feel like you fucking, I feel like a
little bit's good for you. You know? It's good for the creative process.
Anything is good in moderation, including gas. Including putting your head in the
oven. That's what Sylvia Plath messed up. You don't put your head in the oven. It doesn't go in the oven.
No, you sit in the oven with your phone and you watch movies with your phone.
Yeah. I'm so cold. I'm so cold. I'm gonna sit in the oven with my phone and watch movies.
Sylvia Platt turned the oven on?
Sylvia Platt. She just starved. She just laid down, the oven was off.
She laid down, put her head in the oven and she just fell asleep and died.
What about Sylvia Plopp and she's...
And she shit. She has a crap.
She makes that thing shit. She makes that big ass shit.
She, well, yeah.
She always tell how.
Whoa.
I didn't know you could do that.
I got a bell jar for right fucking here.
Yeah, my balls jar.
Yeah, I got a fucking bell jar.
yeah yeah welcome to the pleasurements club welcome to the pleasurements club
um um um I'll be first first name and this shall be last name Eden pussy I'm
being pussy welcome to the pleasurements club I'm captain we have an open bar over
there and a full playground go buck wild this is about pleasure pussy this is
This is about indulging in your deepest, wildest fantasies.
That's right.
Yeah, we got a guy over there, he's eating pussy while doing swings.
Yeah, that's right.
We got the NBA finals on and we have an Xbox controller you can hold and pretend you're
playing the game.
Welcome to the Pleasuremen's Club.
Actually tonight we have our annual basketball game against Dr. Paine's House of Blood.
The Pleasuremen versus the Cenobites.
pleasure men are the exact opposite of the center but it's yeah they're they
find they find pleasure painful yeah but they're also best kiss yeah come give me
a kiss I hate it yeah yeah I hate it no I hate I hate it
welcome to the pleasure men's club here's a robe but there's nothing to tie
it up with yeah it's gotta be a head they have poon
he's walking around explain that yeah I could fuck it now you can fuck it if you want
yeah yeah just tap me on the shoulder yeah you want to fuck my face I hate it
you I mean it hurts so bad but I hate it if you want such pussy to eat with you
we have such we have such it's the I am in hell please help and it's just a guy
I am eating pussy, I love it.
(laughing)
- It's written on the wall.
- They're getting covered in blood still.
- I am eating pussy, I love it.
(laughing)
- They got the one centibite with the teeth.
You know what he's doing.
- He's chomping.
- He's chomping at the bit.
- They got one centibite who got no teeth.
- They call me Gary Gator.
- Gary Gator.
- Yeah, I chomp on the pussy.
on the pussy like a t-bone steak yeah I'm like that I'm like that you want to get
mangled I'm gonna bite your pussy I'm gonna twist around like an alligator oh
I'm gonna pull it off like another most painful thing in the world is pleasure
is lava pleasure lava pleasure men's attack I'm gonna give you I'm gonna put
I'm gonna douche you with lava.
- Oh. - Oh.
- Oh. - Yeah.
- Oh. - Come on, that's lava.
- We did that in unison.
- Caleb's been really getting into a Jim Gaffigan thing lately.
- Yeah. - Come on, Caleb, you're nasty, dude.
- Well, I just know which way that if I say something outrageous,
I gotta get ahead of the curve on it, 'cause you guys get mad at me.
- I mean, that's what Jim Gaffigan does, too.
I mean, if he says he eats a whole cake,
he's gotta hear what I said the other day about...
- I ate a whole cake. - Yeah, he's done with...
- Yeah, he's done with, he doesn't even care anymore.
He's not gonna stick to basketball.
He's gonna stay his politics.
- Yeah, I'm not gonna stick to being fat anymore.
I'm gonna be stupid too.
I'm not gonna stick to basketball.
I'm not just gonna dribble the ball.
I'm more than that.
- Jim Gaffigan, every time he goes for a free throw,
he's like, "Oh, I hope I make it."
- I hope he makes the free throw.
- Free throw, free throw.
Oh, he missed the three pointer.
Oh my god.
- Boo buckets.
(laughing)
- Jim Gaffigan's just walking around the city
and being like, and just saying to himself,
why is he staring at that lady like that?
(laughing)
- Why is he going into the fitting room?
- There's nobody's paying attention to him.
What is he, what dark thoughts are in his mind?
(laughter)
He's evil but he doesn't know it yet.
I'd love to fuck Jeff Gaffigan.
He's gonna be darker than Hitler.
He wants to be darker than Hitler.
Oh, he needs to behead that man.
Oh, he needs to behead that man, doesn't he?
(laughter)
He's gotta do that while he--
While he drives.
and while he has sex yeah what did you say
he's having sex with his wife nothing I was kidding remember I'm a comedian
joking around I'm gonna behead my son I'm gonna behead him
Hey dad, do you have like a, like is that a song playing in the background or something?
Are you just, are you saying that?
So I like to eat cake!
Yeah, sorry son, I'm writing new material.
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
Oh, your neck is gonna be removed from your head.
I'm gonna put a new hole in you.
Your neck is gonna be removed from your head.
He just wants the neck, not even the head.
I'm gonna take neck from my son.
the head I'm gonna take neck from my son
you guys are prude you get mad at everything me yeah I am for a little bit
of a prude so tortillas are crazy I'm the modest one you guys are the freaks
I'm not so you're telling me I may be a pleasure made bread I want to join the
- I hate the pleasure men so bad.
- You wanna join?
- The pleasure men society.
- Let me ask you three questions.
- What's up?
- All right, first question.
I'm ready.
- Now first question, what's up with it?
- Can you throw it back on a millionaire freak?
- I'll literally.
- And make him squirt his girt all over your shirt?
- Real shit, I'ma thaw that pussy out.
- All right.
- I'ma bring it to room temperature.
- You passed the first test of the pleasure men.
- Second question.
- Next question.
What would you do if you received an email from the craziest psycho freak of all time?
Send it back. Send that email back. Hit the reverse button on his email.
Maybe that's not quite the right answer.
Yeah, you know, but I mean he's two, one for two.
He's got energy.
Are y'all done? Third question.
Third question.
Y'all done talking?
When you get up in there and you first see what she's packing and you see and she gets it up there
up there and she and you and you look in the mirror and what do you say?
I wish it was all tip. I wish my shit was tip from front to back. One big tip.
One big tip? I just want one. He's identified the pleasure set. I want my dick to be all tip.
I think we might have the Anakin Skywalker of pleasure men. I'm ready.
- We got to test your sperm count like midichlorians.
- Someday I'm gonna be Darth Flavor.
(laughing)
- We gotta test your sperm count like it's midichlorians.
You might be the prophetic--
- For now I'm just Slamacan.
- The prophetic pleasure man.
- Yeah, for now I'm just little Slamacan boy,
but I could be Darth Flavor one day.
Slammakin guys walkers. Come on. What? That doesn't even make any sense.
It's just my cocker. What? Slammakin my cocker. Slammakin my cocker? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It was
a stretch. I like mine better. Well I like mine better. Okay. Yeah. Having kids pregnant
guy. Right? Yeah. That works. Right? Is that good guys? Yeah. Alright. Join the pleasure
Jar Jar Stinky Thing.
*laughter*