You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
- [Woman] Podcasts for the heartless.
- You're a crap monster.
(laughing)
- Holy cord.
All right, I'm gonna pick up my camera now.
- Okay, pick up your camera.
- I'm just wearing a normal shirt.
- You're definitely not wearing anything weird, right?
- I've decided to become a chef.
(laughing)
(laughter)
- It's for, nobody can fucking see this show.
- This one, I'll post the video of the first 10 seconds
of this episode.
- I have recently discovered my love for cooking
and the culinary arts.
- Do you have the hat?
Do you have the hat?
- Can you just say yes, chef?
No, they didn't have the hat at the store.
- What store?
- You went and bought a chef outfit,
but not a webcam?
- Yeah, what the fuck?
(laughing)
- It was on sale. - You were just saying
you were too broke to buy a webcam.
- It was on sale.
Fucking a webcam's on sale at Walmart right now.
I was there earlier.
- I don't live near a Walmart.
I do live near a Chef Supply Store.
(laughing)
Can you guys just say yes, Chef, please?
- No.
- And confirm that you're hearing me?
I won't know if you guys-- - No, Chef.
- Can hear me.
What the hell?
I'm not used to that.
(laughing)
But yeah, I'm basically gonna get into making recipes and--
- Hey Charlie, you're probably embarrassed
I got the perfect read on you,
that you didn't pick your camera up
'cause you were wearing a crazy outfit.
I knew that, dude.
- No, I'm not embarrassed.
- Hey Caleb, hey Caleb. - The chef has to be
strong and confident.
What? - Caleb, you're 86ed.
- What is, you actually, I'm actually the chef
and you're not wearing any sort of chef outfit.
- You're 86ed. - No, no, I'm not.
- Hey Caleb. - Uh-huh?
- You're food taste-- - Sorry, are you guys
on the line right now? - Hey Caleb, you're food--
- I can't tell.
- Your food tastes terrible. - I am on the line
and I'm telling you. - Your food tastes terrible.
- I'm telling you that you're 86ed.
- My food tastes terrible?
- I'm the head chef now.
- Well, I'm gonna flip your plate over
and say, "Get out of my restaurant!"
- Dude, it's not your restaurant.
- I'm the head chef. - I'm the head chef.
- I'm head chef.
- You don't even have a chef shirt.
- I'm dressed up like the chefs
at the restaurant I worked at.
- That's not a real restaurant.
- It was a real restaurant.
- I am designing a new-- - You never worked
in a restaurant. - I'm designing a new,
I worked at Jersey Mike's for three days
and I got fired because my hands were too sweaty.
You know that.
- That's true, I do know that.
- You do know that.
- That doesn't count though.
- That's a restaurant.
I have experience.
- I never worked the line either.
I only worked front of house.
- That's not a restaurant.
- If it's the person in line makes the sandwich,
since you're instructing them what's going on the sandwich,
there's no, it's not chef.
You're not a chef.
- Right, right.
- You might as well be a factory machine.
- At Subway and Jersey Mike's,
you're the chef when you walk in.
- Exactly.
- I design the menu.
It's not a restaurant, it's a factory.
- I have designed a new duck dish.
(laughing)
- What's it called?
- It's called Duck Caleb.
Or Caleb's Duck in French.
(laughing)
- You're not the chef.
- Look at me in my eyes.
- Stand up, stand up.
- Yeah, what pants are you wearing?
You wearing jeans or something?
- I'm wearing sweatpants.
- Okay, yeah, you're not a chef.
- These are actually black chef pants.
Are they chef pants?
- Yep.
- Chef pants.
I'm gonna Google chef pants right now.
- You're about to see a picture of me.
- Chef pants are a thing.
- Chef pants. - They are a thing.
- Let's see here.
- But basically I'm a chef and I was kinda hoping
that you guys-- - Okay, these are a thing
but they don't look like what Caleb's wearing.
- Well, I'm not gonna show you again.
You got a quick glance but that's all you're gonna get.
- I know that these are not what you're wearing.
- In the culinary arts, we call that a taste.
- Why are you saying culinary?
- 'Cause it's culinary.
- I'm Googling right now. - It's not.
- What does a chef wear on the bottom?
It's not culinary! Stop saying it like that!
First off, all chefs go commando, and then on top of that you have a very heavy, dicky
style pant.
Okay, so I googled what does a chef wear on the bottom, and what Google thought I was
asking is what do the folds in a chef's hat represent?
Oh, okay.
I can tell you that.
Yeah, tell me what they represent.
The 50 states.
What about chefs in like France and stuff?
50 states of France. Isn't that a rule for countries that have 50 states? Is that how
you get to countries? It's provinces because they're Canadian in France.
You are making no sense and this is why I'm kicking you out of culinary school.
No, no, I'm staying in culinary school. You actually, your application has been denied
and you will never be a chef in this town. I'll be a chef before you are. This is what
the folds in a chef's hat represent, okay? Listen to this, listen to this. Like hat height
Tradition dictated the more pleats featured in a chef's hat the higher their experience level
It was said that if a chef had 100 pleats in their hat that represented the number of ways they knew how to prepare eggs
That's basically me. You don't have a hat on. You don't have a hat so you don't know how to prepare eggs.
My hats in the other room. Okay, go get it. I can't I just got I
My I stepped on glue. You didn't step on glue. It's one of the ingredients I work with and I got stuck in it
You work with glue.
Uh, yeah.
What kind of glue?
Edible glue.
Edible glue? That's not a--
What are you making with it?
To make a gingerbread house.
It's my signature dish.
[laughter]
Uh, yes, uh, waiter,
I'll have the, uh,
Today we have a beautiful gingerbread house.
We say gumdrop, lightbulb and frosting.
You have the choice of either men or women standing outside of the house.
And you can choose the holiday for your gingerbread house.
Would you like a freshly ground frosting on top?
Say when.
Would you like a Halloween gingerbread house?
A Thanksgiving gingerbread house?
A...
A Valentine's Day gingerbread house?
But basically that's, yeah, that's how my restaurant is gonna work.
I need to figure out a location.
I'm thinking Trump Tower.
We have a Bastille Day gingerbread house.
Made especially for you.
Yeah, but I'm-
The roof on this gingerbread house is too steeply pitched.
Is this a fucking two-door?
*laughter*
No, no, no! Mansard roof! Mansard roof!
It's all fucking wrong!
*laughter*
Yeah...
This gingerbread-
This gingerbread flat is all wrong!
*laughter*
Oh, fuck me!
Fuck me!
You've put a man and a woman in front of-
You only get one gingerbread man!
Fuck me!
In front of the house!
Fuck me! Where's the basement?
There's no basement. He's lifting up his plate and licking under the plate.
Oh fuck, oh fuck, where's the garage? Where is the garage?
Uh, yeah, actually, Gordon Ramsay would be very impressed by my restaurant.
No he wouldn't.
He would say, this is a kitchen dream to me.
He would call your gingerbread house a-
Yeah, kitchen bad dream. Well, something I'd say a kitchen nightmare.
he would go no I'm fuck he would call your gingerbread house a hotel from hell he
would not call it that he would not know he would not call it a haunted
gingerbread you would call it top gear you wouldn't call I mean he's not doing
anything it's not one of his shows you would call it a show called haunted
gingerbread bottom gear he did idiot abroad he did all that shit yeah the
office he would yeah he's on the office yeah he got real fuck me the office a
stapler in this jail oh fuck me how are we gonna serve this how the fuck are we
gonna serve this send it back but it's yeah be a chef yeah yet again you guys
have absolutely nothing going on and I'm kind of my thing is I'm intellectual now
I've been reading this a little book you guys might you might know of as Lord of
the Rings which is actually a fun fact that nobody knows about it is it's
actually meant to be read as one book but it's separated into three volumes I've
been getting hyphy oh you do have cool new cool new shoes see those would never
work on the on the line what do you mean what do you mean I used to wear d3s to
work you get it I bet you get some sauce
on those shout out shout out to Michael
who sent me those ice creams I'm actually
very excited to receive those maybe
maybe I'll become a saucier and also
those shoes or sir these shoes would work
perfect in a restaurant because they're
called ice creams you don't serve ice
cream in a restaurant yes you do my
restaurant at an ice cream store no it's
called a parlor dumbass
God
Yeah, you gotta take that's right out of your hat dude yeah, yeah one plea gone you gotta iron one
There goes Hawaii 49 left it fuck me
God fuck me fuck me fuck me fuck me. It's called a fucking parlor fuck me
It's called an ice cream parlor
Fuck me this poop is filled with corn fuck me. It's corn all in this
Fuck me the ice cream social is ruined
poop
What's wrong with the poop? It's fucking corn in it
Southwest style sir
I'm sorry chef the next poop will be better chef
Sorry
How old was the Labrador how old was the Labrador that made this?
Fuck me this labs been eating chocolate fuck
It's all ready. He's moving the keys moving the plate around
Yeah, but I'm not a poop chef I'm a normal chef you're a poop show you have no but your restaurant
I don't work at the poop restaurant. I work at a Michelin star restaurant
Yeah, what what Michelin tires? Yep. Yeah, I work at a Jiffy Lube
Yeah, and we have Michelin stars all over you have a hot dog stand outside of a Jiffy Lube
I found out that a hot dog stand renting a hot dog stand in Central Park or renting like a spot is like
$200,000 a year really? Yeah
Jesus Christ, dude, let's do it
My uncle or some some one of my family members used to have a hot dog cart in the common
Really? Yeah. There's a hot dog cart in a gas station in goths town inside the station. No out in front
He upgraded it to a food truck though. Oh good for him, dude. Yeah, it's a food truck
Remember the unless the hot dog stand unless the hot dog stand is gone
Dude, the food truck the food
And I'd like to make a few of those food trucks go boom in my that's right
You know, yes chef
And my hometown dude a bunch of a bunch of food trucks are doing this shit where they'll like
They like you order ahead of time and then they like drive to a place
So it's just like it's like uber eats, but you have to like go to get the food from the car
Like they don't like yeah, you just like order it and they're like, all right
We're gonna be at this park then later today and you have to just go get
Stupid I knew my neighbor started. He wanted to do a food truck and he was he got like
he bought the truck and he like fitted it up with like a kitchen and shit and his
friend was gonna be like the chef and he was gonna be like the money and shit and
then his friend just like stole all the money and bought a bunch of like heroin
and went to Vegas Jesus Christ just so awesome dude yeah that's like that's
that there's nothing more chefly than that chef would be a completely different
movie if that happened well yeah I'd be skinny it wouldn't be such a fat piece of
of shit if John Leguizamo skipped town just bought a bunch of heroin it'd be a
funnier movie cuz there'd be more John Leguizamo in it that's my problem with
that movie put there needs to be the pest put Leguizamo in this bitch yeah yeah
let him do the shower dance again right yeah but let him say one stinky dinky to
stinky dinky let him play Luigi again oh for sure let him reprise his role he's
Luigi again dude. Luigi Mario. Luigi Mario. I'm Luigi Mario this is my brother Mario
Mario. This is my brother Jon Favreau. Dude Jon Favreau would have been a perfect Mario. Oh he would. Oh my god.
I didn't even think of that. That's a Mario Luigi spiritual successor. And I
don't, he's Italian and Bob Hoskins isn't. No neither of them were Italian in the
original yeah it's fucked up fucked up that they're doing that you know did we
could do a new maybe that'll be we need to get into investing I think once my
restaurant takes off I think we'll have a lot of money coming in from all the
food that I am selling and we could maybe make a new movie yeah yeah maybe a
Mario style movie. I think maybe dip your toes into filmmaking make
a documentary about food. You could make a documentary about your restaurant.
That's true. Yeah we could do like a chef's table kind of thing yeah yeah
about my restaurant you know just like a nanananana. His mind is so he has a
he has a huge mind nanananana. It's me cutting an onion he loves to cut this
onion and then they cut to a critic and he's like he's he cuts that he's so he
loves those onions he's beautiful he's got he he's on the number one number one
onion yeah if I had it was the first time I had these on your nice it Wow
- Wow, is that to say, oh, onion, oh wow, wow, wow.
- It's just because of a bunch of critics going,
wow, wow, wow.
- Onion was boiled to perfection.
- Yeah, dude, we could definitely do a chef's table thing.
- Yeah, it's like you're serving,
you know when you make a broth
and you put a whole onion or a chopped onion,
like a carrot and everything in it?
You're just serving people just broth,
like you don't drain it or anything?
Just like broth with like chunks of food in it. Yeah. I serve everything in a cauldron. We're gonna do it's true
I'm gonna hire a bunch of witches to be the line cooks and they're just gonna like throw shit behind them into the cauldron as
Like yeah, yeah, I'll chop it and you are not gonna believe the poems that they're gonna say. Oh, well, that's it
It's kind of like a dick's last resort sort of thing where they actually they serve
They it's the cauldron is is on the table. So the witch comes to the
She puts and so it's like the curse the cursed helm onto your head. Yeah, your friends laugh at you. Exactly
It's like hot it's like somewhere between hot pot and like a like like Benny Hanna, you know what I mean?
Okay. Yeah, and there's so you want to make what a medieval times and
Last resort and the rainforest cafe. You want to be like Steve a Yogi's dad for
Okay, just cauldrons. Yes, exactly. I have an idea what it could we could hire a bunch of witches
we could also have animatronic witches and then you have to figure out which is
which which which is which and that's the name of the restaurant which which is
which which is which and we serve sandwiches yep we serve which which is
which is it's two bottom halves of a sandwich yeah that's what a
which-which is yeah and they'll be like this is this is great this is a
great place mostly because of the name yep the food is not gonna be very good
terrible the food sucks but you're gonna be a real team like that and then I go
to Universal say that they get turned to a newt that's true yeah they get made
into a witch witch and the witch could be like roasting them yeah like yeah we'll
get Lisa Lampanelli to be head head of front of house because she's the best
- What are you saying about her?
- She's the best at roasts.
- You're saying she has a witch style look to her?
That's rude, dude, that's a real woman.
- What do you mean?
- Yeah, real fat woman.
Come on, move it on.
- Hey, hey now.
- Yeah, I mean, come on, yes, chef, I mean, let's go.
You know, yes, chef, thank you, chef.
That's what you guys are supposed to say.
- Yes, chef.
- Anybody listening along, any time I say something,
yes, chef, thank you, chef.
- We don't know if the witch trials are,
like, if they were getting actual witches or not,
'cause they didn't have color pictures back then,
so we can't see if any of the women were green.
- That's a really good point, yeah.
That's a really good point.
- I think what you have to do is check
for a wart on the nose.
- But then the wart also--
- But do you think people could,
back then people could have just been green
and they just didn't put it together
that all the witches are green.
- It could have been aliens.
- A boy green guy is a hulk,
but a green girl is bad news.
- I don't care if you're green, black, white, purple.
- That could be why they said that.
- If you're a witch, you better join my restaurant.
- They would be doing the--
- We can do witch trials and then instead of killing them,
we hire them.
Witch hire, witch hire.
- No.
- No, it's still a trial.
It's still a trial 'cause you're hiring them
on a trial basis.
- And if they're not a witch, we kill them.
- True.
That's a good point.
- It's like Hooters.
- There's a lot of witches who didn't get caught
back in the day though.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause you're right, they didn't know
the witches were green yet.
They hadn't read, there was no picture books yet.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause they had no idea.
- Right, the first time, I mean--
Maybe like some hot blonde woman about to get dumped in a lake and there'd be some
green old hag who's like "Yeah! Get her! She's a witch! Hee hee! There's the witch!"
Yeah, flying around in a circle on a broom and they're like "Wow, she is so good at cleaning."
"Damn, she funny as hell. Damn."
"Yo, funny woman."
"Yo, you like the class clown."
"Yo, she's so good at pissing these people off, too."
"I saw her transform into a black cat and run around the town."
you know i think so funny i think christine is a witch but esmerelda's
gotta be the funniest bitch in town
she funny as hell
did they have people back then named christina? they had no people
yeah i don't know, what were people named back then? dolph?
no they were named like uh... like griselda
griselda? griselda
Zelda the kids the kids from Narnia. Yeah, everyone back there. Yeah, the last name was named aslan and the one which
What up Thomas, thanks for the paper other a mr. Thomas, what were the other guys in Narnia?
It's Cass. Oh, oh
Rubble still know what's the mouse's name? Read it. Read it. Read the cheap
Rule did
you found out it was God. Oh I was 17. I had the box set dude and they did the like Star
Wars thing where they have like the Lion, Witch and the Wardrobe is like technically
like the third book or something. Yeah. Like there's like prequels and I was like oh I'm
gonna start at book one and it's about like a guy getting like abused by his uncle with
magic rings or something and I was like I just stopped reading the book. Which one is
that called? That's called like the Summer Earth. Like the Magician's Nephew I think
it's called. Is that really what it's called? I'm pretty sure it's called that. The Magician's
nephew I'm Google yep it's called the magicians nephew it's the first Narnia
book it's the sixth published there's the horse and his boy yeah the horse is why
there's the silver chair Prince Caspian the last one that has that has a monkey
in it named puzzle and that was one of the main character they go I would not
start with that monkey there's like an evil God who has six arms or something
there's so much wild shit someone named Eustace scrub oh yeah used to Jill Jill
Will Pole.
Diggory Kirk.
Eustace Scrubb.
I think Eustace Scrubb was just like the lame guy that they brought to Narnia by accident.
Lady of Green Curdle.
Wait, wasn't that Edmund?
No, I think Eustace Scrubb is like another guy.
Eustace Scrubb is, I think he turns into a dragon.
Is that in The Silver Chair?
Oh, I think that's in Voyage of the Dawn Treader maybe.
Eustace Scrubb is played by Will Poulter in the movies.
Oh yeah, look at that.
That's crazy.
It's funny that they made more than one movie of that and it's just erased forever.
Yeah, they didn't finish them.
Yeah, but like the fact that they made more than one and I can't remember any like,
I don't think I ever saw anything besides the first one.
Everyone remembers Lion, Witch, and the Wardrobe, but nobody remembers like,
Dawn Treader or any of them.
We should get really into Narnia.
It would be really funny.
I mean, it's like, it's the Stitchy Christ story.
Can we do a Narnia book club with all of the listeners?
I'll fucking pick up a book right now. Yeah, I have the box set somewhere
Restaurant confidential I'm freed up
They finished at a Don Treader and it was magician's nephew was supposed to be next
Yeah
Literally is like he has like an evil uncle who uses like magic rings to like lock him in his house or something and then
He has like a girlfriend. It's called the naughty uncle
Yeah
Uncle gone bad. Yeah. Yeah, it's truly
I remembered those but I read them when I was like a young like like probably in elementary school
So I was like these are so long but they're like 200 less than 200 pages. Mm-hmm. We could definitely read all these
The two children in in the magician's nephew are named Diggory and Polly. Yeah
See those are all those are old witch names to me. Mm-hmm
What listen listen to the first listen to the first paragraph of this this plot summary?
This is maybe the most evil uncle of all time
Okay, the story begins in London during the summer of 1900 two children diggory and already evil meet while playing in the adjacent
Gardens of a row of a to of terraced houses they decide to explore the attic connecting the houses
But take the wrong door and surprise diggory's uncle Andrew in his study
Uncle Andrew tricks Polly into touching a yellow magic ring causing her to vanish
Then he explains to Diggory that he has been dabbling in magic and that the rings allow travel between one world and another
He blackmails Diggory into taking another yellow ring to follow wherever Polly is gone and two green rings so that they can both return
Yeah, I mean with it as somebody with an uncle who dabbles in magic. I
Don't know how I feel about this
If you spread it touching a magic ring then blackmailing your nephew
I mean if somebody asked me to touch a ring I would I'm out I would not see
too many there's there's too many bad stories that ends up badly so often yep
yeah doing that no no way hey buddy touch this ring I promise nothing's gonna
happen I'm not wearing it for no reason mm-hmm just touch it come on if they
asked me to kiss the ring uh-uh no way bitch hell no no uh-uh
fuck no dude yeah I had to read all those books as a kid zero but I got a here yeah
I say you know cuz it which is like it's the funniest like most ham-fisted
allegory of all time I I pick that up I didn't know that I was 17 as a lion yeah
yeah yeah so so in terms of the book Aslan is the line and then the white
witch is the witch and then the wardrobe that they go into that's the wardrobe
and that's yeah and those are all open yeah and that's and that's what they
symbolize that's what they each symbolize it's mr. tum this is Easter
reap a cheap is we're not gonna go there yeah what is it what is reach the cheap
spicer you know what don't worry about it yeah we're just not gonna we're not
gonna go there hell no absolutely not who's Pontius Pilate though I guess
that's Edmund right true no he's Judas oh he is Judas yeah oh yeah good good
because he eats the eats the turkeys the light who kills so who kills Aslan Google
who the White Witch well so she's but she's the devil though it's almost like
these books are terrible I'm scoot okay I'll Google Narnia who is Pontius Pilate
there has to be an answer I'll be so surprised if there's no answer I
I remember I saw a blog spot here.
Last week I dragged my husband and nephew to see Prince Caspian again.
I really loved that movie.
This time I saw a lot more of the symbolism.
It was really quite interesting and it rather enriched my viewing of the movie the second
time around.
This is a woman who is forcing her family to be in love with Narnia.
I saw Narnia with my friend and his dad in the theater and I, like after the movie, he
was like saying something.
just remembered the like him saying like oh there's a lot of good battle scenes
in that movie but we were kind of far away so I couldn't hear him so I asked
him to repeat himself like six times I walked out of that movie with my my
friends or my dad's friend who later died and he was like that was gay let's go
watch Pirates of the Caribbean and then we just went right back into the theater
the Caribbean dude I had a Chronicles of Narnia Stratego set how does that work
it's like Stratego but instead of like spot like all the different explain the
rules of Stratego to me what is Stratego you know is this a jitsu that you've
learned it's a board game I don't know about that me neither I'm in a monopoly
in life mm-hmm now those are the I love you go dude it's like it's like war
what's the whole thing you can't cheat in Stratego you can definitely cheat I think
a rule is you can't cheat in most games yeah well no it's like Stratego is like
you know what I heard it in Zathura in the movies of thorough one of the
brothers says you can't cheat in Stratego and then the other brother says
you've cheated in Stratego would be the worst definitely get sucked into like in
a Jumanji Zathura style the worst board game would be don't wake daddy
operation operation would suck yeah operation yeah that'd be a much worse
sequel to Jumanji than Zathura was. You suck. Would you be...
Are you the doctor? Are you one of the things?
It sucks either way. You and a friend are playing it and you get sucked in and
And what have you as the doctor, what have you as the guy?
And your just going AHHHHH!
NOOOO!
That would be horrible.
Monopoly is, get this dude, get sucked into Monopoly, just real life again.
Yep, true.
It's a whole other world.
Did I blow your mind?
Oh I'm sorry, did the chef blow your mind?
Did I bring too much flavor to the podcast right then?
bad you did not I'm thinking of mixing up some flavors yeah I've been thinking
about good doing salty sweet here's it here's a flavor for you hmm
strong and dry yeah that's a bad combo strong and dry I've got I've got a
flavor for you okay delicious fruit loops fruit loops and milk well I think is it
I mean I feel like the whole thing with with fancy chefs who are on TV is that
they come they take something simple and then they make it yeah make it gourmet
they say here's mac and cheese but I put the pasta in one bowl and the cheese in
another yeah yeah and they're on either end of the room yeah you have to walk
where we and take one bite of each and keep it in your mouth all the way over
and also there's an optical course in the middle and there's a log over a river
yeah this is a cube of mac and cheese yeah I made bread but it's invisible I
made peanut butter and jelly but the peanut butter and jelly are on the
outside yeah yeah yeah but the peanut butter is made out of cheese and the
jelly is made out of meat so the peanut butter the peanut butter is on one slice
of bread and the jellies on another slice of bread but then those slices have a
slice on top of them and it's two different sandwiches and you have to eat them separately.
You have to eat them separately. If I was ever on Chopped I would blow the judge's mind I would make
my famous ham and cheese PB&J. What's that guy's name? I'd make my tortilla chip salad. Chopped.
That guy. Chopped. His name's Chopped. No it's not that guy. Alton Brown. Awesome Brown. It's the
guy on YouTube who he does like his like sex doll reviews or whatever
Kinji Lopez alt no it's not I think it's like over some but no he does the GoPro
video on top of his head where he's Shane Dawson all mystery guitar man I
tried to look up I tried to look up the guy on YouTube who does the sex doll
reviews and I found the top result is sex dolls for sex offenders price. Wait, do they get a discount? I don't know!
Wait, can you submit for a coupon code if you're a sex offender or is it more expensive?
I hope it's more expensive. Why? I don't know. I feel like it's better if it's cheaper.
should be yeah it should be cheaper yeah we should be subsidizing sex dolls for
sex offenders what is this guy's name? I'm gonna take that back. What is this guy's name?
it's something Cobra he's like a goth guy Patrick Doren Cobra and he's got a
ponytail. Goth King Cobra? I think it's Goth King Cobra. The guy they made the
documentary about? Gothic King Cobra I think. Well he made a video where he was
making something he's making like a burger or like a grilled cheese with
peanut butter or something and he's like well my thought process here was I've
seen those Austin peanut butter crackers with cheese so I figure this should be
really good that's like stuffing in it or something I gotta look this up I do
love that though when you it's like when I was a kid I would I would come up with
dishes that I was like this is gonna be so good and it just sucked every time
the thing is like you there there's definitely a chance that you could like
stumble upon some insane new combination that's true like like like people on TV
will make the like craziest combinations and all the judges will be like oh this
is delicious and you can't I can't tell whether okay here's the they're here
easier or here's the name of the sandwich okay chunky peanut butter marmite black
- Black Cherry Cola Cardinal Bacon Cheeseburger.
(laughing)
- Did you say Marmite?
- Yep.
(laughing)
- And it has peanut butter on it?
- Chunky peanut butter.
- Oh, Christ, dude.
- Marmite.
- There's peanuts in the burger patty.
- Black Cherry Cola, I don't know what that is.
- You dip it like an Italian beef sandwich.
- It's an au jus.
cherry cola cardinal bacon cheeseburger oh my god
like a cardinal like a bird yeah he's got no chef
oh chef what are you doing this is an hour long video
takes an hour long it takes an hour to prepare
takes a long time at 16 minutes and 20 seconds in there's a fart
you have to make the mother for it first yeah
And then you can construct the sandwich from there.
Oh my god.
But yeah, I'm basically gonna get in.
Making a PB&J mayonnaise burger.
Wait, actually people love that.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
That's what I'm saying.
I forgot about that.
People will make that sort of sandwich.
Oh, that's the Elvis burger, isn't it?
My grandpa ate a hot dog in front of my dad one time that had mayonnaise and peanut butter
and bananas on it.
My dad vomited at the table.
People will eat shit like they'll eat like bananas and mayonnaise and stuff and it's like,
There's shit like that that definitely tastes good.
The Elvis burger is bananas, fried bananas, peanut butter, and diced bacon.
Wait, so you're saying it's bananas, peanut butter, and bacon?
Yeah.
On a burger.
That's it?
That's probably fine.
That probably tastes fine.
I'm sure it's okay.
I'm sure it tastes good.
The thing is Patrick, if people eat it, it probably is good.
If it tastes like shit, nobody's gonna eat it.
What do you mean?
What do you mean, "What do I mean?"
People eat bugs.
Yeah, people eat poop.
- People love eating-- - Bugs probably taste fine too.
People like eating poop.
There's people who get off on eating poop.
- Like that's their favorite thing. - Okay, but nobody's getting off on eating an Elvis burger.
- It's a type of burger. - Some people are. What about gainers, dude?
That's a good point.
Gainers get off on eating food.
Maybe I'll become a chef who particularly
Are not are not a good idea. Yes. Are not far enough apart to sound disgusting. That's okay. It's alright
I'm gonna come up with combos you tell me if it's if it's good or bad. Okay, I got a copy. Are you ready?
We're in pretzels dressing he's and an apple
Pretzel
Circle pretzel cheese on the inside. That's my combo. I'm gonna vomit
That's fucking disgusting dude here about this chip and a hint of lime
What do you think it's disgusting
The only reason you eat that is to get off on it. Definitely. Yeah. Yeah, what are you fucking free?
Yeah, tortilla chips with a hint of lime. What about Jesus Christ?
It's a tortilla tortilla chip and pico de gallo
I'm I'm I'm so close to vomiting. I don't know why this is but I actually do feel sick to my stomach right now
Thinking about these normal foods
Just the fact that we frame this as a disgusting combination made like chips. Okay. Okay, peanut butter and flour about chips and ahoy
well
Okay, there's my problem chips ahoy is there's no pirate twist yeah, no there's no anchor on the
They're not anchor shaped chocolate chips. It's called a hoy though, so it shouldn't that be enough pirate no no no their mascots
Not even a pirate. It's a baby cookie. They need like grog in the and they need a grog dough
Mm-hmm you know what I mean
Something their mascot the mascot. It's just a chip. So boy. I'm looking at a claymation cookie
That's I don't think ever. I don't think it ever was a pirate
Okay, well listen to this this makes even less sense in the 1960s and early
1970s a chips Ahoy bags featured comic strips of cookie man a superhero character
Who's who does subdued other various cookie devouring creatures such as fruit fly or bigwig his alter ego was Mort Meek?
Who was always seen counting the 16 chips in his chips Ahoy cookie? He was a crime-stopping cookie. He was a Batman guy
Oh my god, dude. What?
What the fuck is that for the in the early 1980s children played 1940 style newspaper reporters interested in the 16 chips story
The chips Ahoy's branding is so fucked up for a time as it should be on 90s advertising labeled chips Ahoy as being
1000 chips delicious
in the 90s they just uh
they really
Could not figure out food mascots like Jesus or is never figured it out
Listen up from 2001 to 2010 Chips Ahoy's mascots were the animated cookie guys with one of their commercials having them drive a red convertible
So you want me by the Human League?
That's how I got about that song. What are we gonna do for her?
That's so fucking funny to imagine them like what are we gonna do for our chocolate chip mascot?
We need a new one. I don't know like a car
What about like what about like a sick-ass red convertible and a girl wants the real bad about like a funny bug
would that be cool as a chocolate chip cookie mascot?
that's honey nut cheerio, that makes sense
you're right, he is a very funny bug
but at least that makes sense
Nabisco says the name as a reference to the nautical term "ships ahoy"
the word "chips ahoy" also feature prominently in a story
appearing in chapter 15 of the Uncommercial Traveler by Charles Dickens
Dickens relays a childhood tale of a shipwright
hmm?
you said Nabisco
Nabisco?
Because it's national biscuit company. Okay, I didn't know that. You know it's short for national biscuit company. Yeah
That's nice dude also what I said way it makes way more sense for national biscuit company than what you said now
This is Co national you say national
National now, what is like? Come on?
Dickens relays a childhood tale of a shipwright named Chips who is taunted by a
Diabolical talking rat who predicts the sinking of chips ship chips ahoy old boy
We've pretty well eat them too, and we'll drown the crew and we'll eat them, too
That was that's where chips that was a curse mascot. They were gonna do a diabolical
Diabolical talking right yeah
He'd be a great pick cheesestores Rex still makes no sense to me. Yeah, just yeah like just do the food
Just pick a picture of the food with eyes
the easiest thing. Like a Spaghetti-O? Yeah! So easy dude. Yeah. Just put eyes on it. It is really easy.
Like, I'm getting it dude. Or the animal that likes to eat that food. Exactly. Cheese, a human.
Mm-hmm. A human with two sets of eyes because you do have to add eyes. Honey, nut Cheerios, a bee.
Yeah, a bee. Cookie, cereal, a wolf. Cookie, cri- that's another. Lucky charm cereal, a leprechaun.
That's another motherfucker that doesn't make any sense. Didn't it used to be different?
Chip the wolf.
I think he makes sense.
What do you mean it makes sense?
Have you ever seen a wolf eat chocolate chip?
No, I've never seen a wolf eat cookies.
They do. It's a natural diet.
Wait, I just looked up Cookie Crisp old mascot. Their original mascot was Cookie Jarvis.
[laughter]
- Cookie Jarvis was a wizard in the Merlin mold
who with one wave of his wand magically turned
Cookie Jarvis into cereal balls.
- Yeah, I remember, dude, I remember Cookie Jarvis.
- Cookie Jarvis is from 1977, Patrick.
- No, he, no, in the 90s, Cookie Jarvis was still around.
- Yes, he's from 1977 and they stopped using him in 1980.
- It's pretty funny that like all of these--
- It says right here.
- All of these mascots got like--
- Why do I remember Cookie Jarvis?
- It's funny that all of these mascots
got replaced before Aunt Jemima.
(laughter)
They were like...
Aunt Jemima was like "this year" but they were like
"Warlock, that doesn't make any fucking sense."
"We have to get rid of Warlock, it's so bad for the brand."
Here's... okay, then after
Cookie Jarvis, they changed it to
Cookie Crook and Cookie Cop.
Okay, maybe I remember that.
'Cause that looks...
I thought Cookie Jarvis was blue.
And then Cookie Crook was given a sidekick
sidekick named chip the dog in nineteen ninety
no it's shipped the dog that i remember okay
it's
that's that's the one i thought it was a good thing to do is not know i would be
remembered looking i'm looking at ship the dog right now i ship the dog was a
wizard
yes you heard
yes i did
that's a wizard named it
Because I remember when they switched over to the wolf.
Because it makes sense, I mean the dog goes to wolf.
They don't even talk about the wolf on the Wikipedia page, this is fucked up.
You have to go to Cereal Wiki for that, I just did.
Just click through your bookmarks, back to Cereal Wiki.
Yeah, because Chip the dog was where the "Cookie Crisp" comes from.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, so that makes sense.
Obviously.
Because a dog does say cookie when it...
That is the noise that it makes.
It's like, you know how different cultures, they phoneticize a dog word differently?
Yeah.
Yeah, so America's is cookie.
We have now decided.
Do you guys like Cars 3 cereal?
Wait, do I remember this thing at all?
Or am I creating a false memory for myself?
You know what? I'm not sure it matters that much.
I'm losing my fucking mind looking at this bullshit.
Get off of the cereal wiki, you're gonna go crazy.
I'm gonna lose my fucking mind thinking about these goddamn mascots.
Yeah, I got so irony poisoned by the cereal wiki.
Oh, fuck.
I think that they should put toys back in the middle of cereal boxes.
Yep.
Do they do that anymore?
They don't do that shit anymore.
They'll do like, sometimes they'll do a piece of paper.
Yeah, it's a QR code.
Or a VR headset.
they had Dunkin Donuts cereal?
nowadays they have a gender swapping button
in the middle of all the cereal
do you remember
do you remember in 2004
something like that
all general mills cereals came with
a movie
what?
yeah they came with a disc
they came with a DVD in the middle of the package
was it just a random movie?
yeah it was like the great muppet caper
was one of them
- Puppets Take Manhattan was one of them.
- That's a good get.
- That was a good get.
- That's good for the price. - And then it was another one,
I think it was like Zeus and Roxanne was one of them.
- They didn't, was the cereal like $15?
- I don't know, I don't know.
- That's an amazing promotion.
- And then you could put the DVD in your computer.
- We should hide a DVD in this episode.
- You could put the DVD on your computer
and it had a thing, it had America Online on it.
It had a free trial for AOL.
- Dude, cereal is like the best investment ever.
- Do you guys know that Funko makes cereal?
- Oh yeah, I just found that out right now.
- What kind of flavor is it?
- We're looking at Freddy Fazbear,
Five Nights at Freddy's tasty treat.
Fun to eat.
- No, it wasn't, it was not the Muppets.
It was not the Muppets, it was--
- We got Cuphead cereal.
- It was Liberty Kids, Heathcliff,
and Super Mario Brothers Super Show,
Madeline, Strawberry Shortcake, Inspector Gadget,
and Inspector Gadget Jr.
- Okay, that's enough.
- And then Sabrina the Teenage Witch.
(laughing)
It sucks getting on any of these like like nostalgia train conversations
because Pat will just he will talk about this for three hours. That's true.
All we've talked about for the no wait no premium episodes is just various characters.
It does come with Muppet Takes Manhattan. It does come with that. Oh my god. Oh my god.
I'm looking at one right now. Can we just talk about let's talk about the news or something.
Jesus Christ. Okay all right I'm ready to talk about the news. I'm ready to talk about this.
lately Fox News breaking news updates Trump is still leader of GOP but should
he be the 2024 nominee yes no it's a poem it's a I love that they're they're doing
poetry just run again dude who else do they have they've nobody run what it's
what it's like what it's like to drive the same kind of car tiger wrecked oh
here's it here's Howard Howard Dean is trending what it's like to drive Tiger
Woods car after he writes it. It's so gross in here. It smells like blood in here. What the fuck is this?
It smells like blood and golf balls. I took Kobe's space helicopter for a joyride. There's so many golf balls in this car.
Oh fuck, there's a fingernail here. What the fuck is this? And a woman's high heel shoe.
Intriguing. Didn't somebody, somebody got in trouble for saying that he, like
someone was like oh he was probably on a bunch of Ambien and crashed the car
someone said like oh given his history or something like that
he was on fucking wham bam thank you Mambien dude he was fucking playing in the car
that's right that's the dangers of road head let's go yeah okay wait let's play
a little game I heard I heard that Tiger Woods almost hit the director of
Grown-ish before he got into that accident like punched him or hit him no
almost hit him with the car. Oh okay. Do you guys want to play a game that I just
thought of? That's what I heard. That's alleged. I don't want to get sued. I'm on foxnews.com and they have a
little section where they have all these little like news thumbnails that
kind of have like YouTube thumbnail style names on them. Uh-huh. So we can kind of
play it like Jeopardy. Okay. Sounds good. Blake wants this at his wedding. It's
got to be Blake Sheldon right? I don't know. Country. Oh a guitar. It is Blake
okay good that's correct let's let's wait on this and see yeah what was it is it a
guitar it's no he wants he wants Adam Levine to perform at his wedding he's
like a human guitar do you remember Adam Levine had a he had a line of you
remember first act guitars the ones they would sell at Walmart no Adam Levine had
his own signature Walmart guitar good for him did that guy we love signature
things. Queen bought what for grandson? Okay, is it the band Queen? No, it's the Queen. Is it
Beyonce? No, it's Queen British. Sheep bought a slave. Could be.
Let's see. A waffle maker. Well, it depends. Does it have Siri in it? Is that a guy who
who's a slave to his waffle maker.
- Let's see here.
So at breakfast now, Meg wakes, makes a...
- A waffle.
- A waffle, yep.
Oh, they're talking about waffles here.
- Dude, I love this news game.
- This is a fun news game.
Do you want the next question?
- Yes, dude, this one's all me.
- Okay.
Listing agents, shocking remark about house.
Don't answer Pat, hold on.
- Okay.
- Don't you fucking answer.
- I'm not answering.
- Don't you dare, can I call a friend?
- Yep.
- Okay, Pat.
(laughing)
Can you answer this one for me?
- Okay, I think I know.
- Okay.
- I think the previous owners had dogs in it
and they pooped everywhere.
- What?
- And that's not a remark.
- Rich people, rich people.
Maybe the remark was like,
"Ugh, there's so much poop."
- Okay, that could be the remark.
- Wah, wah, wee, wah.
- Rich people love to have a small dog
runs around the house and poops yeah I got there's anything I learned from the
Osborne I got there's anything I learned from the Osborne I got there my name was
always shitting oh dear I was very close as close the remark is literally the
worst house on the street and well well why is it the worst house the subtitle
says Philippa Maine hilariously harped about everything that was wrong with the
Zephyr Hills bungalow. Can you imagine going to journalism school and then now you're
writing "Falipa Flame Hesh Herely Harped" That's how you become like Baked Alaska
is you go to journalism school you start working a BuzzFeed and it's like it
breaks your fucking mind I guess so much yeah you become a fucking psychopath yeah
cuz you think you're gonna be like fucking like Michael Hastings or
something and then you end up just making talking about the Spongebob movie yeah
and why see a restaurant it puts what in dining room well I actually am a chef
you might know about this Caleb puts what in the dining room I'm gonna go okay
here final answer food I mean okay regardless of what in the news says I
I want you to know this regardless of what the news says I am correct.
You should throw actually no you're not correct because because um it says that
the dining room was empty the empty seats they can't have food in there.
Fuck! The only time that's not the right answer.
Wait wait wait wait wait wait. Is it wax statues?
It is. Yes. You cheat? No I knew I saw this earlier I saw it earlier
- From Adam Tussauds and--
- Brooklyn Shop House.
- This, what fucking--
- The Brooklyn Shop House.
- Brooklyn Shop House, oh, okay.
- The Brooklyn Shop House, yeah, I'm looking
at the news story. - I thought it was,
I thought it was the Luger Steakhouse.
- It is.
- Oh!
Look at me, I'm the best at the news.
- You're not the best at the news, I'm pretty much the best.
- Watch this, our top story tonight,
chef opens up his new restaurant
and he serves his customers--
- And serves what?
Southwest corn poop
And now name is Kayla licious
And I'm chef is serving his customers this
Okay, I'm also doing the news with you guys, and I don't appreciate how you know
No, no, no, you can't do the news
Master always lies. I do not always or I do always lie. What which one should I say?
Yeah, I quit the news and I'm going back to my restaurant
Back to doesn't have a restaurant. I'm at my restaurant and I'm loving these onions your restaurant is your bathroom
I hate my bathroom you and your restaurant who's in the sink
This chef has turned his tub into a sous-vide
I don't sous-vide my damn nuts in the damn bathtub
This unconventional chef has been sous-viding poop in his toilet in a market basket bag
*laughter*
I think he should be involved with the news more. We asked Jonathan Chabon, food
god, to go to this man's house and eat poop out of a market basket bag. We asked his roommate for comment and he said I don't know him.
Food God Jonathan Chabon is working with Chef Caleb to put gold, gold sauce on
poop. Gold sauce on poop? For a million dollars? And then they'd go to that 2
chains like most expensive show or whatever the most expensive poop in the
world one of those one of those like like Facebook recipe videos where they
like you know that's like an overhead camera they're playing the little
ukulele music but it's just a guy just sloshing poop around the toilet it's got
that whistles other yeah spin the poop around put the poop on your head and let
it rest two hours yeah you don't want to cut into the poop until it rests maybe
I'll become it loses all the juice if you got it you gotta press it like tofu
first you have to strain the poop this is getting so disgusting I told you said
chips and salsa earlier and I almost vomited. Now I feel so ill.
Just like one of those, like a tofu press with the...
Putting it through a pasta maker, too.
Oh, come on, man, I can't get through to Harold.
Making a ravioli where you put poop in it, too?
Dude, some damn linguine, yum.
This chef is putting poop in a bao bun.
I'm not. He calls it, he calls it, he calls it, a poop shoo bow. Bow bow boom bow. Boom boom bow.
And we said, please stop doing that accent on TV.
I kind of want to, I kind of feel like. This new Chinatown restaurant is selling something
a little unusual. Mark. This guy. This guy's putting poop in Bao Bun. I, I don't know,
why did you I don't want to do this assignment anymore this guy we saw in
the street is holding a poop in his hands remember yeah I have it in a banana peel
so it doesn't get on my fingers
man is Bill Clinton yeah basically it's what I've been doing a lot of free time
since I quit presidency. Bill Clinton is making a poop banana on the street yeah they do like a 30
minute segment about like Hillary running for president and it's like meanwhile
bill in New York's famous Chinatown making a poop restaurant yeah basically
I got this restaurant for me and my friends to do some bad things it was
supposed to be just like a front like yeah wasn't supposed to draw any
attention but we thought we thought we thought it would we didn't think it
would arouse any suspicions. Basically we started getting yelled at for that
Pizzagate stuff so we wanted to do something I guess a little less evil but
more fucked up for rich people to do so we started eating poop. That's their next
step like Jeffrey Epstein was like all right well yeah if I if I beat this case
I'm eating poop. Yeah if I beat this case me and the whole family are going to
like this poop Emporium that's like the the rich person after the Super Bowl
I'm going to Bill Clinton's poop Emporium
I'm going to poopney world
Bill Clinton's poopney world
I I that is like the
next to Madame Tussauds
that's like the tip of the rich person's
hierarchy of oh god
damn it
Sticky Mouse and Donald Duke
this is disgusting
We've been talking about eating poop for like 15 minutes.
Yes, chef.
Shit. Damn.
Oh, fuck.
I don't want to. Do I have to eat poop or no?
If you're the chef, man, it's your restaurant.
And for you, sir, I'll have a water.
I already ate.
I don't want to eat a poop.
You sure you don't want a poop Italian soda?
We can set you up a little dookie bag to take home.
Your chef gave me a sample outside.
It's just a bulldog on a chain.
(laughing)
- Dude, I just want to have a normal recipe.
I came in here with so many amazing ideas for recipes.
You know, I was gonna do a paella.
I was gonna do a--
- And what was gonna be in your paella?
- What's a paella?
- Paella is like a rice dish.
- Yeah, I was basically gonna put rice in it
and probably some meat and some vegetables.
What about like a ceviche but instead of shrimp or any food that cooks from the acidic lemon
juice you just put a whole flank steak.
So it just doesn't cook at all.
Or just like 80/20 chuck.
I'm trying this new sous vide method where I use...
I let I let the steak I don't put the steak in a bag or anything and I let it soak in ice-cold water in
My bathtub for a week. Yeah, I've been really enjoying this chicken tartar that I made. Oh
It's delicious dude, Eric Wareheim posted a oh the chicken. Sashimi chicken
So she may be the most evil food I've ever seen. Yeah, dude, like that's the most evil food
I've seen that's not like like a poop burger. I
Mean French bread crostini with a piece of chicken and barbecue sauce on it. I
- I understand, yeah, try different foods and shit,
but a chicken sashimi just sounds made up.
- Yeah, no, yeah.
- That sounds like-- - Don't do that.
- That's like emperor's new clothes shit.
- That's what they would eat in Tim and Eric.
Like, that's not, yeah.
- It doesn't, it's like you trick a rich person
into eating that.
- Exactly. - It's not like a real thing.
- Yeah, well he is a rich person.
He maybe just got tricked.
- He definitely, I can't imagine looking at that
and being like, yeah, I'm gonna eat this,
and I'm gonna post a picture of it on Instagram too.
I want everyone to know that I ate this.
- Your gut bubbling after that, just, oh.
- Yeah.
- Also your brain just like slowing down.
- Right?
- Yeah, there has to be some fucking microbe in that
that's not good for your head.
- Yeah.
- It has to, I mean, the chickens that you kill for that
have to be like--
- That's what I say when I'm watching Tim and Eric.
I'm like, were these guys fucking smoking raw chicken
when they made this shit?
This crap is insane.
- These guys were eating raw chicken for sure.
- These guys must have been out of their mind
on raw chicken.
Jesus Christ, this is so weird.
is chicken sashimi like a thing like i don't know i want to see how long it's been a thing
yeah because i feel that that sounds like a new like chicken sashimi that sounds like one of those
weird fusion things it's made from the part of the chicken that carries the lowest risk of
salmonella contamination okay i guess that makes sense the vagina is it it's japanese lubricated
i think most sashimi is japanese yeah it makes sense but i mean but okay but chicken sashimi
seems like a kind of thing that a white guy would make.
Yeah, it's like a French guy who studied sushi in Japan.
People in Japan--
Ma?
I'm on the website India Today.
People in Japan eat raw chicken.
Here's why no one should do that to their body.
The Japanese have done it again.
That's the first line of the article.
Yet again, the Japanese fucking it up right now.
Just when you thought pufferfish dishes, a naked restaurant,
and a superb non-melting ice cream
was all that you could take of this country's
culinary creativity, their proud tradition of eating raw chicken comes to light.
Oh, it's a tradition?
Yeah, that's what this-
If it's like traditional Japanese, I guess I don't have-
I guess I can take back my comments, probably.
I guess I would like to expect me now-
Yes, raw chicken. You know, chicken that is pink and limp, like only raw meat can be.
Raw chicken that even a dedicated Indian non-vegetarian might not want to explore.
Ugh.
Yeah, 'cause I mean, like, eating, like, raw fish, you probably have the same risk.
Uh...
I don't think so. I don't know.
I think salmonella-- I don't think that's true.
I think technically salmonella is, like, present in all raw chicken or something.
Yeah, I mean, it's raw chi-- yeah, you shouldn't be eating-- I mean...
There's obviously ways you can-- Well, who are we to say that you can't eat it?
I think I'm gonna eat it. Fuck me, because it's disgusting!
Oh, fuck me! You cooked the fucking sashimi! You cooked the raw chicken sashimi! Fuck me!
Fuck me!
Oh, God.
Put it in the time machine.
Make it raw again.
[Laughter]
Put it back in the time machine.
Oh, you fucked this up completely!
Trash.
Garbage.
This whole Wellington is ruined.
Throw it in the time machine.
We don't have a time machine, chef.
Then invent one!
Fuck me!
This is such a- this is the last line of the article.
This is so funny.
While Japan has its own culinary and food culture, we Indians are more prone to enjoying well-cooked
enjoying well-cooked meat, poultry, and fish, according to our own culinary culture.
So while raw chicken sashimi or even the French tartare looks great on a gourmet
plate, they don't really belong on a platter made for Indians. That's right,
yeah. These Japanese people must love making food that gives you diarrhea.
Us Indians, on the other hand, that just, I mean, hell no. We hate that crap. Man, I
don't, I'm thinking about it now, like if I was offered it, I think I would eat it.
I mean I would eat anything I think I've realized yes, I will eat
Somebody says if somebody vouches for it if you're not doing it as a prank if it's not if I'm not getting be my
So I will do it if I saw Anthony Bourdain eat it. I'd eat it
Well, I mean, maybe he maybe that was his last meal dude. Oh
I wonder what his last meal was did his last his last meal was like heroin or something shower water
hotel shampoo
The forbidden vlog that they refuse to release
It's Anthony Bourdain just like with a cup next to the shower. He's like it's perfectly fine to drink
But he's got one of those shower heads have you seen like those those tick-tock shower heads that look like they have the beans in
them
No, no, oh well, then fuck they put beans in a shower
Beans in the shower
It's like one of these shower heads where it's like they put like tiny rocks in it
And that's supposed to help with the pressure or something
No
Making things up now look I don't go on tick-tock
Look up beans showerhead. I will not look that. I don't want I'm afraid that I'll get I'm gonna get some sort of
It's a thing, it's a Luxego shower head with replacement hose and bracket on Amazon.
And it's got little beans in it.
I'm gonna put your beans in my shower.
It's got little brown beans and it's got big blue beans in it.
Ugh.
That's, what, I'm, as soon as we're done recording I have to go vomit I think.
Oh yeah, this is a, I don't like the look of this shower head at all.
I'm so sick right now.
Is this really how we're, oh fuck.
Don't look this up if you're listening.
These are stones. These are stone beads. Those are beans. That's disgusting.
Oh, there's one with a T-Rex skull. Okay, that's actually pretty cool. Where's that?
I'll link it to you right now. We're all using one big computer right now.
Yeah, check this out. Take a dino bath. Does this have beans in it? No.
No. But it's just a thing you put on your shower head. I'm gonna put Pat in my shower and
he's gonna grow. He's gonna absorb all the water and grow to a normal size instead of
four inches tall. Dude, I should get this. I should get this dino shower head and this
dino shower curtain. Yeah, anything to make you take a shower. Come on! Oh! Stinky ass
muffin. I'm not stinky. You're stinky. You're disgusting. Alright. Disgusting. I gotta pee.
All right, bye boys. I'm gonna stop recording. Bye
Bye