You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
Oh my god, we have Mario.
I don't look like Mario. Stop.
Hey, so Mario, does it hurt?
Oh my god, my name's Patrick and I'm Mario.
I don't look like Mario.
You also sound like Mario.
I'm gonna shut the-- I can shut this off right now.
- Mario's classic outfit right now.
- So then it'll just be me, Cam, and Mario.
And then we can ask him questions.
Hey, does it hurt when you go into the pipes?
Does it squeeze you really hard?
- I scream!
- You scream?
Really, they cut that out of the games.
They must turn the volume down.
- They make me mute my microphone
when I go in the pipe 'cause I scream.
- You guys knock it off.
- That's another question.
When you're acting in the games,
do you have like a lav mic on?
Like, how do they get your audio?
- They put a mic on me.
I don't know what it's called.
- Mario, you're so fucking stupid.
You fucking idiot.
I'm just an actor, I don't worry about the...
Fucking short ass idiot.
Are you a dwarf or is Peach really tall?
I was born six feet tall, I got small.
Oh, you got smaller when you got older.
Oh, okay.
Are you guys done with this?
Are you guys done?
Can you not interrupt?
If you're gonna dress like Mario,
the least you can do is let us talk to Mario.
Caleb and I are both doing an interview with Mario,
okay, right now?
- Oh, so Caleb, keep asking all the questions
for our interview with Mario.
- I'm wearing, I got a new red socks fitted.
'Cause the end of--
- I'm wearing Mario clothes, I'm wearing Mario clothes.
- The other one.
- Let's go to, I'm wearing Mario clothes.
- My other red socks fitted was too big.
- Yeah, well 'cause Mario shrinks over time
as we've already established.
- Yeah.
- Cameron, you tried it on when you were at my apartment.
I'm also, I'm in New Hampshire right now.
- The birthplace of Mario.
place of note Matthew Thornton and no and ant the committee where Nintendo is
based is New Hampshire oh yeah yeah buy tickets to the early show let's start
let's plug that now let's play this it comes out the beginning of June this
comes out middle of June yeah this comes out in May you know what I realized so
going from or going from June to July we're in July now right yeah so I
thought everybody was dressing gay because of pride but it's actually
because it's so damn hot that you have no choice but to dress so gay yeah or else
you will die dude I want to get a reflection of the reflects the and now I
feel bad for me and Pat walking around Williamsburg telling all the people
dressed in nothing put some damn drawers on we do do that a lot we do walk up to
people and say put some listen ma'am I think you may have forgotten your drawers
at home yeah cuz you ain't got no drawers on me and Caleb we wear like big
three-piece like Steve Harvey suits and we walk up to them and they're like
they're way too big you look like a kid wearing a dad suit yeah like the sleeves
and pant legs are like trailing on the ground as you walk some extra cloth for
right here. Yeah, take some of this. You look like you've been attacked by a bear.
Here's some, put some damn drawers, put some ass cheeks in your butt front.
This is just nasty. That's a problem I don't think I've thought about in years.
It used to be a big deal dude. People used to get real mad about it. But now it's
like just, I mean like, I'm not like calling you a slut. I'm just saying like
some like draws are like I guess you have to wear them all I'm saying is is I would
like to I would like to throw a trench coat over you and a paper bag on your
head I've been fucking slut-shamed dude I used to sag my pants in school and the
teacher he bought me a big-ass belt yeah yeah embarrassing as giant ass WWE
you'd want a small belt to be so it could be tighter right it's a big belt
it's gonna sag - no cuz it's too big wide but I did have a big ass it's from
anything from big-ass brand you guys brand belts brand of belts yeah yeah and
it was like big-baller brand but for asses a lot of people realize I was a
slutty little kid dressed like a complete slut all the time total slut ass
whoreish kid yeah I was yeah and I grew out of that I was very modest I'm now I
wear pants but I used to have my dress like a hoe now I mean look at me yeah
I used to have my ass and titties out all day long on the playground
And then the as the teacher said put some draws on you little ass boy
You ain't supposed to have no draws on you a little ass boy
And i'd say you're not wait your teacher your teacher told you you're not supposed to have drawers
You're not supposed to caleb. What happened with you and your teacher?
He said put some clothes on and I said hey buddy do something about it wink and he put a belt on me
Which is not where I was going
You're pretty disappointed teacher tried to fuck everybody until I was 15
Yeah, pretty much. Try to fuck anybody. Yeah. Yeah, new family members, you know you go to
like a Thanksgiving and they're like, "This is your, this is your like uncle's best friend's
cousin." Something, not blood relation, but like people be like, "This is like your, your
like twice removed married in cousin." Yeah, "This is your new niece." Yeah, no. No. What
was that? Or somebody like, you know, like friends, parents and stuff, just try to fuck
them show my ass. Yeah, or like your mom got a new haircut and you got confused.
You gotta show, you know what, the thing is, I mean, underboob's a big
thing now. Is it? Is that a big thing now? It's a thing. People are doing
underboob and stuff. I've seen it. What do you, like, when you say people are
doing under boob yeah what does that mean? Like a like oh women oh oh oh.
They're doing under boob I think I think men should have something similar I think
we should have you know maybe like a like just one slit cut in the crotch of your
pants so a ball can hang out. Oh that's actually really smart like okay so so
your zipper makes like a T right and you unzip the bottom part and just like not
like I mean we're not getting disgusting you're not gonna see my entire balls but
- No, it's just a little bit of it.
- Yeah, you're gonna see like a little three, basically.
- It could be like right between--
- You'll see one long pube that I've been growing out
on my ball. - Yeah, that would be nice.
Or it could be like a little horizontal slit
that shows just under the base of the shaft,
but before, if your ball's hanging low enough,
just a little bit of skin.
- What about just like, pair of pants, right?
And just around the zipper and the crotch,
like the whole crotch area, clear plastic.
That's pretty illegal, yeah.
Yeah, like a window into your dick and balls.
I think loincloths might come back.
A reverse loincloth is what we need though.
Yeah, that's what we're trying to make here.
I don't know if you've ever seen a caveman wearing a loincloth.
That thing only works from one direction.
Trust me, I've seen a few cavemen in loincloths in my day.
Also wait, okay, so a loincloth, can't people still see your butthole?
Like I'm way more worried about people seeing my butthole and my penis.
Yeah, because you could have TP crumbs on it.
Because like my butthole is like fucking disgusting.
You know, like disgusting.
I don't know what it looks like, you know?
And the first time that I...
You probably a whore.
You know exactly what it looks like.
I can draw what it looks like for you right now.
Please do, I would like to know.
Yeah, okay.
Press the shift key on your keyboard.
Okay.
Hold it down.
press 8. What does that do? You see what is typed in? That's what it looks like. Open
up Google Docs, set the font size really big. Set it red too. It does kind of look like that.
No mine isn't red dude, I'm not a porn star. It looks like, I mean it's well worn. It looks
It's more like shift three, I think,
is what situation you're working with.
(laughing)
- Yeah, oh yeah, 100%.
I would say shift three with a shift eight in the middle.
- Mine is, I think mine is shift two.
I think that's what I'm working with.
- Oh, definitely, yeah.
But it keeps spiraling on for eternity.
- Well, no, it's shift two 'cause I have a hemorrhoid problem.
- Honestly, my asshole looks like an Uzumaki spiral.
- Yeah.
- It really does.
more of a I've got an alt one type of deal going on I don't know if you're on
I have an alt one in the front.
yeah
that's what my meatus looks like
I think that was that's like a nasty today Jesus. You are nasty. The biggest reason I
probably could never do porn
besides being ugly with a small penis is that I could never do that shot
where they go behind the guy's butthole and they make it
anybody can. Yeah, no one can pull that off, but when someone pulls that shot off, I mean, come on.
At its best, they're doing like, you know that the way that they came up with that shot
was somebody's watching Empire Strikes Back as the ship started moving past the frame.
They're like, I just had the best idea for a guy's balls and butt. This is gonna be perfect.
When the Millennium Falcon's flying out of the worm, that's the exact same shot.
Yeah, and it just keeps going and going and you're just like, "Dude, this would be so funny to make
people watch this and put on a guy's balls."
I know, I think I've said it before on here, but the porn industry is so lucky that Smell-O-Vision
never caught on.
Oh, yeah.
Because that would have been over.
You imagine what it smells like.
The whole room, horrible, horrible smell.
Yeah, just under hot lights, camera right up in the hole.
I mean, I pretty much only have missionary style normal sex and it smells like salami
every single time.
So like, if there was a woman vomiting and crying and butts and holes involved, then
that would be like...
Yeah, like stage lights and also like five guys who stand there whose job is to confer
with each other and then go, "Faster, faster, okay, slower."
Yeah. I've had an Italian sub kind of just sitting out all day next to me.
That's your smell. You nailed it.
Yeah, that's exactly what it would smell like.
Yeah.
I mean, you leave that next to you, like, while you're watching it, you'll have the full picture.
Sex, like, at its best, like cleanest, right out of the shower, smells like a friend's car.
So like the worst version of that is like...
[Laughter]
Like it's gotta be so bad.
It's gonna be so fucked up, bro.
Yeah, it's gonna be fucking horrible.
Yeah, one of the... yeah, five McDonald's bags that are like hiding under the passenger seat.
They're like, "Sorry, people don't usually sit in the passenger seat."
"Hold on, before you get in, let me move a bunch of bags."
"Yeah, let me..."
"Let me..."
There's a box of french fries in the back of the car that are like perfectly preserved
somehow.
"Yeah, hold on, we just, yeah, no, you, here, you can sit in the passenger seat, just roll
that wheel of cheese out of the way and you'll be good."
"Can you, can you move my wheel of parmesan?
Can you move that to the back seat?"
"Yeah, just don't, just don't hit your head on the fish tank, okay?"
(laughter)
- Yeah, and then they're like,
you're like, "What the fuck is under me?"
And you're like, "Oh, sorry, that's my birth certificate.
"I've been looking for it for quite a while.
"Will you hand it to me?"
And then they just like lick a side of it
and stick it to the windshield.
(laughter)
- Yeah, no, can you hand me, no, not, next to the onions.
Next to the bag of onions there.
- Next to the onions.
- Yeah, can you hand me that CD?
Yeah, it's a single CD of Tracy Chapman.
fast car. I really want to listen to it.
As somebody who's never owned a car, I have a lot of fun being on my high horse about that.
There is nothing I love more than walking down the street and seeing a car that's hoarded
style full of trash. Every time I just want to stand and look through the window and see
what's in there so badly.
Yeah, play I Spy with it.
Exactly. I just want to be like, "Oh, I want to see where they've been eating. I want to
see what what yeah what what CDs they gave up on and threw into the back like I just
always everything it's always a pleasure to come to the end of like a like a two
hour road trip and like not really think about it but then open up the door and
they'll be like all right time to clean the car out and you realize that you ate
it like five different fast-food places over that two hours and you have like
giant bags from I'm so fucking glad that I don't have a car yeah reason you would
have the most evil car imaginable. I would have the most disgusting car. You'd be one of those
fuckers who keeps Taco Bell sauce in his glove compartment. Yeah. You know what? You know
that you have to refrigerate this at some point, right? You know, I honestly didn't think of
that until you said it, and I totally would. I would have like six things of like the Diablo
sauce just in the car. Just like, "Oh, I just forgot to throw that out." Yeah. It'd be like
a fucking there'd be like a like a the components of an MRE scattered across
your car. You could like fully make one. I gotta eat and drive at the same time. I'll be doing a lot of
work. I'll be doing a lot of driving. This is for my new... oh man. I gotta get you behind the wheel of a car
dude. Yeah I gotta learn. I didn't know. No, before you learn I have to see you drive
one. No you wanna learn. Do you wanna learn together? I'm gonna learn in the fall I
I think I might I don't know that's you want to teach each other
You guys should get one of those instructor cars it has two steering wheels and brakes and you guys could just both drive
That's very good. I mean one of us would fuck up eventually so that the other one could fix it
I could drive my way around a parking lot and stuff and I'll be me too
I can do parking lots, I just can't.
- That's pretty much all there is to it, as far as I know.
- I took a driving test.
I took two driving tests in my life.
And the second one, when I failed it,
they said that if I fail a third time,
I'll have to go to court to prove.
- You have to go to jail.
- Pretty much.
- If you fail a third time.
- You got into the car and the first thing,
you buckled your seatbelt and then you put
an empty McDonald's bag onto the instructor's feet
and they immediately failed you.
So I was driving, I was taking the test in Manchester,
which is like, everyone told me afterwards,
like, oh yeah, that's like the hardest one.
You should have gone to like this town or whatever.
And I, 'cause Manchester's like kind of the city,
so I was like in like downtown Manchester
and I was like turning on some street corner
and I didn't know like how to turn the car.
Like I just like went in, like I just went in
was like I'm gonna take my driving test today because I passed the written
because I was like oh fuck it whatever and I like stopped in like a two-lane
like thing like I fucked up so bad that she and like she got like really mad at
me she got like super pissed at me I don't remember where the story was going
but I did hit a curb on the way back to the DMV after nothing did after I hit
the
you like you should take us out for all for a drive around the block like to
with your new license and he immediately hit a cat with his entire family. Well a
cat they don't prepare you for. I remember when I took the driving test
they they do like one of the most evil things of all time when you're in the
driving car where they're you're like you drive they find like a little stretch
of road for you to drive on usually in like a neighborhood or something and
say okay accelerate like as fast as you can you're like oh okay yeah sure and
then like before you are really thinking about what's the next step is the guy in
the passenger seat goes stop and you have to just stop as fast as possible
and it's like so fucked up dude it's like the most evil part of the test dude
the thing about the thing about New Hampshire I think is if like even in
that driving test if you miss even one of their instructions like if they tell
you to like turn onto this road and you miss it even if they tell you like like
as it's like you're passing it and you don't do that I guess like that you can
get points docked last time that I went so if you if you don't do the thing they
tell you to then you know like it's docked you if you like I know I know you
fuck you last time I need to go get a new license cuz mine's like insanely old I've
talked about that before. I get fucking, I mean dude, the Roastmasters at the TSA just
fucking own me every time. But last time I went to the DMV, I had to like, I think it
was to get my license renewed or my registration renewed or something, and I showed up and the
lady was like, "Okay, so number one, your license has been suspended for a year, and
And number two, there's a bench warrant out for your arrest because you didn't show up
in court for the reason why you got your license suspended.
And I had like no idea.
And she was like, "So, one or two things could happen.
Either I could tell that police officers over there to arrest you and you would go to jail,
or you can tell me that you were having somebody pick you up from the DMV and you're not going
to drive home and then I just won't tell anybody."
And I was like, "Well, I choose fucking option two, dude.
What are you talking about?"
Right.
Why did the boy even give you the option?
Yeah, I was like, "What are you talking about, dude?"
I guess she did, yeah, she had to like call my lawyer and apparently like my dad's like
traffic lawyer that like handled my passing a bus, a stop to school bus ticket.
He apparently-
Of course, yeah, your dad has a traffic lawyer on call.
Oh, dude, he literally does, yeah.
He pays like a hundred bucks every time he does something horrible in a car.
But the guy apparently was like, I was like, "Hey, did you not show up for my court appearance
for this?"
And he was like, "Oh yeah, I was just like really hungover and I just didn't go."
And I was like, "There's been like an arrest worn out for me for like three months, dude.
Like what the fuck?"
And he's like, "I meant to tell you, but I just forgot."
So he's pretty much the best lawyer ever.
I don't even know his name.
Yeah.
Dude, that's fucking the hungover lawyer.
Yeah, the hungover lawyer.
It was an amazing Better Call Saul moment in my life.
I was just turned 18 and I'd never had any problem with the police.
I never had a lawyer before.
And the lawyer was just like, "You're going to go to jail."
The hungover lawyer.
Let's do it.
Ready?
Oh, your honor, I'm so hungover.
Oh, I'm so hungover.
I don't even want to do this.
May I approach the bar?
I have a motion for a fucking nap break.
Yeah, objection, I'm the hungover lawyer.
Motion for a McDonald's break, your honor.
Motion for a bloody Mary, because I need some more booze in me.
Do you have a fireball nip on you for some reason?
The bailiff seems cool, let's hang out later.
I fuckin' the fireball nip in the morning, that's a perfect hangover cure.
Yeah, 'cause it's candy, which is always gonna make you feel better, and alcohol.
Yeah.
Mix that with a yerba mate, and you'll die.
That's a really great idea.
You'll wanna die immediately.
Yeah, that's the fuckin'-- something with that much caffeine you should not mix with
alcohol.
It's pretty funny that the only hangover cure is beer.
Yeah.
It's like, it's almost like it's a bad idea.
It's almost like drinking's bad.
It's almost like it's some kind of cycle that it's pushing you into.
I don't know.
It almost makes no sense to my brain.
It's confusing.
It's hard to figure out what's going on with it.
I don't like drinking at like breakfast, like Bloody Marys and like mimosas and all that
shit.
I fucking hate Bloody Marys.
Shit'll make me fucking fall asleep, dude.
you'll like like like when my family's in town I'll like my brother will get some
shitty like like brute champagne or whatever that like $2 champagne is and
like orange juice and he'll make bloody marys like every morning and we'll have
three and I'll be like do you want to go to the movies no you're like no dude I
want to like fucking I want to I want to like fall asleep in a car right now I
don't want to sleep at the movies is awesome
yeah but what if I move me but you know that that chair is so comfortable if
you're in like a good movie theater you have a bed at your house somebody doesn't
care about war and I think it's you buddy last time I think I fell asleep
premiere of Star Wars got let into the premiere the 1977 Wow no the premiere of
The Last Jedi I meant to say I for the world premiere you were on the red
The Force Awakens. The day of the premiere, not the world premiere.
December 15th or something like that. You fucking suck. Or something like that.
Something like December 15th. Then I fell asleep. I smoked weed with my
friend Alex and my friend Dylan and then we went to the movie theater and I was
like way too high because anytime I ever smoke I just like can't function at all.
and I was trying to take a picture of just like how big the crowd was because I
thought it was funny it was like all like there was a dude dressed up like
Darth Maul a couple feet in front of me so I was trying to take a picture of like
a bunch of people and just like a Darth Maul standing there and I was just way
too high and I had the flash on and it went off like in front of this woman's
face. She turns to me and is like, "Did you just take a picture of me?" I was like, "No, I was trying to take a picture of the crowd." And I like, I needed to just like, go in. So like, they like, I went to the bathroom and came back and then like, they were letting people in. And that was at like, five and the movie didn't start till like, eight. And I just immediately just like passed out in the theater. Just because I was way too high. I like woke up before
like I think the first like the I woke up like around that time the first day the
you know you know what when Star Wars when it does the taking photos of people
who don't want it the other day I was like on the train and I know and on the
down the victim dude I'm the victim here yeah I was on the train I was just like
Fuck I was like so hungry and I was like
like
popcorn
oh i need a lollipop
i'm so hungry
the steaks are hanging on the train
like rubbing their belly
oh i need a candy apple
oh please
please
i'm so hungry
i need toffee
and then a voiceover comes
on the train, ding!
reminder, do not be extremely hungry on the train
do not feed
this man not the hungry man on the train
unattended lollipops and popcorn
please report them immediately to the
New York Transit Authority
please get me a PBJ
I need a candy cane I'm so hungry
oh my god dude
I lost my bag of candy
where's my candy corn
Guys came onto the train the other day while I was trying to listen to a podcast and started doing lunch time again.
*laughter*
Oh, it's so annoying. They should ban lunch time from the train.
Oh, someone is spinning donuts on all the rails and shit. It's so fucking annoying.
Oh, I need my snow caps. I need my junior mitts. I need a sponge bubble popsicle.
I need wax lips!
*laughter*
Oh god!
Where are my wax sodas?!
I need one of those chocolate
straws that turns to milk chocolate
when you drink it!
I'm so hungry!
Oh, please, does anyone have any
chestmen or milanos or any
kind of beverage for me?
I need a candy g-string!
*laughter*
"OHHHHH! OH WHY AM I WEARING THE EDIBLE UNDERWEAR I WANNA EAT IT!"
So what happened on the train?
I was just fucking destroying a Dunkin' Impossible sandwich.
Just like shoving it in my mouth as fast as possible.
And like looked up for one second to a lady taking a photo of me doing it.
And I just like full Sasquatched looked right at the camera.
*laughter*
And then I just ignored it.
So I just am aware that there is a photo of me just like,
like cheeks full, chipmunking a fucking
impossible Dunkin' sandwich, and looking directly
at the camera. - I hope somebody finds
that photo, I hope somebody sends it to us.
- Me too, man, she's out there somewhere.
I doubt that she listens to the podcast.
- That was a fan's mom.
- Yeah. - Oh, it could've been.
- Honey, here's that bald guy you keep trying
to show me during dinner. - What?
- Yeah, did it look like-- - That's not him,
that's a monkey.
- Did it look like someone you knew?
- Yeah, it actually looked exactly like my best friend.
Really? Yeah, my bad. You're right. Is that true?
It was actually my best friend, yeah.
Oh man, I really fucked that up. I thought it was a stranger.
Yeah, you could have fuckin', you could have told them.
Yeah, it was Darla, my best friend.
You could have told them, "Hey, I'm your best friend."
Yeah, I would say. They probably would have sent you the picture.
"I'm your best friend."
[laughter]
Have you guys ever been, knowingly, had a photo taken of you in public?
Um, I don't think so.
Yeah, I don't think so either.
Unless you count selfies taken with my beautiful friends that I love.
Yeah.
- No, I don't, why would I count those?
That makes no fucking sense, dude.
- I've had like friends take a picture like of me
from behind and then send it to me.
- You've never dressed especially stupid one day
and then like a bunch of construction workers
take a photo of you?
- No.
- Oh, yeah, me neither.
- I mean, in high school I think,
in high school I probably like,
so I'd like tuck my shirts in sometimes.
- I'm sure it's happened that I just didn't notice it.
It's happened to everybody.
- Yeah, I guess.
- I think, it's okay, Caleb,
that happens to pretty much everybody.
- Yeah, everybody has that day, right?
- Pretty, yeah, exactly, a day a week.
That's how often it happens to most people.
It's normal.
- Yeah.
(coughing)
- Like second grade?
- Yeah, everybody has that day where you walk out
in downtown Boston and then the next day
you see a post on Twitter with 500 million likes.
It's a Snapchat photo of that with the caption,
"He on Charlie Brown today."
(laughter)
- Everybody's had that happen to them, right?
Everybody's been in that situation.
- What was, oh, speaking of just like, you know,
dressed in stupid, second grade,
they had crazy hat day, and yeah.
- For a week.
- Some of those hats were crazy.
- What a boon.
- Those hats that day.
- You would not believe this one guy was wearing a hat
looked like a damn chicken.
I said take that off your head.
- It looked like his head was--
- You are not doing that today.
But I, uh, I showed up.
Any other day, but not on crazy hat day.
I had that Darth Vader mask, like the one, the two piece one that has like the chest piece
from like Halloween.
And I like showed up wearing that and I was like pressing the button like talking through
it and they told me I couldn't wear it because it was like too distracting.
So I just went around that whole day with just like the Darth Vader like headpiece thing.
you know like in space balls where he wears like the big helmet and he's just
like yeah all he's wearing I was like dressed up like that for like the rest of
second the day in second grade damn you were a stupid ass seven-year-old dude
that's like the stupidest fucking move you can make it's like oh yeah I'm gonna
bring I'm gonna bring my whole Darth Vader
Oh yeah, we have like a test today.
Yeah.
I know, did you guys dress up for Halloween at school?
Did I?
I don't think so.
I wasn't, in fucking, in first grade I was pissed about this.
My mom didn't let me wear my Yama Yugi outfit.
Your Yamaka?
My Yugi Moto, is that it?
What are you talking about?
Yugi from Yu-Gi-Oh.
Who is the?
Yami Yugi's when he turns big.
That's the one I was wearing.
Yeah.
She didn't let me wear my Yami Yugi outfit because she thought that it was violent or
something.
The school banned Patrick's Pharaoh outfit for certain reasons.
But I had to go dressed up as Scooby-Doo that day and I was pissed off.
Scooby-Doo of all the fucking people in the show that are humans?
dressed up like the dog?
But then when I got home, when I got home I changed.
What was the costume like? What did it entail?
Like a full Scooby Doo...
Like a costume?
Like a big furry costume.
Was it the thing where the dog's head was over your head?
Yeah, the dog's head was over my head.
Yeah, your face is in the neck.
I had to wear that instead of my fucking sick Yami Yugi outfit.
That's horrifying, bro.
That's maybe I was pissed I was fucking oh my god cuz I came home that night and I could go trick-or-treating as Yugi
But I couldn't fucking wear yami Yugi to school. Did you have a dual disc?
Yeah, oh I had the whole fucking serious. Do you still have that duelist? Those are we're not a lot of money now
I broke that when I was a kid my mom
What I I didn't even like
Like watch Yu-Gi-Oh that much. I just thought the costume was sick
everybody thought Yu-Gi-Oh was cool without watching that much of it.
That's the point.
I wasn't a camera level Yu-Gi-Oh fan.
It was like, to me, I wasn't either as a kid.
I got into Yu-Gi-Oh in college.
It sucked, dude.
My family always thought like any Japanese TV show was demonic.
Yeah.
It was like, Pokemon were the devil, Yu-Gi-Oh was the devil.
But my mom made me dress up like Harry Potter and go to one of the Harry Potter premieres
when I was a kid and that was one of the worst days of my entire life.
It's also, I remember my parents, like I would try to watch like Harry Potter.
I remember trying to watch like anime, like trying to like watch anime on TV or like Pokemon
or Yu-Gi-Oh or something and then adults being like, "Ugh, like this animation is so, it's
so horrible.
Like only, like their mouths are moving and they barely even match up with the words and
it's like, it turned on like a Hanna-Barbera or something instead and it's like this is,
Oh yeah.
Are you watching Dora the Explorer again?
That devil TV show?
You fucking piece of shit.
My uncle, one of my uncles, my uncle Kevin would just like tell us we couldn't watch
Dora because she got deported.
Well that's not even, that's just a joke.
That's just kind of a, kind of an alright joke by Kevin.
Yeah.
Yeah whatever Kevin.
It was pretty funny.
Did you guys call him Clever Kevin?
No we never called him that.
You had to have called him Clever Kevin.
I mean I know, I know that guy was going to call him Clever Kevin.
It's like my uncle Mental Michael.
(laughing)
Mental Michael had a lot of really good jokes
when I was a kid, dude.
Yeah.
Yeah, Mental Michael, I remember one time,
dude, this one blew my mind, when I was like 10,
I was like, yeah, I love horror movies,
and he said, "Um, they prefer to be called
"prostitute movies."
Oh my God.
I was like, oh, you Mental Michael,
you fucking, you mentaled me again, you Michael.
I've definitely talked about Uncle Kevin before,
because his, somebody, my cousin Timmy was like,
"I want an eye touch for Christmas."
And he said, "Oh, I want an eye touch myself."
- I mean, that's a mental Michael Lyne fucking word for word.
I feel like all the uncles maybe have a shared consciousness
or something.
- We've definitely talked about this,
but the eye touch was just a gift for uncles.
- Yeah, definitely.
- I mean, not as a joke, I mean, just like,
get your uncle an eye touch.
- Yeah.
- It's a good gift for your uncle.
- Yeah, 'cause they don't have anybody to talk to,
but they would like to play games on it.
They would love talking to us.
They need a camera right now.
Steve Jobs did focus groups and he saw, and whenever an uncle was in the focus group, you
know, they would be in there and they'd be going like, "Yeah, you know, I think this
little device is pretty cool, but I want an iPod myself."
And then they'd raise their eyebrows and nobody would laugh.
And then Steve Jobs was like, "We need to take this up a notch.
We need the eye touch."
Yeah.
That's the next step.
cancer and he was like I need to eat so many grapes now.
Yeah.
Fuck.
I was thinking about that the other day.
I need juice.
It's so fucking funny dude.
Yeah.
That Steve Jobs got like the worst most like fucking aggressive cancer that is like somewhat
treatable and he was like I'm gonna eat a very I'm gonna eat a pineapple and a coconut.
The funniest part of that is that every guy like that who's like insanely rich like some
like tech billionaire guy is like they try to tell they'll like their publicist will try
to tell you like do an interview where they try to say like yeah that guy also
he used to run 500 laps around his office during the day just because he felt like
it needs to jump out the window and it didn't hurt him and then it's like
don't understand how like how to go to the doctor and I jobs doctor was like
four years old or something anyway it's like you have guys and he's like what
should I do some quakes maybe like a strawberry I think that might really make
you feel better. Thank you very much. I'm gonna go meditate. Do you remember that generation
that the iTouch came out? That time period where it was just like everyone, there was
all these fucking apps. Damn. It was just like, like everyone, like it was like Pocket
God and like Talking Tom and fucking like CamWow and just like all that shit. Do you guys want
to get really, do you guys want to get into Talking Tom? Yeah. We should. I'm gonna walk
What the hell, Talking Tom said something so racist.
What the fuck is this?
Yeah.
Talking Tom, come on.
What are you doing Talking Tom?
You can't even get it to say it again because you have to say it.
You have to repeat it.
You can't like sit and write it.
You're pulling it away.
You're covering your mouth.
Yeah.
You won't believe what Talking Tom just said about you.
You said what Talking Tom?
What the hell?
Talking Tom just called you fat as shit.
You know what's really weird?
You know what's crazy?
What?
Talking Tom has a TV show.
Like there's a Talking Tom Netflix animated series.
- That's not that crazy to me, dude.
- Netflix, the Netflix shows are just pure evil.
Every Netflix, like I--
- Yeah, I know, but fucking Talking Tom,
I didn't think Talking Tom was that big.
Like I didn't-- - That's what I mean.
No, they have a trillion kids.
I mean, it's the same thing as like
the four kids YouTube stuff where like it ends up,
like me and my girlfriend were looking for something
to watch on Netflix and we scrolled past this show
called called Larva Island those a show yeah yeah and I was like we were like
laughing about it and I press play and the first episode opens with the little
larva eat some kind of poison and then just repeatedly farts and screams for
like a full minute that's like a static shot and then the entire show just
happens between like two worms yeah that just like for interacting and crying
stuff it's pretty cool dude I'm looking at I'm looking at glad you watched it
too yeah talking Tom and friends the voice of Tom Colin Hanks
that's sick Colin Hanks they don't and they don't use any effects on it either
no whoa really no it's just Colin Hanks does the voice yeah fucking insane Colin
Hanks Tom Kenny Maria Bamford James Adomian it's like a fucking incredible
cast really good cast
but if you check this out talking tom i am doing it i want to read some last
year for four seasons a hundred and forty four episodes what's a hundred and
sixty four episodes of talking tom and friends
and i just started twenty fourteen
that's fucked up with that they had to be a group like just reusing lines and
shit right now we have this is a very little for an over again yeah time to go
to the store
all my god i need to see i just want to look at some
the top rated episodes
i do feel like we're like like i mean were here's the top country of origin
cypress
top top rated episode of talking tom and friends a secret worth keeping part
three
here's the synopsis
no more secrets
with things spiraling out of control at the tech conference talking angela
realizes it might be time to come clean and reveal her secret. But now there's more at
stake than just her heart. Does this mean the end for Tom and Ben Enterprises?
God, I fucking hope not, dude.
How did they stretch this fucking show out this long?
It's crazy watching like, um,
like, even like Animaniacs,
which probably like our parents thought was like
insanely stupid
and like too fast-paced when we were kids.
Watching that and like how slow the jokes come,
and how little
like insane sound effects there are
compared to like any kids' show now.
I feel like we're like accelerating towards
a, like just TV shows
are actually like for kids are just gonna be like a farts it's like yeah just like
a like a ball that well like arts think about think about like what we fucking
like watched on YouTube when we were like 11 like the funniest thing you could
ever see when you're 11 is like Windows Movie Maker like Barney gets shot and
that's like that is a 30 second video of that some kid may like learned Windows
Movie Maker and made yeah we've just been progressing toward like all
All children's media has been progressing towards that.
It's just they don't want to like.
Yeah just like a close up of a monkey's asshole.
You can't kill Barney on TV.
What are you laughing at?
I've just been scrolling through episode synopses for talking Tom and friends.
This is season 5 episode 14.
I'm just on the IMDB page for it okay.
Season 5?
It's called alert parents in town.
Here's the like one line.
Here's the log line for this episode.
okay the friends have to teach the MC to act like a normal adult when his
unhip parents come to town and they have a they have like a multi paragraph
storyline summary and then scroll down and there's the trivia section and the
only thing there is it just says did you know the MC is actually called Maurice
Clairemont.
There's a review that says, "Feels slow, but not bad.
Not the greatest, but overall not bad either.
Story follows MC trying to impress his parents as a businessman."
Wow, dude.
I feel like we've missed out on a television gem.
This is like Larry Sanders show.
We have to watch all of these.
We're going to watch every episode of Talking Tom.
And Friends.
- And friends.
- Yeah.
- You gotta fucking remember his friends.
- Well man, I feel like we should be the change
we wanna see in the world, you know?
Like we need to make a kids cartoon now.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, dude.
- What about, okay, let's just, let's think about,
let's think about like the apps we could exploit for that.
- Oh yeah, 'cause we would, for us to get picked up,
we'd have to come from an app.
Let me look at apps on my phone.
- The Grindr logo.
- Pee nowadays, people would probably love that,
tell
This is perfect.
You can't see it.
It's too bright.
What about, oh, here's actually an app on my phone that I was thinking could be good for
this one.
And, you know, if you need more details about it, you could just ask me what it is.
But I was thinking this, I'm looking at this app right now called BoFa.
Wait, BoFa?
What could that possibly be?
Hold on, I'm getting a call.
Bank of America.
Oh, I have that as well.
Oh, Patrick's getting a call.
What's this?
(Santa Claus is coming to town)
Hello there!
Merry Christmas! Ho ho ho ho ho!
Did you just get...
Santa Claus is coming?
Wait, put me on the phone with him!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Santa, Santa, Santa, Santa, Santa!
Have you been naughty or nice this year?
Yes! Naughty, really naughty, really bad.
Ho ho ho ho ho!
He's laughing!
Fantastic!
Fantastic?!
What are you doing for Christmas?
I want a million dollars and a big gun
Million dollars and a big big gun big ass big ass gun. Oh
Thanks, I know I'll see you soon
Bye Santa
Dude that was fucking like the most exhilarating shit of my entire life. I just talked to a celebrity. Yeah, he's caused me sometimes
condoms. Really? Are you serious? Yeah, sometimes he calls me. Just on like a date, like a first
date. Sorry, I'm getting a phone call. It's just Santa Claus. I have to FaceTime my best
friend. Hi Santa. Oh yeah, oh yeah, I've been good this year. Yeah, can I get a TV and a
box of extra small condoms? Yeah, thank you so much. Oh, a TV and a box of extra small
condoms. Yeah, okay. Alright, see ya.
Just like, yeah, like as soon as she leaves, like, turning to the table next to you, that's
my friend. Yeah, that's Santa.
That's my, yeah, you know. Oh wait, sorry, did you not get a FaceTime
from Santa? That's kind of weird.
You don't FaceTime him? Huh. Oh, strange.
I kind of thought everybody FaceTimed Santa, but I guess.
Yeah, I thought he knew everybody. Yeah, and waiter, could we get the check please,
but only for her.
(laughing)
- Let's see, what other apps do I have here?
- When Talking Tom becomes a supermodel,
he loves being in the spotlight
and getting lots of attention,
until the reality of being a male model hits home hard.
- Wow.
- What is the reality of being a male model?
Does he have to like-- - I don't know.
- Does he have to like make himself vomit or something?
- Maybe.
- That'd be kind of funny.
- When Talking Angela tries to stop the landlord,
I mean, okay, from chopping down a beloved tree,
She wakes up to a swarm of angry butt-pinching bugs.
What?
This show is all over the place.
Talky Ginger tags along with his teacher on a real-life monster hunt.
There's monsters too?
What the fuck?
What the hell?
I will be watching this.
Talky Angela's in danger when an ancient mummy starts taking out her fellow musicians before a big concert.
[Laughter]
Dude.
A visit from Jeremy the Germ's dat nasty brother makes the reformed Germ fall back into his old bad guy habits.
Who the fuck is Jeremy the Germ?
Dude, we would be so good at writing these shows, man.
These are all in a row.
When Talking Tom gets lost in space, Talking Ben needs to find a way to get rid of his anti-tech bracelet so he can save his friend.
That's fucking aw- dude, I mean, we would write the best shit of all time.
Let's try- let's write a Talking Tom episode.
Alright.
Uh, Talking Tom...
Talking Tom smokes a cigarette.
cigarette he smoked a cigarette and it any and he made him cooler yeah yeah and
oh we got some pussy and and and when the guy was there oh my dude it's like
the best episode probably they've ever had if we mean when talking Tom was
listening to his favorite music he was having a fun time that's my idea for one
okay when talking Tom gets assassinated by the president by the president he
finds the true meaning of being a seeing that's all right see there's one in the
one fucking amazing I mean old an idea right we can write a whole season and
just pitch it as like as a yeah I mean we could do that I honestly I might you
know if this goes well I could use these talking Tom episodes in my SNL packet
yeah it's fucking killer dude yeah we've been trying let's see we've been trying
to get on SNL since oh I don't know forever you know
SNL packet it's about talking Tom played by Kyle Moody to get my hate my tech
bracelet hit you get called up dude and then you get into the meeting with
Lauren he's like so where's Tom so I was promised we would see talking Tom at
Thomas coming right right let me let me see so he's on my phone yeah oh hey
Lauren yeah thanks for meeting with me oh sorry do you mind if I take this I'm
getting a FaceTime from Santa and the only time that Lauren does it like he's
like wait really? Okay, drops the Dr. Evil thing. Wait, what the? Did you say Santa Claus?
Hey Santa, your friend. You're on the show, just can I talk to him? Like right now, please?
Can we please get him as a guest? Please. Yeah, Santa's kind of like my version, you
know you have like Paul Simon, Santa's like my Paul Simon kind of. Yeah. Just like he's
always around, he's always helping me out, he's doing me favors and shit. Yeah, you know,
I help him. Do you guys like want him to host the show or something? Oh my gosh, can you
Can you imagine how good of a guest Santa Claus would be
on this show and we could do his list?
- Yeah, so think about this.
- We could do--
- We could file that idea away is all I'm gonna say.
- We could help him make the list and check it twice.
- We talked to him a little earlier so I don't wanna--
- Someone here does have his number.
- Yeah, so we--
(laughing)
I did send him a letter or two, and I have been leaving out a plate of cookies for him
on every holiday.
I have left out a plate of cookies every night.
Do dads always eat all the cookies?
Do you think moms help too?
I think moms eat the carrots for the reindeer.
Yeah, moms eat the carrots.
And dads eat the cookies.
Carrots?
And the kids eat the presents.
You didn't leave out carrots for the reindeer as a kid?
I was a fucking hippie dude. What are you talking about carrots?
I left out carrots too. Carrots and cookies.
You guys are gay.
I still leave them out.
No, cookies dude. Reindeer, you're getting cookies.
You're the reason that the reindeer are unhealthy. You were leaving out so many cookies.
What do you mean they can't eat the cookies? They're magic. What are you, you fucking idiot
dude. They can eat anything. They don't exist.
You can't.
What do you mean they don't exist?
Shut the fuck up.
- Listen, I will accept that Santa was made up, okay?
- But the reindeer.
- But the reindeer are real.
I heard them jingling on the roof when I was seven.
- The reindeer and the-- - You can't fake that.
- And the Christmas cards are real.
- You can't fake the reindeer.
- Did you guys know anybody
who believed in Santa way too long?
- Yeah, me.
- Really, when did you stop believing in Santa?
- I was like nine.
- I don't know how, yeah, I was probably in like--
- Actually my brother probably--
- First grade when I found out,
but I found out from a friend,
as opposed to like from my parents,
which I don't know if that just means it's too late or not.
- I knew somebody whose family,
like their entire family,
would get really in on just like selling Santa Claus
until they were like 13.
- Yeah. - And then, yeah,
they used to like fucking,
they would like leave mud tracks
like of his boots all over the house.
They would have their grandpa
like come sit outside of the window at night,
like dress like Santa,
like the whole fucking nine hours.
I remember I was talking about Santa when I was in elementary school with a kid who was
a grade below me or something.
He told me, "Yeah, actually, it's not Santa who brings the presents.
It's actually Jesus."
I was like, "Is that true?"
I went home and I told my mom, "I just found out some people actually believe that Jesus
brings the presents."
She was like, "What are you talking about?
No, there's no person who thinks that.
It's not like one of the options.
This girl told me that like after she found out Santa wasn't real she was like, "Yeah,
it pretty much like ruined my relationship with my parents for like 10 years."
I was like, "Yeah, I guess that makes sense."
She's like lying about the world like so explicitly for so long, making you like, like cursing
you to be the weird kid at school who's in like eighth grade and they're like, "Are
you gonna go to Tammy's party?
Like we're gonna have sex."
she's like oh no I'm busy writing my letter to Santa this year I stopped
believing in like the tooth fairy and the Easter Bunny before I ever stopped
believing in Santa like it was like well those are fake yeah those obviously
obviously those are fake but like once a tooth yeah Santa that guy's real I mean
I get a presence yeah exactly the tag says Santa right I mean it's not he
He would not write his name.
- Exactly.
- And he has different, way worse handwriting
than my parents.
- If it was my dad leaving the presents,
he would write dad and then cross it out
and then write Santa.
Because he got confused.
It's hard to just write another person.
It wouldn't work.
- Yeah, my dad's bad at impressions.
He couldn't do that.
Doesn't make any sense, dude.
Do you think, if you guys ever have kids,
you think you'll tell them Santa's real?
- Yeah.
- Oh, are you kidding me?
- I mean, at first, I would try and--
- Until they're like six maybe.
- And get rid of it pretty early though.
- Six?
- I think that's like, yeah, I think you gotta,
I think it's gotta be something, you gotta set--
- See, but I wanna lie to my kids about everything.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, so like I'd like to start that,
set that precedent pretty early.
- Yeah.
- You know?
- Yeah, I mean you could make up,
that's the thing about Santa,
you can make up whoever you want and tell them,
tell your kids that person exists.
- You have to go to sleep, Santa Claus is coming tonight,
and Dad is the mayor, so he has to go back to work
at the mayor's office.
He has to sign a bunch of bills,
he's gonna make every drug legal.
And if Santa Claus sees you out of bed, he'll kill you, and I won't be home to protect you.
And I can't stop him, you know, because he's like basically one level above Mayor.
My dad just whispered to me, he just said, "I was Santa."
Your dad was Santa?
Tell him what the fuck happened.
What happened?
Hold the mic up to him.
What do you mean, what happened?
Say, "Why aren't you Santa anymore?"
Why aren't you Santa anymore?
He grew up.
We had a fight and we told him there's no more fricking sound.
here we still have worst interview we have ever fought there saying you're the
worst interviewee
of all you have to get closer to the yeah imagine if you're watching a guy get
interviewed on the news and they're standing twenty feet away from the
mic having
he's having a guinness he won't he won't come over here
tell me he's gonna have my penis pretty soon if you're gonna have a loose penis
pretty soon
if he keeps being a bad interviewee okay what he said
he said you're a public now I don't believe you
No, he said yes, I'm pleased
Please
He's on he's on one now. Oh, he had that Guinness he's fucking he's gone better be on one penis man
Tell me you're gonna sit on my wiener
Just tell him dude
- He's gonna sit on my weiner.
- He's gonna sit on your weiner, I'm not telling him that.
- He just heard that, that counts.
- I guess it does.
- Tell him he's gonna-- - I guess you've tricked me.
I guess you've tricked me into that.
- Tell him he's gonna sit on my weiner
like the top of a fucking,
like the top falcon on a totem, tell him.
And he's gonna be making some face like,
tell him that.
- He's gonna make the weiner disappear like a wizard.
Say that.
- Tell him he's gonna hang off my weiner like a meat hook.
- I'm not gonna say that.
- Tell him.
Please dude, this is, it's making me-
He said, they, they said that you're gonna hang on their penis like a meat hook.
I said wiener.
He said wiener. He said you're gonna hang on his wiener.
Hang on his wiener like a meat hook, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah, like a p-
Say the thing about the wizard. Say, say the thing about the-
I don't, I'm not gonna say this fucking thing about the wizard.
Tell him he's a little piggy and he likes it.
I'm not gonna-
No! Come on!
Tell-
Ask him if he wants to say he's a little sloppy little piggy.
I'm not saying that to him.
Why?
No, I have too much respect for my father.
I will not tell him he's going to eat your slop like a pig.
Tell him he's going to hang clothesline off this penis.
No.
You're going to look like a damn t-shirt hanging off this thing.
Tell him I'm going to put my round peck in his square hole.
He left the room but he said yummy yummy.
Tell him he's going to use my dong like a diving board.
And tell him he's going to play wipeout with this yeehawn.
Tell him I got a USB and I'm gonna upload some data into his womb.
He had his Guinness and he left.
Tell him he's about to fucking...
Tell him...
He's gone!
I can't tell him anything else!
Go find him.
I...
No!
I don't want to care about where he is.
Go find out where he is.
Tell him...
Okay.
But...
When he comes back...
One more thing.
Tell him that when he gets over to my house pretty soon, he's gonna walk up to my wiener
wearing big tall boots and cherry pie will be playing and he's gonna do an insane flag
- He's gone.
Tell him.
I'll tell him.
Okay, will you tell him that he's going to sit on my wiener like it's a throne, but he's
actually going to be sitting on my balls like they're the bottom of the throne, and then
the wiener will be like the back of it, and he's going to sit on it.
And I guess my pubes will be the arms of the chair, too.
Tell him I'm going to play Unblock Me with his butthole until I get a clear path inside.
Tell him he's going to kiss it like he's meeting a dog.
You know, Unblock Me, that app, I'm going to be swiping different interlocking pieces
a poop away until you know there's a space I can climb in.
I'm gonna be clearing lines of dookie like Tetris up in your dad's fucking shitter.
My long straight piece is gonna do a triple Tetris.
He's gonna slide it into his dookie Tetris.
I'm gonna T-spin, just tell him I'm gonna T-spin in.
Just say that, just say that.
You don't have to say anything else.
That's all you have to tell him, is that so hard?
I'm gonna T-spin into his asshole and I'm gonna spit out a drop of cum out of there.
That's it, okay? Nothing else.
Just tell him I'm gonna-
Can we talk about something different?
Yeah, we'll talk about how your dad's gonna play Dig Dug in my thick rug.
Just tell him that.
Downstairs.
Just tell him that, dude.
Oh my god.
Just tell him I got the big dot from Pac-Man and I'm feeling hungry.
That's right.
Tell him he can shoot some ghosts in my mouth, 'cause I'm the hungry Pac-Man.
And I'd be Mrs. Pac-Man if he likes it.
This is my father.
Oh, so somebody can't even like talk to their dad? That's sad as fuck.
Yeah, I mean, come on.
This guy can't even be honest with his dad, you know?
And say, "Listen, my brother Caleb, his wiener's the Hungry Hungry Hippo,
and your balls are the only food he's ever wanted."
My brother?
I'm your brother now.
Tell him, hey, tell him, just tell him.
If you're my brother now, that makes this whole, that makes the conversation very fucking weird.
Just listen, okay? Just quiet for a second and just tell him, the next time you see him,
him that I have the plug and play joystick and we're gonna play pole position. Just tell
him. Please tell him that he's Homer and my wiener is Bart. You better start ringing that
neck. Yeah. Exactly. Please? Yeah. Tell him, just tell him this. This is what I get for
going home. Just tell him I said this. You guys are upset that I'm at home with my family.
When you got a peter like griffin everything looks like a chicken.
Tell him it's about bedtime and he needs to close his eyes and brush his teeth.
Please.
Just please dude.
It's cause I'm home now and you guys are mad, you have separation anxiety and you're latching
out at me.
I'm not latching out at you.
Caleb's special.
I'm not at you.
Caleb's latching out at my dad cause he's jealous.
I'm gonna be latching on to him.
- I'm gonna be latching like Minnie Mouse
when I seduce your dad.
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
- You better not.
- Ding, ding, ding.
- You better not seduce my dad.
- Oh, hey. - He loves my mom.
- He's about to love my bomb.
That's what I call my fucking cock, dude.
Call it a bomb.
- Yeah, 'cause it's round and it has a wick.
- Yep, that's right.
Yeah, it does, so what?
Your dad's about to light this fuse.
I got a burning bomb for your daddy.
He's about to see me explode.
My dad's not going to watch you explode.
Will you just tell him just like a single time we want our wieners to play Ren and Stimpy?
Can you stop saying this about my father?
I just want to sweep around inside his minds.
You know?
That's right.
Yeah.
That's fucking right, dude.
Until I hit the mother load.
Tell him he has to do a hacking minigame on my wiener.
It's as simple as that.
Just tell him Deus Ex.
You know, you don't have to go into any more details after that.
Just say like...
You're not gonna have a day of sex with him.
Just say, just say like, just say, just say like...
[laughs]
Just say like, "Bioshock Infinite."
Just go to him and say, "Bioshock Infinite," and he'll understand what I... where I'm going for.
Tell him my metal here is solid, and he better not be seen by my tower.
[laughs]
I can't even participate in this. It's about my own father.
Tell him he's about to rim me 'til I go up in the sky.
[Laughter]
What?
That's right.
Yeah, tell him, I'm gonna be all over his Elder Scroll.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Yeah, tell him, and we ain't stopping, because I got more to end.
That's right. [Laughter]
[Laughter]
And when we're done, that butt's gonna be oblivion.
Tell him it's that fucking simple dude.
Tell him I hope I don't fall out his new A-MAS.
[Laughter]
Yeah, I mean just tell him.
Next time you see him just say I'm gonna have sex with him.
Yeah, just all that shit.
Bye guys.
[BLANK_AUDIO]