You're listening to Israel's number one pod.
This is premium content!
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately!
Drop that beat!
OOF!
That's good.
Weeeew!
(Siren)
God damn it's so hauntingly beautiful.
It's so good.
I mean it's fucking gorgeous.
It's the most beautiful song I've ever heard.
It's a siren call.
Wee wee, wee wee.
(Laughter)
I think this is finally the time that we become musical stars.
Yeah, I mean we've been musical geniuses but we haven't put our genius to work until right now.
Yeah, this is the first sensitive gangster episode.
Uh-huh.
Where we're gonna make a beat from scratch.
Making a beat from scratch and we're writing all the lyrics too.
Yeah, yeah.
And it's gonna take an hour.
It's gonna take one hour.
We're gonna write a whole song in one hour.
Patrick, you do.
You start it.
You get this going.
Well, we gotta start with-
I think we need a C sharp.
We need a rhythm section.
Boots skirts, boots skirts, boots skirts, boots skirts.
Hold on, I'll pull up, I'll open up GarageBand too.
I gotta record me doing that.
No.
I think we can- Fuck you man!
We got drums.
I'm out of the band.
No.
What?
There's no- First of all, there's no band.
It's a record label.
So you can leave, but you're not getting any money.
Yeah.
Uh, are you guys serious?
If you are.
I'm thinking about leaving.
I'm really close.
Here we got Dez, the trap beat.
The trap beat?
Alright.
Play the trap beat.
No way.
(Arabian Nights music)
- No way.
That's the trap beat?
What the fuck is this dude?
Sounds like Arabian Nights.
- Okay wait.
- Oh it's 'cause I have a track open.
Let me delete these.
- Oh he had his Arabian track on.
- Yeah I had my Arabian music open.
- My bad.
- He was making Arabian music before the episode.
I was making Arabian music and then I decided to switch genres to trap in the middle.
Here, let me just start- Arabian trap!
Let me just open up a new project.
It's more likely than you think.
Yeah.
At least ten Arabian trap artists are changing the game.
Can we pause real quick?
[laughs]
My brother's calling me.
Okay.
What an amazing start to an episode.
[laughs]
Pat just got a call from his brother accusing him of stealing a toothbrush.
Yeah, I didn't steal his toothbrush.
No.
And we let him know that we can't talk about this.
The streets are going crazy.
The streets are going insane getting ready for this song.
Woah.
Nobody wants to hear this.
Play over this.
Wait, let me turn on the arpeggiator.
Okay.
This will, here, we'll set this up.
Here, I'll keep the beat going.
Hold on.
While you guys do this, I'm gonna call my mom and let her know I'm buying her a new car.
Four octaves.
Mom, I got you a G-Wagon.
It's your new favorite son.
Dude, this beat goes hard as hell.
That joint go crazy.
We're about to, hold on.
This has got to sound so horrible in people's headphones.
Yeah.
Which is kind of the appeal.
We're doing something experimental.
Here, I think the song should be very fast.
It should be a two second song.
Yeah, it should be...
That sounds pretty cool.
That's my problem with most songs.
I usually...
230 BPM.
I usually skip.
Okay.
And time signature should be 6/8.
That's a good beat.
Hey Caleb, rap over this.
I've got a hundred friends and I've got a hundred more.
I'm about to go home and go to the store and I've got a million dollars and I've got a bunch
dollars and I'm about to go back to my house till you holler. This is the best
sensitive gangster track we have. Did we just quit the podcast and do this full
time? We should just become rappers who make beats. Okay. Yeah. Obviously I'm the
I'm the vocal talent. I'm gonna be the rapper singer. Sure. I'm gonna be the
one the ones and twos. So Cameron you're kind of like out of a job right now
because we already have ones and twos yeah I mean I could do ones he could do
you guys okay ones twos yeah rapper turnt senga yeah okay I got it I've got an
idea whoa whoa wait was that a beautiful melody
Sorry, is the piano man playing?
Wow.
Is that a heart?
Are you playing a heart right now?
Oh my God, you're so gorgeous right now.
I'm falling in love with you.
playing this and I'm looking in your eyes and I'm actually falling deeper in love
with you every moment. I wish there's a way that we could like do it on the
computer so we don't have to use our phones. No. Shut up. Do you think this is better? Dude I mean we could, it's
safe to say this is already the best episode we've ever done. I mean people
are probably laughing their asses off at this hilarious music. People probably think it's so funny. Yeah.
(laughing)
- Okay, rap over this, Caleb.
- Get going, hang on.
- Fuck, let me catch the beat, hold on.
- Now.
Yo, is it, ah.
- Are you good?
- Everybody in 303,
put your motherfucking hands up in front of me, yo.
Everybody in 302,
(mumbling)
Not hands up.
Notice this man is not hands up.
(mumbling)
Who's afraid of the big bad wolf?
- I am.
how do i stop this? i know you're doing a song
yeah you should be able to answer songs
yeah who's afraid of the big bad wolf? now who's afraid of the big bad wolf?
uh... hold on pause
me! red riding hood! hello! i'm not going to listen to the song if it's about the big bad wolf
i'm the most scared not the most scared the most scared would be little red riding hood
little red riding hood is way more scared or maybe perhaps
her grandma who actually was killed by the wolf
who's actually even by the police scared the woodsman
you know
this once from a mama
rates of definitely do let's pull a major seven year
yeah this is like a this is like a like a jay-z song about it
record a record it mama
this one's for you
mama i miss you
no be flat diminish that's what i'm saying
shut up i'm singing
mama i kiss you
mama you look so beautiful
to me today
mama that was
amazing how you raised me
you never
Raised a hand to me
Mama I've loved you
every day
Mama you look so sexy when you do your walk down the aisle
Mama I just wanna make you smile
Okay, well, I mean how long can we do
Yeah.
Here, at the very least, we can use the sampler to make a sound board.
Okay, that works.
I don't think anyone can hear that.
I think it's too far away from your microphone.
Yeah, I think you need to hold your microphone up to it.
You're not even saying anything.
Just hold your mic up to it.
Ooh.
No one can hear.
They just hear you say ooh.
they can hear the music
you should make a house on we should make a way of the guys i'm gonna record
something for the soundboard and i quite for a second stop at
now that was funny
okay i've never heard of the other side of the road how much did we record
is like nine minutes
it did not it's a nine minute epic it's like a he me and rhapsody or weird
we're trying to figure out...
(laughter)
Do it really high.
(in opposite iodine)
Well, that's like the opposite of...
You got some iodine?
(Now that was funny)
Okay, that's all the soundboard should be.
Now we do an episode...
Yeah, now we just do a normal episode.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm fresh off of shitting my pants. Yeah. Oh, yeah, you did I did Caleb shit himself on the way to get Korean shit myself like
Maybe maybe 80 feet away from my front door
I
shit myself like 80 feet away from my front door on like a mile walk and instead of turning around to
go
Clean myself up. We just kept going. Yeah. Yeah, you just went to this is power to mind over matter, dude
You went to the Korean place with shit in your pants. Yeah, and that guy bowed to me
He fucking took my credit card and said thank you and he bowed and it's like dude you don't fuck yeah
You know you're literally talking. I'm like acting like a baby right now
I'm just walking around yeah, which hit my pants just being like I'll take care of it
I'm gonna eat some sweet and spicy chili chicken mm-hmm, and I didn't it was fucking incredible
and then I shit more when I got home.
Yeah, it was good chicken.
I had more in.
It was amazing chicken.
It was very good chicken.
It made me really full.
It's crunchy.
Yeah.
That's something that the Koreans have perfected.
Yeah, I think it's potato starch in the chicken breading.
I don't even want to know what kind of voodoo magic they're doing to that chicken, but I
just know I like it.
Yeah.
I was trying to close it.
Pat, he's got to...
There's got to be one episode that Pat just ruins with some obsessive thing that he's
doing instead of recording.
Yeah. They got us this and not like an iPhone game.
Yeah. Well this one's my fault. Yeah. Yeah I did suggest this. We were gonna make a
beat. I didn't realize it was still set low. I thought you were gonna use like that thing
that the headphone thing and we were gonna make a beat live on the show.
That's it we should do a stream where we make a beat. That's a good idea.
idea. That's terrifying. Yeah, the soundboard's not as good. It's really, really scary. That
just sounds like Luigi's Mansion. It does. It's just the professor in Luigi's Mansion
talking. Professor E. Gadd. Like a morning radio show. Yeah. So we can hear it from the
craziest color say what we're reading a story about a mission who got stuck in a
zoo maybe we should start doing zoo radio yeah it's a good it's a good idea some
drops and stuff in. The thing is we need a sexy girl. Yeah. Yeah that we call the
pussy. Yeah Patrick. Patrick? Are you? No Cameron. Are you willing and able? Cameron has long
hair. No I don't. Um yeah but Cameron I feel like like you would be. You're way
sexier. No you'd be less sexy as a girl and I feel like a radio girl always has
to have a sexy voice but then looks like shit you know. So Cameron. No cuz he cuz
he has a he has a terrible voice but he looks beautiful thank you yeah yeah who
knows as a girl we'll get the sexy girl who knows or we'll get a say yeah I was
we'll never get one oh we're never gonna get one ah it's two weeks till prom and
we're gonna get a sexy girl oh my god maybe that's our act right now maybe
that's our next big project instead of like a movie or something we do American
We do a prom. Yeah. We put on a prom. That'd be fun. That's a good idea.
But then we all accidentally, we all accidentally ask the same girl. Oh no.
Oh. It tears us apart, but it also brings us closer together in the end. Yeah, that's right.
And you know what happens at the end. You seen Eat Two Mama Tambien? No. That's what happens at the end.
Oh yeah. You haven't seen it? You haven't seen your mom too? No. Well, that's the name of the movie, but in the, oh.
Everybody fucks. That's what I'm saying. Oh really? Yeah. He's back in the studio.
stop hey get out of the studio just keep talking why Cameron's in the fucking
studio they're gonna use this clip in the documentary about Cameron as like the
greatest producer ever yeah and then it's gonna be a talking head of me and
I'm like yeah he couldn't get out of the studio he's addicted to making music he
was addicted he was absolutely addicted it changed to a bark yeah what the fuck
stupid sounds good though doesn't sound good what are we doing here guys yeah
what the hell are we doing so we just be normal for 10 minutes do a reset we just
fucking okay all right reset okay setting the episode right now yeah the
studio is gone yeah no more studio we're out of this studio my people people were
too passionate about our music people start yeah it's like the Beatles like
yeah fucking teenage girls are killing themselves yeah cuz we're out of the
studio but we had to do it have you ever seen like the footage like that them it
like Shea Stadium and stuff and it's just the teenage girls just screaming. I don't
understand that at all. I mean that's kind of how it was with Justin Bieber. Yeah it
was the same thing with Justin Bieber but it's like... Is there a guy like that now
that just people go crazy for? One Direction, Harry Styles still. Yeah and I guess like K-pop stuff.
Yeah it's K-pop. Yeah it is K-pop. But like the Beatles like you look at those guys and it's just
like they look like normal like they're like like George Harrison was not that
good-looking. They didn't have hot guys back then. Yeah that is true.
They hadn't invented that yet. He got good-looking in the 70s but in like the 60s or like at
least the beginning of the Beatles when he had the bowl cut he did not look good.
Because nobody could afford fucking protein. Everybody was fucking 4 foot 11
and weighed 98 pounds. It is funny like it is funny to look like watch old
movies from like the 80s or 70s and see like when they're like oh here's a like
a strong muscly badass guy and they're all they all just have like have so much
fat on them compared to like what you would see in like a Marvel movie for like the nerd
Marvel movie characters.
It's like the early James Bond's.
Yeah like the one.
Like those like mailmen.
Like fucking Kurt Russell in Escape from New York.
It's so funny because he just got like he just like his arms are just he just has like
you just doesn't look like an action hero.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Well not like in.
Well not like.
And then fucking Arnold changed everything.
Yeah.
He really did.
People were like you can be huge.
Once he started being in movies.
Yeah.
And not just in documentary.
Yeah once he moved the window the Overton window from being like.
for a bit well from being like this guy looks like a scary alien to like oh this
is what a cool superhero looks like yeah yeah I ruined everything yeah beauty
and Sylvester Stallone I think no cuz cuz in Rocky he looked normal he didn't get
big until Rocky for me he didn't get big until the Expendables yeah that's true
first I heard of him yeah yeah the first you heard of her that ever heard of him
yeah I didn't know who Sylvester Stallone was until Guardians of the
galaxy yeah that's cool that's not true it's so funny how just like bad he looks
now cuz I hope like many times he got punched in the face on Rocky I don't
think that's why he looks bad I think do you think that you think he actually got
punched in the face yeah I think he was no what I thought he actually did box
and that was I mean I guess he did boxing but maybe for like six months I
thought he actually did Floyd Mayweather is fucking gorgeous and he's been getting
hit in the face for 30 years. No he's not. Floyd Mayweather's hot dude. I don't think
I've ever seen a picture of Floyd Mayweather. I think, I think, why'd you say no he's not?
I think I was thinking of, I think I was thinking of Conor McGregor. I think Sylvester Stallone
got, I think he got like, he has like, the mouth is like that because of like syphilis
or something. You're thinking of Pink Floyd. Oh I'm thinking of Pink Floyd. You're so dumb.
It's a band. Not good looking guys. No. David Gilmore looks like shit. Yeah they look like
triangle with a rainbow yeah but now I guess it is like kpop which is fine it's
funny those they're like raised like chickens on farms yeah yeah it's insane
what our country did to their country
it's pretty crazy yeah just like well you guys have half of this and the rest
of it we're just gonna like we're gonna do a music yeah we're gonna turn you into
a music farm yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
first yeah it adds another year to your age every like every new year. Well that
means when you're a day old, you two years old. It doesn't change your it
doesn't change your age on your birthday. No what that that's like your
international age, but your Korean age is based on the every year in Korea.
Dude yeah, you go rent a car in Korea did oh my God. I mean everything's gonna
I warn you though everything will be in Korean there so I mean you should become
a kpop star I could learn just so I could be 24 yeah no just because it would be
cool for Patrick to be a kpop star people would love me in Korea yeah you'd
be you'd be like like on all the billboards with the kpop band you'd be
like twice their size yeah ate the last guy that's what they think yeah they
would use me in like anti-smoking propaganda over there. Yeah I don't think
that you'll look like this guy if you smoke. You'll turn white. Yeah you'll just go be the
mucinex booger. Yeah oh my god are you kidding me? Dream job. I'm the
mucinex, I'm like a heartburn commercial star. Yeah exactly it's like if you're Korean
and you eat too much pizza you turn into you until you drink Pepto-Bismol. Yeah
yeah yeah we're like around with fire or you could be like that like the Snickers
you're not you when you're hungry commercials but the Korean guys turn into
you and they turn back to themselves when they eat a Snickers they would love that
yeah I think maybe this is my next venture I think maybe I'm moving to
South Korea yeah I'm doing that yeah yeah I'm gonna send you to North Korea
there's some like weird laws in South Korea right yeah like for example I don't
know if you guys knew this I read about this the other day your age you actually
when you're born you're one years old. And that's a law. I know in
Singapore if you spit on the ground you get the shit kicked out of you by cops.
In Singapore, Anjan told me, because he's from Singapore, he was like yeah if
you smoke weed in Singapore they cut your head off. Yeah. I've heard that crazy
stuff like that. Can you imagine how much shit you get done in
Singapore? No drugs. Yeah. It's kind of a deal. Keep all your spit inside. Yeah, you're
not even allowed to spit dude. You're not allowed to throw it. You have to be productive.
Exactly. Well I can't smoke weed and I can't fucking spit. I guess I'll invent a vaccine.
Yeah. Yeah. But I actually think it's a fascist regime. Is it? I think it might be bad. I
think it's beautiful. You're right, it's probably good the place where they cut your head off
when you smoke weed. Look, I'm not one to judge other cultures. I'm not judging them. I'm
I'm not one to judge other cultures.
I think that they have their own set of rules.
And you know, it's kind of weird for us,
but it works for them.
- Yeah.
- So if you smoke a little bit of weed in Singapore,
you get your head cut off, that's fine.
That's on you.
- That's normal.
- That's your fault.
- Yeah, Anjan just told me like,
you have to be like, like if you wanna do drugs,
you have to be like really fucking cool.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, 'cause I mean just, you have to do--
- Well yeah, they're making drugs cool again over there.
- Yeah, exactly.
We're so fucking pussified here.
- Yeah. - Seattle just made
cocaine legal.
- Yeah. - Like dude,
you're not actually doing cocaine
if there's no threat of you getting your hands
fucking chopped off. - Exactly.
- And put on a necklace. - Mm-hmm.
- And sold to me when I'm a tourist in Singapore.
- I don't even know that much about Singapore.
- I don't think you know, I don't even know, I mean.
- All I know about Singapore is the thing
about spitting on the ground. - Where is it?
Singapore is in Asia.
- The thing about spitting on the ground
and that two of my friends from high school
went to visit it, that's all I know.
- Did they spit on the ground?
I don't think so because they came back and they were injured.
But maybe they made them not tell anybody.
Isn't gum illegal there?
Yeah, so that's, there's something like that too.
Aren't shoes upside down there?
Don't.
Well, no, I heard gum was illegal there.
I think gum is illegal there.
I think there's something about gum.
Cameron backed me up on this.
I didn't, yeah.
You immediately went on the defensive.
I'm not on the defensive.
Don't put your arm around him.
You know how jealous I get.
Me and Patrick are a team now.
You guys are on my black casting couch together and I'm sitting on the chair and I'm going
make you guys fucking do so. You're not gonna make me touch him. I'm gonna make you touch
him. I'm gonna do it by choice. Listen, do you wanna get into modeling for JC Penney?
You better fucking suck his balls right now. I could be a JC Penney model. You could. You
think so? Yeah. You could be the JC Penney model. I could be for their big size stuff.
Yeah. Big sized? Yeah, like their big and tall. I'm into the big size section. Like I was
gonna say big and tall but I feel like saying big and tall is giving me too much credit.
Yeah, I would say so. Yeah, I would say that you're not tall at all.
No. You're not even that big. What, do you wear like a 35 waist? I'm a 38.
38? That's not that big. That's what my dad wears. Yeah, my dad wears it too.
What? My dad and I are the same waist.
Oh my god. I can wear my dad's pants, but he, no, he's taller than me.
Wait, I'm gonna do a new soundboard. Me and my dad are the same size, if you know what I'm talking about.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I'm smaller than my dad. Damn!
[laughter]
[sound of a gun being fired]
So that's when someone does like a sick burn.
My dad is six feet tall and I am five nine.
You got owned by God himself.
I did.
I got height-mogged by my dad.
Yeah.
You got fucked, brother.
Mm-hmm.
That's fucked up, man.
We don't need a metronome.
He's in the fucking studio again.
I'm always on beat.
[sound of a gun being fired]
What did I say about going into the studio while we recorded?
He's back in the fucking studio.
You didn't say anything about it.
- Okay, well right now I'm saying
that it's no longer allowed.
- I'm busy.
- I get it.
- You guys do the episode, I'm busy.
- Listen, we're all talking here,
but we're secretly writing songs in our heads.
- I'm busy, guys.
- We're doing a cover of "Fell in Love with an Alien"
by the Kelly family.
- We're doing Tiggle Bitties.
♪ Fell in love with an alien ♪
♪ Fell in love with his eyes ♪
- You ever heard that song?
- Yeah, I have.
- We're doing a ukulele cover of "Nice Guys Finish Last."
- Yeah, oh my God,
That's what I didn't even fucking think of doing.
- Was that?
(laughing)
- A fucking ukulele cover of Eazy-E songs.
Do you know how fucking funny that would be?
- You know how beast mode that would be?
- You know how funny we would look
if we did a ukulele cover of a rap?
- Dude, I'm saying every word.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I'm hitting every note, every syllable.
- It's getting said by me.
- Cruising down the street in my six four.
- Yeah, exactly, instead of fo, it's four now.
I remember when Wu-Tang Clan posted on their official YouTube channel a video of a white
guy playing guitar and saying "shame on my friend" and he's saying it all.
And all the comments are like "it's so great to see Wu-Tang Clan share this and not get
angry at this guy because we need love between the races."
There's just like every comment on it.
There's just like every one where the white boys can say it all.
And that was it.
Yeah.
where's the Wu-Tang Clan from? I know they're from New York but I know it's
Staten Island. Staten Island. Yeah. Kung Fu. Which is like the white guy saying inward
capital of the world. Yeah. Yeah. So they were just like that's probably their dad.
Yeah. Yeah. There's probably a photo of their dad. They're all brothers.
Yeah. They're nine brothers. Yeah. Yeah. That's why it was his dad.
Yeah. The RZA, the JZA. Old Dirty Bastard. Master Man. Ninja Turtle. God. Yeah. Prince of
evil yeah I said man Easter Bunny yeah yeah yeah the the meticulous player mm-hmm
yeah little shiny neo the strange chef the childish Gambino that's right yeah
that's a better Tony Soprano he got his name childish flying from a Wu-Tang name
generator I do have a baby's brain I knew that - yeah I just didn't say you
I'm an adorable baby's brain. I like that you said that you thought I should
explain this. No I didn't. I should tell them. I think some people wouldn't know the joke.
Okay I'm hungover. You know what? I'm hungover. Yeah we may have cooked our brains a little
too much last night. Music might be all we're capable of now. I know. Oh what a curse.
Oh no. My hands all I can do with them is make beautiful music. Oh God. Baby I know you
want me to do the dishes but I'm gonna make beautiful music with these hands. I'm
sorry I have to go play the piano for 16 hours. Yeah. I'm learning. I'm learning.
Yeah my scalding hot piano. I am learning hot cross buns right now. What if you use like a
really heavy piano. Yeah. Like you trained on that so that when you get on a normal piano
you you're insanely good. That's ingenious. Yeah that's not a bad idea.
yeah and what if you use a really heavy car so that when you use a normal car you
can go really fast what if you use really heavy cream so when you use normal cream
it's the fastest coffee in the world fastest coffee yeah ever drink
damn that's wrong god damn that's a fast cup of coffee
god damn almighty oh Christ oh boy I I drank two I didn't know they were
were coronitas. You said that earlier, what is the problem with a tiny beer? I chugged
two of them while we were walking to get more. Why did you think that was a good move? I
don't know. I think it was just the drinking in public. You were like, that's fun. I was
like, I need this. Excuse me, police officer, I just need this right now. I don't even know,
I just think the drinking out of the brown bag was very fun.
No one noticed or watched you.
No one knew what I was doing.
And I opened the bottles with my teeth, too.
Also really, I mean for somebody who complains about how fucking bad their teeth hurt constantly.
That's insane.
It's chipped.
Oh my god.
It's chipped because I grind it and I've also opened a shit ton of beer bottles with it.
And you were like, I'm gonna do this more.
You're so smart.
know what I'm here for fun I'm not here to do anything smart and it was so fun
drinking those on the street it was I mean dude it's insane I mean being able
to do that again after fucking that means been everything's been locked down the
street has been locked down so to drink on the street you just don't go outside
yeah no I don't go outside and I wanted to drink on the streets drink on the
street still doing you get that beer at a pat yeah yeah we're gonna kill you
yeah we're gonna get you like a pinata we're gonna roll you up starting at the
toes like a toothpaste roll it's not the beer it's that maybe I just need to
drink more okay yeah yeah I'll drink one beer right now take a nap wake up and
I'm golden I'm like the gold you'll feel so good if you drink a beer at noon yeah
You'll feel incredible all day. I mean it's the key to an everlasting life.
You chug one beer at noon.
Then you don't have to chug a beer for another hour.
Mm-hmm. I think I told you guys about this, but in high school my friend Mark,
we were low on beer and Mark took out the blood alcohol calculator on
AlcoholicsAnonymous.org and did the math to see how fat, like he was like,
He was like, "Look, if we just drink four beers in a row
"in under an hour, we'll be at like .8 for the whole night."
- Nice.
- He's like, dude, he fucking gamed how to get us fucked up.
- Nobody ever thought about drinking beer fast.
- Yeah, until your friend.
- Yeah, he was the first one to figure that out.
- Well, nobody did the math.
- He's actually a scientist.
- Yeah.
- He's a food scientist, like Alton Brown.
- He became a scientist.
He fucking gamed that shit.
- That's incredible, dude.
- Yeah, and we did it.
Wow. And it didn't work.
Of course not. You're like hungover.
Right. Like drinking four beers in under an hour.
You just get a stomachache.
Not me, dude. I have an iron stomach.
OK, let's see it. You shat your pants today.
My shits have been horrible since you guys have been here.
I've just been fucking pudding.
You told us before you've had diarrhea every day for like five years.
You can't blame it on us being here.
And somehow it's even worse when you guys are here because I'm just drinking a lot.
And so I'm like, I have like fucking pockets of air.
Like my poops look like sponges.
They're like tortoise.
It's fucked up.
- I've been constipated the whole trip, so.
- Let's get that out of you, dude.
- Oh, let's squeeze it. - I'm gonna suck it out.
- Squeeze me out like the Pillsbury Doughboy.
- I'm gonna suck you out like a noodle.
- They're gonna squeeze me like the Pillsbury Doughboy
get that shit out of me.
- I'm gonna put a straw in your belly button and drink it
and suck the poop out like a siphon into the toilet.
- When I was a boy, when I was very young,
I had an umbilical hernia.
- What?
- And it poked out of my belly button.
I had to get surgery on my belly button.
The what now?
Umbilical hernia.
I know.
Herbie?
Herbie.
Herbie fully umbilically?
Herbie fully hernia.
Herbie fully umbilical.
I don't think so.
Full Herbie.
When you get constipated, do you get like little rocks of shit stuck in your butthole that
you have to dig out with your fingers?
No.
Yeah, me neither.
I know you do.
When I was a kid, I would get constipated and I would get black rocks of shit in my ass
you're like a scientifically mysterious ass like there's just shit going on down
there that I've never heard of yeah I think you did they could study you at
CERN they probably will it could they could put you they could make you put
his poop into the large hadron collider and discover like five new particles
everything this was it this was it this was the material we needed I create
time-travel yeah I think I got a ringworm when I was a kid and never went
away yeah yeah ringworm is in your arm though yeah that's not a ringworm can do
be wherever it's like a skin thing are you thinking of a tapeworm a tapeworm
yeah yeah ringworm is like in your skin okay I believe you guys but I think I
got a tapeworm when I was a kid he never left maybe he's been growing in size and
power and now I think of him like a brother yeah I don't want him to leave
if you had a tapeworm it had a family by now. I'm supposed to get rid of
that dude? A beautiful family? How can I call myself a pro-family
Republican American and not fucking... I mean just get rid of a family living in my body.
I would prefer a ringworm. Dude that'd be horrible. Yeah he's busy he's getting busy. He's on his grind dude.
He's on his grind in my shit. Yeah he's up in my shit and he's grinding. Up in my shit
he's grinding it out yeah he's been working for years I don't I didn't and
then I did you have chicken brain I do that's not my fault yeah I don't need
this you gotta take it you got to take responsibility I gotta take this one for
the team yeah I gotta get up yeah I need you to wake up I need you to stop
lounging no that's a huge stop lounging stop laughing you're saying you have
chicken brain you're in a sleeping position this is not a sleeping position
Tell that to my fucking uncle Rick.
Okay, call him right now.
Alright!
Call him.
I'm gonna call him. No, you know what, I'll see him at Thanksgiving and we'll talk about it.
Get your phone out now.
Man, I fucking hate you.
He one time gave me a brick for Christmas.
A brick?
A brick.
Rick's brick.
He gave me a brick and he gave my brother a bat that he broke.
Yeah?
And he was like, "He'll be worth something one day."
He's mean a lot to me.
I don't know why he gave me a brick. I don't think he ever explained it.
The brick is the foundation of your home.
Do you want to just leave?
Do you want to just, just me and Cam will do, you can go to a water park or something.
You play GarageBand, okay, and me.
You were the one who was playing more of it than me.
What?
I was saying you can play, yeah, but.
Anything to say to yourself?
Wait, wait, queue up the damn.
Do you have anything to say?
Damn.
Okay, wait, Patrick, wait.
You're going to have to say that again, Pat.
I don't remember what I even said.
You accused him of using GarageBand more than you.
You use it more than me.
(Sounds of a battle)
And once again proving my point.
Oh my god. Proved right in front of us dude.
Before our very eyes.
(Sounds of a battle)
Stop remixing this episode while we're in it.
Now he's using it more.
I told you I gave you the chance to use it.
I don't have chicken brain.
I have garage band brain dude.
You guys are clucked.
You know what it is, it's not even chicken brain.
Patrick is just jealous I know how to use garage band better than him.
than him it's just a hang can you just explain your jealousy why are you
jealous of Cameron I'm jealous of Cameron cuz he got one one big wiener and two
tiny balls ideal ratio wiener big ball small the balls look small I'm basically
oh my god these are balls are basically invisible and that wiener too visible
too big yeah like a jumbo shrimp excuse me do you guys have you guys carry pants
for men with humongous penises the drop crotch pants yeah you ever worn those
Yeah, I was a ninja for two years. Yeah, I bought a pair of drop crotch pants by accident. Yeah. Yeah me too
I had drop crotch sweatpants. You thought that they came with the car. I like I'm gonna suck on that I had drop crotch
Chino pants like dress pants. Whoa. Yeah, I thought they were just regular. I thought they were regular dress pants
They weren't even joggers. No, I thought they were regular dress pants. I put them on first of all, they didn't fit
So I had them on even with the drop crotch. Yeah, it's too big
So I was wearing, I put them on and just immediately was like full of regret.
You guys remember when it was cool to dress like a ninja for a little bit?
Yeah. Everybody wearing those fucking... Justin Bieber with the t-shirt dresses and the drop crop pants.
The jot-jot plants and the... What do you mean dress like a ninja?
People would wear those like ninja shoes and the ninja pants. What ninja shoes? Like sandals?
Maybe even a mask. Not sandals. I don't know what you're talking about.
Like a ninja style shoe. Just explain it to me.
I don't remember.
The Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles wear sandals.
Well, some ninja they turned out to be.
Well, the other ones wear sandals.
The Foot Clan?
No, the other ninjas.
That aren't turtles.
Who are you fucking...
You are being so confusing right now.
Anyway, the ninja shoes...
Yeah.
Okay, the kind of shoes you would run up a wall with.
What?
So sticky shoes.
Yes.
So people wearing sticky shoes and drop crotch pants and fucking blouses.
Do ninjas wear blouses?
Beautiful ones too.
Do they have like masks?
Why would you want to hide that face?
What face?
Ninja face.
What are you talking about?
Beautiful ninja face.
Now it's cool to dress like Tyler Ninja Blevins.
That's true.
Whenever I do a What Celebrity Do You Look Like?
I get ninja.
Really?
Yeah.
I don't think you look like a ninja.
Ninja and Priyanka Chopra.
Ninja has much worse skin than you.
He for some reason upgraded his camera and it's just like horrifying dude.
Yeah.
You watch Ninja?
He looks like the Nasty Patty.
Sometimes.
He plays Valorant now.
I raided Ninja a couple times.
Yeah, you raided him 10 out of 10.
Ninja doesn't respond to anybody but donators.
Yeah dude, he's a pussy.
Yeah.
He's not a real streamer.
No, Ninja's not a real streamer.
I can't wait till we overtake him.
Yeah.
Ninja?
Look, we're calling you versus Caleb and Valorant.
notice did me versus you in Valorant me versus Hassan in politics me versus
there's another streamer AOC and me there's a fucking big-ass fucking titties
dude me versus Jubio you versus Jubio versus Patrick and me versus Bowser you
think you would beat you actually would be Jubio and being Mexican yeah yeah
he's like the least Mexican Mexican dude in the world okay yeah well then it's a
challenge it's gonna be a close race yeah just do it's just a trivia thing but
it's all in Spanish yeah no it's all it's like trivia about like the three
amigos who is the more Mexican guy you or Juvio you or a guy named Juvio
Patrick or who bill who bill you bought a ballist what a buddy's probably stay
- Yeah, my mom is coming here.
- Really soon.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, he teases me.
He says, "I am going to buy a flight."
And then he just doesn't.
And he says, "Hey, I look at the flight, it's too expensive."
- Yeah, you fucking poor bitch.
- You should pay for him to come out.
- Yeah, fly him out.
- Shh.
- What about a crack rock?
- Don't give him any ideas.
- What?
- Get a crack rock in his wall.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Why are you taking his wall?
- We should get some cocaine and wake ourselves up.
Patrick just reached into Caleb's wall and pulled out a piece of rock.
I'm fixing it for him.
I got a new, I got a guy to buy cocaine from and he insists that I make up a fake name
and use it.
So I don't know, what should I say?
What should I say my name is?
Well, Jorge Acosta.
That's true, yeah.
That's the fake name we have to use for everything.
So all the drug dealers in New York use an app called Signal, which is like WhatsApp.
Oh yeah, that's the like drug dealers. That's the one that communists use so that the police
don't see them saying, "I'm gonna have sex with a policeman's wife." Yeah, saying, "I love Naruto."
Cool, dude. I'm glad you hid that from the cops. Yeah. But yeah, I have to come up with a fake
name. Probably will use Jorge Acosta. Yeah. Yeah, and then just show up and be like, "You gotta
cut back with the cocaine." "Cocaine? No." Okay, all right, then you got me.
The easiest intervention ever.
Dad, you have to stop fucking huffing paint. I don't think I will. I don't think so.
I have to go outside. Yeah, you're grounded. Yeah. Yeah, you're grounded. Yeah. I feel like I'm more nervous.
I would never do cocaine in New Hampshire. No, that's a bad idea. Yeah. Yeah, everything there's cut with fent. Yeah, even weed.
Dude, even water. Yeah, you can't even get a fucking Dasani bottle without being worried. You got to test everything.
I test a handshake in New Hampshire.
I test a kiss from my mommy in New Hampshire.
You have to.
Yeah, I'm testing fucking...
I'm testing...
I'm testing saying hello.
Hi.
I'm testing my brother with gay chicken.
It's just a test, Dan.
It's not real.
Yeah, chill.
It's a game.
Pop quiz.
Yeah, pop quiz and then gay chicken.
quiz I don't I need to cut forward I need to start doing more drugs I need to
start smoking more nicotine I think your apartment's on fire
I need to drink more. I need more. I need to drink way less. Way less you say? I drank like 13 beers on
Halloween I was just by myself you always count how many beers you drink
Well, and then next you're like, oh my god, I drink exactly 12 beers. I count them the morning after
That's it. Then you're never right. Yeah, that's true. Yeah, you drink 50 beers on Halloween probably I
just remember
Now you count them as you go because you join a discord call and you tell me how many you've had so far
That's true. I do count them as I go
Well, it's because they're right next to me. The empties are right next to me. That's then you're just counting count the body
- Yeah, he starts every time he drinks one,
he starts the count over again.
He drinks his sixth beer and he goes,
one, two--
- You count like the fucking owl
from the Tootsie Pop commercial.
- One, two--
- Three.
- A three.
- How many beers did you have, Pat?
- Yeah.
- Shut up, you owl motherfucker.
- Yeah, I think I gotta do a whole month's of--
- Is your mic off or are you just really quiet?
- I think I'm just really quiet.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
a whole month not drinking. A month of not drinking? Yeah. It's honestly pretty easy. Yeah, but then you just get...
The first week you're like, "What the hell? What am I doing?" Yeah. By like two weeks in
you're like... That's the thing, I always go... You should call it a seltzer, it's easy. I always go a week. One week won't do
nothing for you. One week and then I'm like, "Why do I feel like shit? I should
just get some beer. I should just start drinking again." Yeah, dude, it's epic. Yeah. Yeah, I think
September I didn't drink anything. Yeah. Or October, one of those two. No, it was in
October, September. I did a lot of other stuff. Come on man, you think I'm not
gonna party? Come on. I think you shouldn't party. I think I should party
harder. Yeah? Yeah. Well, you've sold me. I think it'd be pretty funny if I died of
drugs. Yeah? Yeah. It'd be hilarious. It'd be pretty funny. It'd be so funny for me and Cameron. I mean
yeah, it would be pretty funny for you guys. Yeah, just having to do this on episodes
where you have chicken brain yeah and it's like oh it's just you guys whining
and making beats back and forth I don't have chicken brain well stop touching
the I'm not touching anything I can see that shit I can see your beak right now
brother you're reaching for a piece of chicken I finished my chicken friend
instead what instead of a chicken instead of reaching for a piece of
chicken reach for your friend that's dead reach for your friend's hands reach
for your friends parts of your friend's body I'm fucking serious if you flirt
with Patrick in my house again that it doesn't it looks like you're trying to
control his penis like a puppet master stop we should do that we should put
dental floss on your balls pretend call them around yeah
- Ja penis. - Ja penis.
- Pinocchio. - Pinocchio.
You become a real penis.
Oh, come over here. I'm gonna make your penis real.
- And then his penis gets swallowed by a whale, if you know what I'm saying. - Yeah.
- His wife. - Yeah, your mom.
- What? - It's just like uncalled for.
Your mom's a fucking whale. A fat stupid bitch.
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na.
Sorry, what the hell sometimes I slip in a battle rhyme mode
To do after a line
Couldn't even put another word at the end of it welcoming you to the jungle nothing rhymes with bitch is like orange
Yeah, yeah, yeah rich couldn't even say I should have said rich. Let me try again
Well a stupid fat bitch if she was made of money, then you'd be rich
(mimics beatboxing)
- Dude, this is a music-themed episode.
- This is the musical episode.
- We were gonna make a beat, and then that didn't happen.
- We did make a beat, and then you made a fucking beak,
you chicken-brained moron.
- Patrick, make a beat.
(beatboxing)
- I heard that.
You made a beat like a baby.
(beatboxing)
Have you ever heard that song, Jordi, "It's Hard to Be a Baby"?
No.
It's one of the, like these French parents like exploited their kid and made him make
a house song.
Okay.
Or they made, I think they were like music musicians and they made a house song.
They're music musicians.
They had their kid sing in French, "It's Hard to Be a Baby."
then they made like a music video and then they had him on like TV shows and
everything and they were going on tours and stuff and I think the French
government stepped in we're like yeah you're exploiting your kid and he was
like well I want to do it I think turning your kid into a musical act is
like the the swaggiest kind of abuse yeah yeah right like Michael Jackson's
dad yeah didn't he like make them maybe a shit out of yeah but I might be I might
be misremembering this but I remember some story about like if they if they didn't
sing well they had to all the kids had to go pack themselves into the fireplace and
sing from there yeah I didn't have to like squeeze themselves into the
fireplace and then just and practice singing in the fireplace Matilda yeah it
is like Matilda yeah that's exactly like Matilda yeah yeah except no except the
magic was the magic was Michael's voice magic was Michael's beautiful voice and
his mind control I can't imagine being Michael Jackson yeah tell me what would
be different about your life if you're Michael Jackson Michael Jackson I would
first of all I wouldn't hang my kid from that freaking balcony he didn't I watched
that video who that was nothing dude that was not he didn't hang the kid he
was hanging the kid to show off yeah shoes he was hanging the kid to show off
how cool his kid was and the fact that he could fly. My kid could levitate!
Watch this I'm letting go at three! Yeah but what else would be different I would
be friends I would have been friends with Conrad Murray hello. I mean if I if you
could live his life and change one thing it would be a baby thing. No I'd probably
as a child I'd stand up to my dad and say no. I bet that would have worked out
great no dad I don't want to be a singer I want to be Peter Pan for the rest of my
life yeah yeah he would have fucking yeah if he wasn't what I hate you with a car
if he wasn't a singer and he was just a pedophile instead you didn't have the
music true that's what Patrick wants no Patrick wants to be a white pedophile
first Michael Jackson might be the first pedophile with a diglio so I don't think
ever confirmed that he had vitiligo? Oh, it's vitiligo? Yeah, or vitiligo. Vitiligo, who
knows. Yeah, I mean that's also true. Yeah, nobody knows if he had vitiligo. Yeah, vertigo.
No one knows if he even likes vitacoco. He got so dizzy he became white. He had vertigo,
dude. Yeah. Yeah, I mean, do you guys think maybe they replaced him with a different guy?
If there was ever a guy that you could make that case for, it'd be him. Yeah, that's true.
the stuff where people are like oh they replaced this guy because he lost weight
like that's compared to yeah compared to like Michael Jackson I think Michael
Jackson is the argument for that one Jonah Hill they definitely replaced Jonah
Hill they didn't replace yeah they replaced him with that guy from Star
Trek who died because he got hit by a time the ocean yeah that's the new Jonah
Hill yeah yeah I like you Anton Yelchin he's cool but you gotta think about but
you killed him anyway but why'd you kill it was an accident sure yeah I thought
that the drive shift was the SiriusXM button. Yeah. I was trying to listen to Opie.
Yeah, well. I was trying to listen to XL Sam and Jim. Anton was checking his mail and you yeah you got in his car.
That's so crazy how he died. Yeah, it's insane dude. Yeah. It's like a final destination death.
Yeah, no it really is. Yeah. Pat was in the car when it happened and he saw him
getting pinned and he tried to, he tried to, he turned on the car to try to
drive away to unpin him. He had it in reverse. Did I ever show you guys my kiss costume when I was 11?
I was Gene Simmons. I think so. Is that the picture of you with the face paint? No that was after.
That's me that's me trying to get the face paint off. That was something different. Yeah that was
Michael Jackson for Halloween. It was MJ, Michael Jordan for Halloween. What is the line where
Could you go as today Michael, or as like 2003 Michael Jackson for Halloween?
You could go as anything.
But would that be okay, you think?
People go as Hitler.
That's also true.
Do they?
Yeah.
People do do Hitler.
I do think that maybe is the funniest Halloween costume.
Yeah.
It's just like, I'm Hitler.
I'm the scariest thing I can think of.
What are you talking about? Of course I'm Hitler.
Yeah.
That's a pretty good fucking--
That's Gene Simmons if I've ever seen one.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
That's right.
I'm going as Gene Simmons.
I'm Gene Simmons.
But yeah, going as Hitler, I think you, yeah, it's like, what's, I mean, you think a skeleton
is scary.
Wait till you see.
Yeah, wait till you see the guy who made it.
Wait till you see what's over the skeleton.
Yeah, it's Adolf Hitler's skin and clothes.
Oh, I think Hitler.
Going as a skeleton, be like, I'm Hitler's skeleton.
Yeah, that would be so funny to be in the middle of a haunted house and it's like a
A guy with a chainsaw, and like Freddy Krueger, and Hitler's on the stairs.
He's on the stairs drinking tea.
Yeah.
Hey.
Ha.
Hello.
Oh my god, I didn't, I forgot to clean up in here.
Oh, it's so embarrassing.
Yeah, that was pretty crazy.
God damn, you're scary and polite.
They had, they had Texas Chainsaw Guy, they had Freddy Krueger, and I don't, Hitler was like embarrassed that...
I think they had, I think they had...
- They had Shy Hitler in there maybe?
- Oh, don't look at me!
- Oh, oh!
- I am indecent!
- Let me slip into something a little more comfortable.
- What if you walked in, what if you went into the haunted house and you saw Hitler sitting on the stairs,
you went, "Oh!" and he just threw a sheet over himself like a ghost?
- Hey, Hitler, I know that's you.
- Hey, you can't fool me anymore.
- Hey, Hitler, I have a feeling that's you.
- This is not me, I'm actually the ghost!
That's not gonna work on me Hitler. I know that's you. Yeah it's like it's like the
ET ride at Universal if you find Harry Potter in the in the background. I don't
know about enough about Universal. That joke is for two people. Yeah, ET and Harry
Potter. What is the what is in the ET ride they put a secret Harry Potter
in the woods a secret Harry Potter in the woods it's an Easter egg for the fans of
Harry Potter and E.T. okay a secret Harry Potter you've never seen the E.T. ride
no I don't look that was too scary no no that's the alien one the E.T. ride is E.T.
is needs to go back to his home planet to fix it what else is fucking new yeah
fucking idiot fucking only loves one thing you ever thought about just eating
lunch eating well he has to go home and fix his home planet with his touch and
like his planet is full of like plant people yeah yeah well and then et says
your name at the end of the ride that voice of pussy does he know your name
you give them your name at the beginning of the ride does that mean that and then
at the end he goes like goodbye bad drink
Patrick! They programmed like a bunch of voices into the ET thing.
Oh yeah I'm going on there and I'm saying my name is Hillary Clinton so ET will thank me.
Goodbye Hitler. He says thank you. Thank you.
I'd be so pissed off. Right? I'd be like it's clear that I'm the one who wrote that.
He says it to me. I'm like did anybody hear this? Jesus Christ! Who let that happen?
First of all, we have to find Hitler. He's somewhere in the line.
He's hiding!
Maybe he's with Harry Potter.
Show me where he is!
Hitler is on this ride.
At the end of the E.T. movie, right before he goes back, he looks at Ellie and he goes,
"Thank you, Hitler."
They're like, "Who taught him that?"
"What the hell?"
Is Caleb standing in the background?
That's the thing, is like, if E.T. was real, you'd treat him like a younger cousin or something.
Yeah, yeah.
Teach him curse words and shit.
Hey, hey, guess what, E.T.?
That's what they did.
ice cream truck only plays music when they're out of ice cream. Oh, is that true? Oh, no.
Yeah, dude, it's seriously true. Oh, no. Yeah, ET, if you jump off the roof of the house,
you actually won't get hurt. You can fly. Yeah. Hey, ET, you want to see me go run to
that rocking bed? I could fly. Hey, ET, you want to see me do that again? Hey, ET, if
you go in the blender, it's safe. ET, put your finger in the blender. Hey, ET, I got
this gun that fires backwards. Aim it at your head and shoot that tree. Yeah, I would. I
If I saw E.T. I think I would kill him on sight.
I think I'd fucking blow his brains out, dude.
I would hit him right down on the middle of the head with a crowbar.
Just right down the middle.
I would cut him in half.
He'd probably get squished like a Cordy in style.
His neck would just fold into itself and he'd go "Aww."
Whoops.
You know what I've seen more than E.T. is Mac and Me.
I've never seen Mac and Me.
Mac and Me sucks.
Let me tell you what.
Mac and Me is like one of the worst movies of all time.
Yes.
yes same with like troll 2 dude paul you're killing it you guys are not gonna believe the room oh my
god it's like the best worst movie yeah when that guy says something that when that guy says
something this freak alien an alien would never say that yeah yeah an alien three movies about
aliens the room mac and me and et let's go yes is tommy wiso doing anything now um i think he said
He was gonna kill you. He said he was gonna kill you.
Is that true? Are you serious? Yes.
Wait. He said, "I'm fed up with Caleb." Why?
"I'm fed up with Caleb." I'm normal. "I'm going to kill Caleb."
From what reason? Probably your attitude. I have a
good attitude. I don't know, dude. You know what's really cool about him is he wears
two belts.
He wears two belts? He wears one belt in the loops and then he wears one like
around his ass. Like he wears like one-
Every time?
Yeah. Like if you look up pictures of like Tommy Wiseau's belts,
he's got like one belt. Like he looks like- he dresses like a Kingdom Hearts character.
I mean everybody has to have one stylistic thing.
Me, I shit in my pants a lot of the time.
I read the Disaster Artist and Greg Sestero explains that
he said, uh, Tommy Wiseau, like he asked him about it and Tommy Wiseau just went,
"Makes my ass look nice."
[laughter]
Like covering it up with a belt?
by making it like lifting it up with another belt.
- I'm gonna start wearing a WWE belt.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- That's cool.
- People will be like,
people won't fuck with you if you wear a WWE belt.
- Like a heavy one or a real one?
- Like the, well at first I have to earn it.
- Yeah. - In the ring.
In the rink.
- The rink. - Yeah.
- The WWE rink. - The WWE rink.
But then, 'cause it's all acting anyway,
so a guy like me could conceivably be a WWE champion.
- What was that, there was like a couple months ago,
there was like some guy he was like a local wrestler or whatever and he was a
heel but his whole heel thing was that he was like all right and he came out
with like a swastika flag or something and his students found it. Oh is he like
the liberal Democrat? I don't know. Well that was the guy that was a that was a
dude who was in like the local like like Tennessee circuit whose whole thing was
he would come out and be like Obama's awesome and then people be like fuck you
"Kill him!" and he like won a couple and people went crazy for him. That's a really good.
Yeah I watched I was watching a movie where there was there was a wrestler in
it named Jimmy Hitler and he just dressed like Hitler. Damn. There's no way.
It's called a movie called a Blood Diner. It was a GLOW and it was
Mark Barron. Yeah. I think I'm gonna beat Hitler and you girls are gonna beat me up.
Alright I'm who are you Hitler who are your guys? I think what I'm gonna do is
Hitler and you girls are just gonna beat up my balls. And that's gonna be... you
girls... I mean you're just gonna take a fucking whiffle bat to my balls. Oh you're just gonna just...
And yeah, I'm Hitler. Yeah and I'm dressed up like Hitler the whole time. Okay let's do
this. Mark, you're not directing the show. What the fuck? Oh what the... that's my catchphrase.
Sorry I gotta say it. I gotta say it once per episode. It'd be good if Hitler
did a kind of a WTF style podcast where he was kind of apologizing to the
people who need to who are you younger that's right wait no hold on wait no no
we need to get the German right yeah German would be man yeah they I think
German if we're speaking German it's like bomboclat why they long penis man
it's like they say bomboclat they say like pond the floor they say big up one
love they love zion well except for hitler i guess yeah yeah yeah hitler hated zion yeah he's not
excited about it making hitler can we just stop yeah it's too far
that's just too much dude yeah it's over the line yeah making hitler yeah what is so so what are we
always sunny in philadelphia come on we can't be doing that kind of thing why not let's see
yeah he has like dreads and stuff no thank you I mean what would that even
sound yeah you guys dreads you smoking weed and what yeah I mean like what
would that even what what what kind of shit what kind of just stop there thing
would eat yeah let's stop yeah we've been talking about Hitler too much
Pat always says that like you can go to jail for talking about Hitler yeah I feel
like people I don't know I feel like after 2016 people stopped liking Hitler
jokes damn this is this is the other day before it sounds now
you just left it in your pocket and it added a bunch of effects - yeah there we
we go. That's classic dude. Oh yeah. Yeah, that was like when I'm when I used to
make runescape videos when I was a kid, I would pitch my voice down to make it
sound like I was an adult, but yeah, yeah, hey, what's up guys? Welcome back.
It's pretty cool. Yeah, there's nothing more to meaning when then when you like
look up how to like a tutorial and how to like do something on a computer and it's
just a kid is like, hey guys, today I'm going to do it's like, oh, this fucking
yeah, this fucking kid knows how to do this and I don't. Yeah, I might as well
I remember one time being like with my older brother.
Especially when it's something, it's how to pirate something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh yeah.
I remember being with my older brother and saying my order for Taco Bell in the drive
through and them saying, "Yes ma'am, sounds great."
And dude, I couldn't even eat.
I was so sick to my stomach.
Yeah.
You think I have a girl's voice?
You do.
You think, really?
You really think I have a girl's voice?
I never got confused for a girl on the phone.
I love Mexican pizza.
Yeah, I would like it.
Yeah, let me get a gorgina, Grangop.
You think I can get a gorgina, Supreme?
Let me get a little bit of this here.
People forget about that.
Yeah.
No, she doesn't sound like a whale.
Oh, a good whale.
Birds flying high, you know how I feel.
Michael Poopley wrote that song.
Alright, bye guys.
Did we finish it?
Yeah we did.
Alright.
Because when I arrive, I bring the fire made to come.
Oh yeah, I'll come down and take you higher with the steel.
Oh God, I just wanna remind you let it rock, let it rock, let it rock.
Let it rock, let it rock, let it rock.
I just wanna remind you, let it rock, let it rock, let it rock