You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[LAUGHTER]
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
Now is how we're starting.
OK, Jai.
I know now you're recording now.
--you were talking about.
Hi, welcome to podcast about lust and seeking something.
I don't know.
OK, I'm going to tell you right now, Jaak,
we have guests, please remember the mic goes next to your mouth.
Since you destroyed the mic stand you built last episode.
We should give Jacques like a dog cone around their lips that they like
have to keep the microphone.
Yeah, I put like a laugh mic on there.
Yeah, that'd be pretty smart.
Yeah, we're doing doing Gaze versus Straights Volume three.
I'm pretty focused today.
I'm going to keep this on top.
I'm going to keep this sucker right next to my mouth.
I think he's turning the mic right now.
Yeah, this is gays versus straights.
I have to bring my guitar back out.
No, no, no. You don't use that yet.
That's our secret weapon.
That is our fucking WMD, dude.
Don't fucking take that out. Don't you dare.
They're going to leave immediately.
I don't want to win.
I want to have a fair fight until the shock and jock can bring out his DJ.
We would destroy your ass and I will.
I will leave right now.
We would be you guys.
If you start DJing, probably all gay guys are over six feet tall and we're all...
[laughter]
Wait, Caleb, I always assumed you were at least 6'7" or something like that.
That... if I was 6'7" I would be in jail.
You can't be this bald and ugly at 6'7", dude.
How is that something you assume, Jacques?
Why would you assume that? What about Caleb conveys that to you?
Um, there's just a certain je ne sais quoi about the way that he...
they're speaking cajun
speaking cajun off of that cajun bullshit
no, Caleb acts like a short guy
I'm not short, I'm definitely normal
no, you're short
hey guys, I'm not short, I'm normal
um, no, I'm
hey guys, I'm normal, I'm actually short
no, I am normal
I'm the tallest guy I know
I'm not a little squeaky mouse
and 5'9"
who's the shortest here?
it's either me or Pat, we've never figured out, we don't wanna find out
did figure this out. We did not. Jana measured us in your apartment. We're the
same height. We're the same exact height. That makes sense to me. I would say maybe
maybe Patrick's got an inch or two. No come on. He's fucking serious right now.
I'm the tallest one in my team. Imagine Jana measuring you guys back to back and there's like a clear
like one inch difference. She's like, "Yeah you guys are the same height!"
She's a ride or die dude.
She's like cradling Cabe like a baby.
Yeah.
Uh yeah, no we're the same.
Yo, you're the same height as Patrick, Caleb.
Don't let them tell you otherwise.
I always assumed Max is pretty tall.
Max is the shortest of the group.
I'm 5'10.
Shortest in Jacques?
Jacques is a normal height.
Jacques is 5'11 right Jacques?
not that terrifies me
jock is not 5'11"
I always assumed jock was like
5'2"
jock being 6'3" he would have been assassinated
I always assumed jock was
like just a little too powerful
now that is really
scaring me now, imagine jock being
taller than me
have you seen fright night 2?
where like the vampire
like rollerblades through the high school or whatever
yes
I would have bet Jacques was any taller.
It's just like a vampire from...
Wait, okay, wait. Jacques...
Jacques had his roller... I didn't know this, and I haven't talked to Jacques about this,
but Jacques, you had your roller skates stolen from you.
Oh my god.
What? And this turns into, like,
you have a GPS tracker in your roller skates?
Did you get, like...
I just want to get answers.
I forgot about...
Wait, tell this story because I literally...
It's court ordered, uh, Jock got pinched, uh, for roller skating while drunk.
And the court put in like one of those, uh, a blow thing.
A tube on like the heel.
His dab, his dab, uh, volume per blood amount or whatever before he can get to his roller
skates.
How much being he's had in one day.
It's a pretty wholesome amount.
It's a pretty wholesome story.
Okay.
This is what happened.
Is it a wholesome story?
Stole it
Jax rollers. Oh, I don't I don't know. I thought maybe you got pulled over and they like suspended your library card
I'm gonna tell you all right now if the cops ever get my roller skates. There's gonna be dead cops
*laughter*
I will kill the poor white dweller on their ass.
I will kill them.
So, um...
Hold on, hold on. If the cops didn't get your roller skates, you can just buy another pair of roller skates.
I don't think it's that hard.
Yeah, steal them from some other child.
Well, no, I mean, I'm getting my pair back.
They're sentimental.
My pair is... they're not even sentimental.
I just want to kill a cop.
But I want to kill a cop.
I do not want to go to jail again.
I spent enough time there when I was 17.
I think you probably do need to spend more time in jail.
I don't know if you were exactly rehabilitated.
I am definitely a rehabilitated criminal.
and
your own keys? Because I lose shit so often, my wallet and stuff. I just started, I got
this like literally- So you're just GPS tracking like every single one of them? Yeah, just like
leftovers, just throwing a square on it. I'm already losing things all the time and now
that I've been introduced to a certain Mexican anxiety relief medication, I have just- You
I've just I've said that like we're supposed to know what you mean.
Yeah, I've become a is that what you call Max?
Yeah.
Well, no, no, no.
But anyway, I've been a little bit more forgetful than normal.
And so I look at the tracker.
I'm like, okay, I took okay.
Wait, tell who how did your roller skates get stolen?
Well, where were you?
I was at the roller.
I was at the roller rink, cancel me, and I'm skating.
Wait, why would you be? Oh, because you're you're not quarantining.
Yeah. No one's going to cancel you for that.
Don't worry about it.
I mean, there's no way you were not the only person.
I bring a baseball bat with me, so if they try to get close to me,
I just push the baseball bat toward you.
You just dressed like Marshall Barley.
I'm a roller skating rink.
So, um, six year old girl who is like three feet away from
John.
It's her the phase of the I took my skates off out to go
outside to smoke a blunt and I put my shoes on.
I left my skates on and when I came back my skates were
gone and I was like, what'd you do?
How did you react?
I was like, okay.
Well, someone's got my fucking skates.
The staff is like all 16 year olds with learning disabilities.
So they're incapable of helping me in any way possible.
Like the stat the owner.
What is this roller rate?
Is that like the theme skate City in Arvada?
No, they're just box.
No, those were eight City in Arvada and the owner at the owner
The manager is like a 5'4" gay Office Depot looking twink.
What? I didn't know there were Office Depot gays.
Is this really that confusing?
Yes it is.
He's a twink, but he looks like he works at Office Depot.
But he works at a roller rink.
He had a red shirt on.
(laughing)
- The office depot.
- So anyway, I'm like complaining,
I'm like look someone took my skates,
they're like look we can review the footage tomorrow.
I'm like fuck reviewing the footage tomorrow.
I'm like let's--
- I'm gonna kill some cops.
- I'm gonna kill some cocks, I'm gonna kill some cops,
I'm gonna do something fucked up
if I don't get my goddamn skates.
And I'm like, and I'm like if you don't tell that
ugly 40 year old mother fucker who keeps spinning in circles in the middle of the roller rink
to put his mask on. I will personally. That's going to be you. Trip him again. He's just
looking in a mirror. If you don't tell me I'm going to make a whole snack club look
like a motherfucking kindergarten. Also the story is really starting to come together in
my head as why my skates were stolen.
Before the skates were stolen, this guy kept skating too close to me and so I just kicked
him as hard as I could.
He fell and he rolled.
It was adult night, so I thought it was okay.
You're just putting this together now?
the
I knocked him over and he deserved it but
No, I mean I just did it really quickly it was a hit and run kind of situation
Late later in the night later in the night I go to
Later the employees don't help you you don't see the security footage
Decide to leave no, no, I don't leave I look at the app and I'm like, okay
What app
I see that that wherever my roller skates are they're still in the parking lot. I'm like
GPS tracker
Yeah, I knew some shit was gonna go down once I started it's like
Inspector gadget or what?
You kicked that guy and then put the GPS tracker onto the skates right now.
Anyway, I see the guy loading in the back of his car, he's putting some other stuff, and my skates are right next to his wheel.
And I say, "STOP! WHAT?!"
And he just starts running.
What did the guy look like? Can we get a physical description?
Okay, literally red hoodie
Pete Davidson
Fuck dude, I know these were your skates. I'm so sorry
Some gay monster
Fuck
Enough anxiety medication to let this situation
Mike Mike. Oh, yeah. I love Mike which Mike which Mike is your favorite?
I found hold it off. Oh, I will hold a microphone to your mouth
please
What kind of
Abuse we have to hold up to it like so every single time we record
So you chase?
person
finish the story
Jacques has cancelled for this
well I grabbed my skates and I just went back to my roommates car
wait so the guy ran and just left his car just open?
yes
maybe he was trying to steal the car too
maybe it wasn't
Jacques was literally on so much Xanax
this is a story of him stealing someone else's skate
yeah running out of the car
he invented a napkin in his head
was like this absolutely barred out on mexicans and i think it's like you might
see what what back
the while the other
uh... yeah i think that it was uh... instead of looking like he gave us a
mispronouncement like i don't know i would like to know
yeah yeah it or or or was a person girl from asana
can i just i don't have a drug
he he was just as i'd rather have a reserve record
he was just as carlisle jones
he was just as cocky as pete davidson
uh... to and that's why i can tell
davidson isn't cocky
he can't even be cocky
he can barely roll out of bed every morning like the only thing he does for fun
is like get shitty tattoos of like
hillary clinton and her pussy
and like uh... the auschwitz tattoos that uh...
i think i got the auschwitz tattoo that all the uh... like warren steffers got
like after she lost
the
a
and
is
like kill a bug is exhausted dude okay I went to five below today which I don't
know if you know what that's where you live it's a scary place it's not
somewhere you want to end up it's a haunted house I thought we're the first
angel mommy video was shot I mean I had to chew to Ambien just to walk into the
store I mean come on why would you it is a crazy store I mean it feels very my
My friend Kirstie wanted to meet me. She's a craft.
You know, she likes like fake mustache humor and things like that,
or not even.
Is she random too?
She's so random. Anyway, this, I go to this store,
I just filled up a basket. Um, I scanned one single item,
which was an eraser.
And then I got like five bags of those pretzel Buffalo's chips and
six canvases and then just walked out with everything.
Yeah, that's like a pretty easy store to steal from.
I think I feel like every store is asking for it.
If you have a self check out self check out is like it's so
easy. I got free groceries for years through self check out
because I'm just bringing everything in as a potato. Yeah,
when I was in Boston, I never bought cheese just for the road
in the bag did it's so easy to steal that I can bring you
you bring your own tote bag to the store and then you can
just throw every other item in the bag.
- I took 15 cases of La Croix at once last week.
- A what?
- A 15 cases?
- 15 cases?
- You took a pallet of fucking-
- 15?
(laughing)
- La Croix?
- I put 15 at the bottom of the grocery cart.
- Were you operating a forklift?
(laughing)
- No, no, no, no.
- Just, it's a potato.
Just scan it.
(laughing)
This is a potato.
- Yeah, we see the-
- Oh, okay, okay.
i think it's a bit bigger ones like yeah that's not okay
hi either way if you know if you know what to do it's still a lot that's like
a hundred
yes i can
not many times
i think them all
now have
maybe a few left i have a copy of the israeli
out of the fifty-nine so and i think it gave me a kidney stone
it's water
this year's war is carbonated though it's got it's got stones in it
Something is a kidney stone and I don't know what it is, but
Is it the bean?
I love that a kidney, like people are like, oh, I feel a cold coming on or,
you know, I feel like I might get a fever, but for you, you've had so many kidney stones
that you're like, yeah, I'm probably going to get a kidney stone. I can feel one coming on.
No, if you really want to hear something funny is that I had my
procedure to have my kidney stone pulverized pushed back from today.
Is that what you just hit on your heart?
So tomorrow, because I
trying to crush something.
Yeah, I just don't.
It is a short dish.
No, it's mad.
But no, seriously.
Yeah, I thought that we were going to do this little recording ditto
on Tuesday.
So I'm like, yeah, we could get my kidney stone pulverized today.
No problem.
What is that?
What they call it?
Is it you making a point for pulverization?
I'm going to pulverize that kidney stone boy.
I call the doctor, you know, Dr. Piper.
What a cartoon character.
Yeah, he works at Piper's Pulverization.
At some point the bar for me to like stop Jack while telling a
story is so high.
You know, it's like Dr. Piper.
You talk to the doctor and you're like, I need this kidney stone
removed and they're like, oh, we can't do that, but we can pulverize
it if you want.
I told him I lost my full bottle of steroids,
so I'm going to get more steroids to take so I could just, you know, whatever.
I'm going to get this kidney stone
UTI thing zapped, get it removed.
I'm going to get them to put a saline solution bag in me.
In you? IV.
Oh, in me.
Since I have health care, you guys could just put that in my ass for free, right?
If I bring you something you guys have to put it in my ass.
And I'm gonna bring my anxiety medication that they gave me and I'm gonna chew it in front of them and I'm gonna say look I'm not anxious, I'm anxious still it doesn't work.
And they're gonna give me a better prescription.
That's definitely how that works.
They're not taking it in front of you, institutionalize you or call the police.
Oh my god, no, these people were friends. They know these games I play.
Why do you think, what has led to your kidney stone?
You're talking about your doctor.
Oh fuck, Shaq's coming back to play some games with us.
He's gonna chew a bunch of pills in front of us and demand we give him a stronger dose.
Hey, can you put this sandwich in my stomach?
This reminds me of my friend, this is a horrible story.
like 14 or 15 we would go and hang out with my friends
pilled out like white wine Xanax mom just to get
fucked up with her even though our friend wasn't there like we would go and hang out with her
mom to 14 15 year olds.
That's yeah. Yeah, and I and we would and I would start getting undressed starting to be like I'm getting
naked. If you don't give me if you don't give me pills right now, I'm going to get naked.
You would do that. You would do that to your friends mom. Yeah, and she'd be like, okay,
Okay, okay, fine.
Well, and then she would get fucked up with us and she would put on music videos on Cox
direct or Cox cable and then she'd be like, I've been practicing a dance for them.
And this woman is not attractive.
She's not a good dancer.
She is not someone you want.
And she would get in front of the TV and kind of like start dancing and she goes, whoops,
and pulls out her nipple.
No
Hide of music videos
Me and then show me your asshole
Doc's friend lived in Carcosa for a long time
Just boyhood friends with the yellow king. Oh don't get naked. I have to turn on the sucker free countdown
It just goes to show you that we all grew up a little differently we that is definitely true
Say I never had any friend's mother do a nip tease.
No, that was a dream, but it never happened for me.
I would have scared me when any of my friends would knock on
my family's house's door.
My dad would answer and they'd be like, Yeah, I'm Jacques friend.
And he'd say,
you shock doesn't have any friends and then close the door.
It's so mean.
Oh, man.
What a mean dad.
That's Jacques.
That is one of the top OBGYN in Louisiana.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
No, no, in the United States.
Oh, in the United States.
Yes. Another curveball.
I know. That's crazy.
You come from a medical background.
Literally.
That's that's nuts.
Why are the guys from Dead Ringers?
What did they do so?
What did they do so wrong that I did?
That's exactly my question.
Why didn't you go into the medical field, Jock?
You clearly are, you love going to the doctor.
Going to the medical field.
Yeah, you love pills.
Yeah, Jacques is smuggling Xanax from Mexico.
That is technically the medical field.
That is a parody. That is not true.
That is a parody comedy.
You said that like eight times.
I didn't say that at all.
Jacques, you can't just smuggle drugs and be like,
"Oh, that was, I was joking."
"I was doing a weird outfit."
"That was just a prank. That was a prank."
Yeah, it was.
No, it break. I'm so sorry that my pranks are next level you guys
Ashton Kutcher wannabes, I'm the real deal either real Ashton Kutcher and the real Ashton Kutcher
Who have you put was less prank you pull? Yeah, it was less good prank. You had let's hear it then
It wasn't something illegal distribute distribute crack cocaine and disadvantage
I live with two people and my roommate left her key one of my roommates left her keys
And she called and was like hey look I left my keys last night
I need to get in in about like an hour or so or either of y'all gonna be there and
She's already kind of fucked up. So it was easy to trick her and we were like we literally are in New Mexico
We're like we're not gonna be back for like two days at least we just got a free deal on a hotel and we're here
and she this girl I almost started crying I felt bad that's a pretty good prank
almost I feel like that's the name of the prank show
someone break down in front of you like all like a ball their eyes out and then
just go psyched. Yeah, feelings in the entire world. This like,
explain to someone Oh my god, did you use a condom? Oh shit, I
think it broke. Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck. Anything I need to tell
you this, but I'm positive. Oh, fuck. I'm really sorry about
this. Ah, shit. Do you have insurance or anything? And then
like, you know, they're crying. They're calling their parents
insurance. Are you cool with your are you cool with your
primary care physician or whatever, like, he gave you like antiviral.
That's all I would ask.
Means that would absolutely be my first concern.
Now that you have AIDS, tell me about your primary care physician.
You know, make sure you're able to go to Planned Parenthood at least and like get that, you know, get the AIDS pill and then just go, you know, like the AIDS pill.
No, you can't get a pill.
If you're exposed to HIV, you just get a pill.
It like makes you really sick and then you don't get AIDS.
It makes you really horny.
Not not it's called prep and no it's not prep prep is
Pepo post exposure. Okay. I
Been I apologize
Wait, are you on prep?
I wouldn't I don't do I wouldn't do proper true father and I don't take it. It's called. Don't be a whore
So the prep you'll need it's called the Bible
*laughter*
I
I'm gonna get it soon and when I did try taking prep that shit
Yeah
Sorry
That shit fuck my body up so yeah
Yeah, yeah, totally.
No, Pep, Pep, the post-exposure stuff.
Oh, okay.
Then, right after I was prescribed PrEP for a month, and I lost weight, and I just, that
shit made my body feel terrible.
PrEP, yeah.
It's obviously not good for you.
There's no way that, like, there's gotta be a way where you can be gay and not have...
They are trying to poison all the gay people with PrEP.
Don't take the pill!
He's an AWOL!
literally how I think about it. Yeah.
But it's going to make you skinny anyways.
So I don't think there's a way to avoid that.
Yeah. We eat a bunch of cheesecake.
Makes you skinny, Jacques.
I don't I don't want to be.
Yeah, I'm just going to start taking it just because
like how women take birth control because it helps their acne.
Yeah. Yeah.
Going on perhaps you can lose weight.
They should make up Flintstones prep.
(laughter)
- Gummies.
- No, they'd have to get a different
Hannibal-Berra property.
- I ate the whole container of the shirt.
- She just is eating them out of like a popcorn bag.
- I ate the whole container and now I actually have eight.
- It would be like Tom Tom and Jerry Prep.
- Yeah, I was thinking Jerry was eating
the pussycats or something like that.
- I love, I love Jerry.
- Pussy in the pussycats shaped prep.
- No, it'd have to be for gay guys,
it'd have to be like Betty Boop.
- Oh yeah, there we go.
Gangsta Betty Boop.
Chola Betty Boop.
Betty Boop.
A little gummy in the silhouette of Betty Boop.
But you can tell she has massive camo pants on.
And boobs.
I thought you said "cummy" at first.
It's like holding an AK-47.
I thought you said "cum."
You're damn disgusting, Jacques.
I love Chola Betty Boop. That's probably my favorite iteration of like...
...like, Cholification of cartoon characters.
It's either that or Gangster Felix the Cat.
Yeah, Gangster Felix the Cat is good.
Gangster SpongeBob is great because it just came out of left field.
Gangster SpongeBob is good.
Gangster Bugs Bunny.
Oh, Black Bart.
I mean, that's like a...
Black Homer.
Black Homer is the gut out of all the Simpsons.
The Simpsons are white.
Black Opoo is a great one.
They're not. They're white.
Marge... I mean...
the
(laughter)
- She is not queer, shut the fuck up.
- Homer is queer 'cause he's bald.
- Homer is the--
- That's actually not, it's actually not queer to be bald,
it's actually like the straightest thing you do.
- I don't know, you and Jacques are side by side
on my screen right now, so.
- But I'm fully bald, Jacques has some hair, that's gay.
That's some gay shit.
- Yeah.
- I feel like the gay people on Grindr,
the only people available to me,
or who are interested in me on Grindr,
all look like Homer.
(laughing)
- Are you, do you have interest in Homer?
Are you eating rotisserie chicken?
- Yeah, of course.
- I feel like Jock is one of those people
who eats like every part of the rotisserie chicken.
- Yeah. - What's wrong with that?
- The bones. - The spine.
- Thank you, Patrick.
Thank you, Patrick.
Thank you for defending my American rights.
- I think Jock eats it like the Tasmanian devil.
There's just like a tornado around it for a second
and it's just bones.
it's the entire chicken meats mouth and pulls out its clean skeleton
leftist liberal
Jacques eats, Jacques eats
wait wait wait, Jacques is about to go off on leftist
why did your Jacques go off on leftist Jacques?
go ahead
you leftist liberal, leftist liberal
trying to tell me how much meat I can eat
I will eat every little skin and bone off of this
I spent 60 bucks
leftist owed
I eat an entire chicken skeleton
I will eat every little skin and bone off of this
I spent 60 bucks
the
There's no key. Why my no, I haven't been eating kale
Please tell me even an Amy's breakfast burrito the very least take that impossible burger and throw it away
I don't know. I don't want your
Come on bro
Stop eating that like a fistful of chicken
and
it
you're drinking ketchup but the fuck
the
always has got their beats when i lived with been all night you know i'm
drinking them
you need to purple the i haven't had a beat and so long
and i think that i'm not even a maturing team and that's up in fact
That is, she did sound like that.
Jesse, you know, I'm not eating them, I'm drinking them.
I like that your impression of Ben is Vincent Price.
[Laughter]
Uh, um, wait, Jacques, what were you gonna say when I lived with you?
I was not at a beat phase in my life then.
No, but when I lived with him, Ben would always be slapping raw chicken breast.
Okay, this literally, no, no.
Shut up! Shut your, shut your dumb little mouth.
He's always slapping raw chicken in the kitchen.
In the kitchen, just throwing raw chicken around.
Slapping together chickens.
This motherfucker opens the container, takes it out of the plastic wrap,
and is just slamming that motherfucking raw chicken on the counter,
not wiping the counter before or after.
That's nasty.
It's part of the seasoning, it's part of the seasoning, Jacques.
You watched me cook an entire meal?
the
Why are you slapping the chicken on the counter?
Yeah, why, why, first off, why are you slapping chicken on the counter?
Apparently all the time.
Why?
Over all of my meals.
No, this is impossible.
The kitchen was its own room at this house and Jacques was never awake at the same time
because Jacques wouldn't wake up until like 4 o'clock.
Eyes again.
Because you were too busy.
You, Jacques, were too busy sneaking in what you call sex worker clients into the home
to smell you for money.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- If you really,
if you really want to slander me
by saying I would flap a raw chicken around,
which would have been healthier than the--
- No, Caleb, I think they were paying Jacques.
- They were paying Jacques to smells, okay, okay.
- Yes, yes.
- Don't put your microphone in your armpit,
it might stuff your--
- Jacques, and I just found this out recently.
One time I, apparently,
one time I was leaving the house Jacques and I lived in
with like six other people.
And Jacques was like, "Oh, hey Ben, how's it going?"
I was like, "Fine, going to work."
And Jacques was like, "Okay, bye."
And he, in that process,
was sneaking a john of his into the home.
And he made this guy like crouch--
- Out of?
- Out of the home.
He made this man like crouch behind a car
so I didn't see him.
- Wait, why can't you just say like,
(laughing)
this is a,
why do you need to make him fucking go--
- I know, I just would have been like,
It's part of the experience
You don't you don't pay to go on the Jimmy Fallon ride
Ride so you can see the a cappella band at the beginning
Tronics those people should kill them
I went to a pentatonic gig when I was in high school.
They keep distracting my for one time.
Transformers beatboxing.
Yeah, they did that shit.
They did like a, like for the longest time,
like beatbox and I was like,
I almost walked out of the fucking concert then.
What kept you in?
I had to go to a concert when I was like in,
I think 11th grade in high school.
Like write a concert review for my music.
you
now because he's European.
Right.
True.
Now in Europe, in Europe, that's that's like the first rule.
Yeah, I've been having sex with little children because that's
what they do.
It's classy.
Literally when in Rome.
Classy.
Yeah.
Now I can finally live my fag destiny.
You got him.
That's definitely what Spanish people sound like.
everyone in Europe is the queen of England.
This is Max.
This is Max on a regular day in Spain.
He's like, Oh, can I please have another glass of white wine with my paella bowl?
the
the middle of town and I did have a big bowl of paella, a cigarette and a big glass of
white wine.
Wow.
So you kinda- Joke's on you bitch.
I think the joke is still on you Max.
Yeah, no you got clout.
You got exactly- You were owned.
Yeah, joke's on you, I'm exactly who you just made me.
Yeah, and I fucking enjoyed myself, I had a nice time.
Patrick, what's the sexiest meal in your eyes?
*laughter*
I don't know.
Double cheeseburger.
I'm not trying to fry.
Food is not sexy to me.
I don't think there's any meal.
Okay, okay, okay. Let me put it.
What is the best food you could eat?
*laughter*
Food you have sex with.
Yeah.
Food I would have sex with.
Yeah, that could be the list for the episode.
Never mind.
Pussy bread.
Pretzels.
I was trying to hit her.
Chicken livers.
Man, fuck this.
I was trying to get to know you to get a good question in, but you throw in this chicken
liver bullshit.
Well, Shock, answer your own question.
What's the horniest food?
Was that the sexiest dish?
Yes, sexiest meal.
Shepherd's pie.
How about that?
- Pepper's pie? - Pepper's pie?
- What the f*ck? - Pepper's pie with the protein and vegetables
one scoop and you got all you want.
- That is very sexy. - Ew!
- It's very sexy to have like a brown gravy. - Protein and vegetables in one scoop.
- A brown gravy hidden under mashed potatoes. - Yeah.
- Nothing gets you off like that. - Slop is the sexiest kind of food.
- He must have different... - That is the one meal I am good at cooking though.
- We should have pepper pie. - Really?
- Pepper's pie is good. - I don't believe you.
I wouldn't call it sexy.
You're good at cooking multiple meals, I can tell.
Me?
How can you tell?
Tell me what about Patrick
makes you think he's still cooking a bunch of different meals?
That sounds fatphobic to me.
Exactly.
I'm going to stick up for Patrick right now.
Since I quit drinking, I lost so much weight.
It's insane.
Why did you quit drinking?
girlfriend or something?
There's an insane amount of calories and carbohydrates in alcohol.
Yeah, I mean, I fucking, I lost like 10 pounds in January.
Like I was like, I was drinking.
Damn, Pat.
You quit because you were getting too lost on the sauce.
You were like street corner wino, like hobo.
Street corner wino.
I was on the street corner singing doo-wop for fucking.
Imagine Patrick is a wine guy, it's so funny.
Drinking, you know like Thunderbird.
Chugging wine.
He really is Thunderbird.
He really rips.
Y'all know what I'm talking about?
Drinking coolant.
That's the thing about Pat is like he drinks and eats everything like he's eating it over
the summer.
Obviously we've all never been homeless before because when I say wine and I say wino, typically
you're drinking Thunderbird wine which tests out.
It's like it tests out like 30 or 40%.
It's a small bottle and this is the most disgusting thing
you could drink.
Do not mix it with mushrooms.
In fact, don't mix anything with mushrooms.
- No, you can mix stuff with mushrooms.
- I feel like people are like,
I'm finally getting mental clarity.
I'm finally not mentally ill anymore.
- I'm a big-- - No, that's not what I'm doing.
- Of micro dosing mushrooms.
I've been micro dosing over many times in my life
and I was always pissed off that I didn't get like a sober high
because people always talk about like, oh, you know, like
that does not exist.
It doesn't exist.
It does not exist.
The sober high is complete.
Like it's a complete fiction.
I was like, why am I not writhing on the ground in pure ecstasy?
Right.
For three months, but it's like two.
I'm at two months now.
It's the first of March.
Yeah, so I don't know.
I mean, I think I like drink more in the summer in the winter.
I kind of just like, oh dude, I was like, I don't do anything.
the
is
are you an AA? is that why you listen to orange juice and all that like faggy rock music?
because you're sober? hey hey hey be nice to orange juice it's a good band. yeah it's
my favorite band. great band. no fuck up jock it's not your favorite band. it's not my favorite
but one of my favorites. it's not my favorite but one of my favorites. it's not my favorite
And my favorite one of my faves whatever
Posers shut the fuck up. Here. Let me
Whoa, whoa opposed to being a poser. I will name my favorite three
songs by this said band lean period
Blue boy, I see the computer
Get my boxing
knock you all the way back to your great baseline oh yeah falling and laughing as one of the best
bass bass lines of all time look at the conversation got me into i hate i hate when
patrick talks about shit that he likes it's oh my god guitar riff no i i like that patrick i like
that i don't care about patrick talking about music at all but somehow in his brain he's like
Conflated like playing 10 minutes of bass at the beginning of every episode into Oh Cameron doesn't want to hear me talk about
You say?
The same and is no when I when I talk about like everything I don't care
Wait, you're my Star Wars that's I do not
You are you're watching that in the Lorian killers. I I gave up on the Mandalorian you watch the Mandalorian
I gave up on you watched the Mandalorian. I saw seven episodes. Yeah
That's too many to give up.
That's enough to make you a certified cop.
Listen, no, listen, I watched an episode.
I forgot my Disney Plus password.
Why are you smoking a fucking like?
It's got a bong.
You were getting.
We're back.
Oh, yeah.
What the fuck is it?
It's going to get hard.
If all's rock.
OK, yeah.
Chuck, take the take.
Take the take the rip.
Take the rip.
Come on, eat it back up.
You guys, it's not.
It doesn't work like that.
That is literally an industrial revolution, Debra.
Look at that fucking thing, dude.
Yeah, that's literally a cast iron.
Xenomorph. Yeah, I think that's iron fog.
That's the craziest thing I've ever seen.
You imagine you'd never have to clean it because it's
you just got to season it once in a while with some oil.
I've only had this for a bang, bang, boom.
I've only had this for like six or seven months.
No less than that.
I've only had it for like four or five months.
And there was something stuck in it and I was like, oh, it's probably just some dab.
I pulled out like a ball of wax.
A piece of chicken.
Damn.
[Laughter]
A whole piece of chicken.
Chuck, how often do you like try to clean out like a bowl or something and accidentally end up breaking it?
Every time it happens.
There was...
I don't, so I don't clean.
I saw this guy, I saw this guy at the skate park one time in high school and he was trying to like...
You would see a guy at the skate park continue.
God, God.
That's where they hang out.
You know what I'm saying?
So he was trying to clean out his bowl, like he was trying to like smack it on his hand
and then I get he might have been too high and thought like, "Oh, I'll do this on the
ground so that I can get the atch out."
And the dude just like went to the ground and just fucking like slammed it on the ground
and it broke into like three pieces and he just looked up and went, "Oh, fuck."
*laughter*
Okay, play your guitar riff now, and then I dab it.
Oh, fuck.
Hurry up, hurry up! We have to hurry!
He has his nail in there.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Keep going, keep going, Jack, keep going, keep going, keep going!
Keep going!
Patrick, go, go!
*laughter*
*music*
There we go.
Damn, this is some tenacious D shit.
*laughter*
Jack is gonna fucking faint. If he dies, it's on you, Pat.
you
the top of my list are gonna be the Mexican pharmacies, Marlboro, Marlboro, the top three
people on the list of who killed me. Number one, the Mexican pharmacies.
For outing them. That's the next list for the podcast.
List of things that killed John. Mattel is going to kill me and Christian Walker
for our- Hasbro is used to potato head, not Mattel.
For our anti-gender crusades. I don't think Christian Walker is anti-gender.
I think he's very pro. He's pro-gender.
Yeah, he's pro-gender.
That's what I meant. I'm anti-gender. He's pro-gender.
If you two linked up, that would be...
Jacques has two genders. One for the plug, one for the load.
There we go.
So, like, obviously Christian Walker is garbage, but I mean, he's cute.
No, he's a kid. I love Christian.
I would love the idea of him even being attracted to me,
because not only am I disgusting and a mess but the complete opposite.
I tried to like argue again.
That's not yeah.
But I don't know.
Someone's getting cold for Christmas.
I think you and you.
(laughing)
- Okay, so now you,
now you claim to be Santa Claus.
(laughing)
You're at that level now.
All right.
- Oh, I'm so high, I'm zapped.
I'm like zapped.
- Dude, I feel like Santa Claus right now.
- This could turn me into Santa, god damn.
- Jock is smoking on that shit
that made Santa go around the world
with all the children.
(laughing)
I gotta get back to my workshop
That last dab felt like the little
Divine really off
Really off the dabs. Oh
Well, that's not you seem like you inhaled like the metal that makes up the rig more than anything. Oh
There's no metal in this. This is quartz
There is absolutely nothing wrong with inhaling aluminum.
Oh yeah, no, if there's something wrong with it.
I've smoked out of enough soda cans.
I have smoked out of so many cans in my life that I am a hundred percent
positive that there is a deposit of aluminum built up in the center of my brain.
So they cut open people's brains with dementia and Alzheimer's and
and
that
Where are you going to look?
I was trying to Google, but I thought this is a waste of time.
I'm just going to explain it quickly.
Over your lifetime, you're exposed to all this aluminum through the deodorant, through
drinking out of the cans, through whatever, whatever bathing products.
For some people, the exposure is so intense that it goes throughout your body and concentrates
in a small deposit on your brain or on the back of your skull and it looks like a drop
of melted aluminum.
It's fucked up dude.
It's yeah, yeah, no they, cause they, uh, they're finding like, like microplastics and
like, like placentas and shit now too.
Oh yeah.
Everyone's turning into robots.
Okay, thank you.
I was hoping I'd...
I can't eat microplastics in my placenta.
I like microplastics.
I believe shock on this one. I think so. I know I know I'm crazy
Microplastics on my micro penis
Yeah, I thought it would give me a boost
Yeah, I had to put some microplastics in it isn't that the surgery that they're doing now
They're just putting like a silly. Oh, they put like a
Part of a fake shaft in there. Yeah
No, it looks beautiful what's gonna
It looks really good. I've been looking into it you guys. Oh my god. Let me see penis implant before after
Be careful with your search cuz then you'll find like penis dermal
Okay
No one I have the best story one time
I was on grinder and I said send me a dick pic and this guy sent me a picture of what I thought was literally
a dead person's dick I
Wish I could find a picture just listen listen listen come to head like a morgue tag
Listen it's better. It's better come to find out this guy. It's better
No, listen this guy's white and he has had a blackout tattoo only on his penis
That's fucking sick was it to cover up an earlier dick tattoo
It was it did not look real did they tattoo his penis head his dick was gray because it was so faded
And it was a blackout tattoo heavily used it. Oh, no
you have not only a dick a fully tattooed dick, but a
Faded fully. Oh, yeah. Yeah Fox
This what you what you say to him jock. We like are you?
Hello, is this a zombie?
Is this so I said when can I suck?
City of Grey come
It was October I think actually
It was on Friday the 13th, I finally remember
*laughing*
When John said Friday the 13th he pulled out a hockey mask and put it over his face
Why do you have that?
Because I like to scare the neighbors
Or I like to scare people sometimes
*laughing*
Let me tell you something
Let me tell you a little trick of the trade
If you ever think you're being pranked
And you think it's me
You probably are
And this is how I'm going to be pranking you
It'll be the middle of the night
Mike
10 30 p.m. Till 4 a.m. And I'll be on my skates in all black outfit
I would feel like a no
Like you think it's like by Isis do you have anybody who like pay a ransom?
I wear...
And I wear...
Well I just wear my private...
Clearly your silhouette.
Like a...
Like bodycon all black outfit.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm wearing a very plain looking outfit.
I'm wearing like a Dickies cover all once.
I don't know if all black with your face covered is a plain looking outfit.
Well I guess my roller skates make it not a plain outfit.
But I'm playing spooky music from the Bluetooth speaker.
the
What is he talking about and where did he go?
Oh, not if I'm not trickspiny
Some kind of speak a
Oh, I have the perfect disc for this
I have
I have this
What the fuck?
It's a torture zone
I found this at Goodwill
How do I play it?
How do I, can I send a
song
in the group chat and someone play it
I don't think, I don't think
to
Better
Once you've Miller torture zone sounds to tell it's
It's in the middle of the night and you hear this scary song and you're an all-black
roller skater with a mask on I usually wear the ghost face killer mask from scream and
I just approached them once you've done you've done this to someone before
Well, I would get bored in Missoula Montana was so fucking boring
It is literally a skip Marvel of like the fact that you were not killed in Missoula, Montana
Yeah
Your survivor of your own terror of the people
The only time I ever thought I was gonna die in Montana. What was when I was floating alone in
In on the Queen Air mattress.
When Jacques says floating, he means floating down the river on a inflatable.
Yeah, of course. One of my favorite facts about Jacques.
And I was turning this way slowly, eating a bag of flaming hot Cheetos very loudly
with my Bluetooth speaker and a baby bear starts swimming right next to me.
It's really beautiful, John.
It is getting, like, you know, getting fish from that, like, the shallow end.
And I'm like, I have all this food. I'm eating Cheetos.
I'm like, literally, I'm like, you know, like, praise Hosanna in the highest.
I'm like, I'm praying to my full mattress. I'm like praying to the Beanie Baby God.
I'm like, oh, please, someone please save me.
me and I start like dropping all of my food behind me and the bear starts getting the
food.
So you made a trail for the bear.
No no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
I got all the food off of mine because I didn't have a paddle.
I just threw all of my food behind me.
Thank God.
You think you would have been eaten by the baby bear.
Well because the baby bear that eats the mom.
Mom.
Caleb are you stupid?
No, I'm just trying to get an idea of what you're on an air mattress.
And I have I have a blowtorch, but I don't know if that's going to kill.
What do you think?
They're going to see a baby bear in the wild and go and be like,
I'm going to mess with this thing.
It can't hurt me.
Jack, do you think you look specifically delicious to a bear?
Yes, he does.
Do I think I look what do you think you look like?
It's like, do you think a bear
would be like extra interested in you for some reason?
Like you are more delicious than the average person?
yes i'm covered in meat grease
yeah you don't i was on the river i just got my honey
i'm sugary and i was i'm sure i'm sugary as could be i'm colorful
i'm i got you know my music probably sounds good
there's a lot of inviting features you have delicious kidney stones for the
beard of finish the meal with i have like an
after dinner meant.
I'm D-dressed.
Excuse me.
This phone is broken.
This is stupid.
What happened to your phone?
Literally seconds before trying to get the Zoom passcode access, which was like getting
into Fort Knox so hard.
It's literally five numbers.
I'm trying to enter the matrix and it's like, "Whoa."
I don't know how you techno wizards out there do it.
He's five numbers and like three zeros.
Five number three zeros.
I don't need it today.
[LAUGHTER]
I really want to show you all that horror music.
It's so bad.
The scary song.
Oh.
I don't want to be scared, Jack.
I'm already so scared.
I don't really want to be scared.
I don't want to be terrified.
It's not-- this is not the day for me.
You know what I always want to do, but I never do.
I always think about hooking up my DJ--
no, no, listen, listen.
I always think about hooking up my DJ board
without saying anything to y'all before the meeting
so that it would just play through the Zoom call.
Oh, you should do that.
That would be fun.
And just putting sound effects.
And so y'all would suddenly start hearing
gunshot noises so loudly.
[LAUGHTER]
That's a new era.
You are a prankster.
You shouldn't have given it away.
Yeah.
- Well, we have recorded before when,
in the middle of recording,
Jacques stands up and walks away and runs around the house.
And then he came back and was like,
"I heard gunshots.
Someone's trying to kill me."
(laughing)
- The assassins finally got you.
They finally found you.
- There was someone who was trying to kill Jacques
at the time, believe it or not.
- So stalking me at my mom's house.
I'm staying at my mom's house alone.
I'm in from out of town.
I'm like, "Oh my God,
like I can't die at my mom's house alone."
I've drank at least 15 Corona Premieres,
which my mom's fridge is stocked to the brim with.
I'm just sitting alone and I see a guy
who I literally have a restraining order walk across
the street from where I'm sitting watching TV.
- Oh my God.
- Of course I'm gonna be like, oh fuck.
And then I record the next day and I mentioned to this,
to Ben and Max and they're like,
(laughing)
You get the guy
There goes
My gosh
Like that there's somebody actually actively trying to kill Jacques and when it came to people
Responsible for their death. They listed Mexican pharmacists
I by all means want to keep living a long life
and I I'm I have a lot to live for but if I do die suddenly I but
literally make the best unsolved mystery because
That would be a great
too many
20 different
It'll literally be like
I'll be the new mystery.
It'll be great.
Oh fuck.
That'll be...
literally, I'm coming for your throne.
Let me just tell...
I'm gonna find your treasure, DB.
That's what I'm doing.
DB Cooper is a raggedy bitch and Jacques is coming for his fucking throne.
They better watch the fuck out.
They better hide that pussy money.
[Laughter]
And my mystery
is gonna be a lot more confusing
confusing than Twin Peaks.
I'm excited.
Very excited for you to die.
This is going to be good.
Yeah, well, we already said when Jock dies, Max and I are just
going to pivot to having a true crime podcast.
Well, that's the first season right there.
That's my gift to y'all.
A martyr for the podcast by being mysteriously killed.
I mean, honestly, if I get physically injured and that
meant more patrons I mean I'm down if that's a tear if that's a good pay to
hurt you if people will pay to yeah or we could I mean we could just lie and be
like Jacques broke his leg me like no fun me I'm always skating and then
posting snap videos of couldn't take a month on his game as soon as I'm done
I'm talking to all you fucking jabronis.
I'm going to the rink and I'm not losing my skates this time.
I'll tell you.
- All right.
Good luck Jacques.
I have to pee.
So I think you have an out to go skate.
- Yeah.
- I think it's time boys.
- I think it's time.
This has been the best part of my week.
I love you so much Jacques.
(laughing)
I think the gays took this one.
- Yeah.
- I think straights, straights two.
- I don't think Mike gets one.
- I think, I think that again, Jacques beat all of us.
- Should I shut up?
Should I have been quieter?
No, you're perfect.
Oh, no, absolutely not.
The non-binary one.
Yet again.
Non-binary supremacy.
Almost unfair, I guess.
Our genderless agenda is going to destroy America.
All right, bye, y'all.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
It was fun.
Yeah, that was very fun.