- Last time on Raw Dogenyu, the Softlossifer Stone,
we reunited with Raw Dogenyu at the Beriberi Academy,
where he met two new best friends, Woody, the Druid Satyr,
and Andre Behavoir, the Goth Warlock Goliath.
- Hello.
- Together, they were sorted into house giants,
and then even went to classes together.
They managed to do well in at least one class,
gifting them a free spell slot to use.
In this case, gifting Woody a free spell slot.
- Oh yeah, man.
- That's going to come in handy right now
since in attacking class,
they were attacked by something
that wasn't planned by the professor.
- Winged serpents. - In attacking class.
They were attacked.
- Winged serpents exploding from the surrounding sea.
Exploding?
Erupting?
- There we go.
- From the surrounding sea. - I like that one.
- With the force of 10,000 dragons.
- Okay, well, you know, I didn't--
- I remember that.
- Yep. - I just remember that.
- I didn't remember until you said the word erupting,
'cause I think the last time--
- That was fire, though. - I think you said
erupting with the force of 10,000 dragons.
- I think everybody erupted-- - I like that.
- With the force of 10,000 dragons?
10,000 snakes?
- Erupted with-- - Yeah, I guess you could say--
- With the force of 10-- - Oh, here's the word
you're looking at, slithered.
- Slithered with the force of 10,000 serpents.
- With the speed-- - The speed--
- Of the snake.
- Combined with a bird. - Holy crap,
roll for initiative.
- Oh, snap.
- Did we already roll at the end of last one or not?
- Yeah, didn't we? - No.
- Oh, okay. - Or not.
- Well, I got-- - A 19.
I got an 11.
Okay.
An 11.
Oh God, I got a five.
Oh God, a five.
Charlie Brown vibe.
I got a five.
It takes every time that I roll any number at all,
I wanna say the Charlie Brown line.
Every time.
Say I got a something.
He goes, ah poo poo.
I always want to.
Why did they do that to him?
I don't know.
- He was suffering back in the day.
I hope he's good now.
- Every single kid is dressed like a ghost, including him.
How did they know it was Charlie Brown?
- 'Cause he fucked up his costume.
- Yeah. - But, all right.
- Not so bad that you need a rock for him.
- So, first is gonna be Woody.
So, just to give you guys the lay of the land.
So, if you remember from the map from before, right,
there's that, this takes place sort of on the left wing
of the Academy.
- Oh, geez.
- And there's--
(laughing)
And there's this sort of a fenced-in area
where this is taking place, and to the shore,
there's a shore that it's kind of up against,
and that's where the winged serpents came from.
The professor, in this case, Professor Aquaman,
he took the kids out, and he said he's gonna come back
after he takes the kids and gets them to safety.
It's a lot of first-years who aren't skilled
at attacking magic, but he was impressed
with you guys, so he hopes you can hold them off.
Now, so they are just sort of like,
there's about seven or so of these winged serpents,
and they're spread out, kind of in like,
kind of scattered and spread out,
but a little bit clumped together.
You guys are about, you know,
you guys are about, I'd say like average range
away from them about 30 feet, 35-ish feet.
And yeah, you could see like, you know,
it's nighttime, so it's harder to see them.
You see the lights of the academy in the background.
You hear them like hissing and flapping their wings.
Just set the scene and Woody, yeah,
there's a few right in front of you.
What do you wanna do here?
- This to me really feels like a teacher's job.
I'm not sure why I'm doing any of this.
Or is there not security guards?
Every high school in America has security guards
to make sure kids don't bring in wrenches,
but we don't have a security guard at the magic school?
- Look man.
- That's a good question.
- People ask JK Rowling that same question.
- Did they? - They did?
- No, I don't think they did.
I mean, they did. - I guess this takes place
a long, long time before-- - They had security guards.
They had Dementors.
- They did have Dementors, but there still was--
- This takes place even before that.
- There was a troll in the school.
- Dementors was the original reason you had,
Dementors was before Columbine--
- They still had to fight a troll in the school.
- But we're even before, we're pre that, man.
- Okay, well.
- Also, Hogwarts literally had an entire,
part of their whole, one of the houses was for evils.
- I will literally, it was for ambition.
- Am I close to, am I close to Dogen or Big One?
- Dogen and Andre are nearby you, yes.
- Okay, I would like to go up to Andre
and I would like to cast Bark Skin on Andre.
- Nice, scribe. - Oh, you're gonna make me
into a tree.
Until the spell ends, one willing creature you touch
gains the ability to move up, down,
and across vertical surfaces
and upside down along ceilings.
Why could I do this?
Oh wait, no, that's spider climb.
(laughing)
- It's like, everybody was like,
that's not what I read.
- And then you, it's like, and then your skin gets weird.
You touch a willing creature until the spell ends,
the target's skin has a rough, bark-like appearance,
and the target's AC can't be less than 16
regardless of what kind of armor it is wearing.
so it is a bit of a defensive style buff for my big friend.
- That is a very good move
because Andre does have very low AC.
So Andre-- - Bring her in, bring it in.
- Your AC will now be at 16,
which is gonna be useful for this battle.
- Oh yeah, 'cause I have an armor class of 12.
That's crazy for a giant. - Yeah, you have
a pretty low AC.
Well, you're supposed to have higher health,
which you do have slightly higher health.
- Yeah, I do.
I'm gonna use this combo this whole campaign, I think.
- Woody, though, make sure you spend
- You spent the spell for that.
- Yeah, I spent it.
- Okay, cool.
All right, great.
So I like that.
So now it is Raw Dogenyu's turn.
- Okay, I didn't get any new abilities or nothing.
- No, you're still the same level five paladin.
- All right, I'm just gonna go,
well, actually, you know what?
I'm gonna try and--
- You have some good items, though.
- I have items?
Oh, I'm gonna use my item.
I'm gonna use the big ore wave
to try and push these big serpents back in.
They came out of the water, right?
- They did, they did, yes.
- So maybe by using the wave,
it will kind of just naturally put them back in the water,
using water.
- Well, that's very possible.
- Nice.
- So I just will go ahead.
- If they got, my problem with that would be
that they got out of the water once.
It's quite possible they could do it again.
- They probably tried to get out of the water,
so they don't like the water, like water must be.
Why else would you be like,
I have to erupt out of this water.
- I guess you're right.
- So let me roll--
- If you wanted to be in there, you wouldn't explode out of it.
- With the force of 10,000 dragons,
I must get out of this water right now.
- Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
And so I'm gonna start rolling for them.
Okay, saved, saved.
- Ah, shit. - Ah, Cameron.
- Saved.
- L. - Saved.
- How many of them are there?
Oh my God. - A seven.
- Saved. - Seven?
- Seven. - Yeah.
- What?
I thought there was two. - These are animals?
- Just by my own thinking.
- What are these?
- These are the animals. - They're animals up top.
- They're human snakes.
- They're human snakes, but they're snakes.
- They're winged snakes, winged snakes.
They're like serpents with wings.
- Serpents, not snakes, serpents.
- Yeah, serpents, sorry.
- Winged.
- And winged, not winged. - So they're winged serpents.
So they have sort of like a fishy kind of tail too
that allows them to swim, and then like wings.
They all saved, they rolled really, really well.
- They all saved?
- Yeah, 'cause your spell save is 14, I think,
So double tap.
- God damn. - All rolled over 14.
- Yeah. - That's crazy.
- But on a failure, they still take one half the damage.
So roll for damage still. - Nice.
- What is the damage?
2D8, so should I just roll 2D8 and divide it?
- Yeah, yes, exactly. - Or should I roll 1D8?
- Yes, 2D8, divide it, yes.
- Okay.
- We're rounding up these days.
- Cool.
I like rounding up.
All right, that's three.
- Okay, so yeah, I mean, they all take three damage.
so they don't get pushed back.
I mean, I think there's a way--
- Can I also--
- They have a sort of resistance to it, you know?
- They have a resistance to it?
What languages do I speak?
Do I speak any weird languages?
I can't find it on my character sheet.
- I think usually-- - Serpentine?
- Oh, here it is, common, goblin, and minotaur.
Okay, well.
I was gonna try and see if I could talk to them, but.
Well, I guess, just say something.
- In Minotaur, I'll just yell out, "Hey, everybody!"
in Minotaur to see if anyone--
- Maybe there's a Minotaur around that might help.
- Yeah, who could help us.
- That's a pretty good idea. - I'll say, "Help, help!"
- In Minotaur. - Guys, I have a spell--
- A Minotaur like a thousand miles away is like,
"I'm coming!"
And starts barreling through.
- Yeah. - You have a loud-ass voice, man.
- Yeah, well, I used Thaumaturgy to make my voice--
- Thaumaturgy. - Ah.
- But I guess that's my turn.
- Yep.
I mean like unless you have that's your action
For bonus action that's kind of really it. I mean you've nimble escape, but there's no reason for you to really disengage
Yeah, I don't have I don't have anything I could do a hide action. I mean there's not too much stuff to hide behind here
I'm not afraid of anything
Okay, well not afraid of seven giant snakes. No wings well. They're not cuz I know where
They're not quite giant. Oh, I thought they were that's why I thought there was only two of them because I thought
No, they're seven scared of these fucking snakes, yeah, I mean either now they're normal human size
It is their turn now, so there's seven of them six of them
Form into a circle or you know a hexagon right one of them
Ends up in the center of that wait. They can't bend their bodies
No, I mean they just like position themselves in this way
Oh, okay.
Yeah, and then one of them ends up in the middle.
That one in the middle looks to the sky and hisses, and I need you all to roll a dexterity
saving throw.
I knew some shit like this was going to happen.
I got a 20.
Very good.
19.
I got an 18.
Okay, wow.
Dirty 20, Pat?
Yeah, dirty 20.
- Very good.
You all only take 12 damage.
- What, I got a 20.
- Yeah, you take half damage in this case.
As lightning comes from the sky and crashes down upon you.
Somehow the snakes together were able
to cast this kind of spell.
- Wait, I have a question. - The snakes are covered
in water from my ore wave, by the way,
so the lightning would probably be more striking
towards them, just based on the mechanics of lightning.
- I don't think, I don't think if, no.
I mean, I could--
- Based on how lightning scientifically works,
which I'm thinking of right now,
it just usually strikes you when it's first.
- This is fantasy, not science fiction.
- I have a question, Patches.
I have a question about this version of D&D,
I'm not sure how familiar you are
with the mechanics of the game Baldur's Gate 3,
but is there a throwing option in this game?
- Yeah, there's always a throwing option in D&D as well.
- Yeah.
- In both Baldur's Gate 3 and regular.
- Okay, Cameron, I think you know what to do.
- And regular.
- Yeah.
- So that's--
- Oh, I don't know, it's not my turn.
I think, well, I know there's one guy on our team
who's the number one thrower, I can tell just by his stat.
- This guy's a great thrower, for sure.
- And it is his term, Andre Behavoir.
- So I'm gonna use speak with animals.
- Nice.
- Yeah, you can cast it at will, right?
- Oh, that's why you asked if they were animals, okay.
- Yeah.
- Yes, they are beasts.
- Technically, yes.
- Ah, fuck!
- Well, no, I mean you could--
- Fuck everything!
- That's an animal, that's an animal.
- Beasts are animals?
- Yeah.
- I just think it's silly to make that distinction.
- Well, I just thought you were turning him down
just then and kind of--
- Oh, no, I wasn't, I wasn't.
- It's in everything a fucking animal.
- Laissez kind of way.
Like, yeah, well, they're beasts, so.
- Yeah, well, actually they're beasts.
- That's what I thought.
- No, no, no, no.
- That's what I thought, too.
- No, you can talk with them.
Sorry, I wasn't trying to do that.
You don't need to cast a spell to speak with a beast, just dial my number, man.
So...
Damn!
Hit my Skype.
Ooh!
Snap!
Okay, Cameron.
You popped off with that.
Alright, okay.
Or an animal, either, now that I think about it.
I don't even want to do my turn now.
Say that shit again, man.
Cameron was too sane again.
Oh my God.
Nah, nah, nah, nah.
So, I turn to the...
I'm going to do my turn.
- Nice and generous, probably, right?
- So I turn to the, I walk over, and I'm a big tree now.
- That's not so, it's more like you're covered in bark.
- Well, I walk-- - It's more like
you're wearing bark face.
- Well, I walk up to all of them.
I walk up and I say, "Hello, what are you guys doing here?"
- We're here on behalf of the Serpent King.
- Oh, okay.
*laughs*
Guys, they're here on behalf of the Serpent King.
Tell them to stop attacking or something.
Ask them why they're- like what does the Serpent King want with us?
Are you attacking for any reason or is um...
The Serpent King commands us to attack.
Okay, well can we maybe come to an agreement, right?
Or like, cuz look, the rest of us here, no one wants an attack.
>> [LAUGH] >> He's right.
>> That's great.
>> It's a good point.
>> Most of us here don't want an attack, but-
>> Say all of, nobody wants an attack
here. >> That's right.
>> Nobody.
>> Most of us.
>> Don't say most of us.
>> Nobody in the building wants an attack.
- Or outside of it. - We're outside of the building.
We're outside of the building.
- Okay, well we're outside. - Ain't nobody here.
- Yeah, the snakes hear that, they immediately go,
"Oh, well, okay, we won't go inside,
but we'll still attack you here."
- Well, okay, well nobody in your immediate vicinity
wants an attack done on them.
So maybe we could work out a deal
or something where you don't attack us.
And maybe we can just talk this out,
'cause I'm talking to you now.
It's crazy that I'm able to talk to you in it.
- I mean, roll persuasion with disadvantage.
- Disadvantage?
- For real?
They're commanded by the Serpent King.
Eight and four.
- Eight and four, yeah, that ain't gonna happen, man.
Why are my rolls so terrible?
What the hell?
- They go, "You try to trick us, leg walker."
I'm not trying to trick or anything. I'm trying to I don't I don't like
What's the word
Conflict that my horn flakes
Corn flakes flakes. Did you say corn flakes? Do you guys like corn?
I hate corn flakes. I hate him too. He doesn't like me. They just said I hate him
I hate cornflakes. I hate cornflakes. I hate them too. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Let's march all the way to the cornflake factory as a group. Yeah, let's go attack the cornflake factory together.
- I don't like it either now that I think about it.
- One of the snakes goes--
- It's a way better idea.
- Well, I like cornflakes.
Shut up!
- Get him!
- Oh, what the hell?
- Get the heck!
- Let's get this guy.
Let's get this guy done.
- Yeah, one of the snakes sort of sheepishly
retreats back into the water.
I'll give you that for this.
(laughing)
But the other snakes are still out there
and they're like, "We hate cornflakes and you."
- Why do you hate me?
- Yeah, I'll hate me too!
Let's get me!
Yeah, I mean you're not gonna convince them but um
Okay, why are you attacking us? Can I at least know that?
Serpent King commands us to
Why is the Serpent King saying this? Did he have a reason?
To bring us the Great One
Who's that?
The Great One
Alright, I'll go! I'll go if I have to
We could find him
We can find him and bring him to you and you know
Then we could all be done with this
All right
You got some information out of it. It's pretty funny. We killed one of them. Yeah, what are they get rid of one of them?
Yeah, I'll give you that. I'll give you that. I'll give you one of those a session
All right, you're up. You're up Caleb. Woody. Oh
- Wait, can I just do one thing before?
- Yeah.
- Guys, I don't think they like me talking to them.
So I'm gonna just stand here and be a tree still.
- We need you to attack.
- That was what you-- - Okay.
- We really need you to be blocking.
- Wait, can I attack?
- No, that was your action.
- That was my action?
- Yeah, that's an action.
- Okay, I'm going to use,
I'm gonna use Call Lightning on these serpents.
- But they already like lightning.
- Wait, they like it? - Yeah, they like lightning.
- Do they have a defense? - They used it already.
- I'm not against this.
- 'Cause I don't know.
- This is the only fucking damaging ability I have.
- Yeah, it's not Pokemon, so it might still hurt them.
- Okay, then I cast it.
- They are flying in water.
- He's saying that 'cause he knows that,
oh, well that didn't seem to matter before, did it?
- When they used lightning, Gyarados can use lightning.
He's flying in water.
- I thought this wasn't Pokemon.
- Oh, shit. - Stop it.
You can't do that.
That was too, that was good shit.
Okay.
- Damn it, all right, let me roll for saves for them.
- 14.
- 14's your spell save DC?
- Or hit DC, yeah.
- Okay, cool.
All right, so far, okay.
- Where does it say spell save DC on the sheet?
- For me, it's on the spell.
- Really?
- All right, cool.
Two of them failed, one of them--
- Oh, I see it.
- Two of them failed, four of them succeeded,
so roll for damage.
Are you casting it at--
- God damn it.
- Level three. - What level are you casting?
Level three, okay.
- Zero!
- Whoa, 24 damage?
- 24.
- Nice, cool, so two of them take 24.
- You said zero?
- It's a zero on the die. - Oh, zero!
- Oh, zero!
- I was like, what?
- I think the ones we, the D10s we have at the--
- Oh no, zero!
- The D10s we have at the office have a 10 on them.
- Yeah, not a zero.
- Yeah.
- Oh, zero!
- All right, cool, that was good, yeah.
You did a healthy amount of damage with them.
They're all kind of close enough
because they did that formation before.
Yeah, so you are now up, Rod Doge and you.
- Okay.
I guess, do I-- - I like that sound.
- Huh?
- Bro just went.
- Bro just did that.
He just did that.
- Okay, I guess our command works on only one thing.
I don't, it doesn't seem like I have much that can go,
- That can go.
- That can go AOE, I'm trying to see,
'cause there's so damn many of them.
Sorry, I'm just looking through my stuff.
- We'll go shopping later, you can maybe get some scrolls.
(gasps)
For real though?
- We're really gonna go shopping?
- I mean if we make it to the end part.
- Okay, I guess I will cast
Hellish Rebuke.
Just like prepare it as a react,
or do I not even have to do that?
Is it just my reaction?
- It's just your reaction, yeah.
- Okay, then I won't do that after all.
And instead, I'm gonna stack the buffs on Andre Behavoir.
Or no, you know what?
Bless is up to three people,
so I'm gonna bless all three of us.
Oh yeah, bitch.
Very nice.
So OK, so now now whenever you get a plus
three or four, yeah, they're going to get a plus D4
on any attack roll they do, as well as a saving throw.
So that's going to be useful.
So now the snakes turn.
So, yeah, two of them are are are right bloodied
and four of them are doing OK, but they got hurt by that call lightning.
So they're going to go after
Two of them are gonna go after you, behave wah.
- Who's saying-- - Oh!
- So, we're gonna roll-- - But I'm built like a tree now.
Yeah, you are, which will be helpful.
You're not built like a tree.
- You're skinned like one. - Just let him think his stuff.
- Bark, you have barked skin. - Bark, you have barked tree.
Okay.
One of them does hit you.
- Oh, bro. - Oh, brother.
And it does...
26 damage.
No, it does 10 damage to you.
Jesus Christ.
The other four are going to roll up on, they're going to go split-siege, so it's going to be two for each of you.
And they're running up, what they're doing is they're running up, you see them like, running up, they're flying up,
and sort of like coming in, like diagonal to like try to take a chunk out of you.
Alright, this is on Dogen. One of them got a crit 20.
Uh-oh!
So that does 19 damage.
- 19?
- Yeah.
- Is someone else coming after me too?
- No.
- Anyway, I want a hellish rebuke.
- Okay, nice, yeah.
- And I'll cast that at second level.
- Nice.
- Who's barking?
- What's the damage?
- My dog, hold on.
- Wife's coming home right now.
- What's the damage you got there?
- Barking, I saw me barking.
Who's barking, he asks.
- I thought you were barking, man.
- Your wife's barking.
- What did you ask me?
- You gotta-- - You better not be barking
on the side. - My nipples are barking.
- What'd you get on the damage for the house of Luke?
- You ever hear that?
- Let's roll it right now.
I got 20.
- Wow, nice.
So you get bit by this one,
and then you incinerate it right after.
- Oh snap. - Nice.
- Yeah.
So that was very cool.
It bit you, did a huge amount of damage,
but then you incinerated it.
Unfortunately for you, Woody, both of them hit you.
- I shimmy.
- And one of them crit.
So one of them does another 19.
- Did you hear what I said?
- I think so.
- He said, "I guess I'm too spicy."
And then I shimmied.
Can you show us what the shimmy would look like?
Can you get up?
Can you get up and do a shimmy?
- I'm not gonna get up, man.
- So you take--
- Do one of these across the room.
I did, I just did it like three times.
Stand up and pop and lock right now.
Not across my room, no, I'm not standing up, man.
I'm playing my PJs.
Stand up.
Oh, is Woody gone?
Oh my God.
I'm not looking at my thing.
He's here, he just is.
I'm here, sorry, one second.
No, no, no, you're fine, you're fine, yeah, do your thing.
He's sitting right in front of you.
I think he's, I have no, I'm jumping between tabs.
He's doing something.
That would actually be a good move is to put like a,
put a cardboard cover.
An OBS, put like a frozen photo.
Frozo all right a photo of you frozen frozen my frozen
Frozo my turn you say photo yeah, you take 25 damage it makes sense in my head
Fucking came back. I've won HP
Caleb Caleb hey Caleb hey
By the way you're dead
You're not dead
I've won. We're all gonna die HP
Which is a hit if we die your HP was supposed to go up
I thought I know when I took 12 and now fucking 25 fuck this fucking stupid game
I'm gonna throw you know so now it is your turn behave wah
Well what I'm gonna. Do I'd recommend not talking to them. I'm not talking to them anymore
They have done enough
You I'm gonna. I pretty good spells I am hitting primal savagery nice, and I got an 18
Very nice. Yeah, that definitely roll for damage whoever whoever is around me is gonna get the wrath of my tree and buddy
It's not all bark
Wow, that's good
And 11 damage acid damage nice. Yeah, you kill one of them
Nice, I screamed timber and I start I roll around
Nice, I'd like this
Timber! Timber!
Yeah, you just squish one of them.
And now, you're up, Woody.
You're back, back to you.
Okay.
So there's two, just two on either side of you right now.
Do I have a healer type of thing?
You probably do, I bet.
Oh, I bet you have Goodberry.
That one is funny.
In my inventory?
- No, that's a spell.
- I do not have that spell.
(screaming)
- Did you not add spells?
It doesn't look like it.
- Uh oh.
(laughing)
- Let's add some spells.
- I think that he failed.
- I'll take the one I have.
- Well, I'm already gonna, after this, okay?
- Okay, fine, I thought you would add them.
- Why don't you add them right now?
- I'm gonna use spider climb and I'm gonna run up the wall.
- There's no wall, man, we're outside.
- There's a wall of the castle.
- So there's a wall.
- You only have spider climb.
- So there's a wall of the building nearby,
but you would have to move out of range of them,
which would provoke an attack of opportunity.
- Not if I'm on a wall.
- So if you move a tree--
- Wait a minute, I'm calling the lightning again.
- Oh, you know what I should have done?
Actually, do you mind rolling a D20?
Sorry, I should have done a constitution saving throw
for you, 'cause you might not have to cast a spell,
or use a spell slot for this.
- 11.
- Okay, cool, so you pass that.
So this wouldn't even cost a spell slot to call lightning again.
If you call it on the two guys near you,
you do the thing you do in CRPGs where you circle just outside of where you are,
and just where they are, you just perfectly shape it.
So I'm going to roll for them, see how they do.
Okay, one of them saved, one of them didn't.
Roll damage.
12. Not as good. It was 12? Okay. Half is good. In fact, so one is... Half is good. One
took 6 then and one took 12? Okay. Alright, one of them is not looking good. The other
one is also not looking good, but it's looking a little better than that. So, but they're
- How many's left? - They're both pretty low.
- Two, one more? - There's four left,
one by, they're all pretty low.
One by Behave-Wa, one by you, Dogen,
and two by your bark friend here, Woody.
- It's my turn? - Yes, it is.
- Okay, I'm just gonna melee attack.
Also, I guess my oar, because I'm not a pirate anymore,
my oar is now a big pencil.
- 'Cause you're a nerd. - Okay.
- 'Cause I'm a student.
- Yes. - Not a nerd, hey.
- No, not a nerd, a student.
- A student of the educational persuasion.
- Yeah, okay. - That is a 13.
- 13 does not hit, so you whiffed.
- Okay, attack again. - Yeah.
- That is an 18. - That definitely hits.
- Okay, that is nine damage.
- Nice, you also have smites too.
True, I always forget about these things.
They're great.
That's a huge part about being a paladin.
How many smites do I get?
Are they, they're not part of my spells.
Yes they are.
Oh no, they are, they're spell slot.
Okay, yeah, I'll do a smite, why not?
Nice, do a level one.
I'll do a level one smite, so 2d8.
Nice.
That is 13 extra damage.
Nice, yeah, they, this one,
you just sort of like whack it with the eraser side
of the pencil and it just erases.
- I guess my first attack,
I should have added the blessed dice,
is what I have been within range,
would plus four, a possible plus four
would have made me hit on a 17 hit?
- A 17, it would have hit, it would have hit.
- Okay. - Okay, so let's count that.
- Yeah, yeah. - Can I roll it?
Well, can I just roll a D4 and if I get a four,
then I hit my first attack, I guess.
- Yeah, we should have, yeah.
No, no, no, I should have thought of that too.
It's part of my job, so.
- Okay, I got a three, so it doesn't even matter.
- Okay, cool, either way, they're gone.
That snake is done, done skis.
Bye bye.
And now it is the other three snakes' turn.
- I have to go open this beer over the sink
because it's going to explode.
- Epic.
- Okay.
- So one of them is gonna go after you, Behavoir.
- Wait, if he's leaving, I'm gonna grab a beer.
- Okay.
I guess nobody's gonna do anything.
- Mark it, 30, 45, we have a complete catastrophic failure.
- Just failure.
- Ju-bio.
- Making complete sense.
Making, oh, if he's gonna leave,
then I'm gonna leave so nobody's on the podcast.
That was the logic.
- Yeah, I like that logic.
- I thought we were taking a break.
- No, you decided you had to because you left.
(all talking over each other)
- I was just saying that so that everyone would know
I'm not just running away for no reason.
- And then Frederick said, "If Cameron's leaving,
"I'm gonna leave now, too."
(laughing)
- He said that?
- Pretty much, yeah.
- Yeah, he was like, "Okay, so while Cam's gone,
"I'm gonna go, too."
And we're like, "Oh, okay."
- I didn't think it was my turn.
- No, no, it's not your turn,
but you are about to receive,
stuff's gonna happen at you.
- Okay.
- So, no, I'm sorry, you're right,
I should be nicer to you.
So this--
- Don't let him win, Patches.
- So this guy is going to-- - Cam, what are you drinking?
- Roll a dexterity saving throw. - Old ass beer from the back of the fridge.
- That puffed up with force. - What did he do?
- Oh, puffed up with force. - Behave-wa, roll a dexterity saving throw.
- Alright. - What the hell is he drinking?
- I'm gonna make a jar of poop water.
(laughing)
- It's the fucking widest jar I've ever seen anyone drink.
That's a candle.
- Usually I have, usually.
(laughing)
- Hold that up, bro.
What the fuck was that?
- Is that root beer?
- Usually I have water, but I was really tired today
'cause I was working all day and then I had dinner
and I was like, I wanna be ready to record.
I need a little bit of caffeine.
And so now I got a poop jar.
I'm sorry.
- Nice.
- He definitely deserves mocking.
I'm so glad you called that out.
- That's an old Mayo joke.
(laughing)
I'm in a shape of that, man, I recognize that.
- I live in the hipster--
- It looks like a full poop type thing to me.
- So, what'd you get on the deck, Sam?
- Hipster's always drinking out of the Hellman's chair.
- 21.
- 21, okay, nice.
So this thing tries to grapple you,
and as it tries to grapple you,
you see like lightning starts to coil around its body,
but you're able to bust out of it before it does that.
- Because it sees my tree, it gets scared of my tree skin.
- It was like, ah, his tree skin!
And it just sort of--
- That's right, I'm a tree right now.
- You were right as fuck.
- Now the other two snakes,
they're going to try to attack you, Woody.
So let's see how they do.
- I'm gonna lay it on hands, I have the healing, I guess.
- Let me just--
- Forgot about that.
- I'll just, here, wait, I have an idea.
I'll die, 'cause I have one fucking HP.
- Yeah, people will be able to heal you.
This is what's gonna start happening.
We're at level five.
- Okay, so we just live in a fantasy world
- No, no, no.
- You can die.
- We don't die.
- You gotta work to failure, bro.
You gotta work to failure.
- That's right.
- I like that attitude.
- You gotta put your all into it.
- Yeah, you wouldn't fucking know.
- You gotta give yourself a zero HP.
- You wouldn't fucking know.
- No, this happened to me recently.
- Put me at zero.
Put me at zero.
- Cam, what did you say recently
where you were just like,
"I'm sorry, man, you aged out of this."
It was about nicotine patches.
- Oh, he asked what Zins were.
(laughing)
I said, "I'm sorry, buddy, you're old."
- I was like, how, how, how would zen?
What do you mean?
I didn't know at all.
- It was even worse.
We were playing a video game and someone had the username
like zen enjoyer or something and Patches was like,
zine enjoyer?
(laughing)
- These bitch.
- Oh my god.
- I haven't smoked since I was a mere babe.
- You don't smoke these you fucking moron.
- Well aren't they like a fucking,
are they like a patch, what are they?
- I showed you these, I popped them at your
Friendsgiving thing.
- Did you?
- Yeah.
- When did you do that, did you show me
or did you show somebody who was also old
and looked like me?
- I was showing you.
- No, no, no.
- You put it up there.
- Oh, it's like dip.
- It was, yeah.
- Yeah, but it's in a little pouch.
- But it's a pouch.
- That would have been way better than dip.
- Maybe I showed your brother.
- Might have shown my brother.
My brother loves dip.
Anyway, this guy did hurt you.
He has a dip, like salsa.
- Buffalo dip.
- Yeah.
- That's true.
- Oh, that's what you're saying.
- Oh.
- Um, yeah, you're knocked out though, Caleb, by the way.
- Okay.
- Is that all right?
- That's right, bro, you work to failure.
Great fail.
- You work 'til you're knocked out.
You do reps until you get knocked out.
- Okay.
- Should I roll a death to the throat or no?
- You should now, yes.
- Oh, fuck, he's gonna die.
- He's gonna get it.
He's gonna get one. - 15, that's a success.
- All right, there we go.
- That's a failure, actually.
- Really?
Okay, then I failed.
- No, no, no, no, it's a success.
I like Woody.
He's a good character.
All right, okay.
Dogen, it's your turn.
So right now you have-- - Me?
- Yeah, you have Behave-Wa,
who's got a very weak, bloodied snake.
And then you got the two other ones
who are hovering over...
Woody's body.
Can I do something really quick?
It's Baldur's Gate where if I heal him he just is back up?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, of course.
Okay, I'm gonna use my action, Lay on Hands, and I'm gonna heal 15 HP.
Nice. Behave well, you get your 15 HP.
So now I'm at 15?
Yeah, yeah. What did you see when you were towards the other side, Woody?
I saw my mom.
You saw your mom? She was dead too?
No, it was basically the exact same scene from the first episode.
Yeah, right, but just...
Love ya, mom!
Love you too!
So nice to see you again, mom.
You gotta get up!
I didn't see ya again, mom!
You gotta keep fighting, son!
I love you too!
Nah, I think I'll stay here right with you, mom.
Alright.
Oh, what's that?
Oh!
No!
A healing touch.
Damn, put me back in, vibe.
Put me back in, vibe!
What's that?
Oh, the Matrix.
I was gonna say, is that from The Matrix?
- Oh, the Matrix.
What's, I was gonna say, is that from the Matrix?
Who says put me back in?
- I think Neo does in the Matrix.
- Anyways, all right. - I think so.
- Anyway, you, the serpents are now up.
They're going after you, Dogen.
They've identified you as a problem.
- Oh, they're about to kill me for certain.
- Roll a dexterity saving throw.
- Okay.
That is a 15.
- 15, okay. - That's a good roll.
- Nice, yeah.
Let me...
Yep, yeah, you saved that.
So you avoided them.
One of them tried to do the grip thing that you--
- Wow. - That you tried to do
to Behave.Wa.
And now another one's just gonna try to straight up
attack you.
And yeah, also missed.
So-- - Nice.
- So yeah, you managed to do that all right.
And then Behave.Wa, this one's gonna try to attack you now.
And it missed.
Okay, you guys are back in this.
- Guys, we're goaded.
Oh my God.
- You're up.
- So before I do anything,
before I do anything,
I turn to my two new best friends
and I pick up this dead snake's body
and I put it on my crotch
and I look at them and I say,
guys, look, it looks like my wiener.
- If I had known that you were this type of guy,
I would not have sat with you.
- Kind of inappropriate.
We're in the middle of a life or death situation here.
Aren't you 15 years old?
You're making up some joke about your penis.
I'm 15 years old.
I don't know any better.
Seems a tad immature.
You should know better at 15.
At 15 I was writing novels.
Are you a teenager too?
I'm lying to him.
I'm lying.
I rolled deception to see if he believes me.
I had antlers.
Okay, I've just rolled...
Trying to boost morale.
I rolled a 12 on deception to try to lie to Andre the Papaw
that I'm an author and that I wrote novels when I was 15.
- Roll insight behavior.
- I got an eight.
- Okay, you think he's an author.
- That's amazing.
- You need to carry yourself with more self-respect.
- I thought that I was gonna make you laugh,
but what I did was actually make myself laugh.
- All you've done is bought yourself a role
as a laughing stock in my next book,
"The Strange Teen."
(laughing)
- Oh, that makes me feel so weird.
Oh no!
and I do Eldritch Blast and it gets 10.
- Okay, cool.
- And it gets 10.
- Okay, 10 is a miss. - Do I roll for damage or no?
- No, 10 is a miss. - 10 is a miss.
- But you should have-- - It really was not that cool.
- You have multiple Eldritch Blasts though at level five.
So I think you should have--
- Eldritch Blast is so fire.
Can I roll another one?
- It's an incredible spell, yes.
- I can roll another one right now?
- I think all spells are incredible.
- Oh my God, okay.
- No, Eldritch Blast is really something else.
- And I'm so embarrassed.
I'm so embarrassed that the Eldritch Blast didn't work.
- Number one spell in Baldur's Gate.
- So I tried it again and it got an eight.
- Okay, yeah, that also misses.
Warlocks kind of are like video game characters
'cause they have like a shoot button
that like never runs out of ammo.
And then they have these new abilities.
They're very like fun to play.
No, you can only do two right now.
- You can just use Eldritch Blast every turn.
Like it doesn't take up a spell slot.
- Yeah, and it takes two.
Right now you have two, as you level up
in the Warlock class, if you stay with that,
you'll gain more Eldritch Blast.
- You get five by level 12 or something.
- Yeah, you get like-- - It's fire.
- Yeah, you get three, I think, by level 12.
Maybe more. - Five, I think.
Just making it up.
- No, yeah, you're gonna get three.
I just checked again.
- It's five. - So, interesting.
You're up, Woody.
- I am going to use Call Lightning again, I guess, man.
Do I need to use a spell spell?
- We'll add some spells for you after this.
- Okay, should I use the spells for it?
- Oh yeah, you're gonna need to
because you definitely lost concentration,
you know, 'cause you were knocked out.
- From dying.
- Yeah, dying will stop that.
- Okay, I casted it.
- Okay, they're gonna need to roll.
- Will you roll for them?
- Oh, I will, I am right now.
- Thank you, bro.
- Okay, one of them did save, the other one didn't,
so roll for damage.
The one that didn't though was the one with higher HP.
13 nice they both just fucking explode
All right, and now there's only one left
Sight and it's by Andre behave wah you're up Dogan
Okay, I'll just run over and hit it and also I'd like to issue an apology it is three
It's not five. It's it's honestly cool as fuck that you manned up like that. I'm sorry
I don't that's right not to make mistakes, but when I do I mean patches being correct. Yeah, right. I know so you still won
You did so I got a am I still blessed
I'm blessed
Regardless you cast I cast blessed. Yeah, I cast a bless on everybody and you didn't get any take any damage yet, right?
Like you have not
No, I'm actually I did I think so. I'm not blessed anymore. No, I just should have I should have just I keep forgetting to do
concentration because we're playing real D&D now. Just roll a d20 to see if you maintain
concentration from before. Okay. Just con saving throw. A con saving throw? Okay, it's
a four. Okay, yeah, so you didn't. I'm willing to bet I'm. Okay. Now my second attack, I
roll a 13, so I don't think I'm hitting anything this turn. My bonus action, I'll shove. Nice,
shove him, like in the video game. Yeah, I'm just going to be playing video game style from
now on? Yeah, hasn't stopped you guys from throwing. Okay, my shove wasn't 8, plus 2,
10. Yeah, it doesn't shove him. It does the thing where it makes a shove sound but then
they don't move. Yeah, they don't do anything. You do the animation and it goes "Oh!" Yeah,
it sucks. But now this guy is going to try to attack you. He's going to play it simple.
- He's pretty scared at this point.
- Me?
- Yeah, he misses.
He's kind of like, he knows it's the end.
You're up, Behave-Oi.
- Okay, then I guess I am going to just--
- Yeah, and I'll say Behave-Oi,
from you talking with them,
you can tell that this creature,
while mindlessly devoted to the Serpent King,
and whatever the Great One is,
is shivering in its proverbial boots.
- Yeah.
- Yes, it is, yeah.
There's one right next to me?
Shake it.
Okay, I grab it by the neck.
Roll an attack roll.
Like it'll be like a grapple.
Okay, so strength?
19.
Yeah, you grab it by the neck.
It's like Homer Bart style.
It's like (imitates grunting)
Homer Bart.
Who do you work for?
Roll intimidation with advantage.
22, don't need to.
Nice.
You should roll again though.
See if you crit or something.
Nope.
Okay.
Dirty 22.
Who do you work for?
Says, it says--
I mean, wait, you already said that.
The Sappid King.
You said that earlier.
(laughing)
I'll let you get one more question in.
Why do you work for him,
And is there any reason why you're mad at us?
It's a two part question.
- Okay, I'm trying to think of how this guy
would respond to that.
- Wait a minute, why is the Serpent King mad at us?
Oh wait, no, you said earlier
'cause you're trying to find the one.
Okay, then who's the one?
- The boy who lived.
- Says, he said, okay, yeah, I think with 22,
let's see what he goes.
- Wait, is it Dogon?
Wait, I already knew that. Okay.
Um...
Uhhhh...
Wait a minute!
He says, Lurks...
I don't have much time to answer my question!
Uhhhh...
You're just sputtering in beast speech.
Like you're hissing at another...
Hissing at a snake, all upset.
That's what it looks like.
(laughter)
- Yeah.
- When it's translated.
- It's like goth kid freaks out.
Like, um.
- Yeah, when it's translated, it's just like,
wait, wait, I forgot, I forgot the question.
- But yeah, he says,
the one that lurks below the earth.
And then, um, that's all it seems to know.
(silence)
- The one that lurks below the earth.
- Wait, the what?
If he's talking about the chosen one,
he might be talking about me.
I've always thought I was the chosen one,
ever since I noticed this lightning bolt scar.
- Is he the chosen one?
- And I pulled down my tunic a little bit
and showed the trunk of my dick
and there's a lightning bolt scar right on it.
- Does the snake react to this?
- Like it's just barely the trunk,
you know what I mean?
Like an Instagram type pic.
- Pete Wentz style right there.
- And the bald head's still allowed online.
- Yeah.
- And I'm baldly shaven.
- Yeah, you see the snake's--
- Nice chop job downstairs.
- And you can tell that it's shaved,
and you can tell that it's shaved
and that I'm not just bald there
because there's a lot of hair surrounding it.
- A lot of ingrown hairs.
- And you can clearly see a circle when it's shaved.
(laughing)
- The snake's eyes widen when it sees the trunk of your dick.
- Ew.
- Okay, out of context, that sounds fucking crazy.
- The snake's eyes widen when he sees the trunk of your dick?
(laughing)
- Maybe he thinks it's another damn snake due to its size.
- True, damn.
- Jeez.
- Yeah, he says, "Big brother!"
Is what it says.
- Big brother?
- Whoa!
- Nice, daddy!
- Damn!
- Very nice!
(laughing)
- You're literally goblin-sized,
so that thing's the size of a human.
You're just riding a fucking dune-ass worm.
- No, no, no, no, no.
The snake is, the snake's eyes do widen.
And--
- Like what you see, snake.
- And--
- Ew.
- And he says, he says,
"You will help us bring him back."
- Wait, who, me?
- No. - Him?
- You fucking, no.
Like, it's just like--
- Huh?
Yeah and he just starts smothering and spitting and then...
Oh my bad!
He's just choking him.
Oh did you just snap his neck?
Yeah.
Okay cool.
Sorry.
And after that happens, the water rumbles more and you see five more come out of the water.
I ain't doing this shit, man.
And, but right on cue, who returns, the professor Quammen,
who comes back and he goes like,
(yells)
and out from his hand comes like a chain lightning
that connects to all the snakes
and they all just like fucking pop.
Wow.
And he turns to you all and he says,
you did good work there, gang.
Thank you.
- Yay, we did good work.
- I...
Seems like, and then I, about 15 seconds after that,
I pull my pants back up.
- Well, we have another class to give to you, so.
- No, I'm not.
- See ya, catch you on the flip side.
- Hold on, hold on.
That damn Serpent King is a problem.
Did the headmaster eat your pussy up,
tell you guys about it at all?
- Did the headmaster eat my pussy up?
- What the hell are you on about?
What kind of a question is that to ask a student?
Maybe you forgot I'm not a teacher anymore.
You can't say stuff to me like that anymore.
- You said stuff like that to everybody, Dogen.
- Okay, part of my class, first of all.
And second of all, it was, no, I didn't.
- And yeah, you see one of the largest crystal
that floats above the De Ministrone, the main building,
is glowing and all of you hear telepathically in your heads,
similar to how I described for Marlon Reese
in the beginning.
- Telepathically in our heads, okay.
- Okay.
You talk, you talk!
You try talking.
- No, I was just double checking.
Telepathically, check.
Oh, in our heads, okay.
All right, go ahead.
- And you hear, oh,
- We hear, oh, we hear it, wait, we hear it now?
- Wait, so we hear it in our ears?
- Did you know that eyes are part of the brain?
- I figured that out on my own.
- It's the ocular--
- That was the person who said that first.
- Getting upset?
- Really?
- Okay, so we hear it--
- My new tactic is to cry when you guys bully me.
See what happens.
(laughing)
- That was fun.
- Yeah, I know, I'm sorry.
But no, yeah, you hear the headmaster eat your pussy up say,
- All students. - Do we hear the headmaster
eat our pussy up?
- Do you even mean yourself?
- We wish we could hear what you're saying right now.
- Please return to the De Ministrone
for an emergency assembly.
- Okay. - Okay.
- And you guys ready to play the penis game at the assembly?
- Professor Kwaman, and he goes,
"About damn time." - Penis.
- All right, let's go.
And yeah, you guys can go there.
- You do go there maybe?
It's up to you.
You guys can skip.
But yeah.
- Oh yeah, I guess I'll go.
- So you see there, and from when you first went there,
you had all the students there,
but they were all sitting amongst the tables.
Now they're kind of just all gathered in ad hoc.
And Mr. Eat Your Pussy Up,
or Headmaster Eat Your Pussy Up says,
thank you all for attending this emergency assembly.
The safety of the students who pay such a handsome tuition
is of utmost importance to me.
It's true that the Serpent King
has been attacking us for some time.
- Okay.
- Well, that's interesting, isn't it?
- Sounds good.
- I lost my place.
- Penis!
- With his abominable winged serp--
- It has been-- - Penis!
- Penis!
- Who's playing the penis game?
- His thaumaturgy, and I say penis so loud
that it's chandeliers start dropping from the ceiling.
- You see his students start to laugh.
- We're battling in thaumaturgy penis game
because I also, I realize just now,
I also have thaumaturgy.
- Just not how you play the, just say it louder.
- Penis.
- What do you mean, that's how you play it,
you say it louder.
- I'm saying it in the lowest vibrational--
- What kind of penis, oh, maybe you played
some kind of weird penis game with your friends
back in the--
- Say it louder.
- When you were in school.
(laughing)
- Fuck off.
- Penis game for him was something completely different.
hot you know you know it's a leap over
uh...
the government of the first thing with my pet without a way to get you guys
figure it out is just saying unit
the
so i i i am a blue
uh...
did you guys figure pet rocks so that would be a good uh...
all right
now i mean a bit if it's too
i'm not explain i know the pocket it is game
- Oh, I'm so flustered!
(laughing)
- That's how it's done, y'all.
Crying once there.
- Now we get, we get five points.
- Yeah, yeah, you guys get five points.
- Five points to House Giant.
- Five points for House Giant, that's huge.
- Wait, does this campaign have a point system
for the houses?
- Yeah, that's part of what the classes are.
You guys drive around the classes.
- But like, you know when they say
five points to Gryffindor?
- Yeah.
- I can add that.
- Can you add that?
I just really want that right now, I really do.
- Yeah.
- The more we play this, I'm realizing
I just literally want to be exactly in Harry Potter,
just completely one to one.
- All right, I could try to add that.
- Me too, I love Harry Potter.
- There's certain things I'm trying to add over time,
so I will add that.
- Just whatever house at the end gets the most points
gets a pizza party, maybe.
- Yes!
- Pizza party would be so good.
- In real life.
- It has been rather unpleasurable.
Just give it to just me, if any of the other houses win.
(laughing)
It has been rather unpleasurable to say the least, but our best minds are working to solve
the case.
We've employed the renowned Nimrod Hunters as well to assist in fighting the scourge
of winged serpents, and there should be no change in schooling activity.
As I said during the sorting ceremony, our pleasure shall not be denied.
I would ask that all students, when crossing the De Ministrone Pond, to just be wary of
the waters.
This is where the Serpent King appears to reside.
I'd recommend you mind your crystals, since he appears to be chasing those as well.
We'll be stationing additional magical security via the Lord Poonhead, head pleasureman from
Trebuchet Village, who has generously offered some of his finest pleasuremen at a discounted
rate.
And my dog, my attack dog too, will be helping.
Fido.
Now, please students, I'd ask that you retire to your dormitories for the day.
Tomorrow, after all, is the weekend, and there is a tremendous amount of pleasure to be had.
Hooray, the weekend!
I hear all the secrets that you keep.
And um, and uh, yeah, so.
♪ I'm a big, common baby ♪
- You're just singing as students start to file out.
And one of them, Regatta Reese,
who you had seen earlier with her matadier.
- Hello, Regatta Reese.
- She's like a seventh year student,
so she's an over student. - Hello.
- And she goes up to you, Dogen,
and she says, "Pardon me, Professor, well, Student Dogen."
- Yeah, it's Student Dogen now.
- Sorry for being so presumptuous,
But I've always wanted to ask you this, since you're a dirt goblin.
Um, I don't know if you know, but I was recently placed-
She's gonna ask you if you're single.
I was recently-
You can't see my scar.
Oh, I didn't even know about-
You can't see it.
-any scar that you had.
Well, now you have to shower!
He's got a scar on his worm.
I just wanted to ask that I'll be working for a lord in the dirtlands after I graduate this year,
and I was just hoping I could ask you some questions
about your time there.
(Dogan groans)
So, and this is also a question for you, Dogan.
So, you obviously hung out with the guys
in Trebuchet Village, that's where you were.
Not just 'cause you're a dirt god one,
it doesn't mean you were ever from the Dirtlands,
but the Dirtlands are, I would say as far as like--
- Dirtlands being bad?
- As far as regions that I've developed,
like it's more underdeveloped,
like as far as my lore goes.
So like, you have a lot of say here
as far as what it looks like.
I kind of always saw it as sort of
dune-esque sort of area, Arrakis kind of vibes.
- Yeah, it's dune, but instead of sand, it's dirt.
- It's dirt, yeah.
That's kind of how I saw it.
- And instead of just, instead of like, you know,
the Fremen walking around, it's like,
like instead of like mystical people
in like robes and cloaks and stuff,
it's just guys walking around with no shirts on.
- Yeah, it's just nasty goblins in shorts.
- Goblins in shorts all walking around.
And it's also, there's no dunes, it's completely flat.
The entire thing is completely flat,
so you can see from one end to the other.
You can see literally everybody who lives in the Dirtlands.
You can see them at all times,
'cause there's no houses or anything.
So you can just look 360 degrees around you,
you can count, so everybody knows
whenever anything happens,
because everyone can see each other.
- I like that.
Yeah, I think, 'cause Dogen the Dirt God
is one of the major gods in the Pantheon.
And he's major enough that he has his own
sort of region devoted to him and his own,
there's lords who worship him.
And Dogen, obviously-- - Yeah, he is a god, huh?
- Yeah, so, well, not him.
Dogen the Dirt God, he was named after the Dirt God.
- Oh, right, right, right.
- But you've sort of fallen out of favor
with the Dirt God now, or you're not as much of a fan--
- Yeah, I rejected him.
- So I don't know if you want to talk to her about this.
- I broke my oath.
- Because he made me eat dirt.
Basically the dirt lines suck dick
and they fucking suck--
- Are you an Oreo guy now?
- No, now I'm a student of knowledge.
- What happens to Oreos now?
- I was Oreos for a while.
- His dirt is now books.
- I went from dirt to water to Oreo and now it's pencil.
I'm joking, the diploma got me.
- I forgot you had an Oreo thing.
- Yeah, it was a spoon, remember?
- Yeah, I remember, yeah.
- Anyway.
- I guess I know, you know, actually I would do a thing
where everyone does about their hometown
where they're like, yeah, I guess like,
I guess it like sucks pretty bad.
I can understand, people don't like it
and I can understand that, but like,
being from there just has like such nostalgia for me
that I just like can't like bring myself to hate it.
- That's really interesting.
Did you ever study any dirt magics while you were there?
- Yeah, I was basically number one in the world.
- Yeah, world deception.
(laughing)
- I was number one in the world.
- Number one in the world.
That's an eight.
- Okay, she's gotta be real polite.
Just sorta like nod.
Roll insight to see if you can tell
that she's now doing it using deception.
- Okay, that's an 11.
- Okay, let me roll deception for her.
She has kinda mediocre charisma.
It's a little bit better than real life Hermione.
- Wow.
- Real life Hermione.
Yeah, you simply can't tell.
- That she's being polite.
She's like, "Wow, number one in the world."
- I think she's buying it, and I'm like,
"Yeah, and by world, I mean universe.
(laughing)
Number one."
I mean, number one still.
- Well, tomorrow I know that it's the weekend,
and I know you guys are first year students.
I'd be happy to help take you guys around the Academy of Town
and take you to some of the shops
and just show you guys around,
at least for the two newer friends here.
- Oh yeah, you would like shopping.
I mean, I like shopping, or we like shopping.
No, I'm number one at shopping in the world.
(laughing)
- Just then, you see one of the delivery flies.
So usually the students will get their mail through bugs
that fly in and carry letters.
And so one of them's carrying a letter and as customary, it collapses on the table, dies,
and emits a message that's enchanted. It says, "Dogan, it's me, Condoleezza. Read the letter.
Thanks!"
That's a short ass letter.
"Hello, bug."
And then the bug is dead. The bug is dead.
Okay, sure.
- Can I stabilize the bug? - We're going in.
- Margotta says, "Well, I'm also in the House of Giants,
"so if you guys want to go tomorrow, just let me know,
"and I'll see you guys there."
And she waves to you, all three of you.
- Not if we see you first!
- And I just remembered something just now,
so I'm gonna do that.
I say, "Quadra Mudmarks, make a note of this
"so we remember to do it."
- Yeah, sure, no problem.
We'll make as many notes as you need me to make.
- Wait, is he a full assistant to us?
- He's a seer. - Quadra--
He's a serial killer.
That's what Patches told me.
Basically yeah.
He's basically you can telepathically communicate with him anytime.
Or take him around with you if you want.
Quadro Mudmarks do you know anything about this...
She's standing right here.
Quadro Mudmarks do you know anything about this weird bitch?
I actually might have written something.
I wrote so many things for Quadro Mudmarks.
This is my assistant Quadro Mudmarks.
He's in your head right now.
I guess you guys wouldn't know him.
Quadro Mudmarks play smooth jazz.
Play gothic music.
Play smooth jazz.
Play the smoothest jazz.
I don't even know what a jazz is.
Yeah, you're an uncultured lout. That's what you are.
I mean you hear honk honk.
I quite like these mud men.
Quadro Mudmarks,
can you play gothic music?
Maybe you can show me
a little bit of what it sounds like first.
I mean I could try it for myself.
Oh boy, here we go.
(laughing)
Worth the price of admission though, I bet.
- I can't think of anything.
I can't think of anything right now.
I'm nervous 'cause you want me to sing.
- Look, I don't know anything about this dame,
but you know, she seems nice enough, okay?
- Do you have any games on you, Quadrant?
- Why don't you read the letter that Condoleezza,
why don't you read the letter
that Condoleezza Carlos sent you?
He's my master too, after all.
- Do you have any games I can play on you?
- Okay, I'll read the letter. - Yeah, for sure.
Do you wanna read Bubble Pop?
- Harpo's Honk Simulator.
(laughing)
- Oh, I wanna read Poppy Jump.
- The letter just says,
"Dogan, when you return to your dormitory,
"we must speak in private,
"but you can bring your new friends.
"Go directly to Mud Marks."
- Let's go. - Hello, Mud Marks.
- All right, let's go.
- Okay, so you guys climb the chutes and ladders
up back to the house of giants.
You see Mud Marks just standing by the fire,
doing a little bit of a routine.
- Don't get too close to that fire,
you're gonna bake yourself dry.
- That's what I tried to tell him.
- Water is an important part of mud.
- But I'm so cold.
- You're not cold, you're barely even a living thing.
You don't have nerves.
- Yeah, but you got some nerve talking to me that way,
I'll tell you that, pal.
I got more heart.
- Oh, you're getting an attitude,
and you keep talking like that,
I'm gonna take off one of your heads.
- Good. - You like your brothers,
don't you?
You like your brothers, don't you?
- I like 'em all right.
- Okay, well we'll see how you feel
when one of 'em's dead in a ditch.
- Now you're kinda talking like a Mod Marks.
- I do, now anytime I'm around them,
I always end up like this.
Say.
- So one of the arms, so the four heads on there
are Mark's, Groucho, Zeppo, Harpo, and Chico.
Zeppo is just like dead, but you see one of the arms
grab Zeppo's head and rattle it.
And then Zeppo's head starts to rattle
and his eyes turn white.
And a like beam of light emits from his eyes at you guys.
And you find yourselves in the tower,
in the lighthouse of Condoleezza Carlo.
The one that only Dogen would really know what this is.
But in the Port Los Berry Berry town,
when you guys met Condoleezza Carlo,
you were in the market,
He talked with some of his black market representatives there, and he brought you to this lighthouse
where he watches ships crash and then has his men sit down and rob them.
And you see him looking at a massive scale telescope towards the sky.
You see Condoleezza Carlo.
To remind you guys what he looks like, he sort of looks like, in Harry Potter terms,
he's kind of like Gilderoy Lockhart.
He's like sort of blonde, handsome.
You see him looking at the telescope, he goes, "Yep, that's the sky alright."
And he turns and faces you guys.
He says, "Dogen!"
And I believe you're Woody, right?
"Aye."
And that's Andre, right?
"Beh-heh-wah."
Oh, don't be so shy, lad.
There you go.
"Hello."
I hope you guys have been getting along well at school.
- How's school, how's it been going?
- I'm new to school.
- It's okay, it's okay.
Hey, Andre, it's okay.
- We're all new.
- He's a friend, he's a friend.
- Yes, yes. - Well, I'm not new.
- Look, and I'm sorry, Dogen.
I should have told you
that there was no sexual studies course,
but in my defense, you were very, very depressed
after all your friends died,
and I felt like it would have been wrong
to say no, not to pursue it.
You know, you just seemed so excited
to teach the kids about sex,
and I just didn't want to take that from you.
Well, it's coming back. I they it's coming back. That's all I'm gonna say keep your eyes open
Hey, if you can make that work, you let me know. I'll pull some strings as well. Okay, I hope
For what
What kind of strings are you gonna pull?
What do you mean? That's that classic humor dog and I miss you man. You know, you're funny guy
Well, anyway, I hope I
- Hello, my name is Andre Behavoir.
I am 15.
- Every time he goes to a new place.
- I am 15 feet tall and I am 15 years old.
I am currently in school.
- Oh, it looks like you updated it since last time.
- He's reading the essay he wrote for his class.
Just let him read it.
- Okay.
- He's really proud of it.
- Okay. - It's a memoir.
It's a memoir.
- Memoir.
Keep going, Andre.
- Memoir is my cousin's last name.
- That's a good one, Andre.
- I have a cousin named Andre Memoir.
(laughing)
- That would have been pretty good too, yeah.
So anything else?
Or is that sort of where you're at right now with the essay?
- Look what I can do.
- What does he do?
(laughing)
- He rolled Eldritch Blast damage.
- Oh shit.
- He rolled an attack, he did an Eldritch Blast.
- I did an Eldritch, I did three Eldritch Blasts.
- Okay.
- And one of them's a 22.
- So--
- I'm not aiming at him, I'm just aiming around the room.
- Yeah, no, I mean it shoots out,
it shoots out and just like dissipates
before it hits anything, you know.
He has this place charmed out the ass.
He says, "Yo, I am disappointed you fellas didn't get in the house Kaiju Manji.
That was my house when I was at the academy."
And you know-
That house sucks dick.
Well, you know, there's been some accusations, but nothing ever really came out about that.
About that it sucks, that you suck dick, that's the accusation?
No, not me, but activity in the house.
Is everyone you ever knew?
Yeah, pretty much.
Everyone except you sucks dick in your house.
So wait someone made an accusation they said everyone in the house sucks dick except this guy
Because that kind of throws maybe more concern about you doesn't really it doesn't really seem like
Logic of the whole scenario
So all right, we're gonna you guys are you guys are funny. I got to give you that you're very funny and
And look, I appreciate it.
I just wish you were there.
Gaston was a big fan of you, Dogen.
He thought you had a great aptitude for the magics.
But I want to--
after recent events, from what I understand,
I want to be clear here.
Now, Mr. Eat Your Pussy Up, he's a very smart guy.
Very smart for a pleasure man, especially.
And a very inappropriate headmaster.
And he's right to be concerned about the Serpent King.
seen his winged serpents, you know, crop up along the Beriberi coast.
Speaking of coast, uh, ah, Sherman, you guys remember Sherman?
He was a little bit Condoleezza Carlos assistant who was British and had a stutter.
And he says, Oh, good, good.
Good to see you, Dogan.
The last ship.
I don't remember you.
Oh, it's I'm apologize.
Um, apologize.
But thank you.
I accept your apology.
He said, sorry, a lot and stuttered a lot.
So you cuz the last ship crashed had some gold and kind of Lisa Carla goes wonderful gifts for our friends here, okay?
Hey guys, you're going out this weekend. How does 500 gold piece for each of you sound?
Yeah
Yeah, so he gives you guys 500 gold. So you'll add that add that to your inventory. Whoa this
Wait are you bribing us to do something is this a bribe? No. No, it's not a chicken mancha. We don't take coin leader bribes
- We're friends, we're friends.
- Chicken muncha.
- What does that mean?
Wait, I'm gonna start using that.
- It says I have 1,015 gold pieces, do I still have that?
- Yeah, add another 500.
- Okay.
- Where's my gold?
- It's in inventory, and then there's a button for it.
- Wait, I have a tattoo.
- What?
- Under my other possessions,
it says a tattoo or other body marker.
(laughing)
- You have a tattoo in your inventory?
- Yeah, I have a tattoo in my inventory.
- What is it of?
- Oh, you better decide when to use it.
- I'll figure out what it is next.
It'll come up next game.
- I wonder if Goliaths have tattoo
and the tattoos in the lore of 5e and that's why.
- Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know why I-- - I think they do.
They do.
They have-- - Oh, pretty funny.
- They're all like--
- To put it in your inventory too.
- Yeah. - That's where you store
that information. - Well, I have no gold
in my inventory.
- Yeah, I had 15 gold.
- Now he gives you 500. - I have none.
Now you've off at 500 before you go shopping.
- Well you have to put it in my inventory.
Oh wait, nevermind, there it is.
- Look, headmaster eat your pussy up
is right to be concerned about the Serpent King,
but he's wrong about where the Serpent King resides.
- The lake. - I see his reasoning
for thinking so.
He thinks it's in the sea.
That's right, and it makes sense.
But he's in fact very much a humanoid creature
that lives amongst us.
lives amongst the academy. - Voldemort.
- Now, maybe Voldemort, but where he lives, I don't know.
I've had my scouts trace much
of the winged serpent activities,
and all I know is that he either lives
within the academy town,
or at least frequents it quite often.
I don't mean to put a strain on your weekend,
but I'd like it if the three of you investigated
the whereabouts of the Serpent King just a little bit,
just to get started, nothing too obvious,
you don't want to tip him off.
Ask around, head to local haunts,
try to gather some leads.
My fear as a Serpent King is somehow connected
to a growing resentment the Academy Town,
for the Academy, inside the Academy Town.
I've seen some of this in Port Los Beriberi.
People are not taken kindly to magic users these days.
The Pleasure Men are, well, they've risen in power
and they're quite cruel.
So I just wanna make sure I know what's going on.
And Dogen, you've done wonderful work with me before
and I just thought I'd be happy to ask you again
for your help.
And you can keep that gold whether you decide
you wanna help me or not.
It's all fine with me.
I just hadn't seen you in a while
and it felt like I could have been more of a support for you
during your unceremonious firing.
All right.
- Hello, my name is--
- Worldwide favorite king.
This guy, the big one, he's good.
Look, Andre--
There's a new guy in the room.
Oh yeah, Sherman.
(laughs)
Hi, hi there.
Hi.
Hello.
Sorry, hi.
Hello, hi.
Oh, this is good, this is like a mirror--
This is a game of wits that I see--
Facing each other, yeah.
Play out.
Before me yeah, yeah, you just keep saying hi to each other
I'll have mud marks beam you guys back if you have any questions for me though feel free to ask mud marks
And he'll patch it to me all that good stuff. I try not to be so
What's the word you know? I'm not trying to be so sneaky. You know hey
Gay, that's fair to
You're filing it that you're acting very guy
Well I should I assume a satyr would know that for sure for certain right
Fuck are you trying to say about my friends?
You're a satyr
Yeah, very usually very sexually expressive and exploratory creatures of course
Roll deception
(laughing)
- Okay, all right, well.
Hmm, 18.
- That's pretty good.
- You did a good job.
- Yeah.
- Impressive, does your mom know your gay technique
from Patches there?
- Yeah, that was pretty well done, but you failed.
- I did fail.
- He doesn't, okay, well.
- I'm happy to--
- You just successfully lied that you're not gay.
(laughing)
- So I'm not.
- All right, I can send you fellows on your way.
You can spend the weekend in the town.
Go shopping, enjoy yourself. - Yes, we want the weekend.
- Okay, all right.
- We're really harshing Friday right now.
- I apologize, well.
And-- - What's the,
give us a recommendation.
What's the best store in the entire town?
- Wait, I know the best store in the town.
- Yeah, you know what?
In the world. - In the world, yeah.
- In the world. - Anywhere.
- The best store in the world.
That's really tough.
The best store in town is Casual Male XL.
*laughter*
What?
It's the best store in the world.
It's the only place I've been able to buy clothes.
The best store in the world was uh,
the Sullivan's General store in Trebuchet Village,
but I think that's been long gone.
Oh, fuck off, shut up, fuck you, fuck you.
Shut up.
I slap him.
No, I understand. Yeah, you guys go back.
Yeah.
And you see a mud mark says,
all right, well, off to bed with a lot of you.
Tuck yourselves in.
I put a gold piece
on four times.
I put a gold piece in Mud Marks's mouth
because I'm trying to make an in-app purchase on a game.
Yeah, OK, you'll be able to pop, you'll be able to honk Harpo's nose
a little bit more next time.
Hooray!
You know, Harpo doesn't necessarily usually wear like a clown nose, but I'm open to the
idea.
Um, cool.
And I guess the battle did take a little longer, so next time we will go on a shopping spree.
Hell yeah.
Hooray!
Fuck yes.
Yes.
Alright.
Hogsmeade.
I'm gonna get my, I'm gonna add a zero to my gold right now, bitch.
Nothing you can do about it.
You're gonna forget.
I will.
I just gave myself a hundred million copper.
Okay.
So I'll change a lot of that stuff then.
- No, I'm gonna add even more.
- Okay, well, you're making it harder for me to change it.
The more gold you add, I have to take each one away
one by one.
- Really?
- Oh, then I'm adding so many.
- Stop!
Stop!
- Well, I didn't add any, so I'm actually--
- Oh, okay.
All right, Julio, can you talk for a second?
Yeah, Julio, can you talk?
- What?
- Can you read out the thing that I sent you?
- Okay.
- Just as a closing.
How do I get my parents to put me back in diapers?
I am really desperate, but I can't tell them.
Please help.
Any way is okay.
- Okay, thanks guys.
- Thanks everyone, bye.
Well, here's another fast food one.
Can I sue McDonald's over there being snot
like substance in my drink?
I don't know if intentional or not,
still unacceptable during COVID.
(laughing)
Jess was getting some hot axe and hot chocolate
to start of my morning.
I've never had any problems before at any other locations till this morning.
I order hot chocolate with my meal, but when I drank it,
taste it like a slimy goopy.
(laughter)
amazing line to be given. This is to go to court. It tasted like a slimy
gooby. Your honor, it tasted like a slimy gooby.
The gooby, please bring out the slimy gooby. The taste was
completely off and had gooey substance all over it. Really don't have words to
describe texture. It was same texture like snot, used my fork and scraped up
lots from the inside. I have photos I can provide if needed, just need place
to send them. I'm never usually that guy, but this is my first time ever
actually feeling like I have to leave a report. I'm open to being tested or
ever to prove it's not my own.
He kept the slimy gooby?
He took a photo.
He took a photo but how are you going to test it?
He's keeping it man.
I had so many of this type of thing of finding slime or gooby.
This should be...
Gooby? You looked up gooby?
This is not a one for the...
Everyone keeps it.
Everyone says I still have it.
I put it in my fridge.
I don't think that this is a problem for the United States court system.
This is a problem for Maury.
This is a Maury that...
It is not your gooby!
It's not your gooby?
Yes!
It's not my fucking gooby!
He does a backflip.
He does a backflip, yeah.
Fifty backflips in a row, not my gooby.
The gooby does not belong to you!
(upbeat music)