Last trebuchet village arc was Tales from the Seabomb, End of the World, Sin Bad, Virtue Good, Lady Better.
Which was supposed to be an adventure to realms deep, the supposed end of the world, in order to rescue Solvin the Frog from his death in the terrifying realm, the one you caused.
You'd explore the islands of the virtue good archipelago, Archipelago? Archipelago? Archipelago.
Learn more about the creatures that live there, both native and colonized by the Terrafire Kingdom,
visiting port towns that hinted at incredible strange lands and adventures unknown to you or
anyone within the kingdom. Instead, you hate Sullivan and decided to try to sail as far
away from him as possible.
The epic joke would have been that because the world is round, and nobody knows that,
you would have found your way to the end of the world either way, and therefore to Sullivan.
However, instead, Patrick Yodar, Evil Stievel, and Rod Doge and you the Dirt Goblin, the
original crew, encountered world pools, hot babes, strange runes and witches, beasts and
Spongebob Islands, fleshy submarines, death, and vanishing acts.
Patrick learned of his uncle/father, Trunchbull's, past as a member of a pirate crew,
60 tricksters eating chicky tinders and their mixing genders with their 120 fingers,
and a maroon placed on his mother who lived on Hot Babe Island.
That killed her when Patrick tried to speak with her about some sort of truth,
a truth she kept long buried, that likely will die with her.
And then Patrick died soon after that.
But not before he helped to create mud marks from the corpse of his mother, himself, and a couple of ugly women.
The goal became to vibe mud marks, and the only place to do that would be the Berry Berry Academy.
In honor of Patrick, they would do so. And also because that would be funny for you guys to do.
Once the now two heroes were set on a journey, a mysterious massive yethound chased you across the sea,
and that became easier to avoid once Evil Ndoga invited Chuggie the Singing Submarine to their party,
and sailed within him, or, they were inside of his body, and they went through the sea.
A couple other adventure-y moments happened until they reached Port Los Beriberi, a port
town where they can get entry to the academy if they knew the right people.
They stumbled on one of those people, Condoleezza Carlo, a powerful, psychopathic warlock who
lives in a lighthouse off the coast of Beriberi and tricks sailors into crashing their ships
and robbing them of their goods.
He said he'd help our heroes become academy professors so they could vive mud marks if
they investigated the Popo Tower at the southern tip of the Terrifier Kingdom, where, apparently,
Stickyfingers was headed.
Stickyfingers at this point was the leader of the Thieves' Guild, or originally was the
leader of the Thieves' Guild in the Terrifier Kingdom, but after King Nardwuar's madness
subsided and people started to doubt his ability to rule, he rose in rank, filled in some sort
of void there, became a more... part of the kingdom in a more official capacity as a
powerful intelligence organization, leader of a powerful intelligence
organization. Sticky Fingers was also a part of Trunchbull's crew, the 60
tricksters eating Chicky Tinders crew, and may have had answers about
Patrick's origin and why his mother died, and may have even caused it, it's unclear.
However, to get any of these questions answered, they'd have to meet with him, but once they
reached the Popo Tower and scaled it, our heroes came face to face with a dead Sticky Fingers,
who died in a fray because of an incredible battle between a massive, harpy, bird-like
woman and a ghost or spirit of some kind that resembled the police, the virtuous god of
good that had been expelled from the land by the Terrifier, the god of evil.
Sticky Fingers died in that fray, right?
And after the harpy was bested by the police, Evil Stevel, for some reason, looked beyond
the horizon across the white fog that surrounds the Terrifier kingdom and vanished.
And it's unclear exactly where, and some of that might be answered in this campaign, most
likely in another one.
But Dogen believes he's dead, and Chuggie exploded.
And so Dogen was all alone, and kind of shell-shocked from the whole experience.
Now other loose ends that have yet to be tied up are out there and are progressing.
And you guys will learn more about them within this campaign.
I'll try to find organic ways to sprinkle in those details about what's going on in the
outside world.
to build that into the story here.
But it's only going to show up if there's, you know, some remote curiosity about it.
But yeah, that's what happened in the last campaign more or less.
So...
Marlon Rees is a hardy tiefling who works in the town of Wayneswood just outside of the
academy, the Berryberry Academy.
His daughter, Regatta Rees, is a 12th year student there, set to graduate and join an
advisory council to a lord in the dirtlands just up north.
Regatta's magical prowess meant she could get a near full ride to the academy, provided
Marlon worked at the crystal mines every day for 12 hours with no breaks.
So Marlin did just that.
Marlin didn't have a knack for magic, he could barely cast an alert spell, crucial to his
mining work.
But he was strong, spending over a decade in the Klutzes, a now dwindling monster hunter
guild.
And he was crafty, fashioning his leather belt with a sigil his daughter enchanted to rattle
in the instance of a cave-in.
He was lucky he could count on her, and when she finally leaves the academy, the money she'll
send back from the dirtlands should provide him something resembling retirement.
Marlon Rees has worked Mine 24A for over 30 years, and he has never been deeper in the
mine than he is now.
His headlamp, powered by one of the many crystals mined by the workers like him, is augmented
with a brighter light that can also sense hostility or precariousness as the cone of
light moves across the surface, creating a faint outline of alternating colors around
lit objects that indicate levels of danger.
It assesses the familiarity with a territory or object, it contains an index for extreme
motion and temperature, as well as the will of anything that is lit, an estimation of
it.
It's an incredibly complex sigil, another of Rigatta's inventions, one that got her
into the academy in the first place at the age of ten.
Despite Beriberi Academy's distaste for her family's ability to pay admission, or inability,
Rigatta's aptitude simply could not be denied.
This far down the mine, Marlin has seen an outline of light orange around most of the
cliffs and jagged rock scattered, jutting about, no longer contained by a proper mining tunnel.
The color likely relates to a combination of unfamiliarity of the territory and the
sharp decline as Marlin continues his descent.
He uses his long, strong tiefling tail to help stabilize his climb, using his claws to grip
the sides of the rock face.
Meanwhile, a container, given to him by the Pleasureman Lord, clanked against his belt.
occasionally interrupting his footing, but he made do, shifting his body and readjusting
his weight, looking for the occasional surface that could almost pass as a platform where
there's not such a risk of each one crumbling beneath his heavy boots.
His years fighting monsters and mining, along with his being a tiefling, made his hands
rough, his body strong, but also his bones beaten and himself fatigued.
Still he made his way down, further and further.
This was his way out, after all.
You'd never have to work a day in these damned mines again.
He just needs to find a soft crystal.
And now we zoom out of this little mine story.
Minecraft story mode.
Minecraft story.
You're doing the Minecraft story mode.
You literally said killing monsters and mining.
And we look now above at the Beriberi Academy.
From the sky above the Terrafire Kingdom, were you to look down on E-Bomb, you'd see
a landmass of browns, whites, grays, and tans, the static blues of the sea, all of it cut
off by a vast, churning, otherworldly white fog. And then, on the southernmost part of
the landmass, a sharp, bright, glittering gleam of azure, twinkling pockmarks upon the earth.
Diving through the clouds, these reveal themselves to be the famous beriberi crystals, massive
deposits that hover just above the green sloping spires that make up the academy, lighting the
manicured garden below. The Academy itself sits atop a pond, seemingly hovering above
nothing. Any member of the Academy must pass an initial test of identifying the interplanar
floor that rests above the water. Once they do, they are able to walk atop of it, between
the buildings. Everyone else can take the magically powered skiffs that litter the pond
and help the non-magical staff and visitors navigate the Academy.
The Beriberi Academy's De Minestrone, the main building at the center of the Minestrone
Pond has a large atrium and auditorium that links to the four massive spires that connect
via alabaster bridges.
Each of the four spires that make up the castle, the minestrone, represents one of the four
houses.
House Birdo, House Megabat, House Giant, and House Kaiju Manji.
They house the students and faculty and have classes that specialize in magics often associated
with each house.
The four spires that make up the Dei Minestrone contain elevators for non-magic users, but
but is otherwise largely composed of rapidly changing chutes and ladders that magical students
and faculty alike must anticipate and navigate to get from one location to the next.
The other buildings surrounding the academy include a center of combat, athletics, and
dangerous magics, a greenhouse, alchemical lab, and runic experimentation facility, artificer
workshop, a creature sanctuary, and a rotating crop farm, grain storage, and warehouse for
non-magical creatures.
There are varying observatories and chambers that exist amongst and atop the spires, all
outfitted to equip any aspiring witches, wizards, warlocks, and the like with whatever they need
to excel.
We return to the Dei Minestrone, that main building, and climb the Kaiju Manji spire.
We pass by all manner of pervy portraits, goofy ghosts, and weirdy cantrips, and make
furniture dance and faculty flail, and we finally reach the dormitory of House Kaiju
Manji.
Along the walls are vast, beastly carvings of unknowable monstrosities, and if you stare
too long you'll go mad.
That is, unless you have been selected to join the house.
Then these kaiju manji of yore give you a perverse comfort and hazy serenity, a oneness.
But none of you have been sorted yet into the house.
Dogen, you sit in the iron, dendritic chairs in front of an everlasting black fire.
chairs what no like looks like no looks like dander no it's not it's like looks
like tree branches or dandruff dendritic Denzel you ponder I sit as a dandruff
chair these days I've been you ponder damn I'm sorry to hear that me too you
ponder how did I get here have I really lost Patrick and evil who was that guy
Well, you can say this all better yourself.
Who is that guy?
Who's that guy?
I don't know that I have questioned that question in my intro.
Where are my friends and who's that guy?
What in the hell is that?
Well, it finally happened.
I, Dogen the Diploma Goblin, am in big trouble.
After arriving at Beriberi Academy and vibing Quadra Mud Marks, I felt a deep void in my
my life, a void created by the loss of Evil Stievel
and whatever that sexual submarine's name was
that I can't remember at all.
I was living like a pig, sleeping 'til the sundial
said, "Aye, aye, aye," and eating depression meals
like hard-boiled quail eggs and whole roast pig
with apple in its mouth.
But then, I pulled myself up by my bootstraps
and landed a job.
That's right, I became a teacher at the academy.
I taught sex magic for two years.
My name was hard for my students to pronounce,
So they called me Mr. D.
These were the best years of my little green life.
But then I got in trouble.
See, the headmaster, Mr. Eat Your Pussy Up,
found something out.
Not only did he find out that I don't have
the proper credentials to be teaching sex magic,
but he found out that there isn't even such a thing
as sex magic.
So he suspended me.
Me, Mr. D.
And it turns out there's only one way to get my job back,
and that's to receive the proper education
to qualify me for it.
In short, I need a diploma.
So now, after years of creating hundreds of enemies
in the student body through harsh grading,
inappropriate comments, and corporeal punishment,
I've been forced to enroll in Berry Berry Academy
as a first year.
I'm so nervous.
What will my school career bring?
Do I need to bring my backpack tomorrow?
Without a steady paycheck,
I can already feel myself slipping back into depression.
The only thing that could save me at this point
is a core friend group.
- Wow, that's great.
- And also I'm wearing, they say dress for the job you want,
not the job you have.
So first day of school, cap and gown.
- Damn, I like that.
- And so Dogen, you sit in the Kaiju Manji house,
even though you don't belong to the house yet.
Now the reason for that is because you're still good friends
with Condoleezza Carlo,
a warlock who helped you guys in the last campaign.
And I will also have to, I just realized this,
I didn't want to take up too much time,
but I will also give a last time on the campaign.
Probably just realized we just jumped right into that.
So I will do that as well, but we'll get there.
- It's been a minute.
- Yeah, it's been a minute.
So Condoleezza Carlo, who's a warlock,
who helped you guys towards the end of the last campaign,
he helped get you the job.
He is friends, or at least seems to know
the head of the Kaiju Manji house, who is...
Oh man, I have so many fucking notes.
Make sure I'm looking at the right ones.
The head of the Kaiju Manji house, who is...
Okay, I need to have like seven different windows.
Where are you, buddy?
Oh, geez.
Gaston, yes!
Okay, yeah, I remember this. Gaston.
And so he was able to squeeze you in here.
You and Mud Marks are here too.
And so Mud Marks, if you recall, is made up of,
I believe, Patrick's head, his mother's head,
and two, like, sort of five out of ten women.
And the four of them together on top of a kind of a mud body,
and they look like the Marks brothers.
And the whole point of the last campaign,
besides trying to avoid Sullivan,
was eventually to vibe him.
And you have vibed him.
And so, uh, yeah, he's, uh, he's there.
Yeah.
To answer any of your questions, if you got them, you know, who is that guy?
It's a Groucho Marx, right?
Uh, wait, wait, hold on.
Wait a minute.
I shot an elephant in my pajamas.
Why he was wearing my pajamas.
I don't know.
That's pretty.
That's all right.
Right.
I mean, he got it.
Got it.
Chico, Chico, Chico, the marks.
Right.
He sounded like it is.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
It'll make more sense.
I'm seeing the vision.
Yeah, and so they're all kind of, they're bickering, "Zeppo's dead, his head just never worked
out."
And then Harpo once in a while will honk a horn.
Yeah.
But yeah, today will be the first day you're going to get your, you're going to get to
be-
I can't wait to get sorted.
The sorting ceremony.
I'm so excited to get sorted.
- But we'll sort of-- - I can't wait to go party, man.
- We'll zoom out from that,
and we'll introduce the two other characters,
and then I'll do a last time on this campaign.
So we're at the gates of,
where all the students are filing in from the Academy town.
They take these skiff boats provided to them
to get to the gates of the Academy,
and they're let in, they show their letter of admission,
their, you know, if you remember from the last one,
that was the whole thing,
was to be able to get that kind of letter
to get in there if you could, and they all have them.
And so I'd like to meet first our friend, the satyr.
- Okay, you hear, off camera.
- It's cutting out on Discord.
- Well, it's cutting out on my mic, bitch.
- I see you making a funny shape of your mouth.
- Clopping and clopping, okay?
(laughing)
Okay.
The name's Woody.
I'm from a druid enclave up there in troll country.
I'm a satyr.
The whole neighborhood used to be satyrs.
But then trolls started moving in and ruining the neighborhood.
They listen to horrid music.
And they stepped on me brother.
And they stepped on me father.
Me mum's making me go to this school so I can get me business degree.
Send coin back to mum.
She actually brought me here.
I'm riding on her back right now.
I can feel a lump on her back, probably not so good.
I got selected by the academy because I got a 1900 on my SATYR.
School should be easy.
Doing card tricks and making a pencil turn to rubber?
Sounds fine by me.
I'm mostly here to attempt to have an inappropriate relationship with a teacher or ex-teacher,
especially a goblin.
Oi, I'm so proud of you.
I'm so proud of you Woody.
I love you too, hon.
- I love you so much, I don't wanna leave.
- The only conversations they ever have with each other.
- I love you so much, mom.
I don't wanna leave yet.
I want you to come with me to school.
- I can't come with you to school.
- There's gold in my backyard.
- I love you.
- Fly on the wall, drop into a conversation
between a son and a mom and they're just going,
I love you so much, I love you.
- I love you.
- I love you so much, mom.
I wanna meet a girl just like you while I'm here at school.
Oh, don't flatter me.
I wanna marry her and bring her home.
I love you, your father was just like you.
Love you, mom.
Till the troll.
Love you.
Bye.
Love you so much, mom.
Mom, don't leave me, I love you.
I gotta go.
Alright, I'll see you later.
Bye.
Bye, mom, love you.
Kisses.
Average Australian family.
Kisses and smooches all the way home, mom.
You know it, honey.
Alright, bye.
you're crocky boy farewell
this is like there's a line holding up or right yeah the door like what mom and
son keep almost having sex well I was hugging he's making it sex positive
Sex positive everyone else died
Of course we love each other and who's right, but who's right behind
This Sater
So we're all on a skiff together I guess
We're all in this boat, and I'm sitting in the way back, and I'm making the boat is pretty much vertical
Because of where I'm sitting
Because I'm a oh you're playing yourself right
Oh
Campaign new campaign. I'm sitting in the back. I'm a
And then I pull out a piece of paper
And I because I think that I have to introduce myself to everybody
And I pull a piece of paper out of my pocket, and I stand up
So you're a Goliath
Pull the piece of paper out of my pocket I go hello
My name is Andre behave for I
am 15 feet tall I
Am from the Goliath Kingdom and I like
Dark things and I like gothic things
Recently I learned that I have magic powers
And I'm going to do my best in school
because I
And then I pee
Actually quite nervous I'm 15 feet and I'm 15 years old right and
And, um...
Is the whole school gonna be on a boat?
Or...
Uh, yeah, you see one of the...
Are we gonna be...
...one of the folks works the gate.
Oh, no, we won't all be on a boat.
Um, there's an academy inside.
May I ask your magical discipline?
Your class.
My class is first grade.
Right.
*laughter*
So, which type of magic do you...
- Okay, do you do, are you a wizard, a warlock?
- I'm Andre Behavoir.
- Yeah, we're gonna do this?
- And I'm in the first grade, and I'm 15.
- So Andre Behavoir is a warlock.
- I am a warlock, I specialize in dark magic,
and necromancy and stuff.
- And also-- - My intelligence is six.
- Yeah, so that's part of what's happening here.
- That's why I'm in the first grade.
- And the-- - You have a bad brain.
- The satyr, our satyr friend Woody
is a druid, a circle of the land.
- That's facts.
And plus I'm an acolyte.
- Yes, and an acolyte.
(laughing)
Some faith of some kind.
And Andre Behavoir is a warlock
who's a patron is a great old one,
and who's packed of the tome.
And yeah, you hear--
- And explain who my--
- Yeah, you hear inside your mind, you hear,
(mimics mumbling)
you know, that kind of like Doppler effect
of like hearing somebody talk into your mind
and then it sort of settles into something.
He goes, "Hey man!"
- Hello, doing?
- Oh wow, I cannot get used to this.
Too weird.
- Dylan, it's my first day of school.
- Oh, okay, pretty cool, pretty cool, pretty cool.
You're telling me that Dylan is a infinite being
that is on other planets?
- Dylan, Patches and I decided that the star
in Dylan's shirt allows him to communicate
between every single world.
- Okay, so in-- - In Gun City.
- Is Dylan right now on Earth?
Dylan is right now, yeah, Dylan's in a,
Dylan is in a Dylan's Candy Bar.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- At the airport.
- Talking to his shirt.
Saying, "Oh no, yeah, the licorice, thanks."
- Oh wait, can you, I forgot me lunch, can you--
- He's walking down Fifth Avenue.
No, I'm sorry, I can't help you.
- You can't put the candy through your shirt
and give me some--
- No, I told you about this already.
It's not like that.
That would be pretty awesome though.
- You can only communicate with me right.
- And give you powers.
- Oh, what about candy powers?
- Hey, maybe that school can teach you candy powers.
I'm fresh out.
- Oh right.
Well, off to school then.
- Look, you're gonna do great.
- I step out of the boat and everyone flies by.
Every single part like like full like catapults back.
They have to swim to the school but there is a piranha in the lake.
What.
Just one. No problem unless there's a whole.
There's one piranha.
One piranha.
But it's big.
It's going to bite you.
So when you guys all when you two walk into the school you're greeted by this
an image that I will put in the discord of
the academy of a beautiful fountain with these sort of large blue crystals floating above
different objects inside of the place.
Yeah, I guess, Jubia, if you want to pull that up, you could pull that up.
I don't know how this works for you, but if not, I could just put it in the Discord.
But you see the green sloping towers and the white bridges and all that.
And as you walk through the fountain, you approach towards the entrance of the main building where
you're being directed to go as you walk through the gardens.
And it is that sort of,
there is, you see students walking on the water automatically
and as you guys take your first hesitant steps,
you realize you can as well.
And that's part of why you're let into this academy
is your ability to recognize
these kinds of interplanar elements,
these kinds of magical things that other people can't.
And so you're able to walk along the water
through the door into the auditorium,
where we're gonna be introduced
to the rest of your classmates,
where you're gonna meet perhaps a new friend named--
- And I know we're gonna meet a Draco Malfoy type.
I know we're going to. - You got that right.
- Don't tell me we're about to meet
a motherfucking Deadly. - I'm gonna kill him on sight.
I'm not even gonna let it get to that level.
If he even seems a little blonde, I'm snapping his neck.
I'm not even letting the rivalry blossom.
- Nope.
So when you guys enter into the auditorium
and you see all the, do you,
do you guys meet each other as you walk in?
Like how do you guys, I want you guys to tell me
how you meet. - I don't wanna meet them yet.
I don't wanna meet them yet.
- You don't wanna meet them yet?
You wanna send your own kind of thing?
- Well I feel like we shouldn't meet for a second, okay?
- Yeah. - No.
- There's no candy cart, we can take some kind of--
- So you see some older girl students.
- But that's the only way you become friends at Hogwarts.
- All right, that's true. - That's true as fuck.
(thunder rumbling)
- I guess, wait, aren't I in a weird different place?
- Well, you should have left by now
to go down to the auditorium.
- Oh my God, I'm late. - What about this?
What about, I'm trying to walk into the only non-magic door
and it's not big enough and it's blocking his exit.
Mm-hmm whose exit
Maybe I can maybe I'm late and I run in when everyone's already seated everyone
I'm gonna go ahead. I'm gonna go you do what you want. I'm gonna go sit in the front
The very front because I like audience interaction, and I want to maybe get crowd worked
I'm gonna go ahead. I'm also sitting in the front. I'm gonna go
only
and some hot wings to my table and
I'm sitting directly in front of him you guys are sitting you guys are sitting right at the front
You're the only people sitting right at the front every other seat is filled up
So the only place to sit is at the front and nobody wants to sit there
Everyone already seeed and then everyone's sitting down and the guy gets on stage maybe even mm-hmm. Yeah, I'd like to turn to
What's his name again reservoir and Andre Andre behavior
Hey there, you big bubble. You like the front seat too, huh? Cold shot going on this event.
You called me a bubble? Yeah, you big bubbler. Look at you! You're all full of blubber.
You look like a damn troll. Are you a troll? I'm from...
Goliath Town.
Goliath? Girl like a girl?
Like a beautiful girl.
It's well
I'm confused now. Oh you take a break and let's watch the show
What do you have you like berries and stuff just the whole I got some hot wings bitch, I just told nice
Oh, yeah, magical and I eat the whole table. Oh, yeah, it is very much like Harry Potter
Sweet sweets and sweet treats are appearing on in front of you on the on the table and the long tables
You see a non-magical,
see very tired non-magical catering staff
just like wheeling in shit.
- And turning into a chunky robot.
- And yeah, and as you guys gather around,
oh yeah, Dogen, are you there
or are you running, rushing there late?
- I'm waiting, I'm waiting,
I'm not gonna burst into the room
until whoever's giving the speech gives the speech.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, for sure.
- I'm gonna have a big entrance.
- You have a big entrance.
- A big awkward entrance that makes everybody hate me.
- Okay, cool.
- Wait, so I can manifest any,
they're gonna manifest any food that I'm thinking of
at this table is what you're saying?
'Cause you cut out.
- I didn't quite say that, but I like that idea.
- That's a crazy thing to jump to.
- Yeah, that's what you're saying.
- Manifest food.
- Was that what you're saying?
- Let's say, yeah, let's--
- They're gonna manifest food onto the tables magically?
- Let's say you're right.
Do it.
- Okay, I have a woolly mammoth's leg.
- Nice.
- A burnt woolly mammoth's leg, and it's so big.
- It's there.
It's funny 'cause what it is,
it has to be pulled from the like,
not like the farm and like, you know,
organic material sort of warehouse thing.
So it's just like, it's like being constructed
and created with like transmutation magic.
You're just seeing like a whole chunk of it
just leave the warehouse and appear in front of you
as a woolly mammoth's leg.
- The Holy Mammoth shows up,
you can see it through a kind of portal thing,
and you can see a man pulling its leg off.
- Yeah, you're like (growls)
and it's just collapsing over, and it's there for you.
- Hooray!
- And yeah, as you're eating it,
a little snot-nosed boy comes up to you,
and he goes, "Hey Tiny, how 'bout a salad instead?"
Oh, who's this? Roger Clemens.
I flick him.
I flick at him. Ow! Oh, you're a punk.
What's wrong with you? You're as stupid as you are big, I bet.
I swing my mammoth leg at him. Because I'm not smart enough to come with a...
Yeah, roll a d20.
Just roll an attack roll. Just go to your character.
Or other is it beyond 20?
Yeah, just drink through now. Yeah, I
Got a 17
Yeah, I mean you you hit him in the head roll. There should be a damage option. I
Didn't see that. Hold up. I would do do your from your actions. Just do your I supposed to have roll 20 open
No, no, I'd be beyond men. Oh, of course just hit the damage button on next to the quarter staff in your
Right, right, quarter staff, where is it?
Tell me what you get.
Hold up, is it in my inventory?
If you go to your actions and all, it'll be right there.
Are you on your character sheet?
Yeah, I'm on my character sheet.
Where is it?
I never remember how to use this website.
Yeah, me neither.
Frankly.
Just click, it should be the default actions.
Yeah, I have, well I don't have a quarter staff
or anything like that. Well it just came up,
You just said that you rolled it.
I rolled it.
I just saw it on my screen.
Okay, thank you.
So I'd refresh your page is what I would do.
That's probably the problem.
It's in the bottom left corner.
Okay no VTT matches were found.
Oh, here's my quarter staff.
Alright, wait, roll.
23 quarter staff.
So that's the attack roll, which you already got.
- Okay, well I got two, if I do, yeah I got five.
- Nice, okay yeah.
So you clobber this guy for five damage.
He's like, "Ow!
"Wait 'til my father hears about this!
"He's on the council at Berry Berry Academy!"
- My father's on the toilet right now.
(laughing)
- Ew, is that Elsa from Frozen?
That sucks!
- I swing at him again, but I miss.
- Yeah, all right.
he says Elsa from Frozen sucks.
- Yeah.
- I'm outta here!
And I'll be seeing you punks later.
Don't try to join House Kaiju Manji either.
And he leaves.
- Okay, I won't try that.
- Okay, cool.
- So we know which one is Slytherin now.
- Yeah.
Well, they're not quite Slytherin.
But anyway.
- So we know which one's Hufflepuff.
- Mm-hmm, sure.
And so then a teacher, an ancient pleasureman,
Um, approaches the stage, lightly floating above, pins and needles inside his head.
Um, and he begins to speak.
It's my birthday!
He begins to speak.
This is how they get you to talk to them.
It's my birthday!
It's his birthday!
Congratulations, and welcome to the school.
Thank you, thank you!
Thank you.
Are you gonna ask if we're together?
I'm going to ask the whole room a question
All right
What is magic really?
It's a series of spells. I take my thumb and my other hand and I start doing this number
Something like this or bad
Right about here. Wait a minute. He's lost his thumb. It looks like I got two thumbs
white to
And a young young woman's raises her hand and says
It's manipulation of spiritual forces that come from the realm between realms
Hermione think I'm gonna have sex with that one
that is
technically correct
Miss regatta Reese
never mind
Put a somewhat different lens on it for all the students today, and then the doors slam open
Running oh my god. Oh my god. I'm so sorry. Oh my god. I'm sorry
I'm sorry, and I'm running down and I've got my cap and gown and I'm running to find an open seat
I step on the edge of my gown I could buy tumble I flip over I land on my head the flat
Mortarboard of my cap I stay I'm stuck on it. I'm standing complete
I'm completely upside down just on my head my good my gown falls up
Falls up and down over my body. Are you wearing a naked body? No
Jostle's my my innards and my bladder punctures and all my pee starts pouring out
Into my mouth and I'm choking on my pee in front of everybody
And also yeah when I turn upside down - everything falls out of my pockets all my keys on my coins
I've had I have like I have five pounds of coins in my pocket gold coins that all go completely across the entire floor
Roll perception Andre, okay
19 okay cool, so you notice in front of you one of the
Teachers who is lining the back was one of the headmasters headmaster of house kaiju manji. This was guest stone
You see him sort of fade into
Like kind of a black abyss and then appear right behind
Dogen and
Woody and he picks both of you guys up by the scruff of your neck
I'm upside down so he holds my butt yeah
- Yeah, you scruffy your butt.
And he goes to you, Dogen, he like,
he holds you up higher so your head--
- First he looks over at Woody,
and like looks him right in the face,
then he turns and he's looking right at my--
- Yeah, and he whispers to your butt.
Yeah, he holds, he whispers to your butt,
he starts to whisper to your butt,
and then he stops and like flips you around,
and says, "We let you stay inside of our house.
"Now I need you to behave yourself."
It was an accident, and if you think I did that on purpose, I'll kill myself.
No! He's gonna kill himself! Don't!
You can't hear that, I whispered.
He's got a suicide vest, bomb on!
No I don't! And I lift up my gown again and show it.
Yeah, come on!
He plops the two of you down next to the Goliath, next to Andre, and looks to you, Andre, and says, "Watch them."
Okay.
I snuggle up on his arm.
I'm just looking down at them like this.
(laughter)
And uh,
Mr. Eat Your Pussy Up
continues his speech.
He sort of goes, "Um, okay, well."
"Can you start over?
I missed a lot."
"Well, I began it with 'What is magic, really?'"
"Oh, well, technically it's, uh,
what, uh, I don't remember what the girl said before."
- Say a series of spells.
- A series of spelling.
- Spells.
- Magic.
Let's put a different lens on it, is what I was at.
Magic as a means to--
- Oh, it seems like I didn't miss that much after all.
Sorry, sorry everybody, sorry.
- You see the students roll their eyes.
See, Regatta Reese is like,
"I can't believe these first years."
You know, she's not having it.
Or is she? Or is she your secret new friend? But then he goes on.
Magic as a means to increase happiness and well-being of others.
Magic as a source of pleasure. The ultimate source of pleasure.
One that can't be denied by non-magical threats or the likes of beasts.
or even the designs of our most ardent enemies.
Our pleasure, your pleasure, will not be denied, children.
Pleasure denied to children? What?
That's not a good thing to say, really.
What did you say?
Well, you're all, even if you're adults, you're children to me, because I'm teaching you.
That's not the thing we had a problem with.
Yeah, well, you said it there.
said it there. Here you will learn, here you will grow, here you shall grow in magical
prowess and spread our ethos throughout the land. I have magical prowess, that's why I,
that's what I, I learned I had magical prowess and then. Berry Berry Academy was founded on
the principles laid out by the original founder Narcotics Minestrone and we are so fortunate to
to even have his great, great, great, great, great,
great, great granddaughter as the head of the house birdo.
You see this sort of, like, sort of arched eyebrow,
high ponytail, let's say a bitch.
- A basic bitch or just a bitch?
- A bitch, Italian bitch,
with these sort of like elaborate feathered gown.
No, she's not basic.
- Hey, I've already dealt with that at home.
- Or these.
- She's not basic.
- And then you start to take in the other people
next to these folks, right?
- Are there any basic people here?
- I mean, some of the students are pretty basic.
- I stand up.
I stand up because I can sense,
or I hear him ask that.
Or were you asking in character?
- No, I wasn't.
- Oh, nevermind then.
I was gonna say, I was gonna stand up and say,
if you're basic, stay the hell away from me.
- And we're lucky to have the esteemed company
of all the heads of the houses,
we have Karen, the head of the Megabats.
- Oh, hell no.
- You see a woman with,
(laughing)
with like white hair,
like spread out, like in shock,
and her eyes wide,
and she just goes like,
(imitating screeching)
She just kinda screeches.
- Classic Karen. - Homo.
the half giant, and the head of the house of giants.
And of course, Gaston, the head of house Kaiju Manji.
You see Hamo, and he's just sort of like a meek giant.
And he sort of sounds like you, actually.
- Is it the same Hamo who shot 50 Cent nine times?
- Maybe.
- Oh my God, we'll get to the bottom of this.
- Hi, hi.
- He sort of waves at everybody.
- Hello.
- And you wave back, you're the only one
waves back immediately.
And you see a Gaston who sort of looks like,
looks kind of like Anton Chigurh,
but with cooler hair.
And,
but yeah, oh man, I wrote,
I'll move on.
And he says, "Now, first year students,
"it's time for our sorting ceremony
to determine what house you will be enrolled in.
- I'm so excited.
What house do you guys wanna get?
- I want to get whatever you guys are in.
That's all I care about.
- Me too.
- This will most likely be the sole house
for the rest of your time here.
The sorting ritual has rarely been wrong.
Its magic is based in its primordial construction.
- Magic is based?
- Its magic is based and not cringe.
The crystals. - I'll be the judge of that, man.
"Each of you shall rise and place the sorting gauge inside of your earlobe, where it will
then ask you questions and work to extract your greatest truths."
And so you see one first-year student go up there, and he takes the sorting gauge, and
he gets it installed in his earlobe, and he's hollering and screaming in pain and crying.
And then you hear him, like, talking to himself and shaking his head.
Then you see his eyes go white for, like, a split second.
You see him come back and he's huffing and puffing.
- Hufflepuff.
- And you hear the ear go, "House Giants!"
And you see the student, everyone applauds and he goes off.
- I immediately speed walk over to the kid
and I'm like, "What did you say?
"What did you say?
"What?"
(mumbling)
- And Mr.--
- What did he say?
Just tell me what he said, come on.
- And Mr.--
- I'll pay you, I'll pay you.
- And Mr. Eat Your Pussy Up goes,
Why don't you come next then, Dogen?
Psst, psst, psst, psst.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
What, what?
Let's all think the same thought
so we get into the same bloody room.
That's a good idea.
How do we get these bunkmates?
So I do have a system--
I guess the bunkmates--
Now we can brush our teeth together.
We can brush our teeth together.
I do have a system here,
so I will see which houses you get into.
Shh.
- You can't put us in different houses.
This, you're joking, right?
- That would be cruel.
- You're doing like a kayfabe here.
- Absolutely cruel and unusual.
- You're doing the same thing that they do in Harry Potter
where he says, the hat says,
Slytherin might be a good choice for you
'cause you're a sick piece of shit.
And then Harry Potter goes,
Gryffindor, Gryffindor, Gryffindor.
- Yeah. - We'll see.
- We'll see, won't we?
- Better not.
- Please not, anything but Slytherin.
Literally anything but Slytherin.
- So you, first thing you have to do
is place the crystal gauge in your earlobe.
- Okay, easy for me.
- Roll a constitution saving throw.
- Okay.
That is a 11.
- Okay, an 11.
- I don't like how long it takes to roll the die.
Yeah.
- All right.
So yeah, you start to feel a little woozy from this.
You withstood it, but not as much as you could have.
Now, as you start to lose blood,
roll a wisdom saving throw.
- Wisdom, okay.
- That is a 14.
- Okay.
Okay.
- They're putting me in giants, I can tell.
- Now, the ear, the lobe starts to ask you some questions.
Simon Says racial hand.
Giant.
- I think it's working.
- Okay.
- He didn't even do the Simon Says, okay.
Next.
- What is your deepest desire?
- To be in the house of giants.
- That could count towards you, it could not.
What is your greatest fear?
- Being small.
- Damn.
Okay. Damn, that's real. I live that life.
You come across a bumblebee aimlessly buzzing about.
As you better take in the scene, you realize it is attempting to pollinate the flower.
However, you notice that the flower is a Neptune bamboozle,
a flowered plant that tricks bumblebees into being forcefully swallowed down their stem
and encased in a translucent purple tummy lurking below the surface.
You also recall that a witch turned your best friend into a bumblebee, so this could be him.
However, your best friend also borrowed your lawnmower for a year and keeps meaning to give it back, but it's too heavy sometimes.
Also, you've had a thing for his sister, and she is in a pretty vulnerable place right now,
looking for comfort from someone who knew her brother well, but in a different way than she knew him.
him. This will help her feel like she'll understand her brother in ways she
wouldn't be able to even if he was alive. Almost know him better than she ever
could have. This would carry an immense amount of meaning for her which you
could use to your advantage. Also you're allergic to bees and if they sting you
it will hurt and you will swell up. But there's a one in 100,000 chance that if
a bee stings you you can cure your allergy and gain bee-like superpowers. But
But you won't look gross and weird, and will instead be able to fly and crawl on stuff.
What do you do?
Grow.
What?
In size.
Okay.
Your mother just came home with pizza rolls.
Grow.
Yummy.
You say grow?
Okay, well I won't get to that.
- It really seems like he wants to be a giant.
- All right.
Last test.
Your eyes grow white.
- This is in the bag, guys.
- You end up in an ethereal arena.
- What?
- It's you versus something from Dogen's past.
A Needle Lord.
They exist in the Dirtlands.
They spring up from the ground and shoot needles.
They pretend to be cacti and attack humble dirt goblins.
Roll for initiative.
- Okay, damn.
Where's initiative on here?
Oh, I found it.
Okay, that's a 13.
- Okay.
All right, you go first.
What do you wanna do?
- I wanna shake its hand.
And show kindness to it.
- Okay.
- And peace.
and largeness
should be the bigger man
all my god
you uh... that's incredible won't even play at the battle you die
uh...
you come back your eyes are no longer white you felt the cold hand of death
and the gauge goes
house
giant
the
racialized
he got what he wanted
We did, okay now you guys, here's the cookie.
Just say a bunch of stuff about being big.
(laughing)
Being big?
I don't know if I can do that.
(laughing)
All right, so who wants to go next of you two?
Let me go.
Let me at it.
You saunter up there, roll a constitution saving throw.
Okay, bitch.
All right, I'm gonna call me a bitch.
That's fine.
Nat 20.
Whoa.
Wow, okay.
Next, roll wisdom saving throw.
As I walk up I go boom, boom, boom, boom, thump,
with every single tiny step that I make.
You got the hooves though.
True.
You do have some booming footsteps.
You got the hooves though.
Yeah, you got the hooves though.
Now what?
Roll wisdom saving throw.
That is a 15.
- Okay.
What is your deepest desire?
- Ooh, um,
large, large-ness.
To be large.
- Your greatest fear?
being away
who got up
but
you hear the bubble the story again what do you do
i'm gonna hear it again
you give it to you one more dollar please
now i'm getting i'd hate them probably
well
next story
Your mother just came home with pizza rolls.
- I love you, mom.
Thank you so much.
- Yummy.
However, she says that you must wait to heat them up
until your little brother gets back from soccer practice.
- He's alive?
- You are so hungry right now.
So hungry.
Mm.
Maybe what mom doesn't know won't kill her.
Let me have some.
Hmm.
Why don't I use the oven instead of the microwave?
That way they'll get crispy and heat up more evenly.
Okay, let me open the oven and just put these on a tray.
Oh, nothing mom, nothing.
Just finishing up homework.
Yeah.
No, that's why.
No, I would never heat up pizza rolls in the oven.
I'm waiting for my baby brother.
The fool, now back to my pizza rolls.
What's your favorite pizza roll flavor?
Margherita.
Okay.
Your eyes turn white.
You enter the combat zone.
You come across a gibbering mouther.
- And which is what?
- A horrible-- - I know about this thing.
- Yeah, it's a horrible-- - It's a blob.
- It's a blob with a million mouths.
And it's coming for you.
You can't tell what you want from it
or what it wants from you.
I would like to go around and kiss every last mouth on this blabberer.
Big deep ones too.
Passionate type deal.
You die.
It's not real man.
None of this is real.
House giant!
Let's fucking go!
Yo!
It was close.
I don't know why I think this but I feel like this last guy Andre
I feel like he's got it on lock for house of it is no doubt. He's gonna be a giant
Joining us brush our teeth together every night
To brush our teeth I like my teeth a lot you can tell that I never brush my teeth
All right, I don't know
Yeah, we need natural oh yeah, joy, you're already giant constitution saving throw
Wisdom saving throw 17
Okay, what if I get house of the small?
What is your dearest not you don't have to worry about that? That's not a house. It's okay. Well, I deepest desire
Pizza rolls
Could he hear what I was hearing pizza pizza rolls for dinner
And what a bumblebee. What is your greatest fear?
Because it's too small. I'm yelling from the
It's too small. He's scared of it. Yeah, right
Simon says raise your hands
Simon says put your hands down
Put your hands up. Oh
It's taking him a long time to raise his hands up and down because I'm bigger than ours
I'll have large muscles and joints cuz I'm a look just put me in the house of the giant
house of the giant
All right, yes
This was too this was too much. There's no way there's no way that I'm allowed in any other house
We can't have a fucking Hogwarts campaign. We're all in doing we'd not room. That would have been yeah
That would have been fucking cruel that would have been the worst
- That's the worst thing I could even imagine.
- It would be pretty funny though.
You guys would have had to try to hang out in another way.
So you see Hamo and he comes up to all three of you
and gives you all a big hug, he's very excited.
He's one of the last half giants alive.
- How tall is he? - Boom, boom.
- I mean, he's like properly 12 feet,
where a Goliath is maybe like eight feet, nine feet.
He's like 12 feet and like girthy.
- So Andre is tall even for a Goliath.
- Why, what's a Goliath size?
- Well, he--
- Goliath-- - He said that he's--
You just said that they're eight feet,
and he said he's 15 feet.
- No, no.
He is not 15 feet, that is crazy.
- I'm 15 feet, that's in my character description.
- Is that how big a Goliath can be?
- That's how big I am, I'm weird.
- Okay, fine.
- Oh yeah. - You're big for a Goliath.
- Twice the size of every other Goliath.
- God damn it, so big, okay.
- He's like, "I'm so excited to have you all
in the house of giant.
- What did you say?
I couldn't hear you up here.
(laughing)
- It's Goliath humor.
It's Goliath humor, Dogen.
We're gonna have to get used to this type of thing.
- I really regret this already.
- Hey, how's the weather up there?
No, I'm kidding.
I can see the weather too.
I'm a giant.
- Wait, how big are you?
Are you the same size as me?
- I'm about, how big is a satyr?
I'm a little taller than a normal person
'cause of my horse legs, right?
i thought i said it was really small okay now they're not like phil i thought i
imagine a normal for james phil no phil is unusual
okay so i'm like five so i'm just i mean i thought that it was going to be there
was a big guy into tiny
all your tiny to okay five-by
to study to him
so the giant takes
the giant house i mean
j
not who's my separate
specifics
- They specialize in the five schools of magic,
which we'll get into eventually.
They're scary magic, funny magic,
creepy magic, healthy magic, attacking class.
So they specialize in attacking and healthy.
So that means lots of abjuration types of spells,
restoration spells, some light necromancy,
but not fully necromancy spells.
And then attacking spells.
So theirs are usually more based in physical objects
and physical attacking, but they'll do like a fireball
as well as like an icicle, just kind of ice spells
and shit like that.
- Both ends of the heat spectrum.
- Yes, fire giants, ice giants.
So it's a good balanced house to be in.
But yeah, so now you've been sorted into your houses.
Let's take you over, let's cut to our story
from before. 24 hours earlier from where we last left Marlon Reese. So from before he
was diving down into that cavern. He was working in the mine as usual, head down, chin down,
arms down. They go back up, then it comes down again, striking the surrounding rock
with a pickaxe, making headway, finding more magic crystals. A telepathic voice echoes
in all the miners' ears, a direct order from the Overseer.
"Marlin Reist, please report to the Overseer. Marlin Reist, please report to the Overseer."
Marlin exhaled, and made his way back toward the entrance to the shaft, past the other
crystal workers who glanced with some grim satisfaction that some other j'moke was being
called. Marlin reached a small outcropping toward the mouth of the cavern, where the
The overseer pours over tedious work orders from the Buryberry Academy, scolds mining
captains and eats copious amounts of yummy gummy snacks.
The overseer of mine 24A is Gale, a stout, snobbish wood elf with a penchant for all previously
mentioned activities, as well as for $20 words, many of which are made from scratch.
Marlin waited a tick just outside the crude wooden door before Gale hollered, "You may
enter!"
through the door, careful not to let his idle tail get caught on it as it swings
back fast on overtaut hinges. "A query, Reese," began Gale, twirling his pointer
finger around a tea-stained document. "And perhaps a welcome reminder for me. You do
not labor delectatiously, no?" Marlin's tail slowed its gentle instinctual sway.
"What could that mean?" he wondered. "Yes, I don't," he complied.
Gail frowned then smiled
So if there were say a means by which you could supplement your habitualities
necessarily or otherwise
Would you?
And Marlon said yes
Gail's expression remained unchanged
He rose from his desk pushing his seat out with his gut and began to make a very practiced circle around his desk
"Qualities to which you've admitted are not always ideal in an employee, Marlin, but you
are in fortu-cessity."
Gale faced the corner of his outcropping office and stood at attention, placed his two fingers
in a V-shape before his mouth.
The pleasuremen saluted.
From the ether suddenly appeared a pleasuremen of fantastic standing, one which we've met
before in our adventures, that evil Stievel knew, though he now finds himself a lord,
Lord Poonhead.
Marlin tucked his tail in at the sight of royalty and performed the salute.
Marlin hadn't even seen Poonhead before, but it's hard to mistake the lord who hails from
the trebuchet region for anyone else with that vagina on his forehead.
Lord Poonhead gestured for the men to be at ease.
He met Marlin's gaze.
This is something worth remarking.
Beriberi is under the Terrifyer Kingdom, which means the much weakened King Nardwar, along
with his crusading son, Prince Jumanji, who is a child now possessed by a black heart of
death due to the influence of three Aerswile adventurers.
But Beriberi is also not quite under the Terrifyer Kingdom.
They sort of have like a weird relationship where they collect tithes.
I can do this another time, but it's just no secret that an open-minded, magically inclined,
and somewhat occult Beriberi region is more aligned to pleasuremen than, say, a nard or
or a troll lord or something.
Nevermind that the Pleasure Men take,
some of the Pleasure Men take a cut of the Minds Prophets
and the Schools Prophets.
- Marlin Reese, I have something very important
to ask of you.
If you do this, you shall be compensated
so that you, your daughter, and anyone who wouldn't,
anyone you love wouldn't have to work
for this lifetime or the next.
It will maximize your pleasure.
Will you hear me out?
Marlin knew this wasn't a choice, but he would have said yes anyway.
Of course, my lord.
Most pleasurable.
Gael, you're dismissed.
Gael nearly protested, but remembered himself.
He saluted Poon Head and left the outcropping in a controlled huff.
Marlin Wreath, you have been mining these tunnels for thirty long years.
You've never moved tunnels, you've never opted to manage those below you.
You know the underground inside and out.
You know what we use these crystals for, yes?
They contain magical properties that help fuel all of the terror fire kingdom, my lord.
They can produce magical light, flavor, kinetic energy, and more.
They help our villages run and our homes stay safe from monsters.
They can enhance our senses and make us stronger, quicker, even granting non-magic users a chance
of performing miracles.
They are difficult to manipulate and quickly burn out, and so we mine them for as long as
were able my lord. This is a pleasurable answer but only partially correct. We
also study them Marlon and in knowing them we hope not to only fuel the
kingdom but collectively evolve into something greater than ourselves. Marlon
Reese I need you to travel to the deepest depths of this mind and return to me a
soft crystal. Of course my lord but if I may what is a soft crystal? In all my
years they've only been brittle and hard and in response to extreme heat, pressure,
and magical energy, they turn to dust. A prudent and pleasurable question, Marlon.
A soft crystal is what it sounds like. A crystal soft like pillows and flesh and intestines and
clouds. It exists, we know that now from our experimentations. We believe that further down
the conditions are right for this very thing. I promise you if you retrieve one, placing it in
in this container, he hands him the container,
you'll be compensated by the kingdom
for all yours and your daughter's life.
I swear I'll do it.
And so, we head back.
You three are now in the giant's dorm room.
It is very big.
The beds are too big.
You guys could all sleep in a bed together.
Except for you, yes.
- Too small for me, I'm the 15 foot.
- I guess it looks like we're bunking together, Woody.
All right.
You see clouds sort of passing over.
You see mountains, sort of mountain
statues and mountain
like sort of wallpaper that's like
moving and looks like it's almost
like a video of a mountain, like
creating this environment of
that's going to be something cool.
OK.
Everything's cool here.
Yeah.
Can I summon Dylan?
Yeah, you can talk to Dylan.
Can I summon him in a portal on the wall?
So that they can meet Dylan?
Yeah, shit, why not?
All right, I take out my, I have a wand, right?
Yeah, you do.
Okay, I take out my wand.
I point my wand at the wall and I say,
Dylan Mulvaney.
That's his name?
- And you see in the image in the background,
like you see like-- - It's not related
to anyone in the real world, it's just a spell.
- Right, you see a man with a blue shirt
and a gold star sitting on a couch.
- A portal type deal?
- Yeah, cross-legged. - Geronimo!
I jump in.
- Yeah, I mean, you can't actually jump,
it just looks like a portal, you can't visit there.
- He's sitting cross-legged on the couch
with his sneakers on.
And, but when he sees you summon him,
he goes, "Oh!"
And he starts to take his sneakers off,
feeling embarrassed.
- Take 'em off.
- And he says, "Hey, hey, what's going on?
"How you doing, Andre?" - Hello, this is Andre.
- From the House of Giants.
Nice to meet you, by the way.
- Dylan, this is
- I'm Woody. - Dogen.
- And Woody.
I'm Rod Dogen you.
Awesome, very awesome.
We are at school.
Oh, you're in school still, that's awesome.
So what, did you learn anything yet?
Not still, we just started.
We found our bedroom.
And it's big.
That's awesome.
That's so cool.
My bedroom's not that big.
But it's cool that yours is.
Do you guys, what are you guys gonna do?
What are you guys up to today?
We're gonna go to a party!
You wanna come?
I wish I could, but I'm still here.
We're gonna drink mead!
Oh.
Yay!
Love me some mead.
Gallons of the stuff.
Love it.
Cow wagons.
Could you say dillons of the stuff?
Dillons of the stuff, well, now I say dillons.
I used to say gallons!
I'll have two pints and then I'm done.
Alright, bit of a light weight dillon.
(laughing)
- What?
- I can't hear you quite.
- Dylan, it's breaking up a little bit.
- I like the star on your tunic.
- Oh, I made it myself, thank you.
- Wow.
- I think this guy's a bit of a fruit loop.
- His star can, I can contact him through his star.
- You see him reach out of the portal's frame
and get a box of fruit loops and pull her bowl.
- I'm not sure what that is.
(laughing)
- Cereal for dinner.
All right, Dylan, seems like you might have
the coolest life ever.
- Well, to us, we're in the past,
so cereal is like a cereal grain,
like a horse would eat.
Like we're a drop of oats.
- Cool. - Cool, man.
- Wow.
- That's my pet horse.
I talk to him in a poodle.
(laughing)
- You think he's, he's always eating cereal,
so you think he's a horse.
I'm not sure what kind of creature this is, but it's disgusting.
It's one of my weirdest pets.
I keep a lot of pets too.
Really?
All right, I'm going to go finish replaying Link to the Past,
but I'll see you guys later.
All right, that's where we are.
Yeah, we're in the past.
Say hello to Link for us.
Very good friend of mine.
Will do.
I pulled a toad out of my back pocket,
but I was sitting down on my bed.
So the toad is...
A toad's like a Mario toad?
- Like a frog. - Yeah, that's what I was thinking.
- A frog? - I know, I got a sense,
I heard Link and I thought Toad, Mario Toad.
- I pull up-- - You had a Nintendo attack.
- A thing of blood, just I see the blood on my hand
and I go, oh darn it, not again.
- You see Homo comes in, he says,
well, it's good to see all of you.
- Hello, Homo. - Hello.
- Hey, Homo, nice to see you again.
- Hello, well-- - Hope there's no
hard feelings now that I'm a student
after what I, you know, I know we had kind of a rough past.
- Oh, it's all fine. - What do you mean rough past?
- What happened in the past? - He was teaching
a sex class to the kids.
- Pardon me? - What the?
- Yeah, we're-- - Wait.
- Wait a minute, he's bunking with us.
- Dougan, you're a teacher here,
so you can give me the test, the pop quiz answers, huh?
- Oh, I wish I could.
I used to be a teacher,
and then they kicked me down to student level.
- Well, what'd you used to teach?
Have you ever read the scroll community?
- Oh, I love Jeff Winger.
- I'm a Jeff Winger kind of character.
- Troy and Ebbin in the morning.
Yes, very funny scroll.
- Yeah, I really like, I was upset when they took
one of the stanzas of that scroll off of ScrollFlicks.
- Yes, yes, very annoying, very annoying.
- Six scrolls and a parchment.
I can't wait.
- Oh yeah.
My favorite scroll is the Young Sheldon.
- I like community, it follows the fairy circle.
- I don't really understand it.
- Every episode's a fairy circle.
- I don't really understand what he's saying.
But he has new kind of things going on every single day.
This Young Sheldon.
- All right, how about--
- So anyways, can I ask you to--
- You know, I'm gonna be honest with you, Andre.
You seem like the kind of guy who read,
who literally read the scroll,
read the Peppa Pig scroll once and made it his entire personality.
(laughing)
He can laugh at himself, I like that.
That's a good quality.
So, let's... you guys have to go to class now.
So...
Wait, check this out.
Dylan Mulvaney.
What class are we going to?
Did I use up all of my Dylan?
Yeah, you gave it to him.
So now it just looks like I'm saying
Check this out the guy's name
Girls name you think Dylan Mulvaney is a guy's name. What the hell
Yeah, I know me too I
Still in the characters a guy yeah
Dylan the character just so happens you think Dylan Mulvaney is a real character
- Not really that much of a payoff at all.
- Let's go ahead and just change it, Dylan...
- Mulberry.
- No, no, no, not Dylan, no.
We'll go Dylan. - Dylan Sprouse.
- Dylan Mulberry, there we go.
- Dylan Mulberry.
- Okay, 'cause it sounds like the other one, all right.
- Yeah.
- So you guys have a few classes you can go to.
- We get to choose?
- You've got-- - Potions.
- I gotta meet Snape.
- Well, the classes right now are,
there's a creepy magic class, a scary magic class,
a funny magic class, or a healthy magic class.
- I need to go to the funny magic class.
- So guys, if we go to creepy magic,
we're gonna meet Snape, right?
I need to meet the Snape.
- You don't need to meet Snape.
- Because what people don't know about the Snape
is he seems bad for the first six times,
but then in the seventh one, he's revealed to be good.
- I wanna meet Snape now.
- The teacher of the creepy magic class is Angeluna.
- That's Snape.
Angeluna Glansberry the
great great great great great great granddaughter of narcotics minestrone the founder of the school oh
Wow, so it's a woman if that's oh, so it can't be a snape. Yeah
Hmm the snape is in the funny magic class
Okay, just what we don't really care about the names of the classes tell us the professors and we'll decide from there. Yeah
Yeah, Angelina teaches the creepy magic class
Karen teaches a scary magic class okay
Homa teaches a funny magic class
Homa, it's all girls as the homo homo. Sorry homo. Okay our giant friend
Oh, I guess dawn teaches the healthy magic class
Okay, so where's the snape dog?
That's me walking into Hogwarts. Where's the snake dog?
Guess on is kind of snake you seem snape ish from the beginning
You didn't kind of a full snape analog
there's also a
Attacking class that's gonna be later in the evening with a guy who is not a snape either
But is more snape, bro. You don't really have just straight-up snape really fucked this I am a Malfoy, okay, okay?
Okay, okay?
Well, there's no snape just tell us right now
Just tell us tell us right now. Which one's name to snake which one is professor flitwick. Yes
Who's a little one you didn't even watch Harry Potter Jesus Christ you've never even watched or read
It's flip like the guy with the pizza face. He's no he's the little one
He's Warwick Davis. Yeah, he's a little pizza face known guy. It's a you remember to me. They use a pizza face and not a dwarf
That's crazy good on you actually
Wizard people dear reader they call he calls him a pizza face what in God's green or what are you talking about?
It was I don't know what the hell he's saying it was a Brad Neely did this thing where he narrated
over
Harry Potter the first is that this is and that's the only time you've seen them is is this no I've seen old comedy
Version I've seen no I've seen all the movies except for the sixth one
there's
More than six movies. There's eight movies the same for the sixth book
I know it was eight movies you saw the clearly did you didn't know what you were confusing yourself, okay?
- Okay, who is Professor Sybil Trelawney in this situation?
- Trelawney, she's the, Trelawney's the librarian
or the alchemist, right?
- No.
- That's played by, what's her name?
- She does future seeing.
She does, she reads the tealers and stuff.
- She's played by Emma Thomas.
She's played by Emma Thompson, right?
- Don't remember.
- Which one of the classes is the analog for the dark arts?
- Yeah, wait, that's a good question.
- That is the attacking magic class,
which isn't gonna get into it later.
- Oh, which isn't, they don't do it yet.
- Okay, well let's just, you wanted to go to funny, right?
- Yeah.
- Let's go to funny then.
- And we'll meet our--
- You'll keep hanging out with Homo then.
- Oh, it's the same guy?
- Yeah, if you wanna meet a guy--
- Oh no, we gotta meet someone new.
- Okay, then I guess we're going to scary magic,
'cause I feel like scary is where a snape would be--
- Karen just yells, I'm gonna let you know.
- Okay, just pick one for us.
- All right, on your way to the scary magic lesson,
you go to the class, and you see the Karen, the headmaster.
- Oh, hell no.
(laughing)
- The headmaster of the, or the head of the house,
house of the megabats.
The megabats are a lost creature
that allegedly lives on the Isle of Gauntlet,
which nobody's been to for hundreds of years.
It's a very large island just directly east of the Dirtlands
if you look at the map.
And so she emulates the megabats
who are supposed to be completely pitch black with gold teeth
and gold fangs.
But she has not a Karen haircut.
She has sort of like a Napoleon Dynamite's grandma haircut.
And she sits perched on top, upside down rather,
and waiting in the class for all the students to come in.
And once you all come in, I need you guys to roll
a wisdom saving throw.
- Okay.
That is a nine.
- Ooh, I also got a nine.
Beautiful. - Crit one.
- Sorry, I heard some of this, but Karen--
- It's fine. - Is this attack class?
- No, this is scary magic. - Scary magic, okay.
- Scary magic often specializes in illusion magic.
It's things that are made to make you scared.
It does it on the obvious ones.
- I had a crit one. - That crit one.
- Yeah. - Yeah, it's pretty bad.
You see, all of you experience this illusion
of you are now the only one in the class.
And it's just you and the Karen.
- Oh no. - And the Karen's head
turns, uh, according to Exorcist style, and faces you.
And then from behind,
- Scarin'!
- You hear a rumbling of black tentacles
that sort of - Bart.
- Come up and grab at you,
and all three of you start to freak out from that.
And you take - Oh!
- 15 damage, psychic damage, from this.
- Oh, God. - Don't tell me we can die
at school, man.
was here early in the first day
fifteen
and you hear the carol
you guys hear that
not really
uh... one e uh... all of you guys role wisdom
just a wisdom check
where
or inside it's really inside nineteen
- All right, I will roll insight then.
- Roll insight.
- I got an eight. - And four.
- I got a 19, baby.
- Okay, you can understand that she is,
what she's basically saying is,
these are the kinds of things you need to
be able to protect yourself from.
From the illusions that will be cast on you.
She says, you can understand her at this point, that 19.
She says, "Okay, smart mouth."
I said, "Listen, bitch, I never liked you
when I was a teacher and this is why.
You're hurting the students.
This is unacceptable and I'm going straight
to the headmaster, unless you give me
and my crew A plus for the semester.
- She says you won't get an A plus
unless you create the scariest illusion.
And the thing is-- - Easy for me.
- Ask her what she's scared of.
- Yeah, what are you so scared of?
A real man?
(laughing)
Um she uh she regards that as she says you're on the right path
Creating what I do creating a scary illusion is about the context of the situation
You cannot just create something scary. It needs to be convincing in the context. Can I try something really quick mm-hmm I?
Start skateboarding
Okay, so Pat you want to do that in real life, right?
Yeah
Okay, I start skateboarding. No I start skateboarding
Because that's a Karen's natural enemy is a skateboarder. Mm-hmm
Do you have a skateboard you have a giant skateboard - do I
Know I can't conjure one because I don't have I thought I brought one with me, but why did you look around?
- To see if you had a skateboard.
Why would he ask if you had a skateboard with you?
- I don't know.
What are my spells?
- That's your dream question to be asked.
Do you have a skateboard with you right now?
Just curious.
(laughing)
- I guess none of my, I guess that doesn't make sense.
- Help, my son is stuck under a car.
The only way we can lift it off him and save his life
is if someone here has a skateboard.
- You'll all get like a scroll to cast like major illusions.
- I use channel divinity dreadful aspect.
- Ooh, describe that.
- Okay, I turn my face into someone loitering.
- And then I start having a barbecue with no permit.
- I turn my face into, I become a cashier.
- Okay, and what about you?
- And I'm ripping up coupons,
a cashier who's ripping up coupons and not accepting them.
- And I become a evil demon.
(laughing)
(imitates grunting)
Okay, cool.
And she says, "That's all very good, very good.
"Those are all things that scare me."
- All right, plus 10.
- So you're kind of a scaredy cat, aren't you?
Shouldn't really be teaching the class now, should you?
Maybe let's step aside, let a real teacher take over.
- She's afraid of a barbecue with no permit.
Let's get one of your own students fellow students up here, and you see watch a scary Joe. Oh god Roger
Clemens I didn't even meet this guy yet
But I'm just getting an awful vibe off him and when I walk back from the front of the class I smack him on the
back of the word
Huh, you never taught him. Oh, it's for he's the first year I
Just smice trip him and smack him on the back. You're a jerk wait wait wait can we tabletop him I?
I stand in tabletop I
You're 10 feet tall yeah
He just falls under you
But then you flop onto his body
We've table top you Roger Clemens
Suddenly all three of you can't move oh
shit and
Karen says you're going to have to stay here for the remainder of the class and just watch
And you all guys we were set because we already pissed so good
She screeches the class goes by you guys get no bonuses for this
Come on, man. What could we table could we bullied that guy?
He clearly is gonna bully us for as well. We have to bully him first
Yeah, not not in the class
You guys can pick another class that I go to today. This is a woke
School this is it. I'll say let's go to school. Let's what else is it. Are they doing are they doing attacking yet?
Not yet
Okay, let's go to helping okay. Wait. You said it's persona like a second helping
helpy magic
So you see guest on?
He waits for you
and
You guys are all there and his classroom is in the spire for the kaiju manji
So has all these weird eerie drawings and weird sort of vibe to it, and he says now
We're going to hello. We're going to have to teach you about
withstanding pain teacher
Teacher is not about you must think
Hello, Lee. Hello. I need to use the bathroom
You may use the bathroom.
Yippee!
They're probably gender neutral in this damn school.
Yeah.
They run out of the classroom.
They are most certainly not.
Well that's good news.
There's only one gender, man.
And everyone has to figure it out.
Man and giant.
Yeah.
He says, uh...
He was wearing a dress all along.
When he walked away from the camera.
...and constant increasing damage.
I'm going to be attacking you.
You will be revived. You will not die.
But you will be taking damage and you must figure out a way to withstand it.
Easy.
Who, well, former professor, would you like to try first if it's so easy for you?
If it's so easy for me, why don't I try last just so...
[laughter]
It's a good point. I'm like I'm thinking it's gonna be pretty hard for me, so I'll go fast
Okay, cool
All right, and so he shoots a constant stream of which bolt at you. Yep. It's really hurting me really really badly
You're gonna take
Well wait you have a resistance to magic right yes, I think you do you don't know I do
Yes, nice. Yeah, you should have make sure I'm getting it correctly. I'm back from the bathroom
Let me see
What happened while I was gone
Nothing I advantage on saving throws against spells another magical effect. So if it is which bolt which bolt does
If I'm correct, is that an attacking spell right though? That's actually an attack
- Okay, let's check.
Um...
You were to the saving throw.
No, it's on a hit.
So this will just hit you,
so you don't have advantage on the dodging this, so.
- Okay.
- So you're gonna take first 1d12 damage.
- You roll or I roll?
- I roll that.
(Burps)
So you take 11 first.
Yep, really heading very badly.
- So now what do you wanna do?
You have this moment.
- I'd like to sit here and continue taking damage.
- There's nothing you wanna do?
- Well, I'm not gonna fight my professor, right?
- You don't have to fight,
you have to just withstand the damage.
- Oh, hmm.
- Or find a way to do it.
Look through your spells.
- Yeah, let's see.
- Feel free to ask questions of him as well.
(sniffs)
- Hmm, I have an odd question.
Might come across as odd at least.
Is there any plants in this room?
- Yes, there are.
- Okay.
- There are a few plants that are like
kind of nice little window dressing.
- I would like to use plant growth
to grow them into a shield in front of my body.
'Cause there's no way this magic is gonna go through plants.
Spill rate are you let me see possible use of spell granting me on it
We choose a plant within range all normal plants become thick and overgrown creature moving to the area must spend four feet
Okay, I like you trying to do that. Let's we'll have you do that. Okay, I can stand
You casted it and then
We think I think that gives you let's say three-fourths cover
Well, no, and so well, let's say it withstand it it cuts off some of the damage and
He says to you Gaston stop shooting the whip which bullet you and he says that is correct
Remember when you were talking about helping people and healthy magic
Only healing will not stop it. You must create shields
you must stop the source if you just restore your health with curing wounds and
and healing words, you'll eventually run out.
- Sorry, can't quite hear you through these plants,
you'll need to speak up.
- You did well, is what I'm saying.
- All right, back to the seat.
- So you will get a, you will retain that spell slot
as sort of your reward for passing that lesson.
- All right, I undid it.
- Yeah, nice.
Typically one of the rewards you get is like an additional spell slot or like a pool of d6s and things like that
So you're gonna retain it for that one
Now
It is time for attacking class oh
Yeah, so excited
you guys I
Have to go outside for that. It's now closer to night. You see the stars rooms and all that
Quidditch I just remembered quit it rug be man
And you go in towards the gymnasium slash
Combat center of combat and all that where you see wizards practicing spells of one another crafting magical weapons
all these things you're led towards the back area where there's sort of a
dirt dirt arena
and you see a
Sort of a long-haired
Sort of sharp featured looking teacher. He had not seen the snake snake snake and his name is
Professor Aquaman and
He looks you all
And he says my name is Professor Aquaman
It's not snake. I
Have a groundskeeper. I am the attacking class professor and
And I'm here to teach all of you how to defend yourselves.
And at this point, the entire first year student body is here.
This is the most important part of Berry Berry Academy,
is learning how to kill and not be killed.
Don't let any other professor tell you otherwise.
Now, who wishes to fight this demon I have summoned?
And he summons a demon.
Who wants to fight him?
I did the last one.
- Oh, I think this guy does.
I'm pointing to Andre.
- Yeah, he hates Damon.
- Go fish.
- You, Andre Behavoir, come on up.
- All right.
- And I unleash primal savagery.
- Okay, let's roll initiative.
- You unleash primal savagery.
(laughing)
- I unleash primal savagery.
- And I unleash primal savagery.
- At least Primal Savagery and I got a 15 on it.
- Dillon is like sitting in front of a TV right now
and his stomach growls, he's like oh.
- Primal Savagery. - Something happened.
- Yeah.
So Primal Savagery is just, that's just like,
so that's a, so you're gonna make a melee attack on him?
Well let's first roll initiative
to see if you go first or not.
- All right.
- Well then I have to roll again.
- Crap.
- What'd they get?
(gasps)
- Six.
- I don't know.
- Got a six.
- Looks like a six.
This demon is gonna go first.
- Wait, I got a six.
- Yeah, I said that.
- I got a six.
- Yeah, that's what everyone said.
- That's what he's saying.
- Wait, I thought the demon got a six.
- No, no, no, no.
- You can see your rolls, man.
- Oh.
- Yeah, so this horrible demon,
Um, yeah, this is gonna be cool.
Um, he, uh, zooms towards you and raises his hand atop, on your head.
He, like, jumps in the air, places his hand on your head.
And...
What is your AC?
Twelve.
Yeah.
Isn't it?
- I'm not liking it.
Yeah, and he does,
put his hand on your head and you feel a cold,
numbing touch sort of drip into your skull
and fill it with an icy, just cold pain.
- Ouch.
- Yeah. (laughs)
And you take 14 damage.
- Does he have bigger blood than us too?
You can see the blood cells.
And they're bigger?
Macroscopic blood cells.
All right, good to know.
All right, well, I got a 15 on the primal savagery.
Mm-hmm.
All right, cool.
What was that, nine damage?
That's 14.
Well, what are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
I was trying to roll my hit.
I guess I'll just roll it again.
That's the damage.
- What?
Oh wait, I'll roll damages.
It says acid damage 20.
(laughing)
- What's happening?
- What's going on man, you good?
- I don't know what is happening.
- Oh okay, yeah, fine.
- I rolled two D10s and I got two 10s.
- That's good, no you did that right, okay yeah.
So describe, when you grow claws and stuff,
what does it look like for your Ferrandri-Betisbois?
My hair.
Your claws?
That's probably more savagery.
My hair grows claws out of it, my long hair.
Mm-hmm.
And it goes up like this.
You kind of remind me of Hagrid.
Nice. Yeah.
And then the claws come out of the hair,
and the hair grows and then turns into big, hairy, claw hands.
And they're dripping with acid, apparently.
- Nice.
Yeah, and you just slash at him.
And you see a Kwaman, he's like,
"Yes, there we go, finally,
"a student with some fucking balls."
And now the demon lurches back,
and he tries to shoot some kind of fire beam at you.
- And I dodge it perfectly.
- You do, actually.
You do dodge it.
- Shoots by you and you're able to sidestep it easily.
(laughing)
Yeah, and he shoots another--
- You think you can shoot me with that shit, bitch?
- He shoots another one and he crit fails.
And the fire gets like caught up in his skull
where you're shooting at him from like (roaring)
so you have advantage in your next attack against him.
- All right, then I am going to use
Vicious mockery
Nice just to make a wisdom saving throw
Wait, I have to roll that so let me see what the wisdom saving throw would be for this guy
Wait, did I roll that correctly? I can't tell he did. Okay, you don't have to roll any seven. That's the damage you're gonna do
Okay, depending on how he does his wisdom saving throw here, which yeah, he's kind of wise
Let's see
Yeah, he does save. What do you say though, trying to mock him?
Pork chop.
Pretty cool.
You friggin' pork chop.
You look like a pork chop.
Cool. And, yeah...
Do you get half damage or no?
or take yeah no it doesn't take half damage so just succeeds and it's head it
recovers and it goes and runs up to try to attack you again the same way it just
did it got a great oh my god I'm dead okay we don't know that yet man chill
yeah so you are knocked out okay you're dead you're dead buddy you can't die in
- In school though, you already said that.
- No, no, no, the teacher's gonna revive you.
The teacher revives you, you're back at full HP.
And he says, "Why did you use," whoops, the wrong voice.
"Why did you use one of your cantrips?"
Do you not have stronger spells?
- Oh.
- You tried to mock the enemy
without fully understanding how to kill him.
Never do that.
Well, I just wanted to say something very mean.
[Swoosh]
Get this giant out of my sight.
Which one?
Me? Him? Him? Or me?
You've got potential.
I think you're talking about me.
And nothing I hate more than failed potential.
And then, nothing. Really nothing.
Hitler. Fine.
And then you hear a whoosh.
And you hear a splash.
Hitler exists.
Hitler, fine.
(laughing)
- I hate Hitler.
- Hitler find the lost stooge.
The lost brother of Moe and Curly.
- And all of a sudden,
these serpents, winged serpents,
fly up from the water beneath the lake.
- Wait, what does?
- The pond, winged serpents.
And they crash into the arena.
The other students run and panic.
- Not us.
- You're not gonna fool us here, Mr. Crazy.
- And-- - Snape.
- What's his name?
- Mr. Snape. - He's running the train.
- Snape.
- And Aquaman--
- I know this is just one of your little tricks.
I'm gonna walk up to him, he can kill me if he wants to.
- I walk right up to the serpent.
- He says, "I need to get these students to safety.
"You need to take care of these serpents."
What what we get your safety and you kill the fucking joy it's nice
No
He takes the students
I'm reporting you to the headmaster as well by the time
I'm done with my first week at school there will be no teachers left because everyone is wronging me in some way or another
And you just moved to the top of my shit list, but he just are screaming because I'm a teacher
People are getting eaten a bit.
You're just like, just 'cause I didn't get tenure
and you did, like yeah.
And next time we will see how that battle goes.
But before we sign off here,
I have to finish our Marlon Rees story.
So, we saw the beginning of his story,
we saw how he got this job.
Now we're back to where he was descending.
Further and further from the mine proper,
Marlon finds himself in a darkness that disallows a positional awareness.
Bearings were not to be had, only rock, crag, cut, scratch,
downward slip, scrape, crack, another, tucking his tail and cursing.
His headgear was alternating between orange outlines, muted blues, and harsh reds.
The outlines were flickering, almost uncertain how to assess all the dangers present.
After heaving himself down through this final, near 90-degree decline,
Martin's foot missed a step, sorry, Marlin's foot missed a step,
and crashed to a softer mound of rubble and loose stone.
In an instant, he plunged to a wide berth that seemed to go on endless.
This could be it. But the impact, while knocking the wind out of him, was
buoyed by a bed of soft, glowing crystals.
As he came to his senses, Marlin could see that this bed was like a
mycorrhizal network, an eerie,
undulating blanket of soft crystal with remnants of delicate edges that once a
prism made but now they gleamed against an unknown light that emanates from all
the crystals. There will be blood. His headgear however was clear as to what he
had landed on as each and every inch of the soft crystal bed was outlined with a
harsh red. These things are dangerous. Marlon recombobulated and took in the
sight before him. He reached for the magical container given to him by Poonhead and went
to take a handful of the soft crystals, like small pods of flesh or dry worms. As he went
to place these things into the container, the sigil on his head lamp glowed more and more
wildly. It was no longer staying on those red outlines, it was shifting into black light,
freaky purples and yellows and greens. A variety of greens, maybe all of the greens, from the
earthy to the neon. The headlamp began to jitter and Marlon's vision became a skull
rattling blur. He took it off and placed it atop the crystal bed but when he did
it rattled more and the colors grew increasingly mad. The crystal shimmered
and he felt the bed before him give and envelop and he began to sink and sink
and then sink. And maybe we'll find out if what that even fucking means next time.
He will abandon his child.
Wow.
He will have two twins.
Next time on...
Rodogon you.
And the
Soft Philosopher's Crystal.
Wow.
That's a great name.
Soft Philosopher's?
Soft Philosopher.
I'm stopping recording.
Feel softing.
Feel softer than a crystal.
(Sound of a vacuum cleaner)
1992, that would be a good year because you can get put in the nines,
but you wouldn't see these people have 1991. Oh, they were patented in 1992?
That's exactly what I said, 1992 would be a good year.
Yeah, yeah, the 90s make sense. But this is, this is, this is complicated.
This is fussy. Like this is too much going on. No, you know what? Here's my thing. I think
the night, these, these 1991, 1992 glasses, wait, they said they were invented in 1992.
to this woman's wearing 1991. That woman is a time traveler. That's
fake. I don't believe that that exists. But here's what I'm saying.
The 1991, 1992 glasses, these have had to have been invented by either
a time traveler or a schizophrenic person, because who looks at the
number 1992 and says, "Oh, glasses." Yeah. I wanna make... 2000, you're
like, "Oh, glasses. Glasses are handcuffs or bubble wrap." Would be
great to merge this off of, but 1992 is a psycho number to look at
look at this guy wearing the 1998 glasses.
Is that Badlands Booker?
That's Jerry Lewis.
Right there, that's Jerry Lewis.
But look at this.
This is like when
you know somebody that's got a dog
that should be dead.
It's like, oh yeah, that dog's been alive.
Stolen hours. Yeah.
It's like, oh yeah, this is my 34 year old dog.
Yeah. That's what these glasses are.
We gotta put them down.
It's time to put them down until it's time for them to come back to life.
feed we're gonna feed the dog a Big Mac with the we're gonna feed these glasses
a Big Mac and then they're gonna they're gonna pass away don't worry about it
nothing happened what did you guys do come on man nothing disgusting nothing
bad happened and we're back with amazing Brandon Wardell California man let's
see what is holly holly weird you hear a lot of this over there in los angeles huh
yeah we got on the soundboard today i'm on the soundboard i always do it loud and if you're near
the oh my god yep still the entire oh no let's see i gotta turn this off no nothing bad happened
were you not here i was not here for whatever happened here patrick what happened i there
Don't worry about it. Who did it? It was you did it, didn't you?
Patrick Spiller. Could have been Caleb, the famous Spiller.
[MUSIC]