Or keep it, I don't- Everybody! It's time!
The Spy vs. Spy finales continue!
What you've been a long been a- long been a-
What you've been a long been a- waiting for.
But now...
Uh oh, we have a surprise guest.
Even though he lost twice.
He's back, but now he's on the coolest team of them all, which is the Dungeon Masters team.
Somehow you're gonna make me fuck it, you're gonna rig this shit against me as an NPC.
I can't. I never- I've never rigged anything before.
That's bull, that's a lie. Piece of crap.
Alright, that's not nice. So, last time we had White Spy and Soy Spy fought, or Gray Spy.
What did we decide you were Cam, Soy Spy?
I was just myself.
He was Cameron.
He was Cameron?
Yeah, when I was versing Soy Spy I thought.
Okay yeah so Cameron versus Soy Spy. So Cameron beat Soy Spy. Soy Spy put up a good fight
but then his sagging weight because he turned into Steven Seagal. I'm still
Steven Seagal. You're still Steven so now it's Cameron versus Steven Seagal. Well I
was Billy Eilish. And Billy Eilish versus Steven Seagal. Did you have sagging weight as well? No I had a
second sure yeah and so now the first round was at the bank and Steven Seagal
tried to use some some commando tactics he was doing very cool stuff jumping in
at a windows threatening to kill bankers but then Billie Eilish got the best of
him using her guile so now we're moving on to the next location that's right
Alright, it's a party.
And what a party it is.
So, it's a big house party.
We got Cameron, you're up there by the bonfire
in the backyard.
- Is this supposed to be on my screen right now?
- Yeah, it should be, is it not?
Does it do anything?
- No, I don't see it.
I only see Billy Eilish.
- It does.
(laughing)
- I see a picture of Billy Eilish.
- Alright, hold on.
It's gonna slowly...
- Oh, here we go.
I see it now.
- I still don't see it.
The way it does it now is you have a,
you used to be in, you had a players tag.
I'm saving Juvio for last.
You used to have a players tag,
and then that would just move all the players over.
But Roll20 did something cool, which is good,
which is where they split it up
so you could have some players on some maps,
other players on other maps.
But now I forget that,
and so then I have to move each of the players
individually over.
- I'm liking the bottom of this map.
- Yeah, so something happened down there with Steven Seagal.
We can definitely get into that.
But yeah, and then, well, I'll get rid of Black Spy here.
Black Spy, you're not here.
Caleb, you're gonna be some of the NPCs that I have here.
So right now it is still Soi Spy
or Steven Seagal versus Cameron.
So Cameron and Pat, both of you guys roll 3D20s,
and let's see what items you get.
- Okay.
Can you, can you announce them so I can just message them to you quickly?
I got 15, 6, and 17.
I got 2, 1, 12.
Wow, I got, if you combine 2 and 1.
15, 6, 17, 2, 1, 12.
Okay.
Cameron, I'm sending you yours.
Now Caleb, fill time.
Yeah, you gotta fill time while I do this.
God damn it, god damn girl.
God damn it, girl.
Holy shit.
I need you, girl.
You're three lovely girls in front of me.
And I need to see your, where you pee.
It was 15, 6, and 7?
Yes, 17.
17, thank you.
Sorry, keep going Caleb.
Need to see where you pee, right in front of me.
Pee on the front of me.
I wanna, I wanna hum your pee.
I wanna see you hunting me.
Hey, I'm, this is the only thing I get to do in the whole episode.
You are my honey bee.
You're a honey bee.
Pat, what was the numbers for 12, 2, and 1?
Yeah.
Okay.
Interesting.
Caleb.
Yes sir.
Do you mind singing again?
Uh, yeah I could sing.
Spy vs Spy, it's like, it's like Bender vs Fry, in, cause it's, cause you my future mama.
Oh damn.
Cause you my future mama.
Future mama.
Damn.
Late Leela, I need ya, you my future mama.
Okay, you already got future mama man.
I'm
carmen's mom then. hey carmen's mama be my future mama. i want you to mouth park. you
want to be carmen's brother in the future? you want to be carmen's unborn brother right
now? yeah let's just do this with every r&b hit ever. let's go through every single lyric
and go okay. it's a good idea for a song being in carmen's mom's stomach and being ready to
be born and being so excited to spend your life. your items have been sent. we can talk
about Cartman's mother later. Okay. Okay. Well let's talk about Kyle's mom. Hey.
There's a song about that. He's got it going on. That one? Yeah. Alright now Cameron and
Patrick both of you guys roll a d20. 13. Mm-hmm.
Six. Wonderful. White Spy you're gonna go first. So you, White Spy, you arrived to
this
Something happened.
And there's a toilet outside.
Yeah.
I run over.
Wait, am I, I'm out right now?
You are in the backyard with Dylan right now?
Yeah.
Dylan and with his wizard friend.
But I should deafen myself on Discord is what I'm saying?
It's Pat's turn?
Yes, you should.
Sorry.
Yeah.
Take your headphones off.
I am.
I'm deafening myself.
That's smart.
Sorry.
I'm going to investigate over here.
I'm gonna go move right here.
- Where's right here?
Okay.
- This area where the woman is.
So I'm gonna move over there.
- Okay.
- Wait, I can't move my token.
- I'll fix that if that's how.
- Okay, yeah.
- I feel like that happens every day.
- Do I use this one?
- You should be able to move it.
- Okay.
I'll re-replace it.
- Well, I move over there.
- Try this one.
- Okay.
Nope.
- Really?
I'll move you.
- Yeah.
Okay, and then I look at the toilet and I go,
my God, what have they done to my toilet?
- Nice.
- Whoever did this is gonna feel a world of pain.
- Yeah, are you investigating the toilet?
- Yeah, I'm gonna investigate,
but it's more of a general investigation.
- Okay.
Of just the surroundings,
trying to figure out what happened?
- Yeah, for sure. - For sure.
- Okay.
For sure, roll investigation.
17, nice. - 17.
- Yeah, you definitely drove your car into the party
and definitely killed this woman who's lying next to you.
- Oh, my toilet flew out the passenger's side.
- And that is your toilet who was on the passenger's side.
Get the woman in the head!
You figured it out very quickly.
Oh!
Alright! Well, time to kill this spy then.
Or Cameron.
Cool.
So yeah, um,
that's, I mean, there's other things you can do.
You can use your items if you want to, or whatever.
Um, well the items that I have
are...
Or, is it a talking toilet?
Oh my god, I'm gonna say
"Hello, toilet!"
What does the toilet say, Caleb?
*fart*
Yes, I know!
I shouldn't have...
I shouldn't have drove the car tonight!
*fart*
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
*laughter*
I should have never brought you on this mission!
*fart*
*laughter*
Toilet's nodding in agreement.
But there's a score to settle!
This man killed your father.
That's right, Cameron Fetter left the dookie so big in the toilet it choked.
The toilet choked to death.
And so maybe you have a toilet ally now who can also take a turn.
I need you to go in there, because, well, for D&D reasons, I can't move anymore, but also
I'm Steven Seagal and I'm winded.
And 30 feet was- I ran for 30 feet and that winded me.
So I'm gonna need you to go in the house and investigate and see where Cameron is.
I'm gonna help you- reset for a second.
Steven Seagal, you sound more like this, man.
I do sound more like that.
Yeah, I got you, I got you.
I'm excited in the moment.
of
We not gonna tell Cameron.
It's gonna be our secret.
Let me see if I can first find a toilet icon.
I have to find a toilet asset.
I'm sure it's out there.
I think he's gonna notice.
Oh, he won't notice.
How smooth are you with adding these assets in, man?
I'm not, I'm not actually.
It's not gonna be...
Oh, maybe I am really smooth.
Look at that. He's not gonna see that.
That's so diff, that's basically.
Alright, where do you wanna go?
Where do you wanna go?
You could just be at toilets.
You can block his path.
- I wanna go to the bathroom, man.
- Okay, cool.
Let's get you, start getting you over there.
So the bathroom is off the kitchen, it looks like.
I think that's the bathroom.
- No, the bathroom is right here.
It's got a toilet in it already.
Here, let me ping.
- Oh, I see it, I see it, I see it.
We'll get you moving over there.
Well unless, do you want to jump through the window?
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, you jump through the window and crash in there and you just see two people there
and one of them screams like AHHHHH like in fright.
The other one is a little too drunk to really like take that in.
He just sort of like backs up and knocks into this case over here.
But otherwise there's been no alarm.
Otherwise.
Patrick, try to get him to take a shit. Okay. You can use your dash action to do that.
Okay, I'm gonna dash and I'm gonna jump into the window. I get on all
fours just like the last game. I pounce into the window and I try to land my
butt on the toilet. Roll athletics or acrobatics.
Nat 20. That's pretty good. Yeah you gotta make a saving throw man. He's a big guy.
Yeah roll a strength saving throw. I think it's a good call. Do it whisper rule.
So do I do that again? It's a slash I think it's slash WGM. I mean you'll
the
perfectly. It worked? It did, you just didn't roll. But you did just put this, just put the,
you did everything right except you have to just make, you have to put the R,
you have to concatenate everything, just put everything together.
Instead of like separating it. Like I think, did you put the slash after the R? Yeah. Don't,
don't put the slash after the R also. Just, just, just get rid of that and just do it Rd20. I think
the
roll for me man. It's just a d20. Yeah I will. Okay you got a 19. So you are able to hold
up his body. Amazing. As he sort of like, you like, Steven Seagal, you crash in and
sort of like, it's like your model resets so that you just land on the toilet perfectly
and the toilet's able to hold you. Sorry y'all. I uh, I needed to shit. Yeah roll deception
with advantage because you look so much like that's true.
19.
You look like a shitter, man.
Yeah, okay.
Nice, yeah.
Yeah, the woman there just sort of is like freaked out a little bit and just sort of
like nods and like walks away like, "Okay."
Do you love me?
She's out of your shot.
Thankfully for you.
I think it's gonna get arrested again.
Okay, cool.
That's your turn.
Take off your headphones, Patrick.
Or Deffin.
What if I just Deffin, yeah.
Oh yeah, Deffin, just Deffin, right.
So much better.
And then I'll do this.
This is the universal sign of let's go.
Yo.
Alright, what's up?
Yeah, so you're chilling in the back right now with Dylan and his wizard friend Marivelle.
Marivelle?
Yeah, that's his name.
Yeah, you guys are chilling at the bonfire right now.
Cool.
Dylan's wearing his shirt. He's gesturing to it. What's up Dylan? How you doing?
Not good. How's life?
See you got your shirt
Best in the house. Oh
Yeah, best in the house, buddy
All right. Well, I'm gonna I actually had to talk to Maribel for a second
Hey, man, he's his own man. You can talk to him anytime you want
Yeah, all right nice nice chat Dylan
Maraville's trying to cast a spell
Okay
All right, I actually need to need it to go do something inside I think guys just
That I need to look for
There's a celebrity here, and I need to find them
Yeah, I mean you could roll deception, but it won't really matter if they believe you
I'm gonna try I guess I'm gonna try to spread a rumor that there's a celebrity at the party. Okay, then go for it. Yeah
Who should be there? Wait, where's my character? She'd go this new interface is always yeah, I know
They should have started again. What the fuck? What is a compendium?
Don't worry about it. Where's my character? It's the third
Tab now. Oh here. It is. Yeah, it's in journal. Oh cool. Yeah, it's in kernel. Oh, they have art library now, too
Yeah, don't pay attention to that
Okay, here's deception. I'm gonna spread a rumor that
Steven Seagal is there potentially no
I'm gonna say that Olivia Rodrigo is at the oh my god. I got dude. I miss
Specifically okay, it's not that believable
Unbelievable.
11 is... but Marivelle doesn't know who that is.
Dylan is just kind of stoked in sort of the way he doesn't take anything really in.
And he's kind of like, please.
So you might have something going.
It's not going to spread like wildfire just yet, but maybe say it a few more times to
the right people.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's planting the seeds.
Yeah, for sure.
Okay.
I guess I'm just going to walk inside at this point.
Let's see.
I see where the door is.
You can move your guy over there.
I'm just going to go in here.
You can control your guy.
Okay, good.
I just couldn't last time because Billy Eilish was custom.
Yeah, no.
Pat's just been having trouble controlling his guy.
You still have a dash action.
You can also use one of your items.
For my teleporting umbrella, do I have to already have marked the location?
Uh, yeah.
Okay, before I leave, actually, can I write on this?
Before I leave, I want to mark Dylan's back.
For sure.
So I can teleport back to him later.
Yeah, you like tap him on the back, like, "See you later, pal."
Yeah.
Yeah, love it.
And then I will go inside.
Cool.
Awesome.
And then I don't have any action left after that, right?
Uh, no, yeah.
That's like your first use of the bell.
Perfect.
Okay, cool.
Alright.
Yo.
Yeah, I mean, nothing's really happened so far.
It's been about six seconds.
You've just been sitting on the toilet.
Okay.
Ah!
Ah, Jesus!
You what?
They're believing me.
They're believing that I'm actually crapping.
You're trying to sell it right now?
Yeah.
Okay, let me roll this out.
Okay, enough.
the
that sound is. Oh, it's just me yelling. Okay, yeah, that's what I figured. Alright, then
I'm gonna get up and I'm not gonna wipe, but I'm gonna tell them that it's 'cause I... that
I had a perfect ghost poop. Why? I mean, they're not gonna hear you wipe. Well, they... Are
you telling people why you didn't wipe? Nobody heard you not wipe. There's a woman in the
the kitchen looking right at me. I'm trying to convince her that-
She thinks she can tell that you didn't wipe? She's looking right at me! I'm on a table
on top of a toilet! Oh, I thought you were in the bathroom.
No! I'm on top of your face! Oh man. This is awesome. I actually like this
shit. Okay, then I- do I roll deception again?
Of- for what? To convince them that I don't need to wipe?
Yeah, go for it.
Okay, I just want to let y'all know that.
It's like this. I had, I looked down.
Spalter the people out front.
Like, basically out of your,
out of vision, they hear you yelling.
Okay, I don't need to wipe.
I don't need to wipe.
It was a perfect marble style poop.
And,
it's okay.
It's okay sometimes that you don't need to wipe.
*laughter*
Yeah, you see one of them look over and go, "Yeah, I guess it's okay."
I just changed somebody's life.
Yeah, somebody's like, "Yeah, I didn't think about that."
Like, it's sort of a construct, you know.
Alright, so then I get off the toilet, and then I'm gonna...
So yeah, you're right now in sort of like the living room.
Can I go upstairs? Do I have enough feet of movement to do that?
If you dash, yeah, you can.
Okay, I'm gonna dash, before I dash,
I'm gonna look at everyone and say,
oh, somebody's asking me to have sex with them upstairs.
I gotta go.
19!
(laughing)
- That shit worked.
- Cool.
- Yeah, people are like, oh damn, Steven's a pro.
(laughing)
- Yeah, and so I'll move you over here.
So as you're moving towards upstairs, you see this guy sort of walk by you and this woman
walk by you and you see them like...
By you!
(Laughter)
Oh, you're bringing me back!
You see them kind of brushing themselves off and sort of patting their clothes down.
Excuse me, do you have condoms?
Somebody upstairs asked me to have sex with them.
You see the guy go, uh, no...
Oh, 24!
You're having amazing rolls, man.
I know!
Guy's like, "Um, no I don't have any condoms."
Ah, that was a test!
I know that you hit that shit raw!
Ha ha!
Shh!
Hey man, shh.
And this guy got herpes too!
You rolled deception!
12.
Yeah, you've been so truthful.
She's gonna be like, "Do you have herpes?"
Like no, I don't, this is just Steven Seagal.
- Ha ha, okay, I'm gonna go upstairs now.
- Okay, cool, your next turn you'll be able
to use the rest of your movement.
Okay, Toilet, what do you wanna do?
- I'm trying to just make it to the bathroom, man.
I wanna go home.
- Yeah, all right.
- But I also think that that would be a good place
to set up maybe a thing where I could chomp Cameron's butt.
- Mm-hmm, yeah, you could use all your movement
to get almost there.
get right outside the door. Yeah, the toilet is 30 feet of movement. Alright, I'll do that.
Toilet's so fast. I'm gonna sit right out front of the door. Yeah, you see people like just
sort of watching that and they're like, is that a costume? Or... I'm trying to like figure
out why there's a toilet moving. Steven, you gotta cover for me, man. Say I'm a new model.
Say I'm a smart toilet. That's my cousin. That's not helpful.
23.
This guy's volunteering all this awesome information I believe.
23, cool.
Alright so you're gonna start heading upstairs.
Alright and that's the end of y'all's turns.
Or at least yours Stephen.
Alright, cool yeah.
You're just chillin' in there, making your way inside, you set up your umbrella teleporter,
what do you wanna do?
You set up an umbrella.
Can I ask, is there any, do I know anybody here?
Yeah!
Besides those guys?
Yeah, you know Matt who's been gaming in the room off over here.
Okay.
There's Matt, there's a couple of dumb bitches in here you know.
What the hell?
What the hell I don't know any of those no beautiful Queens, okay, yep
Let him know Camry
You just know Matt it was gaming yeah, I guess I'm suffering from hella social anxiety
So maybe I'll just go sit and game with Matt who's my boy, and we basically game together all the time, okay cool
I see what he was playing earlier
This fortnight of course yo
Okay, I'm gonna go set some fortnight. We're gonna snag a victory royale
Okay, you can only make it to this Viking I have here
Okay, I walk up to the bar
Yeah, I'm like hey, who are you? Oh, I'm Cameron. I know Matt you seem awkward
Whoa this is a mean-ass Viking I slap him
Whoa we're talking talking to me like that all right roll intimidation
Okay, you should roll slap
That is a 13 okay the Vikings a head whips back
You can talk to me like that one-on-one
We go outside you can say all you want against me, but you do it in front of people
I'm gonna slap the shit out of you.
Damn.
And he gives out a hearty laugh.
I'm basically playing a character that's based on myself, that has some traits of myself,
but in some ways is wildly different.
Like, "Aha!
Oh!
I respect that kind of thing!"
And he holds out his arm to give you like a Spartan handshake or whatever the fuck.
Can I take his drink from him?
Yeah, sure
Okay, you kind of pushing it. He's got it. He's got it. He's got like a respect for those horns. He's got one of those horns
Yeah, that's what I'm thinking Viking like to share their drinks drink from the horn. Yeah, I want to drink from the horn
The horn of Viking yeah, Danny Trejo Viking. I don't know. I can't find the accent
I don't know. I don't know that any I don't know. It's like a Viking accent. Is it sweetest sweetest chef sweet?
Yeah
you know you got a really that expecting so what was scary with the
uh... i'd like to wife please
uh... you know you're going to boost
and
go ahead
it gives you the uh... his horn
he's so pleased i'm also as i'm as i'm to make it seem more authentic because
there's an action attached to it i'm like swinging from the word of my
all by the way did you hear
livia rodrigo's here
here or a century ago
and uh...
by uh...
uh... critical
just add another as they have to be other celebrities here to keep the light
going
yet or that's what i was going to say is good
yes she's outside i think she was talking to
said dylan and that other the wizard guy before so he would go out and ask them a
bit they'd start to believe because he was a uh... independent of me
way europe that was like that was kind of my brain engineer of the room genius
level i mean a brain level
brevard explains that
not everything
most ideas are pretty
no
and most ideas are brain level ideas
yet
swedish f_ is a year
he's saying i think you're mistaken
you're mistaken he's does not
think there's a celebrity here. Alright, no big deal. Let's see, I guess I'm just going
to keep making my way to the, I mean yeah, that's the end of my turn. As far as you can
go right now. However, you do see across the way, Stephen Seagal. Okay, I guess I'll shoot
him. You used your dash to get over here. Yeah, so I guess I can't do anything. So that's
that's that mattress man.
Yut.
All right.
You see, as you're, you see Cameron, he's talking to a Viking.
I'm not upstairs?
Danny Trejo is a Viking, because I couldn't figure out how to do a Viking accent.
I remember the trailer for the Northmen, using that, but I don't remember how he said it.
So I'm not, I'm not upstairs yet.
my blood for my countrymen. Um, no you're not. You're about to be though if you want to.
Um, well no I was gonna go upstairs and then. Cameron sees you, you see Cameron. This is sort
of like a moment of like you can act, he can act. I am gonna drop a caltrop and then go into the garage.
Do you have caltrops? You don't have caltrops this round.
Yeah I do.
No, I think that was last round.
Wait, what do I have then?
Oh, oh, oh, I'm gonna put...
All right, I'm gonna go into the garage and put tripwire down in front of the door.
Okay, nice.
I like that idea actually, it's pretty good.
Yeah, roll sleight of hand to see how sort of stealthy.
Eight.
Eight, okay.
It's not perfect, but if he goes dashing in there, you might be alright.
In there you see this guy, Mack, who's Matt's brother.
Who's Matt?
Oh, you haven't met Matt yet.
Mack, who is building a race car here.
He's trying to build a race car.
He wants to win the big race today.
I look at him and say, "Does this car work?"
Nah, man.
Does the car run?
Not yet.
Does the engine run?
Uh, well, the engine can work, but, uh...
So if I turn the key, if I turn the ignition on, will this car run?
Well, hold on, man.
I don't know if I want you to be doing that.
I'm still building this thing.
I'm not gonna drive away.
I have a ton of bread.
I don't even know if I want you to turn on the car.
I'm gonna turn...
So what I want to do is I want to turn the car on and then shut the garage door.
And kill yourself, or?
I'm gonna shut the garage door and then I'm gonna, I'm gonna shut the garage door, it's
gonna be really cool.
I'm gonna shoot the garage door opener with my crossbow and turn the car on so that smoke
fills up in the garage.
Okay yeah, roll a, okay roll an attack roll.
Okay that didn't work. Hold up.
That's your weapon proficiency.
Yeah. So I roll.
You attack. You'll see it. Oh you'll see it.
How do I... Oh there we go.
Wow it's a crit! You perfectly hit the garage door. It doesn't even slowly go down. It just
shuts completely.
And a bit of a tool, a wrench that was sitting in the way flings off in the air and knocks
Mac in the head and he falls unconscious.
Dope.
Okay.
Yeah.
All right.
So now I turn the, I run over to the car and I turn the ignition on.
Okay, cool.
Yeah.
You turn the ignition on, it's starting to run.
You got a trip wire in there.
You got a car that's partially made.
You came here in a car that was, and you destroyed it.
You're gonna destroy maybe this car too?
Um, nice. It's a good turn.
Let's go to the toilet.
I'm back, baby.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, you head back in there.
Let me just get...
Oh, fuck. Is there a way I can basically get rid of this old toilet?
Or, you know what I'll do?
I'm gonna... Can I make a little...
Two little signs out of, like,
note cards or toilet paper,
and make one that says "women's"
one
And you wouldn't you know it, this is a girl toilet.
I knew it.
Wait.
Wait, it's a girl toilet?
Mhmm.
And it's...
Alright, let me do my thing real quick.
Ready?
Okay, okay.
Okay, I got you.
*fart*
*laughter*
Okay, I'm gonna roll
Persuasion
For you
Thank you man
What'd I get?
Okay, kill her!
*laughter*
I kill her!
Okay, roll an attack roll.
*laughter*
Okay.
Nice, okay, yeah.
You just start beating up this girl, Toilet.
*laughter*
Smash her to bits?
Yeah, you try to slide in there and replace her.
Alright, cool.
*laughter*
That worked out.
just
hello to me. Yeah he doesn't know. Alright. I think that he just invalidated the game,
he just cross pollinated, I think that he cheated by saying hello. You're supposed to
not hear each other man. Yeah, he ran away. He saw you and he ran. Alright. That's what
you know. Okay, and I'm kind of like, I didn't even realize he was at this party, and I'm
like damn that's my reaction yeah you also saw you also saw a toilet walk into
a bathroom toilet walk into a bathroom okay where's the bow is this the
bathroom right here yeah yeah okay a toilet there was it walking like with
legs or was it just walking it is right I'm sorry I realize it did happen in
of
was
about it yeah I did take a huge swig of that that Viking ale. My bladder's probably pretty
full. I don't know I guess I guess I'm gonna go check the toilet. You can do that, you
can do whatever you want. You also got a mat you can play games with. I don't want you
to feel like you have to do that just because I gave you a new detail.
It is, okay, if I was at a party, I'm trying to figure out right now, if I was at a party,
me and I saw.
Everyone else seems kind of non-plussed by the toilet, by the way.
Right, but if I was at a party and I saw two things happen at the same time.
First I saw my sworn enemy who I've been trying to kill and who I have tools to kill, I saw
I saw him run away, but at the same time I saw a toilet walk in the other direction.
What would I do?
Which path would I choose?
It's a hard one, man.
Really.
I'm really trying to play the character here.
I have no idea which.
It's amazing about roleplaying in Dungeons and Dragons.
It's just all those kinds of questions you never had to ask.
Okay, I'm going to roll a d20, and if I get above a 10, I'm going after the white
spot.
This is what you would do in real life.
you would see this happen in flip a coin.
I mean they're both equal importance.
Investigate yeah, trying to achieve my life's goal of murder or investigating something fundamental.
Something is wrong with reality.
Alright, above 10 is white spy.
Alright that's a 3, I'm going to the toilet.
Toilet time yeah, ok cool.
So yeah, walk yourself into the potty.
- Okay.
I'm gonna investigate the potty.
- Mm-hmm.
All right, cool. - Using my investigation.
- All right, yeah, roll investigation.
- That's a crit one.
(laughing)
- Nothing weird here.
- Oh, well.
- Looks like a toilet.
- Yeah, I guess I must have just been seeing things.
Well, you know, a party like this can be,
you know, it can be hard to get into the bathroom sometimes.
So while I'm here I might as well, you know, just take a leak.
Okay.
Alright, anything you want to do, Toilet?
I CHOMP HIS DICK OFF!
Okay, roll an attack roll.
With advantage.
I CHOMP HIS DICK OFF SO EASILY!
16, man!
16 is gonna hit.
Okay.
Alright, roll 3d6.
Oh my god.
My revenge, man!
Yes!
My revenge!
My revenge man, yes!
14 damage.
Really? Yeah, what's your health?
13, bro.
[Laughter]
I'm gonna tell Pat to put his head
Pat, come on.
He forgot where the button is.
Okay.
Dude, I did your job for you, man.
this is pretty good because you're just killing yourself in the garage
what
lately you killed him
charlie chapters did you call the park
are you guys working together
because he only i was a little bit and he hired me that i would have been a if
you have found a uh... that guy that could have been
and i would have been that he found a lot of talk to like four guys and i don't
know anybody bro i just i need to be the toilet
i think it is a little unfair steven seagal immediately started talking to a
toilet and i said what if the toilet talked back
is my thought
i've wrote i'm sorry i didn't but i i guess i i guess a viking or a wizard or
any of those people talk to you know i think it would be a bad
yeah immediately job okay i guess i'm just literally not played it because i'm
just a quick look at the
so i was fine
steven seagal at the meantime
uh... is to kill himself in this guy mac in the garage
you just heard the car on his waiting for cameron
i'm not i'm not a little and i know you have to do you know what
i'm not a little
really you know what you would seek all first cameras toilet
wayne and that's that pat definitely
i would like to stabilize camera
or that didn't happen i didn't get a dozen i have a man he hasn't figured it
out you know i can heard that i don't care if you heard that man okay alright
i think that's fair i'd like to stabilize going i think it's fair use
melodies definite you should not stabilize me you should have you should
just try and kill pet
and nine
yeah and they stabilize me
of you know i think
at the peak
the pat
pat deafened you do
okay let's fail
so so i should
not stabilize you let you die and you should we can't have heard his
my body
okay i do that help for you
uh... do you want we can have our lost because i realized that full-blown
stuffy cameron after a bit i realize is p tasted so good that i think i can't
let him die yet so it's a little it's kind of her tasted
yeah i have to respect somebody who has an amazing tasting p with a great diet
okay cool
there's a lot of stuff man
and went right through me
you caleb then we'll have cameron's items
so okay but i am we get a birdies in him where he's sitting on the to moving
toward
the
it's a dead guy to move it to a little kid yeah
yet so you guys just moving together i like that a lot
uh... and can you get you still have your voice in everything to them i'm
ventriloquizing you
well i'm just gonna
what the fuck is this bro?
what's what? look at what pet just showed up on my roll20
i'm gonna send it to the chat
will you show this to everybody?
this just came up over the map
steal request patrick yoda wants to steal this card
haha i got a check of diamonds
it's not hard to stop playing the card game
letting it go
uh... monolithic
yes
right on and i put it on our deck
alright i wish for some reason
the way the token layers were
see fuckin the toilet
alright so you guys are moving out why can we hear him
'Cause he doesn't mute himself when he deafens, he wants everybody to be able to hear him.
I'll mute him.
He wants to enter everyone else's turn.
I muted him.
Attention.
He just wants the attention, man.
So yeah, where do you want to go, Toilet?
Do I know where Steven is?
No, I mean, he didn't tell you his plan.
You did see him run back towards the garage.
And you would have seen him put down the tripwire, too.
We're gonna head towards the garage.
Me and Cameron.
Okay.
Alright, there's a tripwire there, you know that.
And Stephen will have, we'll figure out a result in a second.
Oh, do you need me to send you my items by the way, to patch this in the video?
No, I did not.
You can just tell me what they are.
Yeah, just tell him, yeah.
They're a portable hole, a teleporting umbrella, and a giant magnet.
What does a teleporting umbrella do?
It teleports you to where I previously marked, which was on Dylan's back.
Oh, true.
Okay so, can a toilet jump?
You can roll athletics I think to jump.
Okay, because I'd like to jump over that trip line.
14. I don't have a character sheet so I'm just rolling.
That's fine, yeah. You shouldn't have any.
Next time I'll make a character sheet.
Cool, alright, you jump over.
Yeah, and so now Pat is gonna undeafin him.
Because you're both in the same room at this point, and your turn's going on.
Oh, I need him, I just realized.
Who?
For myself.
Um, yeah, you see a toilet come in with Cameron sitting on it.
Roll insight.
Well, do I roll with advantage?
No.
You know, probably disadvantage, you have Gat, you have fucking...
Well, I got a 23.
Well, you got a crit.
Cam is dead and he's on top of the toilet.
God damn it.
The jig is up, Cameron.
Damn.
Oh my god, wait a minute.
And then what I'm gonna do...
Oh yeah, sorry, you also need to take...
No, I'm an idiot.
Please tell me he's dead from the fumes.
He's only going to take 5 damage.
You'll take 1d6 damage every turn.
So you take 5 damage so far from the fumes.
I don't know why you started poisoning yourself.
Mack is dead at this point.
He's just unconscious and breathing in monoxide.
Well I see Cameron.
You're the second casualty today.
You're third actually.
Because you killed Cameron.
I didn't kill Cameron, I killed Mac.
So I see Cameron on the toilet and immediately I'm going to throw my exploding canary at
him.
Well you gotta roll for that.
What do we roll?
Just d20s?
I dodge, I dodge man.
14.
You just roll a d20, he doesn't roll anything.
11.
14.
fourteen that is going to be the toilets a c
what's the other statement
ten
all right let's
and giving you a giving you any or so i was and that's a explosions are
incredibly damaging to toilets
you know they're not mad at what i would like to say to be
brooklyn has a lot of people have a lot of toilet has toilet has thirty h p
toilet is
toilet is not a bit of a tank
you do take eleven damage.
And then with my... can I do another action or is that it?
That's fine.
Wait, he didn't hit the tripwire?
Um, nah, that's it right now.
You can also run.
I jumped over it, bitch.
No, it's where it jumped over.
Alright, then I'm gonna Aikido roll.
He knew about it, but he still had to roll to jump.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
With my... using my Aikido ability, which Aikido you're supposed to use your opponent's...
I'm going to use my weight against him.
I think that Steven Seagal could break a toilet because he had to roll a strength saving throw.
So I'm going to do an Aikido roll at him right now.
Like those videos, like those videos where they put the bowling balls.
No, you know the videos where they put the balls on the ramp and they go at the toilets?
on
would you double-cross me? No. I know I told you that Cameron Fetter killed you
killed your father with a giant poop that made him choke. He did tell him that.
Yeah but what I'm realizing is that Cameron's pee and poop is so delicious
that it's not because it's not that my dad was like being forced to do it my
dad wouldn't let him off the toilet and I'm sure Cameron if he were alive he'd
have some flashback to this sometime where he felt as if his ass was stuck to the toilet
yeah Cameron you wanna talk about that?
the toilet wouldn't let him go how that happened?
yeah that actually happened to me this morning it just happened
yeah I'm one day old I just got born
well it's a new how you gotta get a new toilet for the party bro
you gotta have a party you don't wanna use a normal toilet
wait and that girl I killed was my sister oh my god no
no fuck no I had no idea
Sorry, I'm putting it all together. What he tried to flirt with a girl toilet. You got a one to kill her
You tried to flirt with your sister, I didn't know it was my sister
Gasps and this
Jalopy in this garage has been filling up the whole house making us all crazy. We need to leave together
I've always had your back
*silence*
I'm going to run up to him, well, right up to him.
And I am going to bite him.
Yeah, roll.
Damn.
15.
That does hit.
So I have to roll a d6.
That's going to do 1d6 damage.
Okay.
Do I attack now?
No, he does.
And he got 3 damage to you.
It is, well, unless he wants to move.
and
you can see the garage way it will be an attack of opportunity you know opportunity
well you know i'm well because if he if i'm i'm going to use the garage
i said i i said i think it's a lot like myself and it's um... to the pocket of
the laundry wire there are the laundry tube
the one at all the play all the water that's in the laundry i'm going to get
back i get an attack of our business in the middle of a cycle my short bow
Okay.
Well, I got two 18s.
You should just use your knife.
Okay.
Well, okay, that does hit.
So roll for damage.
That's going to do half damage because he's a toilet, but still pretty good.
So that's five damage.
All right.
So now I'm 14 HP.
So toilet, you're at 14.
Yeah, and you went over here.
When he shakes me off, can I fly off and land in the driver's seat of the car?
Yes.
That's my gas and my hands on the steering wheel. Yes, and the garage door is closed by the way
Okay, okay, and you're gonna just you're gonna just wait wait into the wall
Yeah, let him drive. Please. Let me drive through the wall and go on a road trip
Dead Cameron dead Cameron road trip. Yep
And it's it's him dead asleep in the in the car driving through ghost riding the whip bro. Yeah, I'm kidding roadhead. Yeah
Here let me get you a car
I'm in a car. I know but one that can move get out me car
Yeah, and you got that car that can you get the car from get out me car
So wait.
You're gonna look like shit on your road trip, man.
I got you.
Yeah!
Okay, I'm starting to understand how this is a car and not a submarine.
So he just broke through the garage door.
Okay, cool.
So now, okay, so now I don't take any poison damage from the gas.
damage from the gas. Yeah, it is new McLaren.
*snort*
Oh, you did
still take poison damage from the last turn.
So what's my poison damage? Yeah, now there's no more.
After this.
I'm dead. *laughs*
I'm fuckin' dead.
*laughs*
Yeah.
Wait, really?
Wait, the toilet is awesome.
Yeah, the toilet's pretty good.
Alright, Caleb's starting to like the toilet now.
This is the first time I ever won, I was a fucking NPC toilet.
What the hell?
And I wasn't even supposed to be playing, I was supposed to just be walking around.
Alright, well, I will say that Pat basically won, so it is kind of a tie.
Toilet won, man.
Toilet really won, I guess.
So we're gonna put you guys...
I had, uh, I have, I have really, look I have got other maps.
Continue this!
I would rather us do a, really do a...
Yeah wait, can we just keep going?
Oh yeah.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
I'm
or do we roll for new items?
- Octagon. - I'm ready, bro.
Let's do it. - All right.
- Okay.
- We're gonna roll for new items,
but they're gonna be special items.
- 11, six, nine.
- Okay.
- I got 15, 19, eight.
All right.
yes
to get my text that
that is amazing
when you think of it he has conspiring it's the toilet
politics it to you to say you can see it
to something interesting i saw
nowadays
that happened
I'm giving you your items, Pat, and then I'll give you everyone else their items.
[Humming]
Hi, hi, hi.
Guess the song.
Travis officially has a nickname for Taylor and fans are losing it.
So what do you guys think it is?
Tee-Tay?
Could be Tee-Tay.
I think it could be T.
Could be Baby Tim 15198.
Yeah.
Or it could just be something like Sweetie.
Honey.
Baby.
Yeah, Honey and Baby.
I don't have enough items, but some of them will be special.
Or what if it's Mrs. Travis?
Oh shit.
Mrs. Kelsey.
But then she would have two girl names.
Yeah.
I never thought about how maybe that's why he's able to date Taylor Swift,
Taylor Swift is because he has a girlish last name.
Because she's so female.
Yeah.
Boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom
boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom
boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom
boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom
boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom
boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom
It was worth a shot, man.
But you have 30 HP and you have resistance against slashing and piercing damage.
And I'm full of poop.
And you're full of poop. And you have a poop shot.
You have a poop shot that does 1d8 for ranged.
And then you have a melee that does 1d6.
I'm gonna keep it up. Buck with y'all.
The toilet better be a problem in the octagon.
Okay.
Alright, you guys got your items.
It's the octagon, but by the way it has only six sides.
Yeah.
All right, guys, roll your dice.
I got an eight on this, dude.
You got an eight?
Okay.
Yeah.
18.
20.
Nice.
All right, Cam, you're up first.
Sorry, let me make you a little bit more equidistant.
There you go.
Don't call me gay for saying equidistant.
Cam, go.
Equidistant means equally distant.
Let's see here.
Thanks Cam.
What's my weapons like?
I guess I'm just gonna come out swinging and I'm just gonna shoot my short bow at the white
spy.
Nice.
Do I do a saving throw?
Have you guys noticed the toilet?
I don't notice the toilet yet.
I think it might be a part of the arena to demoralize us.
(laughter)
- Okay, hasn't learned a thang.
- No, it just does nine damage to you.
- Oh my god.
- Do I have another action?
- You know what I'm gonna do?
- Or no?
- No, I will say--
- Just a move action?
- Yeah, you have a move action, yes.
I will say that I'll let you guys have,
I'll let you guys have,
just 'cause this is gonna be otherwise so brutal,
I'll let you guys have one healing item you can use that does 2d4+2 healing.
Okay.
I'm going for the throat, man.
I'm gonna...
Yeah, I can see that.
Is this a rock?
Or is it just a design on the ground?
No, it's a rock.
I'm hiding behind the rock.
Nice, yeah, you get three quarters cover.
What I'm gonna do is I'm going to use my spring shoes and I'm gonna jump all the way over
to the rock.
What do I roll for that?
Yeah he got spring shoes this round.
That far?
You just have to roll athletics to see if you can make it over there.
And then I am going to shoot my bow down upon him.
You can get like here.
Okay that is with disadvantage because you were very close to him.
Why don't you just, you have like a knife.
Okay that does not hit.
So you just spring over there and just like take out your crossbow and just like miss
him wide.
Okay, toilet.
It scared me though.
My character is scared.
I'd like to go to this big guy in the bottom right corner and try to get him to shit in
my mouth so he looks like he's taking a dump.
He's like a big doughy kind of guy.
I see him, wow I didn't even notice him before.
I didn't even realize anyone else was here.
I'd like to really eat his shit.
Alright, roll persuasion and what do you say?
I can't say anything.
I feel like there's an implication if a toilet comes and sits behind you.
12, good enough.
He immediately starts to try to climb over the railing to shit in your mouth.
He's gonna roll athletics to see if he can do it.
you got a five he falls on his hands he's on the ground
now
so that please god let me know if he is another big guy over here though the top
right
yeah that's where i'm gonna go next turn okay cool
europe gabrielle
okay uh... i would like to ginger how close is he to me
take ten people are walk right up to him
to the white spot
i would like to gingerly place
my item
directly under his feet I think I'm with this simply and easily oh I think that
Steven Seagal is not good in combat I really wish I could have used a reaction
just put it under where you were okay we can record it that's what happened
like he he flew in the air shot his crossbow missed completely while in the
air if it landed in this hole and went to Looney Tunes land. I'm gonna pick up the
hole and put it in my pocket. Okay so you're not dead Pat, you are in
Looney Tune land. I'm gonna put it in my back pocket to be specific.
Okay yuck. Pat your turn, you're gonna have to skip your turn. You were just stuck in
in
I
I see him. Okay. No, so he's not he's right here y'all
He's the ground I see
All right, you're up toilet
Well now I'm gonna go see if I can get that other big guy's attention
Okay, I'm gonna do the same thing. I'm gonna roll a persuasion 14 same deal. He's gonna try to get up there, right?
Yeah, he starts climbing over the stands
And he starts to make his way up top he's gonna roll
all
want
both
uh... they want to see it in you
i wonder if it's shitty i think you're not quite
so uh...
for me
started with my story and i can
okay walk over the toilet sit down on the toilet
and you remember which pocket i put my whole into the union
and me sitting down the toilet causes the whole to go upside down
you put me in the whole
no i put uh... he's coming out of the whole into you
uh... if that can be allowed to have a way
yes fine or i guess you can go to the whole i don't know i i don't go into the
whole i don't know
i'm not worried about winning this year i'm trying to eat some i was trying to
sit out that guys
shit out steven seagal into your toilet i want one fact i think it's shit
upper decker while the other one does it in the middle
you're freaky bro i know a bit
who's not going to toilet
he's got a lot of people are so
the
uh... i got going
going into the the public library bathroom in hearing the schizophrenic
homeless guy in the stall next to you saying "Damn you freaky bro" to the toilet.
Yeah you dub Steven Seagal the toilet, upside down, his legs are kicking like Winnie the Pooh
just flailing up there.
Steven what are you going to do? I'm out now.
I'm just going to swing my dagger around. Yeah you're out but you're in the toilet.
He's upside down, just takes his dagger out, swinging it inside the toilet.
He's got a 10 AC.
Roll an attack.
Okay, yeah.
Four.
Yeah, so that does hit the toilet, so roll for damage.
So he's just cutting you up on the inside.
Wait, can I use an item now?
He's slicing you up, but he only does two damage.
No!
Can I retcon?
I'm gonna use my explosive barrel.
Yeah, you can wreck on.
I'm gonna take the toilet out with me.
*laughter*
Why?
Dude, you don't- Cameron's gonna win, man.
I just- and I don't need-
Cameron is on top.
So it'll be Cameron-
I'm taking a sandwich right now.
We're all going.
It's a musical sandwich with a Cameron and toilet bun.
Okay. Alright, cool.
It's just gonna be a tie again.
So roll 8d4.
Oh there we go.
Jesus Christ.
Actually no, I have hella health.
I'm gonna live.
I'm at 28 health.
Oh wait.
Why do you always roll them separately?
Wait, I'll redo it.
What kind of strange world are you living in?
20.
Yeah, we'll make my life easier.
So you and Cameron both die.
The exploding barrel.
the toilet is basically almost dead it's in like
it's in this
tired state
he's an NPC guts and blood and shit is that a technical win?
and these two fat guys are trying to climb over
it's your fault man the toilet won two rounds in a row and it was clearly one person's fault
just now it happened
it was one person's fault both times man you killed yourself last time and this time
one of them gets to be on top of the toilet
one of them does manage to climb over finally so who is it if you know i want
to give you my last i want to give you my last item i had a grappling hook i
wanted you to grapple the fact that you
elements we
instead pat blue everyone up
the into one then
toilet the toilet one i i can't wait the whole point is
i've heard it
i've ruined it is the whole point of this was i was gonna be an n_p_c_
but i'm so fucking amazing at this game
yeah i just accidentally won both times as a toilet mind you i will say that
probably cavern would have won if there was no toilet just based purely off the
fact that
steven seagal did just jump into the fray and get shot. no man the toilet
the toilet won the first one and you were trying to be like oh it's a tie we
can't really count that yeah and then you put it to sudden death the toilet won
again that's a confirmation
that's crazy to give it to anybody else i would really want to know how i first
as well and the one that you said he has to figure it out alright
that
that's the
and i was not a very suspicious by going for a couple months now
the eight-week
it's a constant confidence
alright
that's not what i thought
not even me
but we would
This sucks!
A toilet an NPC made an hour ago.
Yeah.
That can't speak!
And only when a decent didn't even know where to set match.
Good night!
I think that is true.
Thanks y'all.
Bye bye.
We need to go up to space, come back, become the Thoughtful Three.
Yes.
The Thoughtful- oh my god.
The Thankful Three.
What would your powers be in the thankful?
Well, I'd be.
OK, I mean I would be at a stretching ability.
No man, you can't.
You know whatever man stretching.
What the hell do I be?
Even new power?
Yeah, OK, I would have acrobatic powers.
OK, that's pretty good and I
would be Mr. Thankful.
Could I should be late?
Have laser beams?
We did it from where my hands,
my fingers, 10 laser beams.
Who and they come in a 10 fingers.
That's too many.
Mr. 10 fingers, Mr.
ten fingers finger.
The finger is good.
Okay, I'll just shoot to from all.
Okay, the finger.
I'll just do you do this.
Yeah, just yeah, you're the finger.
Yeah, and I do this and it shoots it out of my ring finger
or it's lightning bolts.
Yeah, and it's the shocker that the shocker is a real guy.
It's your right.
So the finger would be real.
I would have like the like like the human torch.
I would have water powers and I would be the human drop
And that would be the human drop.
And I would turn into water.
I'd be a water guy.
I'd be the human drop.
I'd be a water guy. I'd walk around.
That's my whole power.
Basically my power is that I give people cups of water.
Who's a super villain in that world?
Doctor Doom.
Okay, so Doctor Doom comes up, right?
Mr. Thankful, I'm acrobatic.
So I do a bunch of backflips to distract him.
him
You get 'em wet, you finger 'em, and I amaze.
(Mario Screaming)