- All right, everyone.
It's time.
Spy versus Spy.
Finale.
- The gauntlet.
- Finals.
- From what I understand--
- Maybe not finale.
- From what I understand,
the bracket looked a little bit like this.
It was Caleb versus Patrick,
and I believe Patrick emerged victorious.
Is that correct?
- That's correct.
- And then it was me versus Caleb,
and Caleb lost yet again.
So which only leaves one final matchup.
- That's correct.
- It's a very small bracket.
(laughing)
Unless we do, unless we do
you versus the winner.
- Me versus the winner?
And then I make all the rules and everything?
- Spy versus God.
- Spy versus God would be so fuego.
That'd be gas.
- I'm interested.
- Me too.
- We'll talk about that.
'Cause here it's, right now it's white spy versus Cameron.
And--
- I'm white spy?
I thought I was black spy.
- No, Caleb is black spy.
- Well, okay.
- Does that change something for you?
- No, I just had to change it in my roll 20.
- Oh, were you actually black spy?
- I don't remember.
- I have you in here as white spy.
- Okay, well that's probably right then.
- Yeah.
I think we flip the coin to find out who was Black Spy
and who wasn't. - Yeah.
I think I might have given Caleb Black Spy.
- That makes sense. - 'Cause of his tendencies.
Let's go to the first arena.
- I want to juggle three butts.
- What? - What?
- What?
- Did that work or no?
Oh, now they have it all-- - No, it didn't work.
- Roll 20 now has it all broken up in a different way.
- Ah.
- All the UI redesign.
- Yeah, they just don't want to--
- I just wanted, for the audio listeners,
I just wanted to explain that I'm dressed up
currently like a spy.
So you don't have to--
- You're not dressed as a spy.
- You don't have to, no, I'm dressed up exactly like a spy.
- You're dressed up as an extra
in a Five Finger Death Punch music video.
- No, I think I look more like a spy.
(laughing)
- You got your ass beat up, son.
All right, what does it look like now?
Are we where we need to be?
I see a place with two bathrooms.
Yep, this is an office, isn't it?
It is the bank.
Oh, I see the vault now.
So we're gonna start, it's gonna escalate
until we get to, you know where we're gonna go to, Pat.
Don't spoil it for everyone else, though.
How do I know?
Because you, we talked about it.
because I sent you guys a picture of your old drawings.
- Oh, okay.
- Wait, what?
- Oh, okay, nevermind.
I wasn't sure, I thought Pat knew.
Okay.
- No, I don't know, but I was just--
- Don't look at your old texts.
- I was trying to be reassuring.
- Okay.
- I thought that you needed that.
- No, I didn't, I'm good.
That's very sweet.
I'm sad I give off that kind of energy, though.
It's not great.
(laughing)
To know about me.
So, okay, we have--
- These are like the dirtiest glasses in the world,
I can't even wear 'em, sorry.
- No, you're fine.
The white spy, Pat, you are at the bank right now,
somebody's putting cards.
- Yeah, where'd these cards come from?
- I found out that you can draw cards.
- Don't do it, why would you teach others that?
- It was an accident.
I made a deck up here and I was dragging cards out of it
and I didn't know if it could see them.
(laughing)
It was my bad, y'all.
- That's so good.
There's lots of games we can play.
We can even add deck drawing elements to D&D
as like a mechanic.
- Yeah, I was honestly just trying to figure out
how to whisper to Julio so I could say something
so nasty to him, but I just accidentally started
drawing cards from a playing card deck instead.
(laughing)
- Cam, you were at the ATM.
Pat, you were at the desk at the teller.
You guys, your job, as always, is to kill each other.
But we're gonna start with you guys figuring out
what gadgets you have in this here bank.
So, I did a little bit of swapping.
Cam, I see the message you sent.
- I didn't send anything.
- Okay.
(laughing)
- I didn't say anything.
- For the listeners at home,
he said I wanna juggle three butts,
I wanna join the circus as a butt swallower.
It made me laugh.
So you guys roll three d20s.
I added some new items, removed some other ones.
So we're gonna have some fun with that.
And once you guys roll those three 20s,
I will send you your results.
- Three d20s?
Okay, I'm gonna roll them right now.
- I rolled mine.
- Nice.
- Okay, is it 10, seven, one?
- Oh, I didn't roll, sorry.
- No worries.
- Wait, no, I did that wrong.
Let me--
- No, it still worked.
You can see the three results.
- 13, 18, 13.
- No, the first 13 is the sum of three D20s.
- All right, that's a good point.
- Yeah, don't stress so much about that kind of thing.
All right, Cam, I'm sending you your three items.
- Okay.
- Ignore that number, it's the new, from the new list.
- There's a new number?
- Yeah, there's a number I put that's on there,
but it's from my new list.
- Oh, I see it.
- Yeah.
It's 'cause I'm doing it all on one giant list
and then just saying, getting rid of these 10,
adding these 10.
And what else did you get?
Okay.
Oh, you got like kind of a cool mix.
- You heard that?
I got a cool mix.
- Oh, you got two 13s.
- No, the first 13 is three D20s added together.
- Oh, okay.
Okay, we'll just take those three then.
- I made it confusing.
Yeah, that's my bad.
- No, I should have just read that too.
Okay.
All right, we're gonna be done in the...
And then was that six and then five?
- Julio.
- And then what is that, two?
- Julio, can I ask you a question really quick?
- Pat got some classic items.
- I think if you ask him a question,
it won't come a pick up at all on the episode.
- All right, here we go.
You guys have your items.
- I just wanted to ask him if I looked like a spy.
- You look like a spy.
Just, I mean, like you don't,
You look kinda, I mean it's a little bit more
like Steven Seagal than a spy.
- I think that's what I'm going for.
- Okay, yeah, he kind of is always a spy a little bit.
- He is always a spy in everything he's in, exactly.
- At least a little bit he is.
He's like elite always.
All right, cool.
Now both of you guys roll one more D20
to determine who's gonna go first here.
- Okay.
I heard this thing the other day.
Oh wow, damn.
Oh wow, what terrible rules.
I know, so horrible.
Let's get him out of the way.
We got a three and a one.
That's gonna go to Pat though.
So Pat, you're gonna go first.
Cam, take off those earmuffs.
All right, well, I guess because I look like him,
I am Steven Seagal now.
Okay, cool.
So I'm looking at the bank teller and I'm like.
Hi sir, what would you like to do today?
How can I help you?
I came here to make a withdrawal,
But I think now that I look at you,
I want to make a deposit.
Baby girl, me want it, punani.
- Okay, yeah, roll, let's have you roll charisma.
Right, just out the gate.
Let's have you do that.
- I'm gonna roll with disadvantage.
- I think it's persuasion, really.
- You should roll--
- I'm gonna roll, every persuasion roll I've seen
once a go is roll with disadvantage.
- Yeah, definitely is.
Okay, a two.
(laughing)
Roll a perception check.
- What, the security guard's gonna go shoot me?
(laughing)
Okay, a 10.
- Okay, you see her visibly shift
and it looks like she might be pressing something
underneath her desk.
(laughing)
- Okay.
Am I perceptive enough to know that she...
- Yeah, you've been in these types of situations a few times.
(laughing)
That's why I'm giving you the 10.
You know what this looks like.
- And I just say...
- It's usually at a chick-fil-a,
I tried to, I tried to, um, I tried to resolve the situation.
Okay, okay. What do you do? What do you do?
And I mean, make a deposit in your pussy.
Just to clear things up.
I mean that I'm, I want to make a deposit into your pussy with my cum.
I'm Steven Seagal.
You just have no money.
- Steven Seagal from the movies.
- Okay, this security guard is coming near you now.
- Okay, then I'm gonna use my teleporting umbrella.
(laughing)
That I've been pretending is a cane this whole time.
- Okay, pick a spot on the map.
- I'm gonna go into this break room
where the cool drinks are.
Let me read what the umbrella does.
- Yeah, yeah, please do.
This umbrella is enchanted to transport the user
to a previously marked location.
Oh, okay.
Previously marked, so.
- I'll say you walked into the bank.
So like, you know, this doesn't,
so here's the thing.
The entrance to the bank is back down where Cam is.
Like you see where Cam is, where it's by the ATMs.
- Yeah. - So it's like, like--
- Okay, I'm gonna go, I'm gonna go outside.
I'm gonna go outside, but all I'm gonna do
is put my sunglasses on
so that they think I'm a different guy.
- Okay, you're gonna go outside the bank.
bank. Don't move your character yet though. Don't move your character yet because
Cam technically would not know that you disappeared from the bank so we're gonna
do a little like we're just gonna we're going to have it that when he enters the
room okay I'm gonna remove your token okay and then I will place it where it
needs to be once he knows where you are but he's not gonna know where you are
yet so we'll have that be the item that you used the security guard is gonna be
like kind of looking around for a guy like you,
but we'll resolve that after.
So that was a great turn.
All right, take off your headphones.
Okay.
- Okay.
- All right, man, you're at the ATM, it looks like.
What are you, are you trying to go,
you going into the bank?
It seems like you might've tailed him in here.
- No, I'm leaving the bank.
- You're done?
You're leaving the bank? - I'm leaving to go home.
- Okay, cool.
- No, I'm going into the bank.
- Okay.
- I'm going to the ATM, I suppose.
- All right, you're already right by the ATM.
What do you wanna do?
You can also like, you, I think the fiction here
in my mind was, White Spy was going in here.
You followed him in here.
That was my fiction, I think.
But like, it's up to you how you were planning this.
Have you been casing this joint?
You know he goes here often.
You know?
- Yeah, I guess it's, in a normal world,
it's hard to miss a white spy. A cartoon white spy.
So maybe I saw him going in here.
>> Mm-hm.
>> Should I read out my items also? Do I need to do that?
>> Only if you want to.
Pat, then read out his items to give you a hint.
>> Okay. Then I won't do that.
>> A hint of what you can do.
>> Yeah. So, I guess I'm pretending to use the ATM.
>> Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
and I'm gonna use my eavesdropper,
my sonic eavesdropper while I do that
to try and listen and hear if I can get any insight
into what the white spy is doing inside.
- Okay, cool.
All right, cool.
So when you use that, you hear some muffling
and then you hear someone go, "Where did he go?
"Where'd that guy go?"
And then you hear a woman's voice go,
"I don't know, he was just here, he was just here.
He was he was saying all kinds of awful things and uh yeah, and that's what you kind of hear
okay, then I
That makes me think that I'm afraid
Of being ambushed
Makes me think I'm afraid so I what I would like to do is
I'd like to I kind of if he's vanished maybe in my mind. I'm thinking he's pro
He either knows I'm tailing him or he's about to go on the offensive
So I want to move outside and kind of like stand next to the door
Like as if I'm hot, you know hiding off to the side of the door
So the door opens I can immediately grab somebody or something
All right, cool. Move your move your character to where you want to go then I go like here
Cool
You see the white spy right in front of you Pat put on your headphone Pat show Pat to put on his headphones
Pat
So, Cam used the eavesdropper device and heard the commotion outside of a security guard
going "Where did he go?
Where did he go?"
And then he was like, "He's gonna try to ambush me.
I gotta make sure that I get the jump on him.
I'll go outside and wait for him."
And here you were.
I'm right in front of me.
So is that the end?
I take mine off?
That's the end of your turn, yeah.
Okay.
So take yours off.
Okay, Pat.
Okay, okay, so I know that he's right in front of me, right?
Can I use the umbrella again or is it once per turn because it doesn't say once per turn the umbrellas?
We were it's a way we were doing it before was like you can only use the item once
so I
I think we'll probably have to keep doing that for now just cuz I haven't okay fine-tune these outside of that
So I see him immediately
Yeah, okay, then I'm right in front. I'm just gonna throw the explosive canary. I love it. Okay, cool
Cam yeah, I'm telling cam to put on his headphones though. Can you help help me tell him? Yeah? Yeah? Yes nodding nodding?
It's got to be another way. Oh, yeah, you just have to think of I mean to what else is message
You would just do a fucking idiot do a thumbs up. Oh, yeah, I was doing that before
They go like like I'm supposed to register this
Yeah, Jibio can do the discord soundboard thing. Yeah, I should
Yes, just do a thumbs up that's okay, I feel like my big-ass thumb
Roll a dexterity saving throw
Okay, Cameron
Let me oh geez I see the white spy
Steven Seagal
throwing a something at you.
- Where's my character, oh here it is.
Yeah, you find it.
- Okay.
Deck saving throw?
- Oh yeah.
- Oh yeah, I need to open up my character sheet real quick.
- That's an 11.
Okay.
Yeah.
Pat, roll 4d4.
- Okay.
- You take 11 damage, he throws an exploding canary at you.
- What?
- Yeah.
- Wait, am I supposed to be at half health right now?
- No, you should be at full health.
- Okay.
- Sorry, yeah.
- I take 11 damage, I'm not gonna say how much I'm at.
- Yeah, you just like walk outside and see Steven Seagal
and he just throws a bird at you and it explodes.
- Looks like I flipped you the bird.
- Damn.
- Okay, I think we just keep the headphones on right now
until you guys are separated again.
You're up, Cam.
- Okay, I would like to use my item to turn invisible.
- Ooh, nice. - Dang.
- Do it.
You turn invisible. - I do it.
- Okay.
At the end of this, this is an item
that you can use continuously, but at the end of the,
well, actually, yeah, so what we should do,
- Well actually, so before you use it,
sorry I didn't tee this up correctly.
The point of it being malfunctioning is that
you'll roll a d20 and if it's greater than 10 it works,
if it's less than 10 it doesn't work.
But then it will-- - Oh shit, really?
- Yeah, yeah. - Oh, I don't wanna use that.
That's, I don't like those odds.
- Yeah, no, it's not great odds right now.
- I say, I go up to Steven Seagal, white spot,
and I go like this, hey buddy, you better watch it.
and i put you in the face
mission okay cool you know
role that actual
i think you have like a knife
the q_r_ have a regular here
here in a row and
you might think you might all have repears
can i
the christianity through here that hits him
yet i was gonna ask with my i_q_-eight and i got to that but
no
now now it's even cigars i can say hey buddy what's the big idea and then i
take out my rapier.
Alright it's your turn now Steven.
Looks like we're in the belly of the beast.
Oh because I stabbed you in the belly.
Yeah and you're a beast.
And that's the movie he was in.
And you behave beastly.
That's a movie he was in.
Oh yeah.
Was that his production company or someone else's?
I think so, it's some Romanian thing.
It's probably his then yeah.
Um, what do I do now?
Okay, so I have a stab in the belly and
you have what I do.
I have a I have a cunning action.
So what I'm going to do is I'm going to Ike
you know, we're all rogues, so I'm going to Ike to roll
like on my back, you know.
Yeah, I'm going to roll.
down the street to my right.
And can I roll,
can I roll a d20 to see how far I can go?
Like maybe that'll determine the yards or feet or?
Hold on.
Yeah, that'll determine the feet.
I can roll up to 20 feet.
Yeah, this is distant.
You're trying to do is use a cutting action to disengage.
Yeah, doing it in the form of an Aikido roll.
Uh-huh.
I'm rolling
my right
towards the bathrooms.
I'll let your, I'll let your, your Aikido roll also determine
if you get like an extra 10 or 15 feet.
Okay.
No, just let them roll and then have that be the number of
feet.
Yeah.
Do that.
Roll.
Yeah, do that.
Roll, roll a d20.
I want you to do that.
Okay.
For my.
Yeah.
10.
Yep.
That's, that's two squares y'all.
Yeah.
Okay, cool.
- Wait, that's, oh.
- That's much smaller than if you just walked.
- You also have a move at, no, well, that's his disengage.
You also still have a move.
- Okay, then I'm gonna go, I'm gonna move towards.
- I'm sorry.
- A 10 foot roll is impressive.
- 10 foot roll and then I'm gonna.
- Sounds like somebody has a light load.
- I'm gonna run through this window right here.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- I'm gonna map this out.
- Okay, so I rolled here,
and now I'm all fours on the ground.
- Yeah, you're outside, so for the people--
- Steven Seagal, all fours on the ground.
- He's outside for all through the window.
He's in the front of the bank, by the way,
there's all these offices where like,
there are like consultants you can meet with,
they're like, yeah, like,
and so there's just people who's like,
I had one of them in here,
but I'll move him in the window you're gonna roll into.
Like one of the--
- I think, I thought it was this one.
- Whatever one you're trying to roll into,
there are people into that. - Yeah, I'm gonna go
into this one here.
- So. - You can add all the figurines.
- So I do a 10 foot roll over here.
Now I've landed, I'm on all fours,
like that photo of Shemar Moore.
- Jesus Christ!
- Says somebody as you crash through the window.
- Yeah, then I jump, well, I leap from all fours
on this tile through the window.
So I think I should roll athletics for that.
- Oh yeah, definitely you should.
- And that'll determine, or acrobatics rather.
And then-- - Either one is fine.
- Okay, and then we'll see how that,
we'll see if I even make it to the window
from that tile on the street.
Oh my God, it's a perfect leap.
- Fucking graceful.
- That's what he wanted.
- It's, it's, it's, uh.
- It's such a graceful leap through the window
that it just leaves like a perfect Looney Tunes
like hole in the shape of your body.
There's no shattering at all.
- Well, no, no, the reason,
- It's hard to kill Aerosagal right now.
- That's like what you tapped into.
You tapped into something ancient.
- The reason that it left such like a perfect hole
is 'cause I'm so big that I was already
the size of the window.
- Yeah, it just sloughed off basically.
Like, you just like removed the window basically
by crashing into it.
- It didn't shatter.
- Yeah, it just did.
- It just like, whoop.
(laughing)
- Cool, okay, you're in this guy's office now.
He's like, get, get, get.
Like this guy's like freaking out. He doesn't know how to react. He's like stepping away back to his desk
He's getting nervous. You also still have an item that you can use this turn. Oh, okay. Let me just
Look through my items right quick
I didn't get any good items man. You have one more item bullshit. Yeah
I'm gonna I'm gonna wait on my items, and then I'm gonna oh no. I'm gonna put my
You've only one item left to you by the way yeah
Then I'd have no items if you're gonna use the item and you want to use it stealthily just or something like just
I want to use it on okay
Like now that you're separated from each other
We'll do the turns like you're not really separated from each other
But you're far enough that like we'll do the turns back to the way they were okay. Should I take my headphones off?
Pat if there's something you want to do or you want to yeah, yeah, I'm gonna okay. Yeah, take off your headphones cam
- Yeah, yeah.
- Okay, I'm gonna throw my caltrops
in front of the window.
'Cause if it shattered the glass,
then that would've, yeah, I wouldn't have thrown them
if I didn't shatter, or if I did shatter the glass.
- Okay, roll sleight of hand to see kind of like
if you can place them quickly and like ably
within this turn in such a way.
Okay.
- I put one down meticulously, so I have--
- Okay.
- Next time, I should have had you do a whisper roll.
Next time we'll have you do that
so that it only shows up on my end.
Yeah, it's okay, it's fine.
Yeah, a couple, like one of them kinda like--
- I put one right in the middle.
- Yeah, one of them sticks out a little bit,
but we'll still have to roll like an insight
to see if he sees it.
- And then I look up at the guy that I just jumped--
- I was about to say that guy was like looking down
and like kind of regarding them in a freaked out way.
I look at him and I say, "I'm out for a kill, baby."
- The guy is like trying to find the button
under his desk now.
He's like frantically looking for it.
All right, we'll end your turn here.
We'll go to cam now, so.
Thumbs up.
- Yo.
- Pat, take off your headphones.
Okay, your headphones are in?
- Yeah.
- All right.
Yeah, I mean you saw that unfold in front of you over the last six or so seconds, so
So I mean or this is also concurrently happening. You know did you?
Did you chase him?
Did you go another way?
What'd you do?
well now that
Pat's headphones are off. I will say I'm so dangerously low on HP that it's I know I was I was like
I know I was thinking about that when he hit you with the canary
Yeah, I have two very good items so I kind of am terrified so
Can he see me from where I am?
No, he would not be able to see you unless he like pokes his head out. Okay, I'm gonna use my last item
okay, and it's a
disguise kit and
I'm going to
Use it to disguise myself and
Yeah, any roles you do to make sure you're doing like a whisper role sure I'm gonna disguise myself as as Billy Eilish
Okay
You just do that that's what the disguise kit is for
No, yeah, normally I would have you do like a charisma roll or something but now this is the skies kit. He's just do it. Okay
So I'm just thinking so
What do you want to do and I'm gonna figure out well, I'll give you a separate token and I'll move that token
Yeah, I just want to walk into the bank
You just want to walk like I'm going to I'm going to open a checking account my first checking account. I just turned 18
Okay, cool, I'll guess finally time
All right, let me okay, let me get Billy Eilish in here that's a perfect that's a perfect
bait for Steven Seagal. Let me add her in here.
Let's pick one with her with one of her big-ass sweaters. Remember hip-hop sort of
looks. And one where she's rapping. Does she rap or just sing? She basically, she
She does, I don't think she raps.
I don't think she does.
- Me neither.
- Wonder if this'll work.
I bet it's gonna be giant.
- It's gonna be pretty big.
- It's gonna be--
- It's gonna make Patrick's eyebrows raise.
- I'm gonna make it smaller,
but first it's gonna be pretty big.
- All right, let's see it.
- It's uploading.
it's uploading.
Oh my god, it's giant!
Okay, I'm seeing Patrick's middle.
It's so big, man.
You have to make it smaller.
He's gonna notice.
He's gonna notice it, man.
I'm making it smaller.
You gotta make it a lot smaller, man.
Okay.
All right, your turn's over.
Take off your headphones.
Pat.
I'm gonna make it a lot smaller.
Okay, I'm gonna make it a lot smaller.
smaller. Okay. All right. Your turn's over. Take off your headphones.
Pat.
Okay. What's up? What happened? I don't, I can't tell you what happened.
You're still in the bank. You have these Cal trips. There's no sign of,
I'm going to roll persuasion and you will tell me what happened. Okay.
Seven. Hmm. It's not going to work. Um, uh,
Yeah, you don't see like any sign of Cam following you through the windows.
Okay.
Because he has invisibility.
He does.
Uh huh.
So, with...
Well you heard him talk about that, but yeah.
Yeah, I heard him say that.
And I know, okay.
Can I roll perception to see...
Roll persuade, I'm gonna roll persuasion again to ask the guy in the, is the guy in the room
still there?
Yeah, you can just, what are you gonna ask him?
Just ask him it.
Did you see Cameron Fetter walking in here?
*Chuckles*
My immortal enemy, Cameron Fetter.
No, no.
I've seen Cameron Fetter on a bayou.
I haven't- *Chuckles*
I haven't seen anyone walk in here except you just crashing through my window.
I can sense your nervous behavior.
And what I'm gonna do is put you in a stranglehold until you tell me what I wanna hear.
*Chuckles* Okay.
So I'm trying to put this guy in a full roll roll an attack roll. Okay, there's strength check. He has a grapple what you're doing
I mean, I guess it's a contest. So he has to try to resist
Oh
My god, he got a -
Full Nelson in the web like he can escape, but he's just scared. Yeah, he's like, please stop. He's just like
Yeah, yeah
What are you doing
You know what I'm doing. I was born to raise hell. I don't know anything about Cameron
I can go I'll go get somebody who can help you. Maybe you're about to be submerged. Please. Let me go
You're gonna be submerged in my body. Don't put me in your butt sir. I'll help you
Tell me did you see a guy come in here who may have had invisibility powers? No. I didn't see anything like that
Okay, I've decided to trust you you're checking your savings
I've decided to trust you okay. Do you let him go?
Now give me the bank tellers cell phone number
The woman give me a cell phone number
Air drop it. Ashley, you can't air drop it.
I have a different kind of phone.
I'll look at the directory I guess. Just hold on.
And then give me your clothes too.
Meanwhile, the security guard is now at the door.
Is everything alright in there?
Everything is fine in here.
Wait, I think I'm starting to piece together what Cameron did.
Who's that?
Can I ask you what I think Cameron did?
Yeah, I'm not going to tell you though.
Okay, I think that he disguised himself as Billie Eilish.
I'm not going to tell you what happened.
He did, didn't he?
I'm not going to tell you even if he did it.
Alright, okay, okay, okay.
I'm going to pick up the guy, right?
Okay.
(laughing)
- I pick him up and tell him to tell the security guard
that, to tell him that everything's fine in here,
but it's a glass wall.
(laughing)
So can I roll to see, can I roll to see if...
- Security guard's gonna bust in here.
- Yeah, the security guard, it's a glass wall,
but I wanna roll to see if the security guard
doesn't like do anything.
- He's gonna, he's gonna do something.
- 'Cause he can see everything.
He can see everything.
- If you touch this guy right now,
he is gonna do something.
You cannot roll your way around that.
If you are touching a man who is employed at the bank,
the security guard is going to come in
and apprehend you or worse.
- Then can I shut the blind?
- While he's standing outside the window.
- Everything's fine.
We're just about to make out.
(laughing)
- Okay, roll deception with disadvantage.
Okay, security guard is coming in to apprehend you.
You're in the middle of shutting the blinds
and he's just opening the door.
Okay.
- He's gonna try to attack you.
- Okay.
I look at him and I say,
you don't wanna do this man.
You're out of reach.
I'm gonna throw you into the sun.
- Okay, that hits for sure.
- Oh no.
- Oh shit.
- How bad?
- Not that bad, he's just a security guard.
- Okay.
- He's whacking you with a baton.
He does four damage to you.
- I have two HP.
- Okay.
(laughing)
Okay.
You still have a chance, you have no more items left.
Mm-hmm.
But I do have my short bow.
You can attack him back.
I'm gonna shoot him with my short bow.
I'll let you do that, I'll let you do that, yeah.
How do I roll that?
Even though I kind of skipped you there.
Probably should have rolled for initiative there, that's fine though.
Oh, just roll 1d20 and add your dex.
I mean, if it's not on your character sheet.
You should be able to just hit it on your character sheet.
(laughing)
Not that.
- All it did was--
- No, do not.
Open your character sheet and hit short bow.
- Yeah, I did that.
- No, in the middle.
In the middle.
In the middle of the character.
- Oh, there we go.
- Your attacks.
- Okay, I got a 10.
- Okay, that, and it's also with disadvantage
'cause you are right next to him.
- Are you kidding me?
- Okay, yeah.
- I got a crit 20.
- No, this guy, this guy does not--
- I got a 22.
- You take out your bow and you just sort of shoot it
at the ground around his feet.
Okay, I'm gonna take off your headphones.
Your turn is done.
It's a crazy turn.
(laughing)
Okay, okay, Cam.
- I don't like seeing that pop up.
- Okay, yeah.
- I don't like seeing the word shortbow with a 22 pop up.
- It's okay.
You as Billy Eilish just hear a lot of commotion.
You see a Steven Seagal-like figure.
You see a security guard go to a place and say,
go to a bank teller's window area
'cause it's perfectly clear glass.
You see Steven Seagal put a guy in a full Nelson.
Then you see a security guard come over
and say, what's going on in there?
But you see Steven Seagal trying to close the blinds.
And then you see that security guard go in there
and start hitting Steven Seagal with a baton.
We see Steven Seagal take out a crossbow and miss
from point blank range.
So that's what happened.
You see all that as Billie Eilish.
- Yeah.
- So what do you--
- Is there another security guard around?
- There are--
- Are they armed?
With guns?
- They just have batons.
- Is there anybody with a gun in the vicinity?
What state does this take place in?
I mean, nobody has a gun right now, I will tell you.
Well, I should correct that.
- What's the deadliest weapon I can see?
- There is a security guard with a gun by the vault.
- Where's the vault at?
It's up in this top right corner?
- Yeah, top right.
- That's kind of far away.
Okay, I'm gonna waltz over there.
- Okay, how are you going?
So, what do you mean waltz over to the bank?
- Just walk up to it with no trouble.
- Come on, come on.
What you saying?
- Yo.
I'm Billy Eilish.
So you're going up to the bank in this case.
Yeah.
I am researching my new album.
That's about depression and all types of dark thoughts.
And I need to have a gun.
Okay.
Roll persuasion to write my album.
Uh, is this on whisper?
Yeah.
18.
Okay.
Yeah.
Fuck it.
why not? Yeah, the bank, I mean, Pat's gonna die. The bank teller is like, "Sure, I love
Billie Eilish's music." And yeah, you get to go in-
You mean my music?
Mm-hmm. You get to go into-
I don't know why you said it like that. It's me, Billie Eilish.
And you get to go into the vault.
Well, I don't need to be in the vault. I just need to go-
Okay, she goes back and then-
I go, "Yo, wait." I go, "Yo, wait, wait, wait. There's no need to let me into the vault.
I don't want to compromise the security of your operation. I just really-
- You're so conscientious.
And so, she goes back, talks to the security guard,
and then she comes back to you and hands you the gun.
- Okay, I tuck it into my whatever type of pants
Billie Eilish wears.
- Yeah, you don't know enough about that.
- It's the perfect concealed carry,
giant puffy Michelin man t-shirt.
Impossible to tell I have a gun,
and I say, I'll be right back, I'm gonna hit the stew.
- Okay, cool.
- Cool.
- And I start to walk over to Steven Seagal.
- Okay.
- But I'm kind of trying to act
like I'm not walking that direct,
like I guess I'm not really walking directly towards there.
- Just show me where you're--
- I'm just walking back towards the exit.
- Okay.
So you're like here now?
- Yeah, I wanna get as close to Steven Seagal as possible
without making it look like I'm beelining.
- Okay, I mean you didn't really do any,
I mean all you did was persuade,
so you have your dash action still.
- Okay, so yeah, I'll dash.
(laughing)
- How far can I dash?
- Well, let's see, you were here,
and then you went here,
and now you'd be going another,
you have like 40 more feet.
So you could go--
- Where's the window?
- Like you can go up to,
you could go up to, wow,
you could go up to like,
like here.
- Okay, I'll go like right here.
- 'Cause yeah, you're gonna want some distance too.
- Yeah, yeah, I wanna be right here.
I mean Billy Eilish does.
Alright, move yourself.
Oh, I have to move you, right, it's really...
Okay, cool.
Alright, and that's what I got.
That's the end of your turn.
Okay, cool.
Alright.
Pat.
This is a nightmare.
What is he looking at?
He's definitely...
He's in full Suica mode.
nightmare.
Pat.
What is he looking at?
He's definitely, he's
in full Suica mode.
Yo.
OK.
You're in the midst of a fight.
Yeah. And OK,
the Billie Eilish moved closer.
There's no way that that's not
Cameron. Also,
I saw
Like this, my screen was still open.
I saw it moving.
I couldn't hear, but I saw it moving.
I think that's a huge oversight.
- No, I think it's fair.
You have a glass window.
He saw all the stuff you were doing in there.
- That's true.
- Yeah, you saw her go to the bank teller.
You saw the teller go to the back, go back up to her.
And then you saw her move over here.
- Okay.
I'm realizing that this is a zero sum game.
- In what way?
There's no way that I'm going to win.
- Well, some of the stuff you did
put yourself in that position.
- Yeah, and that's because I was not embodying white spy.
- You're embodying yourself.
- And I kind of went into this with the Seagal mindset.
- Yeah.
Which is just being kind of a crazy raper.
Basically a big piece of shit.
- So what's your plan?
- Which one?
- Can I use the umbrella again or no?
- No, I think next time I'll have you guys
use items more than once, depending on the item.
You also use, did you use all three of your caltrops?
Groups of, like your--
- I used two, or one.
I have two.
- So you have two others.
So that is true too.
So you can use an item,
and I think I originally did it
where it's like you can use an item and a tag.
- Can I roll persuasion
and just tell the guy to stop hitting me?
yeah for sure
listen man
you gotta stop hitting me alright
i have an attack force that
you couldn't even believe
they call me the shadow man
okay i'm a
they call me my giant
they call me the glimmer man
and i'm out for a kill
because i used to be the foreigner
stop
And but now I'm the keeper.
- All right, roll.
- Before I hit you with this machete
(laughing)
and send you to absolution.
- Was he in Machete?
- Yeah.
- That's awesome.
Yeah, I mean roll it with the T-80.
- And you're gonna get pistol whipped.
(laughing)
If you don't stop.
- Roll intimidation.
- Is it the movie called Pistol Whipped?
(laughing)
- Roll intimidation with disadvantage.
That is a crazy movie name.
- Intimidation?
- Yeah, with disadvantage.
'cause we established that up top.
All right. - 15 and eight.
- I mean, he is just, like, this man is mostly brain dead.
I need to just get him outta here.
So he's gonna try to grapple you.
- What if, what if I, what if,
in a Hail Mary attempt,
I convince him to throw me out the window again?
- I will let you try to do that.
- Okay. - This'll be your last try.
- Okay.
- What do you say?
- You better throw me out of this,
you better throw me out of that window
'cause I'm gonna hit you with the force of execution
so hard with the perfect weapon
that the last thing you'll see is the end of a gun,
you China salesman.
- Okay, let's make this a China salesman.
I like that you're just-
'Cause I was born to raise hell, and you're gonna get some urban justice!
Today you die!
I like the idea of this being reverse psychology so there's no more disadvantage.
Uh-huh.
So just roll regular persuasion.
Whoa!
Holy shit!
[Laughter]
You gotta crit, folks. Okay.
This guy says, "Man, you're hard to kill,"
and throws you out the window.
You crash- - No, no, no, the other way.
- Oh, the other way?
Okay, yeah. - Onto the street.
- He throws you out the window onto the street.
There is no camera in there.
- I know, I knew it.
- You're correct about that.
I'm just gonna move his icon over to this side.
But you're back outside.
What do you wanna do? - Do I have a move now?
Uh, you can still move, you can still--
Okay, guess what I'm gonna do.
What?
Oh, I guess--
You-- you have-- I will say--
I can move, but I can't do another Aikido roll, huh?
Uhhh, you can either-- so here's-- you can either--
I'll just-- I'll just walk 30 feet.
Here's the thing, you have-- you have a clear line of sight to cam.
Yeah. I'm gonna walk 30 feet, though, 'cause I want to-- I want to confuse him, so I'm gonna go here.
Okay, cool.
To this tile that's 30 feet away.
- Okay, cool.
Move on over there.
- Okay.
- And that's not by the window pane,
so you'd be out of the like, sight of that.
- Yeah.
- Okay, cool.
All right, take off your headphones.
- Okay.
- You heard him babbling, vaguely.
- I heard him babbling?
- Yeah, I mean you saw the security guard
throw him out the window.
- Okay.
And then you saw him walk off to his right.
If he were facing you.
Okay.
Well, I'm just going to keep going out the exit.
Um, yeah, I can't control myself, but I'm just going to try to leave the bank as if
I'm Billy Eilish leaving the bank.
Okay.
Do you want to go straight towards out of the exit then?
Okay, so it's 30 feet here.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Um...
And I can't see him from where I am right now?
No.
Let me then do a secret roll to you
of my cloaking device and see if I can get that off.
Got it.
But I'm not too pressed about it.
How do I do that?
How do I roll a secret...
Whisper? I think it's...
Oh, God, what is Whisper Roll?
I remember or as in guess it doesn't matter I have googled it before oh yeah
it's just slash W slash W followed by the player name you want to whisper why you
want to whisper to us the player name whatever man I'm just gonna - whisper
just space GM I'm gonna roll a plus zero athletics roll to you okay I can do that
That's fine.
That's a 17.
Okay.
Yeah, that succeeds.
So, he basically sees you still here then, really.
Okay.
Or did he saw you walk off and then, so you're gone and then now you're there, but you're invisible.
Okay, cool.
And I can't move anymore?
No, that was, no, I actually decided that the items are like their own separate action.
I just did that with Pat, so.
so.
All right. I'll go outside then.
OK, cool. Where do you want to go?
Just just tell me where you're.
Actually, no, I I'm not sure because I
don't want the door to look like it's
opening on its own now that I think
about it.
Yeah. He would get a chance to
perceive that.
Yeah.
I will just kind of stand right
next to the door, my invisible body
right next to the door.
I guess.
Got you. All right.
Or even, you know what, here I'm gonna play 4D chess,
watch this, I'm going to open the door and close it
invisibly without going out.
- I do love that, okay cool.
- All right, that's what I'm gonna do.
- Yeah, all right, take off your headphones.
- Okay.
- Okay, Pat, you see the door open and close,
but you don't see anybody do anything.
- He's invisible.
I know that he's invisible,
so I'm gonna do another Aikido roll.
- An invisible Billy Eilish?
- Yes, I can sense an invisible Billy Eilish
with my Aikido training.
Okay.
- You do another Aikido roll.
- I want to do an Aikido roll into this room.
It will be 15 feet.
- Athletics or acrobatics check.
Okay.
- Oh, 12.
- It's good enough.
It's just much messier,
but you still crash through another bank teller's room.
You just crash through it.
And they're like, "Oh, say, what's going on here?"
- Look, I'm gonna level with you.
I'm drunk.
- You hear a security guard.
(laughing)
You hear a security guard walk out of that room
and start sprinting towards you in the other room.
You heard a crash.
(laughing)
It's like, not again.
- This is the worst character I've ever played.
(laughing)
I just can't keep, I can't keep myself from fucking up.
- You're having too much fun.
It's just, it's like no, zero good roles.
(laughing)
It's the worst.
Zero good decisions.
There's not been a single smart thing done.
(laughing)
You just began it by sexually harassing a woman.
I'm really embodying Steven Seagal.
Yeah, you're doing a great job.
I'm doing such a, I think the next campaign,
I think I should just be Steven Seagal.
You should, I think you'd be great.
I think this is the intro of the perfect character.
I love that.
I like the idea of us testing that out here.
Beta testing.
Your perfect character.
The most horrible character in all of D&D.
Fucking rocks.
Alright.
Alright, so the security guard comes in and shoots me.
(laughing)
- We might have to do a mercy kill, but not yet.
He doesn't have enough movement yet.
So he's just in the room.
So take off your headphones.
- This has a glass wall as well?
- Yes, it does, yeah, yeah.
- I can't hide under the desk?
- No, I mean, it's open.
Oh, well, yeah, you can hide under the desk if you want to.
- I'm gonna try.
- All right, so before he gets there,
then roll a stealth roll, yeah.
- 16.
- Nice, you are able to hide in a,
I mean, I'll roll actually, I guess, inside for him,
but he's not gonna, he's probably not gonna pick up on it.
Yeah, no, he just barely is not able to though,
that was pretty close.
He was going for 14. - Oh, hell yeah.
- So he walks over there and does not see you in there,
but he does see the like broken glass
of the window in there.
- I hold the crossbow, I'm under the desk with my crossbow up
at this bank teller's nutsack.
- Oh, please, don't!
- I say to him, I say,
I'm a dangerous man.
And I've been driven to kill.
If you tell that security guard that I'm in here,
you're gonna get a gut shot straight to the gut.
Security guard walks in and goes,
I know you're in here, where are you?
Oh, he's not here, he's not here at all.
He's like, you don't have to be afraid,
just tell me where he is.
He just left actually, he went outside.
And we're gonna roll a deception for that guy
against the security guard's knowledge of what's going on.
That guy got a 20 on deception, nat 20.
So unless the security guards,
insight check, is that good?
Nope.
He then goes, all right, just stay put.
And he walks outside.
He walks outside to go there.
He's using the rest of his dash action.
So he is now gonna look for you outside.
You are now under this guy's desk,
safe with the crossbow pointed to his belly.
And we'll end your turn there. Take off your headphones.
Okay.
Very nicely done. Okay.
That's right.
Yo.
Yo. I don't know how we're gonna get to all the other maps.
Probably have to time for do one more map.
This has been a good one.
Well, is this over?
No, it's just, it's not somehow.
He somehow avoided dying just now.
I won't get into the details, but anyway.
You just heard another crash through another window.
Okay, that's all you heard.
But you're still in the ATM area, invisible.
Okay, I'm not trying to metagame,
but based on hearing another crash,
I'm gonna assume that he went back inside.
It's not metagaming, that's like what you heard
and what you've seen him do already.
Right, but the reason I say that
is 'cause I can see his tile inside.
Oh yeah, that's fair.
So I think I will invisibly go back into the bank
and scout around and try and see if I can see him.
I really, at this point, I have one,
my only thing I'm ever gonna do on a turn from now on
is just try to get close enough to shoot him in the head.
- Okay. (laughs)
- I have no more items left.
I have two HP.
I am a teenage pop star on a mission.
- Okay.
On your next turn, we're gonna roll again
to see if you stay invisible.
- Okay. - Okay, cool.
So you're just in the bank generally.
I'm gonna like say that you are,
I mean I know there's another way to do this,
but I hate it, so, but like I know where you are generally.
We'll get there. - Sure.
- We'll get there, okay cool.
All right, take him off.
- Okay, or should I roll perception
to see if I can see where he is?
Does that matter?
- You can roll, you can roll perception.
Let's roll perception to see if you got
sense of like of where he is right now. Yeah. Um yeah I mean that would only be
to confirm what you're already metagaming I would say. Okay all right.
That's like the most information you'd get out of it. Yeah. Okay. Okay cool. All
right. Take off your headphones. Maybe text Pat. Pat. Pat. Pat. Pat. Oh he's so
close he's almost his eyes are almost up
folks at home Pat I think saw a stain on his shirt and so he's just trying to rub
it out he's definitely not texting someone or looking up his information
- Looking. - Musical movies.
- Yep, nope.
If you want me to be completely honest.
- Yeah, for the viewers at home, yeah.
- I was watching videos of what different basses sound like
when you play slap bass.
- Well. - I thought that
I had more time.
- No, that's fair, his term was short.
You don't notice anything has happened, really.
- Shit, that's not good.
but the Billie Eilish is still at the door.
Okay, so I'm still under the desk
and the guy is still in the room.
- Yeah, you're cross-boded.
- So I look at him and I say,
my man, you need to take off all your clothes
and then you need to give me your clothes
and then you need to dress up in my clothes.
And then, so, and then you wear,
and can I have, and then you wear my clothes.
- Okay.
- He nods like, like--
- We're gonna change clothes.
- Yeah, he nods, and you guys do this.
You guys do change clothes.
- Okay.
- All right, what do you wanna do?
- So now I look like a bank teller, huh?
I mean, you look like Steven Seagal as a bank teller.
- Yeah, the shirt's a size...
It's like a size 14, 30 dress shirt.
Does not fit me.
- No.
- I'm wearing size, they're size like 28, 36 pants.
- You look like you're dressed up as a slutty school girl.
- Yeah, pretty much.
- Yeah.
- All right.
I'm just, I'm gonna walk on out of here
Like a normal bank teller.
And no one's gonna even know
that I'm gonna go into this bathroom, which is...
Wait, hold on.
How do you do the, oh yeah, there we go.
I'm gonna take my 30 feet of movement
to go into this bathroom.
Okay.
So I'm gonna do that.
So I'm gonna take, yeah,
I'm gonna use all my movement points
to just go into the bathroom.
- All right, cool.
Well, not you, the bank teller really.
Okay. - Yeah.
- Hold on.
Don't take off your headphones.
- Me? - Yeah, don't take 'em off.
- Okay. - Okay.
- All right. - Cam, I'm having Pat
keep his headphones on for a second.
Roll perception, Cam.
- Okay.
A crit one.
Take off your headphones, Cam.
I don't know how you did it,
but he thinks that's just a regular bank teller.
(laughing)
Walking into the bathroom.
So that does happen.
But he does see that coming out of there.
- Who does?
- He sees a bank teller coming out of the,
that room. Okay. Which is you. And now you're in the bathroom. Okay. Okay. What do you want to do in there?
Is there tile ceiling in there? Sure, yeah. Okay. I'm open to it. I'm gonna go
Breakfast Club. Okay. Yeah? Yeah. Alright. John Bender and Breakfast Club. I'm gonna
do that. Yeah. Roll athletics to jump up there. Or acrobatics. Whichever one.
13 okay yeah you're able to climb in there into the vent okay okay
tick off your headphones okay okay yeah you don't notice anything in particular
to
- Ooh, then what do I do?
I'm still looking for him.
- Yeah, roll a d20 first.
- Oh, true.
- We'll see.
- 10.
- Okay, yeah, you survive.
- Woo!
So I'm still just looking for him.
I mean, since I didn't try to do a perception last time,
I guess I don't know where he is.
- Yeah, I mean, you can try to see
like which of the offices you thought he came into
or whatever. They're all glass windows, so you can just peek in.
Yeah. I'm still just looking for him.
You also see this security guard run outside too.
As well.
Okay, I don't...
That seemed to start happening before you came in though.
Yeah, I also feel like if the security guard is going outside,
maybe Steven Seagal is just going inside and outside over and over.
I'm not gonna do that.
So I'm just gonna go look into all the offices and see if I can figure out where he is.
Okay.
Check the first office.
Check the first office, you don't see him in there.
Second office, you don't see him in there.
Third office.
Pat, get that shit off the fucking screen.
Alright, roll...
insight. Okay. 19. You see a very scared bank teller dressed as Steven Seagal in the third
office. Okay, can I walk up to the bank teller? Yeah, you can walk into the office. Okay,
and do I still have an action for my gun? Okay, can I tell Pat to put his headphones
on and narrate what I'm gonna do? Absolutely, you can. Can I narrate it? Of course you can.
Pet. Yeah. You see none other than one of the most beautiful celebrities in the world,
Billie Eilish, walk up to you and she smiles at you.
- Mm-hmm.
- You know it's a scared bank teller
dressed as Steven Seagal.
- Fucker!
- Okay.
Then what do I, then nothing happens.
- Unless you--
- Then I still believe it's Steven Seagal.
- Despite knowing that,
unless despite knowing that,
you do what I think you're gonna do.
- I thought the other way around.
- No, no, no. - Yeah.
- Well, I still do what I do then.
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna shoot this person in the head.
- Okay. - With my gun.
(laughing)
- Yeah, so--
- Which that's gonna alarm security, right?
'Cause there's a gun. - Oh yeah.
Oh yeah.
- Oh, it's Billy Eilish.
- You hear a gun go off.
Security guard's like, "Fuckin' A."
And just starts running back inside.
- Okay.
- But he's not there yet.
Your turn's done.
Take your headphones off.
Wait, I'm also still invisible.
Yes, you are still invisible.
Okay, so nothing of what I said made any sense.
Yeah, I thought you knew what was happening
and you wanted to tell him
that you were about to kill him.
No, I completely, I thought the opposite of what you said.
You said a bank teller dressed as Steven Seagal
and my brain heard Steven Seagal dressed as a bank teller.
No, no, it was the other thing.
All right, take him off.
That's that, I guess.
Okay, Pat.
So, yeah, you hear a gun go off
but just you're like, you hear a gun go off,
you hear people screaming, you're in the vents.
- He must've been killing Salazar
because of the Onion movie.
- Okay.
All right, so what do you wanna do?
You're in the vents right now.
- I'm just gonna crawl until,
yeah, I guess I'll just use all my movement to crawl.
- Yeah, roll, where are you trying to crawl to,
I should say?
Um.
The break room, no, no, no, no, no.
I think I'm going to crawl.
I guess to where the gunshot is to see what it was.
Roll a perception just to like make sure you're pinpointing that correctly.
Eight.
That's fine.
It doesn't actually really make sense.
What I just said, but, uh, yeah.
All right.
We'll do another roll.
Yeah.
Maybe insight.
No, I just mean that you're kind of fine.
Like you would kind of know where the gunshot is.
- Yeah, it was next to the bathroom.
- Yeah, that's what I mean.
Like you wouldn't have to roll perception for that.
And you probably would have deduced that it was like,
you know, where you were.
Like, I just don't think that's, that makes sense to do.
- Yeah.
- So what you can do though, is roll a like,
I will have you though roll an intelligence check
just to see if you can like remember,
like by crawling through the vents,
it's like, how am I getting back to that room?
- Eight.
- Okay.
kind of just end up going like towards closer to the second room.
But yeah, you could start to pop out and you can see below you like the
main area of the bank, you see a guard running towards that room.
So you're not back towards that third room.
You're kind of hovering over right in front of the second room.
And for people listening, there are like three rooms that are like facing outside.
Each of them are like glass windows.
And that's where all these like different tellers have been and where
Steven Seagal has been jumping in the windows and cam went into the third one,
much where Steven Seagal last was.
Sorry, I just want, okay, yeah.
So what are you gonna do?
You can pop out of there, like he won't notice.
- You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna, I'm gonna, can I roll,
I'm gonna roll sleight of hand,
I'm gonna drop my caltrops, the remaining caltrops.
- That's pretty nice, okay.
Okay, yeah, do it.
- 16. - Nice, yeah.
I'm gonna roll insight for the security guard running by.
- Oh, wait, wait, wait.
(laughing)
- If that's what you're doing.
- No, I wasn't trying to kill the security guard.
I was trying to just place them down
so that if Cameron comes out.
- Oh, okay, you're just placing them outside the door, okay.
- Yeah, 'cause I think that he's in the second room.
- Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay, cool.
So you place it outside the front of that door.
He's the security guard, he's not gonna run over those.
He doesn't notice them though.
But yeah, he's gonna keep running.
- Okay, then that's-- - That's your turn?
- Yeah, then I end my turn.
- Okay, cool, all right.
Yep, you're good.
Outside of the outside the blood on your Billy Eilish ass outfit.
Invisible.
Invisible outfit.
Security guard comes out here.
Another one is going to come back this way is moving towards you this way.
But you're just standing there.
Invisible though still.
Invisible.
And they just see a bank teller dead.
uh... we couldn't handle the pressure
he just say that
uh...
uh... yeah there's a lot of cases
uh... god i'll have a good line though if i do if i get to do this if i get to
shoot the whites by got such a good line man but okay
uh...
that fucked it up
okay we did it
as the window in this room broken
yes it is
and it's not as cleanly broken is the other one
team that's not nice
patrick is watching video right now we can be here in a few years and i would
consider it
uh... it's the second bucket idiot table my pick
come on
uh... ok i'm gonna try to go out the window
very carefully
uh... you're able to do that that's fine they come again to make you roll for
that do i see him outside
you do not
then I guess I will just loop back around and go back into the bank.
Okay, you're going to use your dash action and everything, so let me just measure that.
Cool. You'll make it from that way into the ATM area.
Okay, yeah.
Okay, cool.
Yeah. Cool. T.A.D.'s a good game. Okay, yeah, take off your...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You see the guards just run by that second room and just open the door and go, "Oh,
Jesus Christ!" and nothing else.
Okay.
Um...
What do I do now?
I don't know.
I don't even know.
I think I'm just gonna stay in here.
I'm gonna do nothing.
I'm gonna yield my turn.
Cool.
Do it.
Alright.
- That's that.
You're both in a similar place if you couldn't tell.
You're both waiting for the other one to strike.
- Yeah, well I have no clue where he is so.
- You can do an investigation too.
- Okay, that's what I kind of have all been wanting to do
is to simply find out where he is.
- Okay, do an investigation check, yeah.
Yeah, for inside the bank.
- In the jail. - 17.
- Very nice.
(laughing)
- You notice, you're investigating around,
you're like, where could this guy be?
And you notice a slight depression
on one of the ceiling tiles.
(laughing)
- Okay, and how far away am I from the ceiling tile?
- You look down from the ceiling
and you see like three small caltrops on the ground
from where that ceiling tile is.
- Okay.
- The ceiling tile is like right outside the second room
where the depression is.
He got a 17 investigation for those listings.
- Wait, is the depression meaning like a sagging ceiling?
- Yeah, like a sagging ceiling tile, yeah.
- And underneath it there's caltrops?
- Yeah.
- Okay, I'm gonna walk over to as close
to the ceiling tile as I can
without stepping on the caltrops.
Yeah, you're fine.
And I'm still invisible, right?
You are.
And the security guards are all in the other room?
They are.
Okay, I shoot the stacky part of the ceiling tile.
Okay, roll an attack roll.
With my gun.
Okay, what's a gun attack roll?
It's gonna be 1d20.
Yeah, it's just the same as shortbow.
Okay.
Goddamn.
24.
You're gonna kill him.
You're gonna obliterate him.
Do you want him to put on his headphones?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, okay.
- Yeah, okay.
- All right.
So, Cam walks in to the bank.
He does a little investigation,
and he notices a sagging ceiling tile.
(laughing)
- Oh man, I almost fucking had him.
I was gonna wait, you know what it was?
I was gonna wait until he was under me.
- Yeah.
- And I was gonna wait,
and then the weight of my body,
I wanted to kill him by the ceiling tile.
- There were two very funny endings possible here,
it's true.
- Here's what I do,
I walk over to right next to the caltrops that you left,
and I just take my gun out,
and I just shoot the sagging part of the ceiling tile,
and it breaks, and you fall down,
and you land on the caltrops,
and then I go, I decloak like a predator,
and I'm Billy Eilish,
And then I point the gun right in your face,
and I start singing a song.
You know what I sing?
- I'm the bad guy.
- I'm the black spy.
Duh.
- Oh man.
- And then my gun does the beat of the song,
like a YouTube poop.
- Yeah.
That was great.
That was so much longer, obviously,
than I thought it would be.
- I mean, that was great.
That was by far the most--
- The most involved one we've done.
So I think I can't I can't I guess this is gonna have so bad
Multiple rounds I think in that case like what I mean like this is just part one
Like oh like we're gonna have finals will continue the finals will continue because there's yeah
What do we have three rounds that we have to do of this? I was good. I was gonna do best three of five
Damn, I have four. I should do best two or three. I think the next one should decide
Yeah, I'm down for that too. Yeah, okay cool. All right
Yeah, that was that was great cuz then Caleb gets left out, and he's not yeah, but I don't really
He likes being left out he does he's obsessed hey Caleb, that's right. Hey Caleb eat this
Nice
All right, so that's one victory for Cameron black spy
And one long to tell you I did I did not deserve it for Steven Seagal whites by yeah
He really messed that up at one point. You just killed a bank teller I
Am but it worked in my favor because it got all that security
It's true. It was a weird way that it all kind of worked out that way. I'm gonna be I'm gonna be honest
Mm-hmm. I think I was made to play this game
- I think you brought it, man.
- Yeah, you missed, yeah, Cam,
'cause you didn't get to hear
all of his great Steven Seagal moments.
It was really fun.
- I could tell he was doing the voice
by seeing his body language.
(laughing)
- He did some really great moments
that weirdly worked out in his favor
because of just the improvisational,
the extra improvisational nature of this thing.
- There were so many moments where I fucked up
because I was so in character.
- It was great.
- That it was just me bumbling and being just like,
how Steven Seagal would act in an actual action scenario.
- Were you just going inside and outside the windows?
- Yes, pretty much. - Yes, that's what I thought.
- Crashing in them and going outside of them
and holding somebody hostage.
- Yeah, I would be like looking,
my turn would start and I'd be like
looking for you inside the bank
and then Patches is just like,
"You just heard another window crash."
(laughing)
- Oh my God, this comes off so easy.
- Yeah, it sure does.
All right. - This is acrylic paint.
Take it easy everybody.
I didn't have any eye black at the office.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Bye bye.
A sandwich I ate the other day gave me indigestion so bad that my whole chest felt like it was
jumping out of my chest.
I feel like I can't even eat turkey ham anymore without the nitrates going into my system and
just totally bubbling me.
I feel like I got bubbles in my stomach and chest almost every day I wake up.
Walking to the train station I feel this gulp gulp gulp gulp gulp gulp.
I shouldn't be eating that turkey or that ham man or the turkey ham.
This stuff is destroying our men and our women.
Mostly men usually eat more cold cuts than women.
On average, on average, okay.
I've developed an adult gluten allergy.
I never thought it would happen to me.
But here I am, close to 27 years old, and the only bread that I can eat is sourdough.
Sourdough's good for breakfast, and it's good for sandwiches.
I can't eat Hawaiian rolls anymore.
Those are my favorite savory breads.
Just the other day, man, I was cleaning out my humidifier.
It had a heavy mineral scaling.
Mineral scales were collecting onto the humidifier's heating element.
I soaked it in a solution of vinegar and water for about 15 to 20 minutes,
I started to scrub it with a soft brush so as not to damage the element.
And I was rinsing the brush under the sink so it wouldn't just have vinegar residue and
minerals in it.
I flicked back the bristle, the vinegar shot straight into my eye.
And you know, when you think about how men are treated in society nowadays, every single,
The way that women make us feel is like we always have to act like Howie Mandel.
We always gotta be thinking about putting a rubber glove on our heads and doing Bobby's
World impressions and talking like Gizmo.
But I don't know if I can be Howie Mandel every day.
Man, Hollywood has failed us.
Chicken Run 2, Donna the Nugget will not be showing in theaters.
Straight to streaming.
Netflix.
Lose out on billions of dollars at box office.
Can't watch Netflix.
Girlfriend's grandma watches it every day.
Locks us out of the account.
(Bowser roaring)