Okay, cool
Yeah, so
We another hello everybody. We're doing another spy versus spy except this time
It's not spy versus spy. It's spy versus Cameron
Is that what it is? Yeah, I don't even really know what the original thing is for there to be a so
Okay, you're not version of it. You're not near the movies
Which is the other so Patrick is what and he wanted us to do spy verse Cameron?
And it would be about how Cameron's near the movies, and he didn't really
Elaborate on that. Do you just say you just do whatever we say?
Yeah
really
Like almost always yeah
Yeah, yeah, that's on us. I should have known that yeah jumped in I've been like yeah, I have no original thoughts. Yeah, that's okay
- Near the movies. - It's a nightmare.
- Yeah.
- Well, at least you, now I'm a little bit mad
that you didn't do everything he said.
- Yeah.
- You just did the spy versus camera thing,
but you didn't put him near the movies.
- Well, there's--
- I don't wanna be near the movie.
I'm not near the movies really that so often, necessarily.
- I just thought that there has never been a third spy.
I guess it could've been a gray spy.
- I bet there's a girl spy, Venus de Milo style.
- You could be a girl spy. - I bet there is a girl spy.
- I had the full Spy vs Spy collection when I was a kid.
- I could do a quick acid swap.
- Some of those ones, the guest artist--
- No, let's go, it's pretty gory with it.
- That's horrific.
- You wanna restart this again?
- No, no, no, no, no.
- What's happening? - We can't restart this again.
- No, I just Googled Spy vs Spy female,
and I'm seeing Gray Spy, aka Lady in Gray,
is a third spy appearing in some Spy vs Spy comic strips.
- That's so smart.
- And she's called Lady in Gray.
- Oh my God, she's gorgeous.
- She looks like a different species.
- She does not look like--
- There's a huge degree of sexual dimorphism.
- Yeah.
- She's kind of like a female black widow spider.
- And the other ones are plague doctors.
This is very different.
- They're kind of bird-like.
- Hubio, are you near,
you're in roll 20, I'm not seeing--
- Oh, you're not in the map.
- You're in the map, yeah,
'cause you're not moving with the screen.
There we go.
Yeah, cool.
So you can see here where our first,
so the way that this worked last time, Cameron,
is that your job is to kill your fellow spy
using your various gadgets and trickery and smarts.
You're gonna be given random gadgets
at the beginning of each little vignette.
and then you'll roll to see who goes first,
and then you'll begin sort of like trying to figure out
how to do this in a way that's discreet,
'cause they're in these real situations,
there are people who might take offense to you
trying to do something whack,
but if you do it quick enough, it won't matter.
- And a word to the wise here, Cameron,
the better an idea you have,
if this is anything like the first game,
the more likely it is that you will lose.
- Okay. - So have just kind of
the most basic, stupid ideas, don't over-complicate it,
because you will lose if you try to do something
even remotely interesting.
- Am I me? - Okay.
- I guess so, yeah, unless you wanna be Lady in Gray.
It's up to you.
Now you are you.
You're you. - But I'm me.
- You're you.
- Okay.
- I made you you.
So--
- Is that a giant baby bottle next to me?
- No, that's a corpse.
- It's just a dead body.
- It looks like a baby bottle to me.
- Bust looks like the nipple of a baby bottle.
- Yeah, he does look like a nipple.
- His sheet looks like milk with rippling.
- Oh, rippling milk.
- Rippling milk.
- Yeah, it does look like bountiful.
- Okay, so. - Ocean of milk.
(laughing)
- Okay, it could be a bountiful baby bottle.
This is a fast and loose, we want this to have fun.
- Okay, so this one's kind of unlike our normal D&D stuff,
this one's kind of off the wall.
Yeah, we can kind of do whatever we want here.
That's the bottle I'm getting so far.
Okay, so that's a baby bottle.
Got it. Okay, first things first.
Both of you guys, let's start with you, Cameron.
Roll a D20 three times.
And then I will DM you on Discord.
Discord.
With what items you'll get.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Okay, I got a two.
Are these the same items as last time?
No.
I got a 15.
It's some of the same items but not all of them though.
I got a 19.
Okay.
Now let me check my discord.
It could be coming down the pipeline for me.
And these are items that I will have.
Yes, you will have them for this adventure.
Now I will do it.
Yes, you do it as well.
I will be copying and pasting from my list.
I got 3 of 15 and an 8.
Okay, so we got 2, 15, 19, 3, 15, 8.
Please tell me what the expense of canary figurine.
What?
Yeah.
Well we won't know yet.
But when we get our 15 we'll know what it is.
Till the other has.
We won't know till after.
We don't know our own items?
He means that...
We don't know what number is attached to it.
I can give you guys well, maybe you do have just ate the order it's in
true
But now you're gonna scramble it
No, I said something he's gonna scramble it isn't he see I might be a problem
Cameras too smart for this game. I'm literally trying to strategize right now
Last that you were just a you're a chess player you're playing with my chest
Yeah, I'm more of a cookie clicker player
Every game I play is cookie clicker
Sorry, I'm just cookie click copying from one note means I have to do I keep bringing have to do command
Control shift I mean because it just pasted as a picture nobody
Man, nobody cares about this
That's okay me and camera can talk about our days or something. Yes. I went on a walk a long walk today
Just through Manhattan. I was feeling the magic of New York. Oh wow
- You went all the way over there for a walk.
- Yeah, well I had to go do something there
and then I just wandered around for like an hour.
I went to the water, I went to a bunch of different areas.
I was seeing types of things.
It was kinda nice.
- He texted the group chat, you were like,
"I'm gonna go for a walk today."
- I didn't say that.
I would never say that.
- Yeah, he doesn't like us knowing where he is.
- I would say that once after I got home.
- The prank war is still on.
- Yeah, well you never know.
Anybody could get hold of anybody's iCloud and see anybody.
Okay, I've just gotten one item.
- No, you got three items.
- I've just gotten three items, everybody.
- And Caleb, here comes your three items.
- I'm excited as fuck.
- Okay, you got three, oh, that's cute.
That's fun.
I like that.
- Okay, don't tip Cameron off that I got a cute item.
- No, I just said it.
- I mean, he said this is gonna be a rubber ducky
or a teddy bear.
- Well, I also have to think about
what kind of twisted thing Patches might find cute.
And it would probably be like an alien dragon.
- Yeah.
True.
- Yeah, like a dark rune.
- Or a pho-- yeah.
- Yeah.
He is esoteric.
Okay.
Well, I'd really like these items.
- I heard yours got clogged up somewhere down the pipeline.
- It seems like it.
- They're coming.
It's just, it's just, you don't, you don't understand.
- Seems like I'm still rolling my item cube.
- You don't understand why this takes so long.
- You have to manually type out every item?
- No, it's just I'm stupid.
- What are you, coming up with them right now?
You stupid fucker.
- That would be cool.
- Send them to me and I'll send them over to Caleb.
- That is not gonna work, that would be complicated.
- I'll handle part of it, that'll make it a lot faster.
- It's a good trickity trap though.
- No. - Send me the full notes then.
And I'll copy and paste it for you.
No.
Oh, but then you'd have to copy and paste the notes, huh?
Yeah, which he seems to have a real problem with, so...
Okay, you'll know in my life.
That is tough.
It's not easy.
Are you having trouble reaching the C key from the control key?
Yeah, he's very little.
He's having Donald Trump, Donald Trump.
I deal with the last orange-ass hands.
Oh, I got one!
Oh, I got all three!
You got all three.
Okay.
Alright, it's been pasted.
Wow.
Okay, now both of you's rolls initiative.
Okay, here I go.
This is going to be a serious roll.
Serious roll.
It's going to be a very serious roll.
Geez.
My computer is running so slow.
20!
Oh wait, where's my initiative?
Do I have a character sheet?
You have a character sheet.
Sorry, I was about to just roll it.
Wait, what kind of stats does Cameron the character have?
Wait, where's my guy?
It should be shared with you.
Go to the notes.
Oh, is it this one at the top?
I didn't see it because it wasn't in a drop down.
Why is this running so slow?
Geez Louise.
- It's roll 20.
- Okay, I got a five for my initiative.
- And I win again.
- Okay.
So, Caleb, or should I say black spy,
you are at this bar.
It's called--
- Cameron just take his headphones off.
- Oh, I just take them off?
- Oh yeah, take them off.
- We'll give you a thumbs up when you're ready.
- It's a thumbs up?
- Yeah, thumbs up, thumbs up.
- All right, see ya.
- So not a thumbs down.
Okay.
It's a big, it's a fancy bar, it's called the Podcast About List bar.
And you're on a date.
Nicely done.
Yeah, you're on a date with a female police officer right now.
Okay.
And, but of course you know what your real mission here is, which is to end Cameron.
Can you tell me something?
What's up man?
So with the dynamic of black spy versus white spy, it makes some sense because they hate
each other because I guess they have different allegiances I would assume, different countries,
different...
Yeah, stop there.
One's MI6.
Why does black spy want to kill Cameron?
You want to know your motivation, your character motivation here.
Just give me something here.
I got you.
Okay.
So I think think of it like this.
Cameron is probably the one who's maybe he's the one
who supplies white spy with the with the gadgets.
Oh, no. Right.
Like, I think like that. Right.
I think that's probably what it is.
Yeah. He's some kind of dirty arms dealer. Mm hmm.
Mm hmm. All right.
They've got your own.
There's a buddy dealer. Yeah, me too.
So, yeah, you're on this day with this female police officer.
And she says, so what do you do for a living?
I hope it's not being a criminal or a spy.
As you can see by my all black clothes, I am a goth.
Oh, that's fun.
Well, no, it's not very fun.
It's actually kind of the opposite.
Oh, right.
I'm sorry.
That's so stupid of me.
What do you do?
Are you some kind of blue spy or something?
What is this outfit?
- No, I'm a female police officer.
- Oh, wow.
- So I'll try to find out and find bad guys and arrest them.
- So it's kind of just the same as a normal police officer.
Why are you even saying female?
- I think it's important.
- Okay, well, if you'll excuse me,
I think I might go check out
that giant baby bottle over there.
- Okay, yeah, that doesn't require deception.
That is probably what you're interested in.
It's kind of an interesting thing, right?
Yeah, it's kind of an interesting thing. I think she just buys it.
Okay, cool.
So, yeah. What are you going to do then?
What's your plan?
Hmm.
I am going to...
Is there any way that I could
use my movement
to get a little bit closer
and then throw my sonic eavesdropper,
the small handheld device
that allows the user to listen in on conversations from a distance?
Could I throw it in range of where Cameron is?
I mean, you can already use that.
Like, this is the proper distance for that kind of item.
Like where you're sitting.
Maybe I'm going to walk up to...
Is there somewhere that I could...
I'll walk up to the bar and maybe like over...
maybe like the far left, like bottom left corner
corner and kind of crouch, hide behind the bar a little bit so he can't see me and maybe
poke the eavesdropper around the corner aimed in his direction.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, go for it.
So just move your character there, poke it there and do a slight a hand check just so
in case a bartender notices or patron does.
All right, let's see.
Nice.
Very smooth.
Yeah, you just sort of slide it under there.
Just like your normal walking by a thing and you put your hand on the thing.
It's great.
Looks very good.
So for the next turn do I just get to keep my headphones on?
You picked up on that.
There you go.
Okay.
Here, we'll tell him and I'll turn my volume down.
Okay, cool.
Do it.
Alright, cool.
Alright.
Alright, and that's the end of my turn.
Alright, cool.
Alright.
Okay.
So I'll let him know what happened.
So for reasons I can't explain, just I can't tell you about.
- Well, you don't even have to tell me
'cause unlucky for you guys,
I can read lips at 10 frames per second
and I know everything that was just said.
- Okay.
- No, but what's happened?
- Oh, okay, so yeah,
Caleb is gonna be able to keep his headphones on
for this session, for this round.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
- Well, I'm sure you're gonna have a fun time
listening to me ask what is going on,
how does this game work,
why did it start with me not being able to listen to anything.
- Don't worry, I can help.
- So maybe you can help me out here
'cause I don't even really know at all what's going on.
- Okay.
So here's how it is.
You have to kill Caleb, who is the black spy,
in hilarious ways using gadgets.
You can also try to stab them and stuff, but
the the trick is to try to do it in a way that it doesn't
get everyone all alarmed about what you're doing.
So you don't get stopped or tackled by someone and have your whole thing ruined.
Yeah. So the idea is to each turn you have, you know, same as in D&D action,
bonus action, you know, reaction, whatever.
Most of the items just do actions.
They'll just take up an action.
Some of them, like we can discuss if it's like an action
and then like a bonus action to reuse it.
But I think it's just most of them just take an action.
And so it's just to set yourself up to position yourself to do the best
so you could talk to some of these people.
And like Pat last time
sent some people in certain directions to
confuse Caleb and Caleb.
It didn't work, but then you still died.
And thanks, Matthew.
Caleb did stuff to where he forgot what some of the shit you did.
It was very fucking cool.
If you haven't listened to it, go back and listen to the first one.
It was cool. It was cool.
You were kind of like, no, no, no, no, no.
You're going to get an idea of my techniques.
Yeah, you can't get his techniques down. Yeah, sure.
Mm hmm. So you can use one of your items
and I get to listen to every single thing you say. Yeah.
So right now, because because of an item that Caleb used this turn,
he's going to be able to listen to basically
whatever you say, whatever you say with me, where usually it's like
because it's a versus, yeah, like to try to keep it. Yeah, right.
But so. OK, so I just do a random stuff now.
Well, you're trying to kill Caleb.
So whatever it is you want to do, you just tell me what you want to do
and what you're thinking.
You're in this bar.
It's called a podcast about Liss Bar.
And I just have one turn?
Yeah, you just have one turn, just taking turns,
like in Dungeons and Dragons.
Oh, OK. So it's not like so.
No, no, no.
Then I will go back.
Yeah, yeah.
And go back. OK.
Well, all right.
Well, I guess and he'll only be able to listen to this turn.
Yeah. And like I will say that, like, because it's a meta, it's a meta item.
So like, I think it's fair to just do it this turn.
And then, yeah, you just have to be kind of
You have to try to be cagey and no DMing me
because then that defeats the purpose.
And also it would be bad radio.
Sure.
Yeah.
Okay, well.
How far can I move here?
30?
Yeah, 30 feet as always.
Four, five, six.
Can I speak obliquely about my item
to ask a question that I might not use it?
Yeah, absolutely.
- Third item, how far of a range is that?
- Look at your items again.
- Ooh.
- Yeah, that's like a, that's...
- If I moved 30 feet, would I be in range with that?
- Let me see.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, with him?
- Yeah.
- No, it's gonna need to be,
you're gonna need to be within 10 feet for that.
- Okay.
- If you think about it. - All right.
Well then, I guess all I'm gonna do
I'm just gonna take a big slurp from this bottle of milk.
God damn it, man!
And I guess I will also...
Can I... Do I have any type of Final Fantasy-esque guard action?
Can I just be... Can I just give myself a bonus if I'm gonna get attacked?
You know what I mean? Like I don't want to do anything, can I just...
Oh, I mean you can prepare an action.
Like you can do that. Yeah, you can defend.
Yeah, I'll defend.
I also, not only do I not want Caleb to know anything I have, but I also have no idea what to do.
So, I'm going to start out by defending.
You can do the guard action, so that's just going to give you
plus one on your AC for the remainder of the turn and then the first attack
against you is gonna have disadvantage. I'll do that and I'll also drink some of
that milk. Okay that milk yeah that's a free action to drink the milk. Yeah when
you start drinking the milk everyone in the bar stops talking and just watches
you drink the milk. It's a big bottle. It's huge! It's twice the size of me!
When you're done drinking the milk they all just resume talking to the people
around them. The milk was booby trapped with a silence creator. They just
regard, they always regard you when you drink the milk. Okay, milk is an attention getter.
Yeah, take your headphones off. Okay, well backed. Alright, is there a designated fire
exit in the podcast about Lisp Bar? Yes, there is. Also, second of all, I will say
that you can reapply, you can reapply it, but then you have to reapply it.
And then that's your action with that item.
I should have mentioned that.
But anyway, yeah, the fire exit is.
I mean, I guess it's behind the bar, which is dumb
trying to find out where it would be.
I guess it would have to be in the back of the bar, but I don't know where I put it.
Would it be these stairs or would it be this thing in the front?
No, that's the front door.
Let's say the fire exit is here.
I think that's fair, like in this corner here.
OK, this guy's running for the fire exit.
He's like, I think there's a fire.
OK, and I know he's going to return. Yes.
Yes. OK, I'm going to throw
my portable hole right behind the fire exit,
like right in front of the door.
And this is a pretty dim bar, no?
I'm open to that.
So, yeah, I'll ask him to roll a
I'm
It's kind of like you're trying to make it look like you're not throwing something.
It's just going to be a straight up roll against his perception.
Yeah, it'll be that.
I would also say before you roll it, hmm, that if you like walk closer to it,
you're going to like.
Like, I'll get I will give you like advantage if you move closer to it
on your side of hand roll, like then you're you're repositioned to over there.
But like I because I just don't want you to like
You just throw it from there, like...
Yeah, is there any kind of...
I'll move closer to it.
Alright, I'm gonna move over here.
And then, is there any kind of like...
throw rugs or anything?
Could I take a cushion off of a chair and cover it?
These chairs don't really have cushions.
But you could grab a menu from off the table.
Okay, I'll grab a menu and I'll put it...
I'm going to I'm going to roll my sleight of hand.
You said I get advantage. Yeah. Yeah.
OK, 24.
Now I'm going to place the menu over it.
Yeah, the menu over it is.
I mean, that's you're not going to get advantage on that sleight of hand.
Check if you want it because you're I mean, let's just do it again.
Yeah. Eleven. OK, fine.
So just the whole when you placed it, it was like aces.
Like he's going to have to crush that perception check to notice it
in this dim bar.
The menu, you're like trying to be like,
"Oh, oh, I don't know what to do with this."
And like, looked a little sus.
- Okay.
- As they say.
So I'll find a way to frame that to him.
- And I moved 15 feet, so I'm gonna move 15 feet back.
- Cool.
- And then I'm gonna end my turn.
- I like that.
All right, cool.
Nice.
All right.
- I'm gonna go pee real quick.
- Pee pee.
All right.
-First thing you're going to do, man,
is roll a gosh-darn perception check.
-Okay.
Perception.
You're--
For--
That's cool.
You are able to--
You notice that Caleb threw down a menu on the ground.
He, you don't know why, it was kind of like a weird,
it didn't seem like a normal thing to do.
(laughing)
- Sure. - He had a rough day.
All right, so that happened.
(laughing)
Fuck, man.
I think to myself, well that doesn't exactly seem normal.
- You just suck it in the milk.
- Yeah.
Cool.
It happened around here.
OK, hold on, wait, sorry.
My screen management is fucked.
Give me a second.
And I'll put a like a marker there.
Yeah, just put down.
Well, let me rearrange my screen
really quickly.
I got the solve here.
All right.
Cool.
That's maybe not the best color,
but like here it's a five
foot by five foot menu.
OK, right there.
All right. Yeah, sure.
So the Cheesecake Factory size
menu. Yeah. Yeah. Gotcha. And that's all. That's all I see. Yeah. Yeah. Nothing has
happened done to me. Okay. Um, well, I, okay. Here's a question I have about the portable
- It's just a hole, a one-way hole.
It's not a portal.
- Let me read it.
What does it say?
- It says a small black disc
that went placed on the surface.
So it's not necessarily that I could go through it,
but I couldn't make something else go through it.
Like, the thing that goes into it is like, kinda gone.
- It's like, gone, yes.
- But you can pull it out maybe,
but it's not like it goes somewhere.
- It's kind of like the banish spell in 5e,
except that like you're gone, gone.
Like, okay, like unless you bring it back, right?
So if I went in there, I would die.
Yeah.
But if you store items in there, right, it's like you can store items, pull stuff out.
Yeah, I can.
Exactly.
Yeah. Yeah.
Okay, I gotcha.
That's.
So you can put stuff in there and then trigger it is like an idea I've seen.
I've seen people do in my mind when I've thought about it.
Yeah. Well, so and putting so I'm going to put the milk into my hole.
It's fine.
Yeah.
I want to put all that stuff in my hole.
Come on, man.
That's what I want to do.
Is there a problem?
No, I guess not.
Do you want, do you care if anybody sees you put the milk into the hole?
Or can I try to roll to see if I can do it a little surreptitiously?
I guess I don't care that much, but it would be nice.
Maybe.
Yeah, sure.
Uh, and you mean also, sorry to clarify.
You don't mean the bottle.
You mean the milk inside the bottle?
Are you storing them?
Just loose.
Okay.
- If I put loose milk in, can I still pull it out?
- It'll be like if you try to drink water
from a stream though. - Can I shake the hole
so it splashes out?
Not like a concentrated stream, but like--
- That, yeah, that way.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I can do that.
Of course you could do that.
- I can splash, okay, then yeah,
I'm basically putting-- - Oh, that was a thumbs up.
- No, no, my friend, you stay far away
from my scheming plan. - Sorry.
- Okay, I wanna act, okay, in that case,
I will do this stealthily.
I'll be kinda holding the hole next to my mouth
while I'm drinking the milk and having all the milk
- I love that. - Go into the hole
instead of my mouth.
Or I can even put the hole in my mouth
to do it really stealthily.
- Oh, roll with, if you're doing that,
roll with a sleight of hand with advantage.
- Okay.
- If you're putting the hole in your mouth,
which means you have to just like.
(laughing)
You have to be so careful.
- Is that a success? - I don't like this laughing.
- That's gonna be, that's gonna be a, oh God.
- It seems like you're laughing at my expense, man.
- I don't want you to just, I don't think it's fun
if you just die that way.
Though it's kind of fun.
- So what I'd like you to do is do a--
- I got a 21.
- Okay, great, perfect.
All right, I wasn't sure, that's perfect, okay.
- I can't tell me I'm gonna die from a 21.
- No, no, no, no, I was gonna give you another,
I was gonna do, what I was gonna do
was gonna be like a deck saving throw on top of that.
- Well, that's fair enough.
- And then if you fail that,
then you can abort doing it is all.
So we'll keep that slight of hand if you nail it.
So do the deck saving throw though.
10.
That's fine, that's fine.
As long as it's not below a 10.
If it's below a 10, I'd have no choice.
I want this to work, obviously.
Yeah.
Okay, so I got the hole in my mouth with the milk.
So yeah, everybody just looks at you.
You see them, they kinda get a little mad
'cause they see the milk's gone.
Yeah.
And they go back into doing what they're doing.
Sure.
Yeah.
Okay, I'm gonna kind of, can I walk too?
That's a free action.
Oh, well, that's an item, I guess, too.
So, yeah.
All right, so--
You could place the hole too somewhere if you want to, if that's what you're thinking.
I want to keep it in my mouth and just like keep it in there.
Alright, yeah.
Keep it in there.
Okay.
Can I go here?
Where are you trying to go?
Sorry.
Oh, he moved.
Yeah, you can definitely go there.
Do I move now?
Yeah, yeah.
Is that how the system works?
Yeah, it's like D&D, so you can move at any point.
Okay, I just didn't know, I didn't know, because of the asynchronous element.
Yeah, no, understandable.
Yeah, you're good.
Okay, I'll go here and then I would like to I guess try to stealthily set a tripwire right in front of me
Okay, you have to use that in your next turn. Okay, that's fine. Yeah. All right, then I will be done. I love it
All right, great. All right, take off your headphones
Okay
All right, what's up
Now you tell me man you looks like you've tried to set up a some kind of like fire escape trap
Yes, so watch this or piece of fire exit stupid shit. That's fair
voice throwing megaphone
Okay, okay. I would like I believe it. He's trying to read my lips. It's not gonna work, buddy. I would like to
Put oh my god. He's like he's pacing
He's so nervous about what I'm about to do to him. I would like to use my voice throwing megaphone
Okay.
To make it sound like I'm coming over the loudspeaker.
And I would like it to say, "Fire!
Fire!
There's a fire in the building!
There's a fucking giant fire in the kitchen!
Everybody out!
Everybody out!"
Okay, I like that.
And then I would like to walk through the exit, the fire exit, and jump over the menu
that I know exactly where it is.
I placed it there.
Okay, cool.
and make my way out of the building.
Okay, I like that.
Um...
Okay, so here's what we're
going to have to do, because here's...
there's...
He's gonna know.
So, I want to help.
Let's workshop this. Like, cause you need to...
You need...
It needs to be like that you convince him.
So this is kind of like a performance
check. That his
insight check can either succeed or fail against.
So for you to be like,
it'll be someone throwing their voice,
but he has to believe it's not,
he has to believe it's you.
I'm trying to think, I guess what I'm trying to do is like,
I guess I could just hard, just do this hard.
- I just need you to sell it.
I need you to sell it.
- I think I can do that
if you roll a high enough performance check.
- I need you to make it seem like
this was a, one of your cute little twists.
- Yeah.
about to head to the second map.
- Roll a performance check. - He doesn't know.
He doesn't know.
He doesn't know what the fuck he's gotten into.
- You can roll a, you can do a whisper roll too.
I think, or you just roll to me.
- How do I do that?
- Let me make sure I remember how to do that.
Hold on.
Whisper roll 20.
So I think you could do that,
'cause I think that's fair to have you do that for this.
Uh...
Yeah, okay.
Slash... uh... W.
Okay.
Um...
Slash W, and then space, GM.
Uh-huh.
Oh, wait, here. I'm an idiot. I'm an idiot.
Move over. You can roll the dice and only you and the GM can see.
GM roll just forward slash GM roll.
That's what you do.
And then do I just do I press enter or do I roll?
No, then you're gonna have to type in your
your performance like stat.
It's like going to be this.
It's one.
So it's going to be 1d20 for sure and then plus something
depending on what your character sheet says or minus.
Performance.
I think it's gonna be plus.
It's just one.
It's just one so it's gonna be 1d20 plus one.
Yeah.
Okay.
So this should only show up for me if it's /gmroll.
12. Not that good.
Okay. Not great, but not terrible either.
And then do that again for your jump over the menu though.
A performance again?
Yeah.
All right. This is going to be good.
Well, it didn't work out.
What do I do? GM roll?
Yeah, remember to do /gmroll and then 1d20+1.
1d20+1.
Yeah.
Hey, even worse.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, so you basically, yeah, you say it.
I'll try to match what you said.
And then when you jump over the menu,
you like, actually, it's like an inverse performance check.
You don't make it look natural.
You like pirouette over it.
(laughing)
- Okay, it looks a little too perfect.
- Yeah, yeah.
I think that's kinda how it is.
- Once I'm out of the building,
I would like to re-enter from the entrance when I can.
- Cool, that sounds good.
So yeah, move your guy, can he even go all the way out?
- Well here, just wait to bring him out
until you take him out when the fire starts.
- 'Cause he'll know it's up if I leave first.
- Yeah.
- Okay, cool.
-Okay, cool. Let's do it.
-All right. That's the end of my turn.
-All right.
-Okay.
-Nice rolling, Caleb.
-You hear over the loudspeakers of the bar, Cameron.
-Okay.
-There's a fire in the building.
-No.
-Yes.
You start to see people getting to the door.
You see Caleb run to the door and do a little pirouette through it over the menu.
-Oh, I understand.
-I'm willing to wager here that the item that we share is either the hole or the trip wire
and that's what's the deal with the menu is.
I can't imagine I'm too far off with that.
- Yeah, I don't know.
Yeah, yeah.
- All right, well, I didn't see him move
or do anything before the loudspeaker went off.
- No, no, no.
- So he probably conceivably didn't set a fire
and there might not be a fire in here at all.
Well, is there an outside map?
If I what?
Yeah, he's just like outside the bar.
OK, all right.
Well.
You know, I, you know, I just
thought about his date with the police
officer.
I got to bring that back.
OK, because what going he was on a
date, I didn't tell you he was on
the day in the beginning with a female
police officer.
This.
Yeah. And the last episode or this
episode.
I totally forgot about her.
- Okay, well.
(laughing)
- Okay, sorry, he just.
- Thank you, yeah.
- Sorry.
- You're basically trying to make me lose my neck
giving me crucial information.
(laughing)
- Sorry, keep going, yeah.
- Okay, do I have any weapons?
Oh yeah, I have a bow and a,
can I see him out the door?
Or I guess I don't want anyone to see me.
Nevermind.
- Yeah, you don't want people to know
you're armed like a rogue.
- Are there any other exits?
'Cause it's, you know, you're supposed to have two exits.
- There's a front door exit.
Yeah, your front door exit.
Where, where's that?
Right here.
Sorry, can you?
It's not working.
It might be covered up.
Far right.
You'll see it.
It's next to the bathrooms.
Oh, I see.
And I was covered by my character sheet.
Sorry about that.
Oh no worries.
Okay.
So he wants me to chase him, I guess.
Um, or maybe he's doing doubled psychology.
Either way, you know, I'm not really going to run.
Uh, I will leisurely walk.
Is everyone out at this point?
No, people are just starting to get running.
How long is my trip wire?
How long of a space can it reach?
It can be up to 15 feet long.
All right.
So I'm going to go ahead and is this guy right next to me?
Is he is he gone?
He's starting to run towards the fire exit.
All right. So he's not looking at me.
No, no, no.
All right.
I'm setting up the trip wire across these three squares to the left of my my tile.
I'm sorry.
I don't really want to click on them.
Yeah, I know.
I know you're looking there.
I like to set it up there.
Cool.
One of my three tripwires, I guess.
To the left.
Yeah, to the left.
To the left, to the left.
Okay, cool.
Let me ask you a question.
Has anyone else made it out of the fire exit yet?
This guy is
is starting to make his way out.
He's gonna go out.
- He's starting to make his way out?
- He's gonna go out at the end of time.
- So nobody's reached the menu yet.
- At the end of your turn.
- 'Cause I'd be pretty curious to see what happens
to everybody in this restaurant
when they cross over that menu.
And I just would like you to remember that maybe that's there.
- Yeah, no, I will. - 'Cause if my theory's right,
I'd like to see what happens here.
- It's at the end of your turn.
At the end of your turn, I'll let you know what happens.
- All right, yeah. - Your next turn, yeah.
- And is there anything else I can do?
Do I have any more types of actions I can take?
- Besides setting up the tripwire. - Not right now, no.
The only thing is that I will say that like...
Alright, you're waiting to set the tripwire
after people have gone by you, right?
- Yeah, I don't want anyone to trip on it. - Okay, cool.
- This is kind of like a failsafe. - Then I'll allow that to happen.
Like this guy is already over here,
this guy is already going this way.
Yeah, I'm just trying to... I'm basically...
I'm setting up a spider's web.
Got it, got it, got it, got it.
- More than anything, yeah. - Alright.
- You're gonna do your turn? - Yeah, I'm gonna end my turn.
You're gonna see this guy disappear.
Disappear, not go through the door, but disappear.
All right, yeah, I thought that that might be the case.
You're gonna see this guy disappear.
(laughing)
What's going on, you guys?
Okay.
All right, okay.
Good one, K.
(laughing)
I'm sorry.
- Okay, listen, I would like--
- Four people call me a person with a child's brain.
I do not have a single damage item.
All of my items are trickery and illusion.
- You do, here's the other thing too though.
Like, so I thought that was really clever.
I think something we might wanna,
I'm gonna think about doing this,
'cause it's one of those things where it's like,
how much do you hand it over to the player's own intellect
as much as you go, your character fails an insight check.
So next time I might, I'll do something like that
to just see how that plays out.
I liked doing that, that was fun.
Yeah, you just made like four patrons disappear.
Your date is, your date vanished too.
She's just gonna run through the hall.
- Okay, well then you know what?
I'd like to walk back in to the bar,
through the fire exit and go like,
what the hell, where'd everyone go?
And then I'll just go sit down at the bar.
I'm gonna go sit right there.
- Okay, cool.
Yeah, all right.
All right, cool.
(laughing)
- Wait, let me, hold on, let me look at, wait, no, no.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
- Hold on. - Wait, no, no, no, no.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
- And then?
- You have weapons, you can prepare attacks.
- You know what I'm gonna do?
- What are you gonna do?
- Can I move the portable pole?
- What you did achieve doing
is that everybody is out of here.
So if you start attacking him,
like you're okay to do that at this point.
I'm going to sit down at the bar and just look directly, just straight ahead, right?
And can I place the, can I sneak the portable hole right behind me on this
tile, right behind my bar stool?
As if, if somebody were to come stab me in the back, maybe they would
fall into this portable hole.
Do a slight of hand as you pick it up with the menu.
Okay.
Hold on.
And GM whisper, whisper that to me.
Yeah.
Let's do that from now on.
Gmwhisper d20
Gmwhisper
Gmroll right? Yeah, yeah, gmroll d20 plus 7. Yeah, your sleight of hand's great. Oh
Crit one man
That's sucks. It just happens every time
You really do get pretty bad rolls, man
Damn, okay. I fall into it and I die? No, not quite.
You pick it up
I hear I think you think you picking up the menu with the hole and the menu falls in the hole and you're just like
Whistling holding the hole and just place it behind you. Just very clear
All right. Well, I guess my turn's over. Okay
All right
Okay, so Caleb
-After everybody falls into something.
-Yes, into something beneath that menu.
-Yes.
Caleb pirouettes back in and says, "What the hell just happened?"
Then he picks up the menu, but the menu falls into a hole.
He's just carrying a hole.
He goes, "Oops," and places it right behind him.
He's just sitting at the bar.
-It's right behind him?
-It's right behind him.
Nobody's in here, right?
Nobody's in here anymore.
I tried to stress that to him.
OK, I'm going to shoot him hard enough
that he falls backwards into the hole.
I would like to shoot him with my what's my ranged weapon here?
I'd like to do a special role where the emphasis is not on damage,
but pushing him back one square back.
Yeah.
Oh, I wonder we can call this a shove action.
I'll have you roll.
Let's have him like I got.
Listen, I got a hammer in my inventory.
I'll throw that.
I just I want to push him back five feet.
Like in D&D, technically, not getting some knock back is like a,
you know, an added thing.
So what we can do.
Is. Let's have you
let's have you roll a yeah, OK, you can throw your hammer at him
and try to knock him back.
Let's have you just roll a
Definitely just roll it, I guess, like a athletics check.
Let's just do athletics first before I do that real quick.
Can I can I this is a bar in the middle, right?
Yeah, I just bought this bar.
So I have nice cover first.
Yeah, sure.
Just just top like right, right here. Yeah.
All right. I'll do that.
And now I'll do my athletics check.
And do forward slash.
OK, that's fine.
Okay. You keep your headphones on, okay?
Okay.
This is just happening now.
Your thumb is not in the frame.
Sorry.
You're hurting your thumb.
I was going like that? Yeah, that's cool.
You were fisting the cam.
I thought you were hurting me.
You're both going to have your headphones on now.
No.
I need you to roll a dexterity saving throw.
This will be easy for sure.
- I need this so bad, please.
(laughing)
Please give this to me.
- Dude, what the fuck did I tell you?
I just rolled two crit ones in a row.
Something is happening.
Cameron, Cameron.
- Tell him what just happened.
- I told you, I told you.
- So he saw you--
- Your plan sucks dick, bro.
I had the same item as you and my plan was so much better.
- He saw you pure wet in and go,
"What the hell happened?"
And then pick up a whole bunch of stuff.
Pick up a hole and put it behind you
He jumped over the bar and threw a hammer at your head and knocked you into the hole
That's fine, you know what I'm over these the items I got were terrible I'm over this episode
Wait, I have wait. I have I have a can I do a victory pose? I'll die forever in the hall
I have an important victory pose to do
After I do that, I stand up on the bar and I shake my head around and all the milk sprays out of my mouth
Wait, hold on. Make him roll dexterity and if he loses he falls into the hole also.
I'm not anywhere near the hole.
He's not near the hole.
So what he did is he put the magic hole in his mouth, Caleb, and he drank all the milk out of it.
Wasn't sure what he was gonna do with that, but it's pretty funny.
Well, here's my plan was that maybe the bar had some type of blowtorch where they do some kind of flaming moe type drink
and I could shoot scalding milk at you and burn you from my mouth.
You could have ordered a flaming drink.
Probably would have done if it wasn't for that hole if the hole didn't work. I probably would have thrown my voice to death
That's what I would have done to you. This is the only other fucking item that he gave me
All right next time. I'll try to even use any of my items
I use the hammer at me. I didn't know we had hammers. It's in the character
So you have like you have a bunch of thieves
So here's what we could do. We can do that. We'll have you have one mulligan
So you know one one we roll
Of an item no you don't think so item. Oh an item. Yeah single item. No not a whole round fuck that let's do
The second thing to also Cameron which I told to Caleb is like I think
I'm gonna try to instead of being like
You have to buy
Caleb's crap it's gonna be like you're good characters gonna roll against an insight check on something
- Okay.
- 'Cause it becomes, I don't know,
we're gonna see if that works.
- I think that makes the most sense
because it's otherwise we're just,
- You're just like, you're just, yeah.
- Anything is 100% suspicious.
- Yeah, yeah.
So we have to do that and you have to just like behave as if.
- I did, yeah.
I do think it was really funny
that you put the hole in the door
and then did the fire alarm
so I saw every single person in the restaurant
falling into the hole.
- I thought that maybe you would be a brave soul
and you would go in first.
- My metagaming was I knew that you had
one of the same items as me.
So I thought maybe it could be the whole,
or the other thing I had was a trip wire.
So I was like, there's no way I'm running anywhere.
- Oh yeah, that's good.
All right, let's go to the next map.
- This time I'll try to dumb it down a little.
- I will smart my stuff up.
- Okay, cool.
All right.
Whoa.
- Boobies, okay.
- Oh yeah, sorry, I didn't clean that up
from whenever you guys-- - Is this a laboratory?
This is an office now.
It's a laboratory.
Oh wait, this is the exact floor plan of our office.
It's kind of crazy.
I don't really like this being public.
I don't know when you guys...
I didn't realize that when I was adding it in here. I'm sorry.
You guys are at the office.
You're coworkers now.
In this classic spy vs. spy type of...
like y'all, you know each other
in this scenario.
Dwight and Jim.
A Dwight and Jim situation.
- Wait, that's what it should have been.
(laughing)
- Yeah, let's reskin it completely.
- Yeah, this one is Jim versus Dwight.
I'm Jim.
- Yeah, okay, I'll be Dwight.
- All right, okay, cool.
So, okay, and then here's Michael Scott over here.
- Okay.
- Pam is just in the general boobies area.
- I go to Pam.
- You know, I go to Pam, yeah, okay.
- Both of you guys roll your 3D20s.
- All right.
- 5, 14, 11.
- How did you roll so fast?
- You click D20.
Oh, now he wants to come to the master.
Well, I'll let you figure that out, big guy.
- You click, what?
Oh, I found it all by myself.
- Okay, you got five.
- Okay, so.
- 5, 14, 11.
Okay.
and I got 16, 17, 5.
God damn, we have the same item again.
I know, it's scaring me type.
Crazy guy.
It's scaring me type.
Oh, you guys both got 5. Okay.
And then 14 and 11. Okay.
I got 1000.
You did not.
It's a game of bluffing.
This is the game of bluffing, so anything goes.
Goddammit.
Man...
Sorry, it's formatting.
Sorry, formatting.
Formatting is probably one of the most significant things of the modern era. Anybody agree?
the
fifth
And tell me how the fuck Mia Khalifa is news nowadays? Is it because she's getting...
Well, because she was poolside.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, so now every time that a porn star goes poolside, we hear about it?
Well, not every time, but sometimes you do.
I'm gonna turn on... my parents are gonna turn on the news and see this? This is what passes for news in this country?
I mean, I guess, yeah.
Jesus Christ.
All of the major news outlets and Mia Khalifa went bullseye.
What the hell, her breasts are out.
- What the hell are breasts?
- Well, I need to go to sleep.
- All right, got yours.
- I guess it makes more sense for that to be news
than Mia Khalifa is filming a new porn video
because she probably does that all the time.
- True.
- Oh man, you got-- - Probably flood the news.
- You're saying she's a slut.
Yeah.
Yeah, you might say that.
You could say that.
You might say that.
I'm not sure I would but one might say that.
All right, who goes first?
Roll.
We didn't roll you.
Fuck me.
I almost got your items.
In the meantime, it's annoying.
It's just others.
I've rolled a 12.
Six.
You got a 12.
God damn it.
We're going to do the exact same thing with the item that we both
I know it.
Let's just agree to not use the item that we both have.
No, I'm gonna use it.
Let's do a no items round.
Shake on it.
No.
Shake on it right now that you won't use any items.
I promise not to use any items.
See, I'm promising right now.
I like my items this time.
I have deece items.
I didn't even see mine yet.
How come you're giving him more time to prep his items
then you're giving me time to prep with mine.
- 'Cause it's not a problem for me to read.
- Well, who got the initiative hire?
Cameron did. - Me, Cameron did.
- I see. - So I'm gonna need
a second here to read this.
- Yeah, take a second.
- Okay, so my first item.
- All right, I'm taking my fucking headphones off.
- Yeah, you got the-- - Okay.
- I didn't wanna say this to Caleb.
- Yeah.
- You got the most broken item in the game,
which is the anvil.
- Oh my God. - That is just...
- Wait, what's the range?
- It's anywhere.
- It's worms, bunker buster vibes?
- Yeah, precisely.
- Wow. - Oh, wow.
- Haven't had that thought.
- We should do a worms D&D.
(laughing)
- It's all from the side view.
- I would love that, actually.
- All right, so this is the office.
And he's all the way over here.
So we don't even have a line of sight
to each other right now, right?
- No. - So first of all,
where are the exits here?
- You do have to be able to see him, I will say.
- Yeah, yeah.
(laughing)
- What's the point here where I can see him all the way?
- The furthest point where I can.
- He's like, yeah, it's like all these different,
you're like, if you get on like a stool or something
and you can see over all the office cubicles.
- What's the button for ruler?
- Oh, what?
- Sorry, I'm just trying to do line of sight here.
Yeah, that's...
That's one of the sites. I guess it's just there.
If you go up the stairs, you could just see him.
Really?
Okay, let's do it. There's no one near him either.
He just got into work. You're just taking off.
I'm just doing my Dwight shirt shit.
Alright, just doing some Dwight shit. Just go up the...
All right, hold on all right just I'm going I'm I say loudly just have to do some Dwight stuff
Forward slash GM roll 2d 6 all one word. Yeah, GM roll. Yeah
Christ okay
And I guess he's gonna have to do a deck saving throw all right
- Which is gonna, yeah, he's not gonna, all right.
He might, but he's gonna take half damage either way.
Okay, yeah, all right, cool, all right.
Okay.
Oh, sorry, I forgot to do thumbs up.
- Am I dead already?
- Not yet.
Okay, so.
(sighs)
- All right, roll a dexterity saving throw.
- Do I have to?
I got a crit one last time I did this.
- You gotta do it again.
- 18!
- Very nice, okay.
- Fuck you, Cameron, fuck you!
- So this is what happens.
You see, you're just sort of like hanging out
in the office doing gym stuff.
You hear very far in the distance, you hear,
I'm just off to do some Dwight shit.
And then an anvil falls out of the sky
and you just dodge roll it in time.
Oh yeah.
That you only get beat up by it a little bit.
You kind of like get knocked around a little bit,
you don't get squashed.
So you take four, you take four damage.
Okay, I'm at nine.
You wanna play ball Cameron? Let's play ball.
Yeah, and you see some people you see Oscar
Roll up and he's like "Los Cientos"
Okay, what does he say?
Besides Lucien Jones.
He says, uh, he says
He says, "Oh my god, what happened to you, Jim?"
Um, I think Dwight might be up to one of his old pranks again.
You hate Dwight, right?
Dwight is the worst. Dwight's the worst man. I fucking hate Dwight. Okay, listen. Yeah, you gonna do me a favor?
Absolutely, Jim. Will you find Dwight and tell him that Pam needs to talk to him?
Yeah, that's not a problem. Thank you so much. Okay, he runs off, right? I'd like to go over to Pam's desk.
Okay.
Pam's desk. Where's girl? I have the girl here.
She's like
"Gotta do it next turn, man. She's too far."
You can get it like shouting distance like you can get um, let me see
You can get here and her desk is like
Like she's over like here. Okay, so you're within like I'll just call her
Okay. Yeah, do you have a go over there?
Yeah, I'm gonna go right here, okay, all right, I'm gonna call her
Okay
Hey, baby girl, how are you?
I'm good. How are you?
Yeah, I'm doing all right. Hey, listen, I'm trying to kill Dwight. He tried to drop an anvil onto my body luckily
Very spry special forces type guy so I died. Mm-hmm
No
Here's what I'm gonna do. You're in a cubicle. Yes
Mm-hmm. All right, so there's an open top. So I'm gonna throw these things. They're called
Caltrops, I'm gonna throw them over there
OK. OK.
If you wouldn't mind, baby girl, just kind of set them in front of the door
and be expecting a visit from Dwight.
Okey dokey.
Thanks so much. I love you.
Bye bye. I know you do.
And then and you're going to tell us
Oscar's going to tell him that Pam wants to talk to him.
OK. And I'm so I'm going to throw these things over. Got it.
Yeah. You threw them over there right in front of the door.
They're hidden.
Cool.
I'm just going to set up my phone.
He's going to do some checks.
All right, cool.
Wow, that's classic Jim.
Okay.
All right.
You hear a thump, a thud.
He rolls away.
He's limping now.
You hear Jim limping in the office.
Yeah, and as Dwight that makes me joyful.
Yeah, Dwight is happy about that.
You get, um...
You, uh...
Oscar
comes up to you.
And he says to you,
"Dwight, Pam needs to see you in her office."
Okay.
Yeah.
Am I rolling an insight on this?
Yeah, roll insight on that.
Alright, how do I roll a stat privately?
I guess it doesn't matter so much.
Just forward slash GM role and then just add the insight.
That's all all I know about how to do it.
All right, cool.
And a 20 plus four.
OK, that's an 11.
Yeah, you don't suspect anything.
I don't suspect anything.
No, I mean, it's just a thing that would happen.
Yeah, yeah. I'm like, all right.
So am I following Oscar or or am I just going?
No, you're just going to go to the office.
All right. Where's the office?
It's over here is where Pam's office is right near boobies,
right near boobies.
OK, well, I will start on my way there.
Yeah, it's going to take you some time.
It's going to take me a long time.
It's going to take you like eight turns.
Is there anything you want to do, though?
To with the. Yeah, can you tell me?
All right, so.
Cool. First off, I'm here, right?
I want to put down some...
Cow traps.
Okay.
Um...
Familiar with the stuff.
Yeah, and I would love to put them down...
Uh, hmm.
If I put them down on a spot that I'm gonna have to walk through, is there gonna be an issue with me?
No, you'll know where they are.
- So it'll be okay if I throw them in front of me
and then I walk through them next turn,
I won't have any risk?
- If you know where they are, you're fine.
- All right, I'm gonna go ahead and throw them at the,
do you see the two squares to my right
that have the plus sign pattern on them?
- I mean, you should roll like a,
you should roll like a,
I'll say this, you should roll like a fuckin',
just a straight dex check with advantage.
- Okay. - 'Cause you know
where they are, but yeah.
- All right, but not to throw them down, just to cross them?
Yeah, just across them.
Yeah. OK, so I'm throwing them down.
Yeah, throw them down.
I mean, like nobody's paying attention to you.
This is the office.
It's a little different than the bar.
Let's put it that way.
OK, so I'm going to throw them down at this.
This bottleneck right there.
OK, cool. I know where you're from, which also.
Yeah, I'm going just to be clear, I'm going up on on the upper side of this block.
Like I'm going over here, right?
I don't know how to make. I'm right.
I know. Oh, yes.
That's where you're going. Yeah. OK.
All right.
Yeah, then I'm going to throw them down at that like square in that square.
Bottle neck. OK, got it.
OK, I know exactly where you're saying.
Cool. That's fine.
OK, and I also want a quick report of what in my immediate vicinity
is made out of metal.
OK, cool.
Any of the computers, staplers
like the.
So there's just generally stuff around.
There's generally stuff around.
That's OK. All right. That's fine.
Then I'm done. Yeah.
And you see Stanley and he looks at you and he goes, Hmm, Stanley.
Uh huh. Mm hmm. OK.
And Kevin's dropped the chili.
No, man, no. All right. OK. Turn.
Hello, mate.
All right. Yeah.
So that was your turn.
You're on. You've been on your phone. What's going on?
I'm checking out just pictures of Pam that I took.
Guys are pictures.
Picture of her cooking, pictures of her cleaning,
kind of imagining our future life together.
That's awesome. This is early office.
Right.
Is she still dating, what was his name?
Is it Roy?
Rudd, Roy.
Roy, was it Rudd?
No, it was Roy.
It was Roy, okay.
All right, so that sucks.
Cause I probably, you probably want to be dating her, but what do you want to do also?
Well, we, you know, we have a crush, which is pretty cool. Um, let me look at my items
one last time. I made the office too big. Yeah. The office is huge, mate. It's so big.
Um, Cameron is over there. My defense is from another campaign. There's no, there's no,
There's no area of effect on this pocket mirror of mind reading, huh?
No, it has to catch somebody's eye
Okay, there are other office characters though, yeah, yeah, yeah, I know but I want to talk to this guy that's near Cameron
You know what? Maybe I let's see. How far is this?
God this is the biggest
I'm a too big
So I can walk here.
Uh-huh.
And I have, what, 15, 20 foot arms?
Uh, you can use your dash action too to get there faster, but
you won't then get to be able to take an action.
You know what I mean?
I just want to, this guy right here, I would really, really, really like to read his mind.
This white guy. Or is that, that's Oscar.
That's Stanley.
Oh, that's Stanley? Yeah, I want to read Stanley's mind so badly, man.
Oh wait, do I have a donut? He's fat.
Yeah man, you got a donut.
All right, I stick the mirror in the donut and I just kind of toss it to like,
like how can I ping?
Without him noticing you mean?
No, no, he can notice.
Oh cool. Just like you hold it down. That's all.
Okay, yeah. I kind of toss it over here about 10 feet.
Okay. Or you know what I do? I use the mirror like a plate and I slide it across the ground
with the donut on top. It looks like a little serving plate. Okay. I like that. All right.
All right. I'm going to roll for Stanley. See if he gets duped by that. He's very wise,
so he's decent wisdom but he falls for it though anyway. Yeah. So he goes he moves
he looks he goes Stanley and he starts walking towards the donut mirror and you
hear his thoughts and his thoughts are Dwight through something weird. That's it?
and then just back to donut donut donut. Yeah, Dwight did something weird on the ground. It's
gonna be those caltrops. I know he has them and he knows I have them too. Let's see. He
doesn't probably know. You're probably more familiar with the items. No, but he knows it
because he knows.
Because of the order that you sent him in.
Yeah, maybe. Yeah.
That's how I figured it out.
All right. Well, I already used my movement and my item,
so I think I will just...
That mirror can be used every turn though still.
So if you want. Okay, cool.
So you can use it to take advantage of people.
Here, wait, let me call Pam real quick.
Okay, ring, ring, ring.
Hi.
What up, baby?
How you doing?
Did Dwight end up stopping by and dying?
You know, he's coming by, it's just at every turn,
they have to move 30 feet.
So he's on his way.
Oh, okay, I forget about that office rule.
His office is so big.
Yeah, yeah, we really should have made the office smaller.
It's only six or seven people who work here.
It's kind of absurd.
Yeah, it's pretty wild.
Well, if you wouldn't mind, maybe--
We might even, if you guys don't come up
with new stuff to do, we might even just
make you guys move faster for the rest of the round.
That would be pretty neat.
That's actually a pretty good idea, Pam.
Yeah.
Oh no, don't--
I'm not Pam.
Okay, well, will you do me a favor?
Yes.
No, he's Dwight's gay if you flash your tits out of the doorway he won't care
Okay
Just sit there and look pretty baby
All right, so what's going on it's to dig a new office rule
where everyone has a
a lot more movement because this is crazy.
Yeah, really?
Like, but you did see Stanley just sort of wander away.
And look, he's looking down at something, but you don't know what
Stanley is. Yeah.
OK, I don't care about Stanley.
OK, well,
how much more movement do I?
I'll say you can make it to Pam's office this turn.
I think it's crazy to.
Make that take too much longer.
OK, on the way, I'd like to throw down another set of Cal traps.
OK, behind me. Oh, wait, I also have to roll, right?
To get through my.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
All right. Just a dex roll or a dex save.
Just a dex check.
I mean, can we get acrobatics or whatever?
Like acrobat, you might proficiency in that.
So do that.
I don't, but I'll do it anyway.
And it's with advantage because you know where it is.
Yeah, you pass the 21 you pass.
All right, and I'm just going to leave another.
I'm just going to leave more of them right next to it as I go.
Okay, cool.
I know where that's going to be.
And where's Pam's office?
Sorry,
Shoe P.O.
Sealed at me to talk into the mic.
What?
Where's Pam's office?
Again, it's this...
Yeah, it's this one over here.
Yeah.
Okay, I'm going.
I'm there.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, roll a Perception check.
All right.
I'm going to hide it.
GM roll 1d20
plus
Perception 2.
Damn.
(laughing)
- Okay.
You see Pam and she goes, "Hi, Dwight!"
And you take six damage as you step all over
these fucking caltrops.
- Oh. - They're all over
your feet now.
And she goes, "He he he he he he!"
- He has an ally?
- Yeah.
- I take six damage?
- She's making friends in the office.
- Bruh, he's using my unfriendliness against me.
- And then she closes the door.
You should take her hostage though.
- Yeah, that's fine.
I mean, I'm just gonna stand in front of the door.
She's not getting out.
And I say through the door, "You're mine."
(laughing)
- Oh, ow!
She goes, "He he he he he he."
- All right.
- And I go, "Pah, pah, pah."
(laughing)
- All right, cool.
So you're just gonna chill there for now?
- Yeah.
- All right, cool.
You heard Dwight make Dwighty noises
as he stepped on his Dwighty toes all over your caltrops.
- Yes!
- Yeah, and you heard Pam go, "He he he he he he."
Thank you, Pam.
Yeah.
I do this with my fingers.
People in other countries do this.
Yeah?
Yeah.
All right.
He knows that.
Cool.
So yeah, also now you can move just basically
to where you want to go in the office is what the new rule is.
OK, I'm liking this rule.
Yeah, because I'm just--
it's just too much, man.
Well.
Mm-hmm.
I'm going to walk over to Stanley.
Now that's a proper office item I gotta say.
Yeah wait where's... he's not gonna go back to his desk.
Um...
Stanley.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I'm gonna walk over, actually, yeah I'm gonna walk over to Stanley.
Hey Stanley!
'Sup Stan the man?
How you doing, Jim?
Good, brother. You know what you look like you need?
And not a donut. I already saw you eat one, you fat motherfucker.
You need a new pen.
Look at these pens. These pens are shit.
These are big, low-quality, bad pens sitting in your pocket.
Roll a persuasion check.
Or a deception check, I guess.
Because he doesn't need a pen.
I don't want you. I'm going to...
and
happens.
Stanley says "OKAY!" grabs it, and presses it, and blows up.
Alright, how much damage did I take?
Uh, you don't take any. Stanley's just dead.
And you don't have to pay anymore.
I was right next to him.
Yeah, alright, shit.
Come on, let's be honest.
Mmhmm.
Also, I have a show I have to go to, so I'm okay to die.
Oh yeah, that's true too.
Oh shit, okay, you take 11 damage.
You actually did die.
It's 4d4.
And you just like...
got completely destroyed.
Okay, now I feel bad.
Alright, you know what?
Fuck it, man.
The what? The...
The roll's only going one way tonight.
Cameron, put your headphones on.
I'll explain what happened.
Okay, so based on what I was seeing,
I'm guessing maybe something good happened?
- For you. - Yeah, for you.
- It's so cool that it's just been his owed items
that have been killing him.
So he rolled, he went up to Stanley and said,
"Take this explosive pen."
He didn't say explosive pen, he said,
"You look like you need a new pen."
Rolled a persuasion check, got a crit one.
- Third crit one of the night.
- Stanley said, "Okay, I'll take the pen."
And he took it and pressed it, and then Stanley died
and he took 11 damage. - And I died.
I died
That's crazy, this is the kind of thing that's been happening to me every single time
I play you are you're not even letting me get a plan off. Yeah, I know you scheme too much
Dude, that's not my head much
I had I had I put down a shit ton of
Caltrops behind me at what I was walking and my plan was you're gonna walk over them take some damage and then as soon as I
Saw you walk over them. I also had a giant magnet
So I was gonna turn that on and then all they were all gonna fly into your body and kill you
- That's such a good idea.
- Tell me why you actually went over and talked to Pam.
- 'Cause I failed my insight check.
- Oh, okay. - I tried to do that.
- I knew it, I was like, there's--
- I actually, he didn't even feel,
I specifically said, should I roll an insight check?
'Cause I knew I was supposed to.
- I almost put my headphones back on to say,
of course this is a trap, but you're supposed to--
- Yeah, but it was okay.
- No, we're trying, I think that's better,
I think it's better for the game.
- I think I played the first one a little too meta-geared.
- It was fun. - But I understand
the vibe now, I think.
- Yeah. - I think it makes sense.
I think it is, yeah.
I wish I got to use my magnet, man.
I was also hoping I could--
- We'll definitely be doing Jim versus Dwight again.
- Yeah. - Yeah, Jim versus Dwight.
- I wanna do every versus.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- That exists. - I'll start,
if we're gonna do that, I'll start leaning
into the characters.
I'll make it more of a thing.
I like that. - Speaking of characters,
I just wanna say here, Pat, as I'm looking at,
I just noticed on the character sheet you gave me,
for myself, I see here you've made me a level two rogue,
which is nice.
- Everyone's a level two rogue.
- Under background it says multimedia artist.
- Wow, that's very flattering.
- That is very kind of you.
But what I'm noticing here, for race,
you put standard human.
As my race, you've put standard human.
- That was the option they had.
I just like, I used the character banter.
- Wait, did you talk to Oscar Cameron?
- Uh, I don't remember.
- Okay, you wouldn't remember the voice patches was doing.
Yeah, oh wait. No. I did talk to Oscar. Yeah, he did he did do this
He didn't say the same or Oscar just talk to me at least did he say Luciento to you?
Did he tell you that I said I'm just doing Dwight stuff
Yes
He did say that no I heard you saying you heard him say that from like from like it said like I got from a distance
You just hear you just hear Dwight go. I'm just doing Dwight stuff
Thank you. Yeah, dude
He told me that I could use the anvil thing on you as long as I had line of sight so I was like yeah
Okay
I'm just gonna find the point on the map that I can walk to where I have line of sight and I was gonna have to
Walk like multiple turns to get there and then he was like, yeah, you can just climb to the top
Okay, that's it for you
That is that's a damn, but that's not a bad idea. Yeah, they'll give him a taste of medicine
I would I wouldn't mind all run that line. Yeah, I would like that. All right, cool. Maybe okay. Bye. Bye
Bye bye.