Uh, last time on Sullivan Quest...
The year is 2042.
And so I've been blackmailing her and I think she can get you a good audio book deal.
Give me a week, I have this manuscript that I'm working on.
Give me a week to punch it up, how's it sound?
That's great, yes, a week is perfect.
Thank you so much.
This is going to change our lives, man.
I press record.
How about I read you a bedtime story?
Once upon a time there were three friends.
Caleb, Cameron, and Peter.
I got this new game I wanted us to play.
It's an RPG called Sullivan Quest.
Reminds me of Patches who died, beloved, and was never betrayed.
Press start?
Don't mind if I do.
Wow! I can't believe I turned 15 just this morning!
It's Belinda Croaks, the prettiest frog in school!
Oh hey Sullivan, happy birthday!
Oh no, it's Bullyfrog the Toad!
Well look at what we have here!
Oh gosh, uh...
Bullyfrog, why don't you knock it off?
You're dead meat Sullivan! I'll see you after school, punk!
Today class, we'll be wrapping up a short documentary about Sullivan de Granouille,
the worst explorer in Gan City history.
The Grandoui documented all of it in his journal, which he called "Sullivan's Quest."
However, he misplaced it, so now we don't know what he saw.
When he died, he said, "In many years, a young frog just like me will have his own quest,
and he will discover the truth behind Gun City."
Well, time to get home.
Wow, it's my tough-as-nails cousin, John Carlo.
Now, Sullivan, John Carlo's gonna be watching you this week while Mama heads to Cancun.
Sullivan, wake up! We gotta go!
Guess I gotta follow Giancarlo!
Uh-oh. It's the Nightmare Assassin.
That young frog is impressive.
Could he be?
We'll have to find another way.
Move out, operatives!
Let's get moving. We have to get to the base.
This place is amazing!
Welcome to the pond, Sullivan.
Your quest begins here.
I think I'm gonna head home.
Wanna play this again tomorrow?
If we have to.
I remember the last time a recording felt that good.
But what to call it?
Maybe just...
Maybe just Sullivan Quest?
So I come up with the name Sullivan Quest,
do a line of CCP approved nutritional supplement,
and start grinning like a Cheshire whore.
That first chapter felt real good.
But before I could even start working on part two,
I was gonna need another pick-me-up.
So I went outside for the first time in a while,
while. Stepped over that Amazon crackhead fellow that went down to the bodega. They don't scan
you with this one so you can go in and out real quick. I'll grab some beef jerky, got
a meal of high life, and I start flirting with the girl behind the counter. You many, really
nice. I think most of the mail service workers are in one of those plants in central Jersey.
You have a better pay, a couple days vacation, you can start at 14 too if you're not a party
member, or you can't afford high school or whatever. Now here you need to know just a
a little bit of python too and you're good. Not that I have anything to do with that shit.
You know, it's not my bag. I avoid that world, thank god.
But anyway, I'm flirting with the girl behind the counter. She hasn't said a word to me
for 20 minutes, but before I know it, it's night time. So I'm rushing back before a curfew.
I'm constantly looking over my shoulder, I forgot to bring my badge, I could have gotten
the fucking chip in my arm to avoid a lot of this crap. You know, the chip thing, but I
was too lazy. I've been too lazy. But I really couldn't afford to get caught, you know, hold
off to re-education, because that can take days, and I need to finish Sullivan Quest before
the week was up, or Price would have my fucking head.
This province got such a fucking raw deal, I swear to God.
But anyway, so, right when I think I'm home free, I'm rounding the block, right where
my brownstone is, I see a few of these stupid fucking Pinkertons patrolling.
They're hassling the Amazon crackhead now.
And I know that's gonna entertain them for a while, 'cause, you know, beats running goods for climate refugees, so...
I about face and I just end up going down Hanover for a couple blocks, you know, I'm just sort of beelining it, like I don't know what the fuck's going on.
And I turn into some lobby, I think it's a lobby of a yotel, but it was a theater.
You know, I'm still bugging out a little bit from the supplement and the other shit I've been doing.
So I don't even know what the fuck I am and then my eyes start to adjust and I realize
it's new Webster Hall.
Some nothing burger 16 year old staring at me like I'm half crazed which I am so I get
it.
And he's like "Oh can I help you sir?"
I can see security's starting to get a little antsy so I just tell the kid "Yo I'm fine,
I'm just getting out of the rain."
He can see there's no rain.
But he also can see I'm not going to cause any trouble.
So it's past curfew, obviously, you know, a little down and out, just, you know,
let me just duck in here for a little bit, yadda yadda. So he's like, "All right, okay."
You know, I watch the security, they sort of put the hazes to the side, he gives a sort of
curt nod to me, like, whatever. So I start to shuffle over to the theater's cocktail bar
in the lobby of these places. So I start to shuffle over there, I'm gonna order a drink,
and then I start hearing people laughing inside. I ask the kid, "Oh, who's playing tonight?" He
He says, "Oh, some pre-G American stand-up.
You know, some pre-G art."
Nobody gives a shit about pre-G art anymore.
It's all about whatever's going on now.
But, you know, that was my time, so it's important to me.
So I'm like, "Oh, can I pop in?"
I'm interested in that.
And the kid says, "Okay, sure, you know, just for a second."
And I'm like, "All right, well, fuck you."
So I start to walk up the stairs, and we get to see the show.
I start to hear the comedian now a little bit more clearly, you know, the words start to take shape
I start to get phrases intonation and slowly I start to piece together an act
And it's an act I begin to recognize
Because it's fucking Caleb
You got isn't it it's it
It's funny how you guys ever notice how people are afraid of Godzilla
That son of a bitch is Tory, and he's crushing it too, and he's alone.
I even kept up with those fuckers, but I thought they all stuck together after the Apatow deal.
Did it fall through?
I was gonna shout at the audience, y'all tell 'em they're watching a traitor.
They're giving their money to a bastard who would sell their own mother down the river,
but soon it'd be broadcast about shit.
It's like, uh, if I was Godzilla, and I saw all these damn, all these fuckin' little guys everywhere,
Hell, I'd be scootin' my lizard ass back into that there ocean.
And I might even call a bigger Godzilla to take care of the problem.
I couldn't stand it anymore. I was fuming.
I needed to go home.
You know, let them take me to re-education.
As long as they don't have to hear this.
It's a dope, but they all live on without a care in the world.
For everything they did to me.
Everything.
So I thanked the kid.
And I gave him a tip or an old tissue or something in my pocket.
And I sprinted home and the Pinkertons were gone, thank God.
So was the crackhead.
I burst open my brownstone, rubbed one out, thinking about the bodega girl reaching for mace behind the counter.
I opened up my laptop and then...
*sigh*
I calmed down for a second, I was so possessed by this ravenous spite.
I missed a couple texts from my wife.
So I start panicking because she only talks to me when I'm really fucked up.
But it was just some pictures of her with the kids.
I don't think she meant to send it to me though because she also wrote "wish these kids were
ours" with a heart emoji.
I pressed record.
Good evening, young Thomas.
Hello, Uncle Jake.
What are we going to do for fun this evening?
Well, Thomas, I thought we'd keep reading the "Podcasters Play Video Games" book,
since you seemed to so enjoy the first chapter last night.
Uncle Jake, I don't know.
You know I only have so much time left on this here earth...
With my disease.
Heh heh! I know, I know.
That's why it's good to read.
And enrich yourself.
To strengthen your resistance to...
The outside forces that try to corrupt your mind as they have your poor, sick little body.
*Groans*
Okay.
That sounds important.
Read the book then I guess.
And I might even call a bigger Godzilla to take care of the problem.
That's so funny dude.
So awesome.
Looks like I just walked into the laugh factory.
You just missed one of Caleb's classic bits.
Oh wow.
Was it one of the ones Patches wrote for you back in the day?
Of course! Patches wrote all my best bits.
The hip-hop doctor, the Malaysian conductor, the hip-hop tennis player...
He was even bald first.
No way!
I had no idea.
Well, you never asked him.
So true.
Anyway, I brought Sullivan Quest again in case you guys want to play it.
What do they keep bringing up?
What's... what's his name?
*stuttering*
Patches?
Uh, well, see the thing is here little tiny Tommy Tim-time, Patches was a podcaster too.
A friend of theirs.
What?
I don't get it.
Why don't they just play the game?
Or, I don't know, talk about things?
What is that like?
They just keep talking about their dead friend.
That's not important.
What's not important?
Uh...
I don't know.
Sullivan Quest?
Yep.
[Music]
Ahahahah! Ahahahah! Ahahahah!
I'm splashin' in the water! I'm splashin' around!
Ahahahah! Waaah!
Waa-WAAAHH!
Woah, take it easy, Sullivan. You're still gonna get used to your powers.
And, and, and... Don't use frog arts so casually.
Sorry! This place is just so great!
Well, it's sacred, too.
It was sealed off from the world for hundreds of years, and through frog arts, it kept out of sight of the city.
A lot of frogs from the city found their way out here when they learned they had...
These powers, I bet the knowledge of these powers was being suppressed.
Oh, wow.
Even more, I've lived here their whole life.
Never even seen the outside world.
Wh-why?
Well...
Giancarlo, you've returned!
Elba Ribbit, it's good to see you.
And you as well, my friend.
And I see you've brought a visitor.
Not just any visitor, that's a cousin.
Hi, my name's Solomon the Frog.
It's nice to meet you.
This is...
Thee Sullivan?
Yeah, it's him.
Well then, the pleasure is all mine, Mr. Sullivan.
Mr. Sullivan?
I know he's young, but uh...
We've run out of time.
He's asking a lot of questions and uh...
It's not really...
It's not really my thing.
I see.
Mr. Sullivan, are you enjoying the pond?
Why, yeah, it's... it's amazing.
I've never seen so many of my kind in one place.
Particularly a place so lovely as this.
It's pretty nice.
How wonderful.
These old legs don't hop so well anymore, but if they could I'd be hopping for joy.
When you're ready, Mr. Sullivan, I'd be honored if you'd join me at the ephemeral pool.
Take a look at your map in the pause menu and press R for the local map view.
You'll be able to see where all of the landmarks in the pond are, including the ephemeral pool.
Oh, neato!
Thanks!
Please join me soon.
Until then, Mr. Sullivan.
Okay, bye!
Uh, do I have to join him?
Yeah you do.
Okay.
Look kid, there are a lot of things about this world that have been hidden from us.
Not just from frogs, but from all of us.
I'll be by the pool as well.
Just join us when you're ready.
Yeah but ready for what?
That, that, that.
Oh come on!
Well, I guess I can explore the pond for a bit. It's pretty neat
But then I better head right over to the ephemeral pool. Who cares about this shit open the map. Okay, I did
There's like an item shop and a weapon shop and armor shop. Naturally. It's a bunch of towns folks or
There's that pool. Don't go there. It's gonna start the next scene. Let's just shop a bit
Hey, didn't we level up on the way over here got a new move to multi attack right? Yeah, sure
Also, didn't you get one game over on the way over here? That was yesterday. So the turns since when?
Hi, welcome to the pond weapons and armor shop, how can I help you?
Do we have money? Yes, we killed a ton of monsters that dropped a ton of tokens
A photon blade? Sullivan can't equip that. Is Giancarlo in our party still?
Nah, he's not in the menu. I'm guessing he's too overpowered to stay with us. Just like Patches.
Do you have any recommendations?
You should get the best weapon that fits in your budget, and get the best armor that fits in your budget, in that order.
Oh, okay.
It's not rocket science, buddy. Just get the best equipment. We make it very clear here which is best.
Hover over an option you can see if it raises your attack or defense.
No, no, I got it now, thanks.
It's really easy to do. Like, really easy.
Hmm, okay, I'll take the Buster Mop and the Gap Kids Ensemble.
500 tokens.
Thanks, come again.
Thank you!
Actually, I would like to sell also these 37 Monster Bones.
Whoa, dude, what the fuck? Why do you have so many bones?
Giancarlo told me these were 17 tokens apiece.
Maybe if you're Richard Ramirez. Oh my god the smell. Oh my god. I'm sorry are these
They for crafting
What the fuck about this weapons and armor shop made you think I was gonna buy three dozen pelvises. What the fuck are you doing?
I don't know. I'm sorry. I'm leaving
Thanks for the bop in the armor. Thanks come again
Okay
Alright, well, I guess I'll have to, uh, find a way to get rid of these bones.
Uh...
But first, let's meet some more of my fellow frogs!
The pond keeps us safe. I sure hope the city, or the board, never find us.
Elder Ribbon and the pond guard will keep us safe. I'm sure of it.
By Anora, I hope so.
Hi! Would you like to hear the story of Onura?
The goddess of the frogs-
Absolutely not.
I hate this shit.
Pete, stop!
Fuck!
Yes!
Why did you hit yes?
I thought I had no selected, the UI is confusing.
I'm actually preparing for my initiation into the council of Senor Frogs, so it helps to talk about it.
This is fucking miserable.
I'm trying to skip it!
All frogs had tails, and then there was Onura.
She gave the gift of without to the frogs.
Following the rebirth, when Onora fell, this was the second metamorphosis.
And that's the story of Onora.
Phew, think I did okay.
Do you want to hear it again?
I won't!
No thanks.
Okay, farewell.
I was just a tadpole, but look at me now!
That's my son. He was just a tadpole, but look at him now.
Alright, I'm good. Let's go talk to the old guy.
This must be the ephemeral pool.
Um...
Hey!
I'm here.
Good, good, good come Mr. Sullivan.
This pool sure is beautiful.
It's been in the pond for centuries.
Really?
Yes.
Yes, definitely.
Anyway, Mr. Sullivan, have you ever heard of Sullivan de Granwy?
Yeah, we just learned about him in school actually.
When I was, I guess when I was going to school.
Am I still going to be able to go to school?
Not the whole story I'm sure.
Nor the true one.
His story is the same as Gan City's.
And the whole of Planet E-Bomb itself.
You see, De'Gronwi was an explorer employed by the board long before they were called that.
And long before they ruled Gan City.
He was sent on an expedition here, in Planet E-Bomb.
Then, just an uninhabited planet of little repute.
He discovered the planet was rich with resources, enough to sustain any civilization for millennia.
He spent years here, documenting the planet's brilliance and beauty.
He even developed the planet's first settlement right here in this very pond.
He began to bring more frog folk to the planet, to share with them the joy and potential he saw.
When the Gromwe returned to the board, he told them of his exploits.
He told them that Planet E-Bomb could provide for everyone.
And he showed them his journal where he documented his adventure, better known as "Sullivan's Quest".
This did not sit well with the greedy board. You see, resource scarcity helped them maintain control
and fund their planetary exploration and conquest. So they took de Grenouille's journal, blasted
Planet E-Bomb into a barren wasteland, slaughtered all the frogs de Grenouille brought with him,
And worst of all, they tarnished his name, called him a weird guy, and a sucker.
Oh my god, that's horrible!
But all hope was not lost.
They grown we and his allies before their defeat.
Used the last of their frog arts to seal the pond and the few frogs who remained underground,
away from their enemies.
But I thought-
That he died from the wound in his balls that spread to his penis.
Yes, that is true.
I wasn't...
Alright.
remains of the way Planet Yibaum was before the arrival of the Borg, before they blasted
this place to shit.
Our surviving ancestors kept the story of De'Gronwy alive, but they also kept us underground,
hidden and isolated from a world that tried to destroy us.
Most of the frogs who came to the planet, who settled above ground, long after De'Gronwy's
expedition, soon forgot his story.
They forgot the pond, the frog arts.
Even our goddess Anura, bless the one who gets no tail, believing the lies the board told
them.
But the frogs are always drawn to the pond.
This is so hard to follow.
So the old French Sullivan explored the planet a long time ago, saw that it was good.
The bad people didn't like that, so they made the planet bad, killed French Sullivan
and his frog friends.
It's pretty simple.
But why is he French?
Hold on boys, I gotta take this. It's Juna.
Juna...
Here, Sullivan! Look at this!
Wow! What is this?
It looks delicious!
When De'Gronwe sealed the pond, he also sealed one of the seven amber shards of Anura in here as well.
Within each shard is a fossilized fly that contains the power to restore the planet.
The shards however are unbreakable to everything except for the fly eater.
The fly eater?
Oh so you heard me.
Uh uh uh.
No, that's good.
*clears throat*
De Garnouille said that someday the fly eater would come
and that he would collect the shards and restore the barren planet.
The key to finding the shards is in Sullivan's quest.
Which, as we know, was stolen by the board!
That is, until your cousin John Carlo stole it back a few years ago.
I'd been working for the board for a while, and eventually found out they had Sullivan's Quest.
We had enough since we were told it was lost.
Then I saw the board had files on you, kid.
What? What about me?
Well, they suspected that you were... that you're the Fly Eater.
The one destined to restore the planet?
Wh-what?
think they really knew what that meant but they were starting to piece something
together and I wanted to do it before they did so I went looking for answers
and I met Elder...
More like I met you! He was quite the sight! He was
passed out for a week! The whole pond worked together to nurse this one back
to health!
Yeah yeah old man, things got complicated with the board, let's put it that way.
But once your cousin finally awoke he showed me Sullivan's quest, thought lost
forever and told me about you. Myself and the Council of Signor Frogs had been
scrying the ephemeral pool searching for the fly eater. We saw it could be this
Sullivan the Frog. That's my name. Yes and by Enora I knew that there was hope.
I don't know. The other six shards were hidden throughout the planet by De
Granouille during his travels all of which he documented in Sullivan's quest.
But Crafty DeGranouille used his frog arts to erase the journal's contents, meaning he erased the shard's locations as well.
But the journal, just like the planet, can be restored if...
Well...
Mr. Sullivan...
If you truly are the fly eater, hold the shard in your hands and think of your happy place.
The one you think about when you use your frog arts.
Then, use your tongue to eat the fly.
But this shard is hard as rock or metal or stone or rock.
If the stories are true, it won't be in your hands or with your tongue.
Okay, I'll try.
Wow!
My tongue, it phased right through the amber.
That tasted pretty good.
Whoa!
Where am I?
This is like my dream again.
What's this?
I feel a power within me.
This is your power Sullivan.
Your quest.
The organism demands it.
New frog are unlocked.
Lightbringer blast.
How do you feel Mr. Sullivan?
I feel strange, but good.
I feel strong.
Where was I?
You were right here.
You just floated in the air and peed yourself a little.
Oh no.
Elder Ribbit, you must see.
Above ground.
Yes, yes.
Sullivan! Giancarlo, come!
Oh my god!
It's so green!
Beautiful! There's a river here!
Trees! This was not...
when we came here, Giancarlo!
I know, kid.
I know.
The land above where the pond is sealed,
it's been restored!
I wasn't sure if I believed it before, but...
Kid, this is a miracle.
Okay, now, now, look at Sullivan's quest!
Hurry!
This is amazing!
It's like an illustration come to life!
What did the grown leave right?
A hero?
This farm is a miracle.
As is rhythm.
It may never grow dry.
These trees, the fruits they bear
incredible and delicious. If all the land is so plentiful, we could feed generations.
This planet is something special. It truly is. Tomorrow I shall head to the cave
north of here. At night it glows and shimmers, made of colors beyond the imagination.
I can't wait to see the wonders contained therein. I shall mark it on my map here
And?
Then there's nothing.
This is spectacular.
Okay, everyone, back into the pond.
Hurry, hurry, we don't want the board to see.
I told you, it's not...
No, well, who cares if it's just one...
This is big.
Hi, Juna.
She says hi.
She says hi!
So...
There are frogs...
And there are humans...
But there are like...
Like I think we saw goblins too?
Yeah, it's a fantasy world.
It just...
The fly eater-
Do I have to explain everything to you?
The French frog wrote a book, and in that book he reveals the location of amber shards that hold magic flies.
But he secretly erased the book to hide the shards from the bad guys
because when the fly eater comes he eats the fly which restores the planet which the bad
guys hate and it also restores the book which reveals the location of the next shard.
That way only the fly eater can truly know where the next shard is, restore the planet,
save the world, whatever.
Pretty simple.
I don't know it seems kinda complicated.
Grumble grumble.
What's your deal?
Nothing.
By Enora do you see now Mr. Sullivan?
Once the fly eater, you, collects the shards, Sullivan's quest will reveal itself and the
barren planet shall be restored.
This is what Degon Wee told us.
This is your destiny.
But what if I can't do it?
I'm not strong or tough or even all that smart.
Yes, that is true.
But by Anora, you are the fly eater.
No!
I mean, yes, maybe, I don't know, but no!
I'm just a frog.
Like Mama used to say, "A frog's a frog and a frog he shall be.
No harm in that, no harm indeed."
That's who I am, just a frog.
My child, so was de gon' we.
I know, I just...
I just...
I don't know.
I don't... I don't know.
Elton, let me talk to the kid.
Go ahead, I'll be staring.
This is crazy, Giancarlo.
I was just a student, like a few hours ago.
How can this all be true?
You shot magic out of your mouth a few hours ago too.
Now I'm scared I'm gonna vomit magic on somebody by accident.
What if I hurt someone?
I don't know, I was just flashing around the pond and I could have hurt someone just by...
Oh God...
Listen Sullivan...
If you go on this journey or not...
The board's gonna keep coming after you.
But why?
I didn't do nothing.
Neither did the Gromwe.
He found a miraculous planet full of unlimited resources with no inhabitants and wanted to
share it with others.
And look what happened to him.
But you could change that story, Sullivan.
You could change the meaning of his quest.
You could do a lot of good.
Well, I want to do good.
I know you do.
You've always been like that.
It's fucking irritating.
I always thought the board seemed mean, but I guess I never thought about how bad off most
folks are in Gun City.
I don't even know what people's lives are like throughout the rest of the planet.
There's enough stuff to go around, really, like the grown wee says.
I guess I should do something, shouldn't I?
If I can.
Sometimes you have to grow up kid. It's never on your own terms, trust me.
Just how it is.
Okay.
Seems like I got a big job to do.
People can't afford to wait for me to be ready.
You'll help me.
With all of this, right?
I'll do everything I can.
And you'll keep my mama safe?
Of course.
Well...
Um...
Alright, okay.
Alright.
Alright, there we go.
Okay.
That was, uh...
Alright, now let's take a look at the map that the Grand We drew.
That's the Crave Cave.
The ore veins in there were supposed to be the richest in the world, until it dried up a few centuries ago.
It was a mining tycoon, Twiggy Hancock. He was the culprit.
He disappeared along with the ore and all of his goblin workers.
So you think the shard is in that cave?
I'd say there's a good chance.
Then it is decided!
Tomorrow morning, I shall see you all. Sorry, I was just standing right next to you guys.
Yeah, it's whatever.
It's cool.
Sorry!
Don't worry about it.
You are the hope for all of us, Mr. Sullivan.
For both frog and man, and everyone in between.
I shall see you in the morning.
Good night, Mr. Sullivan.
And may Enora bless you and your quest.
Good night, Elder Ribbit.
Thanks.
Go mention it.
Why don't you get some rest tonight?
The Elder and the Signior Frogs got a bed for you in the citadel north of here.
I'll see you off in the morning too.
You're not coming with me?
There's a lot I have to do to make sure people don't find out what you're doing, Sullivan.
I'll be helping you in my own way.
You gotta do this quest on your own, or at least without me for now.
Okay. Alright.
Okay. Okay.
Giancarlo? You really think I can do this?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure.
Th-thanks.
Dat dat dat.
Well, goodnight Giancarlo.
Wait, Sullivan!
What?
Nothing.
Okay...
Good night, Sullivan.
(music)
Now that we got all that dumb lore out of the way
Caleb stopped his chit chatting. The boys can move on with
the story. Just not the way that they thought.
What, uh...
What...
What do you mean?
Oh, young Thomas!
Heh, heh, heh!
Your curious mind will be your downfall.
Meanwhile, back in Gun City...
*sad music*
*yawn*
Wow, another normal dream.
I love the big house I live in, my girl boss mom and my male feminist stepdad.
Better get ready for school.
Someone can now move me around using the directional buttons.
Oh, it's one of these things.
Can I play now, pe-
I didn't die, it's just a new character.
Maybe Cam should play as Belinda, because she's a girl.
BOOM!
But no you're not playing. Fine. Speaking of girls, how's Juna?
She's uh...
She's good.
She's good. That's nice.
Sounded like a pretty serious conversation you guys are having. I guess. Who cares? Just game.
Hey, honey up bright and early as always hey stepdad sure am you want some of these notorious
RBG pancakes I made they're shaped like her head
Sounds delicious, but no thanks stepdad. I'm all right. Hey more for me
Sullivan lives on Lane Street
He's also wanted for the murder of five Jollibee officers evading arrest and kidnapping more details on that as they arise
Something wrong, honey. You know you can tell me anything no stepdad. It's nothing you got it kiddo
I'm gonna get a move on but I'll see you tonight
Okay, have a great day, honey. Oh and for dinner tonight. I'm making Louis CK burgers so save some room for that
Hey Belinda, it's me your friend Rachel.
Did you see what happened last night?
The explosion on Lane Street?
Yeah, pretty exciting, huh?
I guess.
Usually the precog division stops that kind of thing before it can happen.
Well, time for class.
See you later Belinda.
Bye.
[music]
Time for attendance, as always, going by first name, starting with B, then jumping to S,
then proceeding as normal. Belinda Croaks?
Here.
Bullyfrog the Toad?
[toad sound]
[laughing]
Duh!
Wonderful. Sabrina?
Here.
Sasha?
Present.
Sally?
Here.
Other Sasha?
Present.
Hmm, I don't see Sullivan in his seat.
Saxophone?
You know how I roll, bitch.
[laughs] Saxophone.
Sullivan?
Sullivan the frog?
He probably got scared because yesterday I beat him up so bad.
Bully frog, everyone knows what actually happened.
No!
Well, no Sullivan. Hmm. That's his first ever absence.
That's right. Sullivan is never absent.
Something seems fishy.
So, what'd you guys talk about?
Uh, who?
You and Juna?
Uh, not much, just about your mom, mostly.
YOOOOOOHOOOOOO!
Hm, that's funny. You guys never talk about my mom.
Yeah, I was joking, you fucking idiot.
So, what'd you talk about?
I don't know, just, whatever. Can we focus on the game, please?
Thank you.
Well, class, today we're going to learn about Gunn City's geology.
There's all manner of substrate throughout E-Bomb,
But the Gun City landmass once had the richest deposit of ore on the whole planet.
Some say the ore would gleam in the night if you looked at it, have all manner of colours
(hot wash, my opinion) but nevertheless, impressive still.
That was until hundreds of years ago Twiggy Hancock, famed mining tycoon, nearly drained
the continent of all of its ore to the point that the board had to step in, which they
hate to do.
Perhaps an inevitability though, after all.
Ore can't last forever, can it?
Heh heh.
Well, that's it for today.
Don't forget to take your knowledge pill before you head home.
Now, all of you, get out.
GET OUT!
Bye, Belinda. See you tomorrow.
Bye.
I know I told Dad I'd head back for dinner,
but I have to check on Sullivan.
Fast Travel to Lame Street
Well, I'm on Lame Street.
Wonder what happened to Sullivan.
I hope he's alright.
My little hackers and Vestigoggles can see hidden clues that will help me here.
All I have to do is press Y and I can toggle on sleuth mode.
Great.
Now let's get looking.
Weird.
Weird, the officers here don't appear to be regular Jollibee officers.
What's this? Sullivan's homework? Why is it in the street?
Should I talk to these officers?
Maybe I should find another way.
Why don't we talk to them?
No, they're obviously setting this up so that we fight them if we do. There's probably another clue.
So we're afraid of a little honest conversation with some lovely officers of the law?
With people we'd maybe consider friends close friends even who wouldn't lie to us. What are you implying?
Okay, I'll just talk to them
Excuse me officers. I'm looking for my friend Sullivan. I think he lives on the street young lady
I'm gonna have to ask you to leave the premises, but sir you want to fight. I'm not a real cop
I will fucking ruin your life. You're not supposed to say that me. I don't give a fuck
I'm done being kept in the dark waiting on the boards every command. I'm gonna kill this kid right now
All right, you asked for it
Looks like a stun gun isn't going to cut it. How am I gonna take this guy down?
I know I can identify his weak spot with my little hacker scanner, and then I can target for extra damage
It'll only take a turn.
Analyzing enemy.
Enemy's weak spot is left leg.
Injured three days ago trying to close refrigerator with hip.
Slipping on Reader's Digest left on the ground.
Perfect.
Ooooooh, my left leg!
Don't mess with a Lil Hacker.
Level up!
Yeah!
Now, tell me, does Sullivan the Frog live here?
We were told he was speeding away on the bike with the ex-board operative John Carlo the Frog!
Oh no! Sullivan! I gotta find him!
Sorry, Stepdad. Those Louis C.K. burgers will have to wait.
I have to find my friend, even if it means leaving the city.
Hey, should we do something about that creepy kid standing over there?
The one who's been following that girl?
I don't care!
So, Sullivan was kidnapped. Can't exact my revenge if he's dead.
I'll get you Belinda, and once you lead me to Sullivan, I'll get you both.
You'll never embarrass me again!
Bullyfrog the Toad.
My name is the Nightmare Assassin.
God damn.
His name is dumb.
Like that's got to be like a translation thing from the original Japanese, right?
Wait...Cam?
Why don't you ask Caleb?
Uh...Caleb, what do you think?
I don't know, I don't know.
Maybe you should call Juna, maybe she knows.
Okay man, seriously, what's got your goose?
You got my goose!
If you want to exact your revenge, you can be of some assistance.
Come with me.
Rock and roll, Nightmare Assassin.
And now the boys will return to our protagonist at his pond, as their quarrel in real life
continues to heat up.
*yawns*
I'm starting to get
real uh...
what's the word?
*snaps fingers*
sleepy again.
Well, pry open your
peepers kid, I poured a
cup of mud just for this
*laughs*
Before I open your peepers kid, I poured a cup of hot scalded mud just for this occasion.
*Inhales*
*Groans*
Great.
*Music*
Well, I guess I'm off.
I'm sure I'm gonna miss this pond, Elder Ribbit.
It's been wonderful here, and I hope to be back soon.
I hope you are as well, Mr. Sullivan.
Farewell, and may it no longer guide you.
And you as well.
Thanks for saving me, Giancarlo, and helping me and all that.
I know you can't come with, but it means a lot that you're looking out for me and my mom.
Don't mention it, kid. What are cousins for?
Right. Just go collect those shots. I will. I'm off to the Crave Cave. Goodbye everyone.
Goodbye to the pond. Hello to adventure. Bye Solo Man. See you later. Bye Solo Man. Do
it Solo Man. Bye Solo Man. Alright. Back in the world map. Whew. It got kind of heavy
in there. Been long. Guess I better equip my new gear. And check my map just to see where
to go. Great! Alright. Let's get going. Here we- oh. God damn it! Every three steps it's
a- alright. Well I guess this is a good opportunity to try my new Nightbringer Blast ability.
Wow, that's cool!
Can't wait to try it on even more enemies!
Dude, stop being a pussy.
Just say what you're thinking.
Why don't you just be honest with me and Pete?
I don't care.
Well you should!
Why should he when there's nothing to care about?
So you admit you care about nothing.
Okay, guys, that's enough.
We're in the cave now!
Oh man, this place is scary.
It doesn't look anything like it does in DeGroenweesburg.
I didn't know it would be this dark.
What happened to all the colors?
Reflecting light and gleaming from the ore.
I guess all the ore is gone.
I should have stocked up on more items before I left.
Hey!
Ah!
Why are you yelling?
You scared me!
Yeah, well, that's because I'm always sneaking around.
You know, you could have really damaged my ears.
I'm sorry.
Ah, don't worry about it.
Actually, well, back in school, the recruiters, they were scouting me to join in the special
forces because there were these neighbor kids and they always threw firecrackers at me.
and they were really impressed at how good I was at hearing them
and so I could take damage from extreme sounds
A guy like you probably couldn't hurt me anyways, no offense
Wait, you're not a girl, right?
No
Okay, good, cause girls are actually way worse
because if there's crap like Justin Bieber or the Kardashians
they can screech so loud
Alright
Huh?
Oh, okay, I...
No, you go ahead.
I'm Johnny Tench.
I'm Sullivan.
Okay.
So, are you gonna buy anything?
What?
Basically, I have to sell a bunch of crap all over the world in order to earn enough money to buy a sweet guitar
because my old one broke because I'm always getting beat up at school.
Or maybe I can get my mom to sell me something nice for her birthday.
Oh.
Yeah.
Look, if you're not interested, I don't really care.
There's like a thousand goblins who come here and buy crap for me,
so you can just keep walking if you're too poor.
It doesn't really matter.
No, no, I do. I actually, I would love to buy some stuff from you.
Wait, really?
Okay, just be quick about it.
Sorry if I'm being rude.
Uh, it's okay.
I'd like to have three health potions.
Okay, yeah, that's uh, 150 tokens, please.
Great.
Um, would you by any chance want to buy some monster bones?
Yeah, sure! I'll buy those for 17 tokens a piece.
Wow, great!
Yeah, they're not for me though, because there's a lot of goblins in here who always try and buy bones off me.
They do all kinds of weird crap with them.
Oh. Okay.
Yeah, basically they work for this weird guy who lives down here.
They call him Twiggy Hancock. He's like some kind of tycoon or something.
Twiggy Hancock still alive?
Hmm...
They wanted to make me a tycoon but I said no because I gotta sell my wares.
Anyways, are you done?
Uh, yes.
Thanks Johnny.
I hope to see you in other odd places so I can buy some stuff in a pinch.
Okay.
Bye Sullivan!
Bye.
Okay, I'm gonna sneak away now so don't whine.
I'm not looking.
Okay, good because I've actually been betrayed a lot of times,
Especially back at school when I was betrayed by my band because they thought that I was gonna be...
Well, they knew I was gonna be the front man and they hated me because I was now rocked on too hard so they betrayed me and...
Great. Now I got some potions.
This cave won't be so scary any longer.
Hopefully there are fewer random battles in here than in the overworld.
*sigh*
Well, this guy looks tough. Better use my frog arts.
Oh man, that didn't seem to go so well.
How do I beat this guy?
I said, how do I beat this guy?
This guy is clearly resistant to Sullivan's regular frog arts, yet he's the Lightbringer one we got earlier.
Okay, that's it.
Oh, come on, man, it's just a joke.
You know how much I love figuring out monsters' weaknesses, and you know that I'm sensitive
Specifically to people making fun of me for knowing the weaknesses of monsters.
Especially in caves!
Uh, news to me, I thought you just hated phone calls.
I am going to attack.
I would love to see you try to attack me.
Which one should I pick?
Goddammit, Pat, there's only one other one!
It says "Lightfinger Blast, good against monsters who favor the dark."
We're in a cave!
Either start thinking or let me play!
I mean, Pete!
Come on!
Jeez, man, take it easy.
Yeah, take it easy, Ken.
Never! Not when my friends betray me!
Oh my god!
And then the next battle was with 10 slime things and that took 10 minutes cause, well,
you don't kill one of the slime things after a certain number of turns, it becomes like
two slime things and it's like a whole thing, whole reveal and they didn't buy any antidotes either so
it's all of them was taken poison damage.
Yeah, why is uh, Cam so mad at Caleb?
Oh well I uh, I'm not sure young Tommy Bahama.
Seems there's some gentlemanly dispute going on.
Hard to tell, but perhaps if we read more of the story...
Well, I mean, yeah, but that stuff just, you know, it seems all so...
petty.
Especially compared to my...
you know...
my deadly...
terminal illness...
and the forces trying to turn me deviant.
Yeah.
He's right.
Can you guys make up already?
Well, I didn't do anything except to take a call from my wife, Juna.
I know that wasn't Juna, okay? That was Price.
I know something's going on.
Nothing is going on!
Here, look at my call history.
You can edit that, I'm not stupid.
Yes you are stupid!
Perhaps it is, my little baby Thomas.
But, maybe we don't know the full story yet.
Perhaps Caleb betrayed Cameron in some way.
One which we don't yet understand.
So you think I'd just start some solo career and not tell you guys
that I'd abandoned us at the height of our podcast?
I didn't before, but now I'm not really so sure, man.
You are fucking loco.
Yeah? Then pinky swear?
Absolutely not.
Pinky swear right now, pinky swear on Patch's grave
What?
That you wouldn't betray us
How dare you
Why don't they, uh, just talk it out, you know
Just grab a... coffee or...
Lot lot lot a because people are
Cheap and steamy
So they need to be controlled
Because they will otherwise resort to their base instance. All right, that's enough Caleb
pinky swear right now
Do it. I don't want to do it now
Fine cam
Cam okay
I'm sorry
It's okay
Sorry, too
All right, are we good?
Yep
Yeah, that's more like it
All right
So is that
Then what happened well, this is it the end of the cave
Southerman's quest, it's glowing. Maybe the shard is near.
The shard is near, frog.
Twiggy, Hancock.
The one and the same.
Hand over the amber shard. You don't understand its power.
That's rich, almost as rich as me. I know exactly where the shard is. It's been mine for hundreds
of years. It keeps me alive, sustains my hunger for ore. It's my tool for conquest. My maze
of achieving all this wealth and power in the world.
And you?
You're just a insignificant little frog who gets lost on his way to Lillipad.
You hoppity scum.
Hey!
That's a frog slur!
Yeah, so what?
Goblins, attack!
The shard is mine for all that!
Ah!
That hurt!
Go my goblins!
Attack!
The shard is mine for all this!
Ah!
That hurt!
Go my goblins!
Attack!
Here I go!
Hi-ya!
Darn, he's tough!
Oh-ra-gobby!
Ah!
He's folding me up!
Oh no, my speed fell!
Goblins, go!
No, they get to attack again now!
Ah! He's folding me up! Oh no, my speed fell!
Goblins, go!
No, they get to attack again now!
Ah! Oh no, I'm in trouble!
Man, how do I win? I fucking hate this guy!
Pete, please let me play. Please!
No dude, only when I die! Those are the rules!
Hey, come on man, you're being a total blockhead!
Just let cam play. All right fine
Thanks, buddy. Don't mention it. Okay. So first Sullivan needs to take a potion
Then we have to use the multi attack to take out both goblins at once
They're not that strong. So it should take them down in one hit plus will chip away at Twiggy
Easy now, he'll probably use a turn to summon more goblins rather than do his full attack
It might bring a blast!
Ah! Damn you!
That's it! Here, Bashard! I command you!
Uh oh!
With the power of the shard, I shall continue to drain all the orm from this world.
And with my goblin army, I'll be unstoppable!
CRAAAAAA-
He looks like shit.
In the second phase, they always do.
Now, try this!
I am Twinkie Hancock, master of all, lord of the minds!
I am God!
No you're not, you're just a failed businessman who's in way over his head.
Melinda, what are you doing here?
What do you think?
I'm saving your behind.
Thanks Melinda.
Oh my god, shut up!
Shut up!
His armor's really tough.
Shut up! Shut up!
His armor's really tough. I'm having a lot of trouble breaking through it.
You can't just fight hard, Sullivan. You gotta fight smart, too.
That's what my dad always said. I'll scan this joker.
Analyzing enemy.
Weak spot can be found in his sternum from poor goblin craftsmanship.
If hit hard enough, could make him disassemble.
Now we're talking. Hi-ya!
Oh! That hurt! Take this!
Ow! Belinda!
Tch, he is tough.
Belinda, wait! Close your eyes.
Imagine your happy place.
We don't have time for that, Sullivan.
No, trust me. Close your eyes and picture a pond or a big breakfast or a...
Pushing someone out a window and watching them hit the pavement.
What?
[Growling]
What was that? I just shot some kind of magic out of my eyes.
That's your frog eye. You're an eye caster.
Wow, so awesome!
Now to finish him off.
Buster mop, go!
Ooh, hell yeah!
Let's go!
No, no!
We did it!
I just wanted to suck up all of you in the world.
And become a huge guy made of metal.
Or something. Or be super rich with the metal.
Oh, come on man. I don't know.
Oh no!
Thanks for coming to my rescue again.
It's no problem Sullivan, but what are you doing out here and what was that I just did?
I promise I'll explain everything, but first I need to take that shard.
Woah, Sullivan, you're peeing your pants.
I don't know why that keeps happening.
Huh, the dream world again.
This is your power, Sullivan.
Your quest.
The organism demands it.
New frog are unlocked.
Sullivan, look!
The cave!
Wow!
It's restored!
The ore, it's returned!
It's so beautiful, all the colors!
Sullivan, what is going on?
Yes, Sullivan's quest has more in it!
In here, there is enough ore to sustain a small city alone.
Once more as I chip away at it and then apply heat, they all grow again.
Like a magical plant or something.
Imagine what we could do with this.
We could build galaxies for people to live in.
Wow, I can't believe it.
Sullivan, I did come all the way out here to save you.
Ok, ok, I'll explain.
Sullivan explains it to her.
Whoa.
Yeah, I know.
So do you have to do this alone?
I don't think so.
I mean, the grown weed didn't. He had his companions, Belandella and the other guy, Rapard or whatever.
Well then, why don't I join you?
Really? You really mean that?
Yeah, why not? Is there anything better than going on an adventure?
No, you know what, there sure isn't.
That's right. So where are we headed next?
Well, according to Sullivan's quest, next we're headed to...
Follow them, and be sure to move quietly.
Obviously!
Who the fuck do you think I am?
I'm Bully Frog the Bad Guy!
Now that was a doozy.
Well,
I'm glad we resolved the underlying issue between you two,
and won't have to deal with anything like that again.
Yeah. Same.
Anyway, I'm gonna go lie down and look at my hands.
But, let's play again soon?
Definitely.
Of course.
Alright, see you guys.
Later, Caleb. Sorry for not trusting you.
It's okay, man. It happens. Take it easy.
What would Patches do?
Were he alive?
Hey Caleb, I'm back in your apartment.
I'm here to kill you.
Me too.
GET OUT!
Okay, bye.
Alright, that was pretty good.
I liked it when they killed the bad guy.
Was pretty cool, huh?
I hope those podcasters find a way to get along.
Oh my sweet little Thomas.
The thing about Westerners is that they have no sense of community, no sense of family to
one another.
I wouldn't hold out too much hope for that.
Oh, okay.
Well, would you look at the time.
Quite late.
You should get to bed my little, little Thomas Begg.
You're gonna need it if you're gonna combat that illness you got.
Sounds right.
Will you read me, podcasters playing video games tomorrow too, Uncle Jake?
I feel like my mind is growing stronger and...
Cool...
Kinder.
Of course, man.
Oh, God, keep kinder.
Of course, my little sweet nephew.
Get some sleep now, okay?
Alright.
Good night.
[laughing]
Another chapter in the bag and I'm fucking hooting and hollering.
And then I remember I gotta log my hours for the day in the Gijon Wii computer.
I tab over for "artist" and then "podcaster/novelist", put in 15 hours, and promptly fall asleep.
It doesn't matter how many hours I put in, really.
I wake up 45 minutes later, though, because of that hard thing I've been ignoring, and I feel completely recharged.
Ready to record another one.
But before I could even do that, my phone started ringing again.
I start freaking out, it's like, "It's my wife, it's my wife, it's my wife, it's finally, it's finally the day, it's finally the day she's gonna...
He was gonna leave me, but...
It was so much worse.
It was Caleb.
[Music]
Hey honey, it's your stepdad. Your mother and I were wondering where you were. Just give me an update when you can, cause I trust you. Girl power. Ha! Pussy grabs back.
Oh, also, I read more about Louis C.K. I don't know if he's such a great male feminist.
I am very sorry for making you those burgers dozens and dozens and dozens of times.
So yeah, anyway, call me back when you get the chance.
We love you, and we'll see you soon, I'm sure.