"Uh, last time on Sullivan Quest..."
That first chapter felt real good.
And I turn into some lobby.
I realize it's new Webster Hall.
It's fucking Caleb.
"You got... isn't it... it's... it... uh..."
I press record.
"What are we gonna do for fun this evening?"
"Well, Thomas, I thought we'd keep reading the Podcasters Play Video Games book."
Why do they keep bringing up... patches?
That's not important.
Sullivan Quest?
Sure.
Anyway, Mr. Sullivan, have you ever heard of Sullivan de Grandouille?
So the old French Sullivan explored the planet a long time ago, saw that it was good.
The bad people didn't like that, so they made the planet bad, killed French Sullivan and his frog friends.
When de Grandouille sealed the pond, he also sealed one of the seven amber shards of Anura in here as well.
well. Within each shard is a fossilized fly that contains the power to restore the planet.
The shards, however, are unbreakable to everything except for the Fly Eater.
The key to finding the shards is in Sullivan's quest, which, as we know, was stolen by the
Board. That is, until your cousin John Carlo stole it back. Myself and the Council of Señor
Our frogs had been scrying the ephemeral pool, searching for the fly eater.
We saw it could be this, so live on the frog.
That's my name.
The French frog wrote a book, and in that book he reveals the location of amber shards
that hold magic flies, but he secretly erased the book to hide the shards from the bad guys
because when the fly eater comes, he eats the fly, which restores the planet, which the
bad guys hate, and it also restores the book, which reveals the location of the next shard.
That way, only the fly eater can truly know where the next shard is, restore the planet,
the world. That's the grave cave. The ore veins in there were supposed to be the richest in
the world, until it dried up a few centuries ago. It was a mining tycoon, Twiggy Hancock.
He was the culprit. He disappeared along with the ore, and all of his goblin workers. Meanwhile,
back in Gun City. Well, no Sullivan. Hm. That's his first ever absence. That's right. Sullivan
is never absent. Something seems fishy. Sorry stepdad, those Louis C.K. burgers will have
to wait. I have to find my friend, even if it means leaving the city. So, Sullivan was
kidnapped. Can't exact my revenge if he's dead. Bullfrog. I'll get you Belinda, and once you
lead me to Sullivan, I'll get you both. Bullfrog the toad. My name is the nightmare assassin.
If you want to exact your revenge, you can be of some assistance.
I'm Johnny Tetch.
I'd like to have three health potions.
Okay, yeah, that's 150 tokens, please.
Can you guys make up already?
Well, I didn't do anything except to take a call from my wife, Juna.
I know that wasn't Juna, okay? That was Price.
So you think I'd just start some solo career and not tell you guys?
Well, they, uh, talk it out, you know.
Well, this is it. The end of the cave.
Twiggy Hancock.
The one and the same. Goblins, attack!
I am God!
No you're not. You're just a failed businessman who's in way over his head.
Melinda! What are you doing here?
What do you think? I'm saving your behind.
No!
We did it!
Sullivan, look! The cave!
Wow! It's restored!
Why don't I join you?
Really?
You really mean that?
Yeah, why not? Is there anything better than going on an adventure?
Well, according to Sullivan's quest, next we're headed to...
Follow them, and be sure to move quietly.
Obviously. Who the fuck do you think I am?
I'm Bullyfrog the Bad Guy.
I'm glad we resolved the underlying issue between you two,
and won't have to deal with anything like that again.
Before I could even do that, my phone started ringing again.
It was Caleb.
Hey buddy, how's it going?
Hope you and the family are doing alright.
I'm, um, I'm gonna be in town for the next week or so.
And I was thinking we should get dinner.
Tomorrow night work for you?
Writing Solomon Quest was starting to get to me.
I mean, don't get me wrong, it still felt better than a boxy blowjob to crank that shit out, but...
To write it at the level that satisfied me, you know, an artist,
demands a significant amount of time and energy,
more than I'd spent on anything in years.
With only a week to get this done, I was panicking.
I didn't pick up when Caleb called, but I listened to his voicemail after.
I was shocked by the invitation.
"We have this great restaurant in Midtown that doesn't even require a badge or chip to get in after hours.
Real relaxed place, pre-G holdover. I'll drop a pin."
I'll drop a pin.
I swore I'd never talk to these guys again.
I swore they were dead to me.
That their betrayal was too vast and varied and painful.
For me to even consider the idea of perhaps, even the possibility of perhaps maybe, and very very unlikely at that potential, even think about the conceptuality of perhaps talking with them maybe.
But instead I got out my phone and ordered a Palantir armored pallet lift and headed
to Midtown.
Still, the matter at hand was finishing Solving Quest.
So in the car on the way there, I gave Price a call.
Hey man.
Hey, come on, stop.
I don't...
My Mandarin's not that good.
No, mine's not that good either, but you really should brush up on it, because you can swear
at Chinese waitresses.
Right?
I told you.
Yeah, no, it sounds like a lot of fun, Price.
You can swear at Chinese waitresses, right?
I told you.
What's up?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, of course. Yeah, obviously, yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
Um, so just a little more time.
Another week on top of this one.
Another week?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Well, so you know what, Patgy?
You called me before the deadline this time, right?
Instead of after.
Mm-hmm.
And, uh, as much as I'd love to see your growth and to hear that you're making progress, um,
I think you should just finish it.
And I'm, I don't think I'm gonna, I don't think I'm gonna be able to swing it for more time,
right?
that's in the cards this time.
- Come on, Bryce, that's bullshit.
- Yeah?
That's bullshit?
- Okay, fine.
- Okay, so there you go, right?
That was easy.
And just again, just anything that is even a little bit,
oh, hi, hello!
Sorry, all my friends came and I'm going to be doing cocaine
with all of them, my friends.
Okay. - Yeah.
- So yeah, just turn in anything
And, uh, just between you and me, it doesn't even have to be good.
Uh, it definitely doesn't have to be a masterpiece, right?
Just any file that I can open on my fucking laptop is gonna be just perfect, right?
Yep, I got it.
Okay, I'm waiting on that email.
Alright, alright.
See you, take it easy, folks.
Why don't you come by around 7, we can catch up.
No need to call back if you don't want to.
I know things ended kinda weird for us.
I got out the car and walked across the street to the spot Caleb wanted me to go.
My mind started racing.
You know, Caleb and I were pretty close towards the end.
We were the first to get married and settle down, so...
We had that in common, that, um...
Domesticity.
That shared, uh...
Perspective on life, in some ways.
None of that meant shit, I guess, in the end.
He was a road comic through and through, after all.
No ties to nobody.
Just jokey, jokey jokes.
It's always just jokes.
Look, I love this place personally, so I'll be there regardless.
I walked into the Benihana and the waiter told me that Kayla was in the back.
I made my way past the hibachi counters avoiding airborne slop
and looked for the shiny bald dome of my former friend,
reflecting bog inflorescence amongst gaudy decor.
You show up, great.
If you don't, hey, that's life.
Miss you, man.
Hope to see you soon.
I found him.
No shit.
Caleb?
I didn't think you'd show.
Me neither.
Well it's good to see you man. Come sit down.
I'll stand.
Okay.
Well, you look good.
No I don't.
How'd you know I was in New York?
Wild guess.
Also, I saw you at my show.
You did?
Well yeah, you started screaming and convulsing on the floor about betrayal.
And someone named Tina and Price and then security came and you ran out.
That's not how I remember it.
And maybe that's the issue here.
The way we remember things, you know?
I don't follow.
How's the wife?
Good. Fine.
And the kids?
Good, yeah.
That's great to hear, buddy.
You know, childcare in this province...
And here, look at the menu.
I recommend steak if you're getting hibachi, which you gotta get it.
But yeah, childcare.
It's tricky because you send these kids to the daycare, right?
Providence provides it, great, sure.
But then they come back and they speak Mandarin, which...
Also good, but then I don't speak it.
You?
Not really.
Exactly.
I'm trying to learn it over the next couple months.
Hoping it helps me with a new special.
Why did you invite me here?
Let's order first, okay?
How are you doing today?
My name is Lu Shi Xin and I'll be your server for this evening.
What can I do for you, gentlemen?
Is that your real name?
Blue Shi Shen?
Why yes sir it is!
Crazy, see?
Just crazy.
No offense, it's a lovely name.
We're pre-Xi so we're just not used to it.
Of course sir.
I think we're ready to order though.
Right Patches?
Yeah.
Great!
What will you be having?
I'll have the Yakisoba to start,
then the Hibachi Steak,
and a Bud Light.
I'll take a bowl of rice and a Mike's Heart.
Alright.
Would you like to take a seat as well sir?
Nope.
Okay, great. The chef will be right over for your hibachi.
Watching your figure? Pretty much anything outside nutrition supplements fucks up my stomach.
So you're just full of supplements now?
It's easier.
Do you remember when we were in Tokyo and Pat ordered...
Pat ordered a... what looked like a live squid?
And he started crying?
Yeah. Yeah.
and now we can even go to tokyo middle open up it's just until the men and men
are dealt with
yet they have enough actual military guys now you know
i don't know when it'll end
the fuck anyway it's useless fight
hi my name is matthew and i'll be a chef for this evening hell yeah now we're talking
watch when he does a volcano thing okay
(music playing)
Look, can you just tell me what this is about?
I got a lot of stuff going on and this is...
Ugh, it's like whatever.
Alright, fine.
But you have to promise you don't do whatever it is you did at New Webster, okay?
I don't even know what I did there, so I guess I can't promise anything.
And what do I owe you?
Exactly. What promise do I owe you?
Man, see, I don't know what you're talking about.
The betrayal!
Come on, man.
The betrayal you guys fucked me. No we didn't nobody fucking coordinated effort to
That's no that's not what happened is this the Steve Harvey thing more than that you know it patches patches
Please just calm don't you tell me to calm down look look look okay, okay?
Let's just
Do you want to talk about?
the betrayal
Don't know
Okay, well let me just say what I was gonna say and then if you're feeling it we can talk about it, okay?
Okay
Fine
Good
so
How do you feel about Vegas? Neutral
right
How about the four of us?
performing in Vegas
How about the first ever podcast residency in Vegas?
You're kidding. No, I'm not.
Caesars Palace Presents Podcast About This.
The first ever podcast residency.
I think I can make it happen for us.
I was just gonna ask Cam and Pat, but seeing you drool and curse on the floor of a theater
reminded me that you were also in the group.
I think it could be really fun, man.
We could do it as long as it makes us money.
I don't know, my family is...
They can come, or they can stay here. We can figure that out.
I'm in the middle of working on something too, so...
The audio novel? Price told me.
You can finish that up and then do the residency.
I'm not going to be able to put everything together right away, and you can work on that from anywhere.
Sure.
Look man, I know this is a good opportunity for you. I'm not stupid.
So what do you say?
I can't do it.
You don't mean that.
I won't do it.
Exactly.
Fuck you.
Man, what is your problem?
I mean, like, if you don't want to do it because of this or that, but like, I don't even know what you're mad about.
Nobody can figure it out.
It's because nobody understands it!
Yes, nobody understands it. I'm giving you an opportunity, and you're acting like a freak.
I don't need your opportunity.
Yes, you do. All this shit is painfully obvious. You're a fucking disaster.
Fuck you, fuck the podcast, and fuck this restaurant. I'm out.
You have my number if you change your mind, asshole.
And June is fine, thanks for asking.
What are you looking at?
Keep flippin' the meat around.
I got a pal and left home as fast as I could.
I should've known he'd lure me into something like that.
No apology, no recognition, no nothing.
Just wants to talk about it like an asshole
Like an asshole who doesn't know what he did
They all did what they did
The thing they did the thing that they that they did that thing
I pressed record
Good evening young Tannis
Sorry, Uncle Jake. I don't mean to make all these
disgusting noises around you.
My illness...
Your illness is no reflection on you, Thomas. Whether you fight to defeat this disease,
well, that is the measure of a man.
But I'm just a little boy, Uncle Jake.
A boy is merely the first stage of becoming a man. You must
of yourself beyond your own life. For sure. Well you for sure right my little Timmy Tommy.
Now where were we in Podcasters Play Vigi Games?
Hey Pete, where's Caleb?
He's out with Price.
He'll be here later.
Oh, alright.
I brought Sullivan Quest.
You can start this time if you want.
Obviously I do.
Alright, get it going.
I'm uh, gonna get a fizzy drink.
You want one?
I'll have a fizzy drink.
[MUSIC]
Come on, Sully, what does Sullivan Quest say?
Where do we go next?
Well it says...
I see on the horizon a lush and magnificent forest.
I wonder what kinds of wildlife grows there.
I wonder what miracles will await me further on this wonderful, glorious planet deep under.
I must follow the grazing patterns of the magnificent animals to find my way there.
It will be a long journey, but worth it, I'm sure.
Well there aren't any animals around here.
They're pretty much all either dead or penned up.
Hmm, well is there a forest nearby?
Don't you ever pay any attention in school, Sullivan?
Not really, but I try really, really hard.
Well nearby is the No-No Woods.
According to what we learned in school, it's always been barren.
But I'm thinking based on how amazing the Crave Cave is and was, that's another lie from
Gun City.
Well let's head on over there.
There's a town nearby too.
No no Hamlet, I'm sure we could go there while we search for the amber in the forest.
Let's hop on my little hacker's Vespa and get going.
Whoa, you have a Vespa?
Of course!
What, you think I'd walk over here?
There's dozens of dangerous monsters.
What dope would walk through all of this?
Definitely not me.
Let's go!
Alright, I'll just select Vespa in the inventory now that I'm on the world map.
Alright!
Vespa controls are up to accelerate, back to brake, and then turn left and right with the
shoulder buttons. While on the vehicle you won't encounter any random battles.
Wow, neat!
Now let's get driving! The Gun City Super Highway is just a bit east of here. Let's take it to
to Nono Hamlet.
It'll be a lot easier to get to Nono this way.
Definitely better than staying in the world map.
With all those monsters.
Uh oh, we got commuters headed to Gun City for work.
(car honks)
- Boy, you have butt too dry
'cause you're farting all over the road.
- Sorry!
- Piece of cake.
Uh-oh, here comes some more.
- I got fizzy drinks.
- Wait, Pete, did you know this game has multiplayer?
- It does?
- Yeah, the instruction manual says
it can be up to four players for battles.
- Whoa, instruction manual?
- Dude, this is sick.
Okay, plug in a controller.
You can control Belinda.
No way, no.
No, I have to beat Sullivan, I'm not a girl.
Okay, but if I'm controlling out of combat it's going to default to me controlling Sullivan
and any new party member not assigned to another player.
Just hand me the controller when the battle starts then.
Done.
Okay, fine.
Belinda's probably too complicated for you anyway.
She has a lot of utility moves through her Lil Hacker's augments.
I'm not a girl.
There's too many commuters!
What do we do?
Wait, Sullivan! Didn't you unlock a new frog art when you swallowed the fly in the Crave Cave?
Why don't you try using it on those commuters?
Oh yeah! Good idea!
Sonic Blast!
Whoa, it's working! The commuters are parting!
Way to go, Sully!
You can use that frog art out of combat when it gets real congested.
Cool!
Wait...
Who is that?
Is that...
Well, well, well. What do we have here?
Sullivan the Clawed and Belinda the...
The...
Belinda the fucking stupid.
What do you want, Bullyfrog?
What any well-adjusted amphibian wants.
REVENGE!
Good luck while fighting on the road.
Vroom!
Bleh!
Ugh!
I don't remember Bullyfrog having that attack.
Guess he learned some new tricks since we last ran into him.
Thanks to the Nightmare Assassin, I'm really strong!
And that's how I'll kill you!
The Nightmare Assassin?
That's the guy you told me about who works for the board!
Exactly, the very one!
Well let's not mess around then.
Agreed.
Pete, you're up.
I'm just gonna use the frog art.
No, don't waste frog power!
When it's my round I can scan him and then we can see if physical attacks or arts are best.
Come on, just let me try it!
Fine, do whatever you want.
I am Sullivan.
I'm not bringing plans!
AHH! What the hell was that?
Told you!
Frog art magic guys!
AHH!
Oh man! How did you guys figure out how to do such cool stuff?
You're not gonna stop us Bully Frog!
What is that?
Bully Frog what did you do?
I didn't do anything!
Woah woah woah!
M-m-m-m-monster on the road!
What the heck is that?
Some kind of lion, fox, pelican, turtle, bear, tiger?
I can't make sense of it!
Looks incredible!
Phew! It's gone.
Now, back to our fight!
Retreat for now, Bloody Frog. I have the information I need.
But... what? But I almost got them!
Enough, Trader! Fade back!
You'll fight them another day!
Ugh... fine.
Well, it seems I have more important things to do than waste my time with you losers.
Have fun on your little road trip.
It'll be your last.
Man, that was close.
Look! The town is just up ahead!
Thank goodness, now I can use some rest.
So this is No No Hamlet.
Yep, it was a lumber town back when the Gun City civilization was just settling on the planet.
Of course, with the mass production of synthetic wood, there's no need for whatever scant lumber
remains. Cool! Now it's an industrial lower middle class cyber slum. Some people have cell phones and
cars but do they have heat? Only 47% according to my little hackers demographic enumerator.
There's a frog folk population of roughly 1.2%. The rest are humans or human adjacent. No non
folk races. Okay. And the famous no no woods completely dead looms nearby. A sorry sight.
Also I downloaded a map for us to use with my little hackers map downloading program.
Let's head to the interrest. All right. Let's go. Oh, I also have my little hackers sand
and my little hacker's USB charger,
my little hacker's glasses,
my little hacker's flashlight,
my little hacker's shoes,
- Pat, pick up your phone, come on.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- I mean Pete.
- My little hacker's gun.
- Yeah.
Hey.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, we're at cams.
Yeah, okay.
So what are you wearing?
That was Caleb.
He said keep playing without him, he'll be over here in a bit.
Big news apparently.
Great.
Pardon me, I didn't see you there, little frog.
Oh, that's alright.
Have a nice life.
Wait, wait, wait, please allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Light and Red.
I'm Sullivan.
Nice to meet you.
And you are a frog, no?
Yeah, frog folk.
This is most excellent.
You see, sort of an Irish scientist who specializes in helping animals like yourself.
Well, I'm not exactly an animal.
As semantics, you're unique.
You have an important quality.
Ah, and who is this?
Another froggy.
Mm-hmm.
Well, I see I've taken up too much of your time.
But if you ever wish to talk with me about...
science...
You'll find me in my laboratory.
Congrad students!
Toodaloo, froggy!
Goodbye! Goodbye, grad students!
Wow, first person we met here and he seemed real nice.
Not so sure about that, Sully. In any case, let's head to the inn.
Wait, this town seems cool. Go talk to some people.
No, we should rest up at the inn. No reason to talk to NPCs here, probably.
Maybe there is. I don't know, I'm just saying.
Hi there, welcome to the No-No Hamlet Hotel. Would you like a room?
Two rooms, please.
Wonderful. That's one room with two beds and no bathrooms.
Did you want a treasure chest in your room?
Uh, s-sure, I guess.
Great, let me just put that in there, the system.
Can we please have a bathroom?
Hey, trust me pal, you don't even want a bathroom.
All kinds of strange noises have been coming out of the plumbing lately.
What do you mean?
Look, speculation is above my pay grade, man.
Aren't you the innkeeper?
Innkeeper?
Man, it's a hotel, I just work the desk.
Okay, and you're all set.
That'll be five tokens.
Have a great stay.
Alright.
Should we head to the No No Woods then?
Sounds like a plan.
Oh look!
Some kind of leader of the town is giving a speech.
Now as the mayor, which is a kind of leader of the town, it is my job to understand what
is going on in No-No Hamlet.
And from this here vantage point I can very well see that times are tough.
And things haven't been going so well, and there are no jobs, no future, and it's one
of the worst possible times to be alive and sentient in our town's history.
I hate being sentient!
Oh, this town has already damned that boy!
Oh, that sounds weird!
I gotta make that commute to Gun City one more time.
I am gonna utilize some kind of weapon on just about everyone.
Hey now, cut that out or we'll have the Gun City secret police here.
Now I understand your pain.
Like I said, as the mayor it is my job to understand how bad everything is.
But it is also my job as mayor if you'd let me finish to make things better.
[Groans]
And things will be better soon, thanks to a recent addition to No-No Hamlet.
Our esteemed guest resident, famed scientist coming all the way from Gun City,
Dr. Leiden Dredd and his wonderful research team.
That's a pathetic, quiet student, uh, servants.
Not wonderful research team.
It's that guy we bumped into.
Dr. Dredd and his servants have been here for the past few weeks analyzing our wounds,
And they have come to the conclusion that we are a prime candidate for a massive injection of capital,
courtesy of the board.
The board!
And this capital, along with Dr. Dredd's ingenious experiments,
will be used to revitalize No-No Woods back to its semi-adequate glory of yesteryear.
But I'll let Dr. Dredd speak for himself.
Thank you, Mayor Sherman.
And, uh, guten tag, No-No Hamlet.
I've been on scientists for over 30 years specializing in the field of biological phenomenology and eugenics in air quotes
My work has done wonders for the millions who live in gun city
And I am quite thrilled to provide the same benefits to your lovely hand by experimenting on the bizarre
brilliant energies
emanating from your nano volts.
What experiments are you doing?
I'm glad you asked
Let me show you just a fraction of my work. You see our analysts picked up some
Fascinating energy coming from your vultures and we've set to work on replicating it
Here grad student bring out the Venus milk truck
Hey, that's a plant with boobs
Others to be perfectly pedantic and a venus fly trap for the immortal.
You see there is a massive potential to create all manner of creatures with just a little bit of ingenuity and a smidgen of radical reappraisal of what constitutes life.
See here, a coochie coochie coo, a coochie coochie coo.
There's milk in the boil!
Here, try some of this milk.
That's good!
Hey, I don't give an ass!
The foods will soon be full of these hybrid creatures, never before seen on Ebor.
And you, Nuno Hamlet, will supply the city, Gond City, with delicacies.
And they will supply you with ooters and ooters of tokens.
I shall restore this land and wrest industry, progress, and tourism from its ancient loins
and rightly grant these benefits to your esteemed population.
While here, my team and I have created enough Venus Milk Trucks for everyone on the house
courtesy of the Board.
Isn't that wonderful?
Now you all see that with Dr. Dredd's help, No-No Hamlet will be a burgeoning locale.
Dr. Dredd, I would like to preemptively give you a medal for the contributions you'll most certainly be making to No-No Hamlet,
as a show of good faith and fulfillment of a contractual agreement with the board.
Hmm. Well, he's talking about restoring the land, making the town a better place. Maybe he's not so bad.
I don't know. Something still feels off, Sully.
Remember, this is the board we're talking about.
I suppose so.
Now let me just find this medal to put around your neck.
Well, it seems I've misplaced it.
No, you haven't!
Oh, it's the mayor's kid.
Yes, it is I, Indio Parsley.
I've stolen your medal, a symbol of corporate greed and obsequiousness.
Then, in a further symbolic gesture, I use the ribbon from the metal to tie myself to
this tree, which you will never chop down.
Plus, I have released all the animals from captivity, including the injured ones.
And I won't stop doing any of these things until our town is free from this corporate
stew.
I told you, no one is chopping down that tree.
The wounded animals-
I will not answer to that name, father! It's bad vibes!
Doctor, just know that you and your team, your servants, have been awarded a medal and that I'll have a replacement made soon.
And this town does appreciate your efforts and the wealth you can bring it.
And I do apologize for the interruption of my foolish but well-intentioned son.
Of course, of course, I understand the rebelliousness of you.
I remember those days of mine own, trying new experiments that nobody would try.
Being laughed out of lecture halls by small minded cretins who didn't understand my ideas.
I hope your son and I can find common ground one day.
After all, we seem to share a love of the planet and what it can provide.
You know nothing of decency and mindful compassion.
You are the snake charmer coaxing dark juju from E-Bomb's soul with your crude experiments.
The planet rides in pain at your every touch.
You are a man cut from the spirit of sin.
You are a fuck, but I still call you brother.
Okay, thank you all who attended.
Please carry on your day.
Remember, no no says yes yes to prosperity.
One day dad, you will understand that this injustice cannot continue and all of you here,
we must stand together or we hold no hope against the avarice of gun city.
Oh hey, no, wait, hey, hey, hold on everybody.
Wait, oh man, could somebody cut me down?
Shit!
Come on, let's help that guy get down from the tree he tied himself to.
Alright, I'll use my little hacker's, uh, I thought I downloaded the little hacker's
There's a lot of rescue pack.
Never mind, I'll just hop up there and help him.
This guy looks weird.
He's like a purple-y guy like his dad.
Just the kind of guy they have in this world.
He's like Dr. Manhattan with blonde dreads.
I'm getting another drink.
You want more fizzy?
Grape, please.
Okay, just keep playing so we can get past this cut scene.
Okay.
All right.
One fizzy drink coming up, buddy.
Open wide.
- Phew, this sure is a tall tree.
Hey, can I help you down?
- Oh, yes, thank you.
Bless you, brother.
- Are you all right?
- I'm good, man, all vibes.
Now, who are you guys?
- I'm Sullivan, and this is Belinda.
We're travelers.
- Adventurers.
- Yeah, and we're trying to restore life to the planet.
Oh, that is so fucked.
Oh, okay, that's...
Okay, you're getting close to me.
That is exactly what I want to do.
Oh, phew, okay.
My given name is Rex Sherman III, but my chosen name is Indio Parsley.
I am a warrior and an agent of socio-ecological empathy.
My dad is the mayor, and the richest guy in town.
He hates my music.
Let me join your radical crew.
I promise to help you restore E-Bomb to her natural glory.
Yes! Join us!
Now that we are a unit, please let us hold hands.
Okay...
Then repeat after me.
We are siblings in the conflict of the universe.
Radical inclusion and decommodification strengthen us against our would-be oppressors and forge
us a blade of decency.
And the will of the righteous soul that flows through us like Zephyr, our eternal western
wind spirit of the material plane.
For we don't need effects of those corrupted by the inherent greed intertwined with modern
structures of capital.
Radical inclusion and decommodification
strengthen us against our would-be oppressors
and forge us a blade of decency
in the law of the righteous...
So, I wield a walking staff carved from ancient wood
and with my dashiki I can sometimes deflect ranged attacks.
I also can use my forage ability to scrounge up a random herb
with healing or poisoning properties
and a chakra beam to do elemental damage on multiple targets.
Wow, neat!
Welcome to the team, Rex...uh, Indio.
We're trying to head into the Nona Woods to find a lost artifact to help restore the planet.
You think you can help us navigate the woods?
Of course!
My band and I are always practicing music in the woods, trying to heal E-Bomb with song.
Do you want to know more about my band?
Pete!
What if his band is cool?
You know his band isn't cool.
Fine.
Yes!
Sorry.
I'm a fan.
a drink. Oh! Nice! We're called Mystic Melon Wonderful. Not Wonderful, Wonderfall. See?
It's like a psychedelic improvisational sort of jazz-ophonic. So Tyler, Lee, and Gumby
all play the same drum. And this one track we laid down, Pilot Magistrate Windsong, is
like bow bow and then like monkey comes in with the bass like chika bow chika bow
chika bow and then I come in on the digital sack
raise shots of Parliament best of us come bring me down jaw then we all chant
women of the world for the last 10 minutes even though my dad paid for the
studio space he said the music is obviously bad what a jerk right yes
Anyway, if you ever want to talk about my band, just click the interact button when you're
next to me.
I'll be following behind you and Belinda.
Will do Indio.
Let's head towards the woods and find that amber shard.
No one's allowed in.
Hey, no one's allowed in.
Hey, don't you...
Stop that.
That's just some corporate jamoke that works for my dad.
Allow me.
Hey, brother.
Hello, Rex.
Indio.
Of course, Indio.
What can I do for you?
My compadres and I are invested in entering the woods and absorbing the energies therein.
May we pass?
I'm sorry, Mr. Parsley. We're under strict orders from your father to allow no one in the woods while Dr. Dredd is performing his work.
Hmm, if you say so. Thank you, brother.
What do we do? Should we sneak in?
One guard can't stop us.
Alright, let's try to go around.
Dude, you're walking by all these guards.
What? You want me to talk to them?
I don't know, yeah.
We're literally trying to sneak around them.
Sometimes they're actually really friendly or they have an item on them or they're different.
Usually they at least have a different coloring in that case.
In that case, let's just try to find an entrance into the woods.
Oh no! There's an invisible cyber barrier, like the one outside of Goon City, and it's keeping us out of the woods.
We need to go to Dr. Dredd's lab. I bet we can get some answers there.
Where is it?
It should be underneath City Hall, where my dad works.
I happen to know a way in through the emergency exit through the sewers.
But first, we'll have to get the key on the other side of town so that you can see the whole town.
Otherwise, you won't see the whole town the devs designed for you.
Okay, okay. Let's do it!
Interesting. Seems Sullivan has a new friend.
A weird dirty purple guy.
I better go warn the scientist about what's going on.
Oh, I love my little Venus Melt Drug.
That milk is so good.
I thought we could sell this.
These people don't understand. Hybrid creatures aren't even new.
What do you mean? I don't see anything about hybrid creatures in my little hacker's bestiary.
That's because the board doesn't want you to know, man.
They've been controlling Gun City forever.
An oligarchical corporate kleptocracy designed to maximize profits for themselves
and destroy the will of its citizens.
My dad was a corporate operative for Asus for a long time.
I wonder if he knew about any of this.
I don't know. Dads are evil.
Oh, look! Here!
The key is behind that bush.
Okay, I'll get it.
It's one of those plants!
Wow!
It's running away and hiding behind different objects in town!
My little hackers and Vestagoggles can help!
Press Y to enter sleuth mode!
Nice!
And hit A to interact when you think you're next to the plant!
Can you handle this?
I drank way too much fizzy drink.
I have to go pee!
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Oh yeah, I should get gear.
Ugh, fine.
So I went home, now it's going by the old run down logging factory.
Man, this town is fucking sad.
This town, what a dump.
If only things were like they once were.
Sometimes I just like to take my little brother here to play.
It's better to be out of the house when my mom starts drinking.
Is that why you're here too?
Damn.
Wow.
The mayor really did try to reopen the logging factory,
but the woods haven't been able to grow nothing good in decades.
My father, his father, his father's father, and his father's father's father worked right here in No-No Hamlet.
Now I commute to Gun City every day to sell...
VR ad space to board-approved brands.
I got paid about half as much as my dad did working right here.
What a world, huh?
Pete, what are you doing?
Just go get the plant!
Hold on, man.
All these guys have little stories.
Yeah, sure.
Give me the controller.
You know, Patches would love to chat up NPCs.
Yeah, well, I don't.
And Pete just starts bawling right there like, "Oh Patches!
Oh Patches!"
Does this not move you, Thomas?
Yeah, yeah, it does.
It seems like a weird way to behave.
When a comrade falls, there's nothing strange nor feminine in expressing your emotions, young
Thomas.
I understand.
I can see him!
He's behind that wall!
Then it's time for my sonic blast!
Found you!
Wow!
He coughed up the key!
Nice!
Now we can open the sewers!
Let's go!
Okay, the sewers are just this way.
Oh, this is really gross.
No, you need to re-frame your thinking Belinda.
This is the people's waste.
The waste of our brothers and our sisters.
We should embrace it, bask in the stench.
Let's just try to get out of here and get to Dredd's lab.
Maybe if we confront him he'll answer some questions.
So monsters, these look like rats with bug wings and they have a flower growing out of their head.
Another hybrid creature.
Probably scared out of its wits by its own freakish existence.
Death will be mercy.
Whoa, so I can kill the new guy?
No.
Well, I'm first player when we battle, so it should default to me anyway.
Yeah, so you're gonna give it back when it goes to him until Caleb shows up.
That's so annoying.
You did the exact same thing to me, pretty much.
No, I didn't.
Hold on, we should really stretch before fighting.
Allows for energy to flow.
They're actually making me skip his turn so he can stretch?
They're actually making me skip his turn so he can stretch.
Keep doing that! It seems to work on these guys.
You should pick Chakra Beam. Are you gonna pick Chakra Beam?
Nice. I love Chakra Beam.
(phone ringing)
- Level up.
- Yeah!
- We're at a fizzy drink.
I'm gonna go get some.
Just hold up until I get back.
It's still my turn. - Oh, come on.
- Just go on your phone, man.
I'll be back in like five minutes.
- Fine.
Remember to get grape, okay?
- No promises.
- And a promise is a promise.
Repeat that.
A promise is a promise.
And committing to that is key, young Thomas.
It is how you will elevate not only yourself, but the collective as well.
It is the integrity of such...
Oh...
Well, the integrity of my bowels seems to have been called into question.
I'll be right back.
Now don't you go reading ahead, young Thomas.
I won't.
Okay.
Now...
Let's see here.
Great work team! Let's keep going!
Indio, earlier you were saying that hybrid creatures are new.
What did you mean?
With my friends and I jam out in the woods,
Sometimes we see like birds with little antennae and stuff.
Or a vine covered in fur.
No scientist necessary.
Usually we're on some extremely intense psychedelics though,
so nobody really believes me or my friends.
We saw a real massive hybrid on our way here.
You saw Roger?
Roger?
That's Roger!
The biggest hybrid in the woods!
Monkey once swore he saw him while he was tripping and even we told him to fuck off.
That's insane man. Monkey's gonna be stoked.
Did you guys see these creatures before dread came a few weeks ago?
Definitely. And the few we saw were always really peaceful, if a bit skittish.
That Venus milk truck and those rat things have really bad vibes.
The parts mashed together is like, like forcing a collab, you know?
Don't I know it.
There's so many extra lines in here. Where did these come from?
Yo, Sullivan. Hey, bro to bro, Belinda is super hot. Nice work.
Oh, uh, no. We're just friends.
No, dude, seriously. The best intimate coupling of my life was with this girl Sky C.
We stared into each other's eyes for like a week, but then she had to go back to work
doing UX design for a defense contractor.
I'm getting very similar vibes from Belinda.
Great, thank you.
Kiki, kiki, kiki.
Who's it from?
Ah, it's Sullivan McCloud himself and his new best friend, Purple Guy.
Easy brother, we are all children of the universe.
We travel the same ley lines as our forebears, and sup from the same mother's mill.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Why are you working for the Nightmare Assassin anyway, Bullyfrog?
How could you stoop so low?
Maybe I am that low.
Maybe I'm the lowest, stinkiest, creepiest, twerp of all time.
You ever think of that?
No! I just thought you had a bad homework!
We need to get to Dredd's lab, Bullyfrog.
We have to restore the woods.
Restore the woods?
Ha ha ha!
Don't make me laugh.
You two have always been such goody goodies.
The world is a harsh place with fathers who hurt you, who call you lame, and make fun of
your creative endeavors.
You two.
Shut up!
Well, it looks like the ultimate sewer hybrid is here.
The ultimate sewer hybrid?
After I told the scientist what you doers were up to, he made sure to send the ultimate
sewer hybrid your way.
Looks like I stalled for just enough time.
Good luck losers!
Oh boy, here we go!
Oh shit, no no, oh fuck, I don't know if I saved.
Did Uncle Jake s-skip some parts?
That Mike's heart was starting to get to me.
I knew I needed to take a break.
Maybe just take a couple supplements.
Just lie down for a bit.
Try not to think about Caleb or the guys.
Just try to remember what I like about my life.
Oh.
I decided to call that part 3.1.
The next would be 3.2.
My first double chapter. The first in the medium too.
I thought.
I don't know, I didn't really look into it. Fuck you.
Hello! All my friends are here!
I'm doing cocaine with all my friends!
Oh...
Sorry, um... I'm doing cocaine with all my fri-
with all my friends.
[laughter]
(laughing)