The year is 2042.
It's a summer day in Brooklyn, hot as hell, and I'm sweating my balls off because President
Xi turns off amenities between 1pm and 5pm on weekends after Weird Al's son made a song
parody of the Chinese National Anthem.
My phone is ringing upstairs.
It's my agent.
It's going to change my life forever when I pick up that call.
But right now I'm sitting on the balcony dangling my little toesies between the banisters,
tossing eggshells at the crackhead sleeping on my brownstone stoop
trying to scratch his cornea
somewhat unconsciously but I know what I'm doing
when my phone's ringing
so my first instinct, I scream for my wife
then I remember
she took the kids on vacation again
she always takes the kids on vacation
we have these two
miserable
little redheaded shits
and that's her side of the family
in every way, and I don't care what they say about recessive genes
that's all her shit
I'm 5'7"
I'm swarthy
with a little
less than generous hairline
beautiful thick brown mediterranean hair
she's a 6'1" scandinavian mutt
of some kind
so whatever freak
northern italian blood or sicilian bullshit I have in me
you know it's not nearly as responsible
uh... you know quantitatively
and uh...
qualitatively right then the sanguine concoction
courtesy of the
fucking hill people she sprang from
for the redhead thing
anyway
she's always taking the kids
and and
they're these awful
little kids
really awful twins
completely dead behind the eyes
and that's my fault really
i was touring nine months out of the year
for a better part of the decade
selling out venues everywhere
across the planet
podcasting night after night after night
i probably should have been home
my wife's a cardiologist
smart lady
but overpaid and underworked
she could have done something
She couldn't bother with kids, you know, when they were infants.
So she passed them off to my poor mother, who was a disaster at the time, and continues to
be a disaster, since my father died in the bathtub thing he did with the rope.
So those little pukes, my stupid fucking kids, had free reign.
They're posting note app apologies when they were three and a half to give you an idea
of what was going on.
You know I have a buddy who knows President Xi, knows him, and he said his kids, the ones
with whatever her name, his fourth wife, Olivia Rodrigo, his kids with her, they were weaned
off all that shit before anybody else knew about the thumb cancer or the Palantir squads,
killing Tim Cook, all that shit.
So he knew, of course he knew, but I didn't know, nobody knew really, but I didn't know
I'm
I lost another egg shell at that crackhead who honestly
looking back
he might have just
might have just been some
amazon guy
you know you can't really tell because so many of them
are the
metal dogs right the Boston
the Boston dogs so you just see a skinny guy
who looks like he hasn't eaten or slept in 3 days
and you think uh
you know whatever it's just some fucking crackhead
they're being round up anyway
so
I might as well throw an eggshell.
But so, anyway, I walk to the third floor.
So I have to do that. I go upstairs and I have to pick up the phone.
And I pick up the phone.
And it's my agent.
Hey, Price.
Patchy, how you doing, buddy?
I'm alright, man. Why you calling me though?
I told you, email only.
I know, um, I understand.
But I wouldn't call you unless it was something really special.
Oh yeah?
Yeah, I'm not pulling your dick, Patchy. I'm serious.
Hey, I wish someone would.
Oh my god! Yeah, see that's what I like to hear, that's actually hilarious.
Okay, so remember when you and the boys-
Don't.
Okay, right, so you and the um, what are you, the podcast about betraying Patches?
That's right.
When you all toured for a while, and we stopped in Nashville one night, and you got your head stuck in a sink, and that girl pulled you out.
The one with the ass, what was her name? It was like Sarah or Serena, something with an S?
I don't remember her name, but her @ was Tina Fuego.
Yeah, Tina. Okay, so it turns out the Cash app was bullshit.
'Cause her dad created a chemical that wiped out the homeless in San Francisco after the first cataclysm.
And so I've been blackmailing her, and I think she can get you a good audiobook deal.
I paused for a moment there.
Even when I worked with those traitors.
And I was putting out some of my best shit.
Making more money than I knew what to do with.
The book deal was all I ever gave a shit about.
This teena girl was really that rich.
Maybe I really could become
The guy who wrote and recorded one of the great American Wang Shichuan province audio novels.
You not yanking my cock price?
No, this is 100% brother, it's real.
So, you got something I can show people or what?
The real answer was no, but I said no.
Sorry, I didn't catch that.
I got nothing.
I mean, uh, nothing good enough right now.
It's, it's, it's, uh...
Okay, so, don't get in your head about it.
Just give me anything.
Literally just give me whatever you want.
Okay, okay, okay.
Uh, can, a week?
Give me a week, I have this, um...
manuscript.
Yeah, that I'm working on.
Give me a week to punch it up.
How's that sound?
That's great, yes. A week is perfect.
Thank you so much.
This is gonna change our lives, man.
Okay? Yeah.
Yeah, and I really believe that. I'm not just saying that.
And I- and people have been waiting for this, uh, forever.
And I- that's also true.
And the comeback is here, baby!
And that, uh, all- I believe all that shit.
So, I'll call you in a week.
Alright, ciao.
Fuck.
So after...
drinking my chemical peel smoothie and doing poppers for what felt like 30 minutes,
I felt ready to turn something out, pen to paper, microphone to audacity program.
But staring at that blank .AUP file thinking what the hell was I going to say, I started
to panic.
It was always easier when it was the four of us together, even after I suspected that
they betrayed me.
The pod boy, the pod traitors.
It always made this look a hell of a lot easier than it is, and made me feel like I could do
it too.
Now that I'm on my own in my perfect, beautiful Brooklyn brownstone with my fat-titted wife
and loser children, it's not the same.
Maybe that's...
Maybe that's what I have to do though.
I have to record something that recreates that feeling.
You know that feeling of
telling stories and jokes with your boys
Recording something for each other not for anyone else not even the audience
Hanging out staying up all night watching
Dashcam vids watching
Stupid fucking movies made by whack jobs
building our own
stupid weird mythology around all the moron shit we like
Gaming in way way too late into the evening buying each other joke gifts
Building children on the internet
Doing it all again the next day
Before we got huge
Before we played at the garden
Before that plane crash killed Chapo
Before Wang Xi Shang
For the blue check killings
I pressed record.
It should start kinda classic, like a Princess Bride-y kinda thing, right?
So, uh, not ne- an uncle telling a story to a nephew, not like a grandpa to a grandson,
something different.
An uncle telling a story to a nephew, a fantastical story, you know all the beats, you know how
it's supposed to go, but, but, you know, you know that I know too.
Oh ho ho, Sonny Boy!
How about I read you a bedtime story?
Hey, redo it. I fucked- I cut out.
Fucking God damn it.
You did- I heard one and then that was it.
I was like, why did he start at one?
Alright.
We gotta do another countdown.
Well, Sonny Boy!
How about I read you a bedtime story?
Uncle Jakey.
I don't want another bedtime story.
I want to play video games.
Well Tommy boy, what if I told you there were video games in the book?
Ah, I'd play those instead.
Oh my sweet, sweet Tommy boy, you can't play video games in a book, but you can imagine them.
Imagining stuff is always better than actually doing it.
(Groaning)
Okay.
Well...
Read the story then, Uncle Jakey.
And make sure you keep in all the scary bits.
I can fucking handle it.
I know you can, my Thomas.
Well, once upon a time there were three friends.
Caleb, Cameron, and Peter.
And they were about to play a video game.
Okay, and then we'll have another layer.
And this time, it's three friends who are hanging out, and one of them brings a video game over.
And those guys are a bunch of...
You know, they're mourning their friend who died, who they never betrayed.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey guys!
Can you knock, dude?
Seriously, Pete, what if Caleb and I were doing something privately?
Well, how could that be?
There are no secrets between us.
That's true.
Yes, that is true.
I mean, we'd never take a trip with Steve Harvey to the UAE without any of us, right?
Definitely not.
Especially not Patches, who died defending a thousand women from a shark.
That's right.
Anyway, I got this new game I wanted us to play.
It's an RPG called Sullivan Quest.
I think it could be really fun and reminds me of Patches, who died, beloved, and was
never betrayed.
Cool.
Pop that bad boy in.
[Gameplay]
Press start?
I don't mind if I do.
And then the final layer.
That's the game.
Hello?
Where am I?
You must strike now, Sullivan. The organism demands it.
Organism?
Well, where am I in school? What's going on?
Oh God, I didn't study for this test. I'm gonna fail!
Pencils down, please.
Oh no, I didn't even finish.
Oh no, now I'm making it to the sports ball championships, oh god.
Oh no, it's another bad dream.
And now here at the sports ball arena we have Sullivan the frog on the field who is showing us one of the worst bodies of all time.
Am I seeing this right, Jack?
Oh that's right, that's right Steve. This is probably the worst body I've ever seen in my history playing the sport and uh, I played it a lot.
That's exactly what I was thinking Jack, that this was maybe the worst body I've ever seen. Disgusting in almost every way, even for a frog.
Oh no, my poor sweet Salamander. I can't believe you're such a stinky little...
Mama no! Not you too!
This is the Gun City Police. Open up! Open up! You're under arrest!
I am Sullivan the Frog, guilty of all charges.
May God have mercy on your soul.
No! You got the wrong guy!
You got the wrong guy!
You must strike now, Sullivan.
Strike at the organism. Cleave it in twain.
It's a dream. It's a dream. It's a dream.
It's just a dream. It's a dream.
This is no dream, Frog.
This is your nightmare!
*Alarm*
It...
It says press A to wake up!
Just press it.
*Alarm*
*Gasp*
*Sigh*
What a terrible dream.
Surprise, Sullivan!
*Screams*
Oh dear.
Oh.
Oh, Sullivan baby, I didn't mean to scare you.
I'm sorry about that.
And look, now you fell out of your bed and took one point of damage.
That means you only have one point left.
It's okay, Mama. Thanks for wishing me happy birthday.
Of course, sweetheart. Fifteen years old, you're nearly a man.
I can't believe my own two froggy eyes.
Well, come downstairs when you're ready. I have your favorite breakfast prepared.
Spanakopita? Really?
That's right, sweetheart.
Oh, thank you, Mama. I know Gun City outlawed Greek cuisine last year, so that means a lot.
and I plan for my special little tadpole.
Oh, mama.
Well, I'll see you downstairs, hun.
Just use the directional buttons to move
and press A to interact with any objects or characters around you.
Gee, mama sure is sweet.
I better go downstairs right away and eat that spanakopita
before mom goes to jail for making Greek food.
So, you can move around now, I guess.
Oh shit, Pete, try to read what's on his desk.
*Pete's desk*
Is it gonna make that noise every time he moves?
God, tablet, check some of his stats.
*Tablet*
Wow, he really only has 2 HP.
He has no weapons or armor either.
Wait! Oh no, he has a banana peel.
Banana peel? Use it, dude.
*Banana peel*
*Pete screams*
*Pete dies*
He just slipped and fell and died.
*sad music*
Hello?
*everyone talking at once*
Why would they make this unskippable?
And so they watched the intro all over again.
But Sullivan did have his spanakopita, and it was delicious.
And he gained back that hit point he lost.
But eventually, even frogs need to go to school.
[school bell rings]
[music]
Wow! I can't believe I turned 15 just this morning!
I wonder if anyone will notice how much I've grown and changed since yesterday.
Let me try talking to my fellow students by pressing "A" when I'm next to them.
Bug off, Sullivan.
Bug off Sullivan.
Oh wow!
It's Belinda Crokes, the prettiest frog in school.
A straight 4 out of 10.
Should I press A to interact with her?
Uh, hi Belinda.
Oh hey Sullivan, happy birthday.
Wow, you remembered?
Sure, why not?
Wow, I can't believe she remembered.
Maybe she'll be my friend.
Oh hey, I'm Belinda Crokes.
I'm a pretty frog.
If she remembered, maybe she'll be my friend.
(Bully Frog and Toad talking)
Oh no, it's Bully Frog the Toad and his Toadies!
Well look at what we have here!
Sullivan the Clod, a total dunce and a loser.
Ugh, Bully Frog, you don't mean all that now, do you?
Hey, what did you just say to the boss?
I don't remember him asking you to speak either.
Oh gosh!
Why don't you knock it off?
Ooooooh!
Oh wow!
Sullivan has a girlfriend!
Ewwww!
Why don't you go back to the hole where you were born in and drink gallons of poison and
fucking kill yourself you stupid bitch!
Hey, don't talk to her like that!
Ooooooh!
You can have your meat!
Oh that's it!
You're dead meat Sullivan!
I'll see you after school punk!
You know, you didn't have to do that. I can take care of myself.
Oh, I'm sorry. I... You stepped in so I just felt like...
Never mind, Sullivan.
I have to go to class. I'll see you later.
Aw, now I gotta deal with Bullyfrog after school.
Today, class, we'll be wrapping up our unit on the early days of Gun City
With an AR film directed by Gun City High School alumnus,
Melanin Brooks, who made a short documentary about Sullivan de Granouille,
the worst explorer in Gun City history.
Now everyone, put on your Da Matrix 2 gogs and watch the movie,
Teachy Nee Drinky.
[Groans]
Guess I'll equip the gogs and get watching.
Long ago, Gunn City was a barren land.
Many explorers wished to travel to the Gunn City Landmass and pave over all of that shit
and put up 100 apple bees.
One such explorer was Sullivan de Granouille, a frog folk explorer pathetic in almost every
way.
Hey Sullivan, that sounds like you to a freaking T man!
Sullivan de Granouille traveled the vast wasteland of the Gunn City Landmass and documented his
journey in a cyber journal. He traveled with many allies, but his two dearest
companions were a four-hire mercenary toad named Bule Krapad, who was said to
be one of the strongest mercenary operatives in Blackwall, and had
pronounced issues stemming from a broken household.
"Duh, hey, bully frog, that sounds a lot like you."
"SHUT THE FUCK UP!"
And the other, a beautiful heiress to a pharmaceutical company named Berendela Croaca,
who was said to have amazing abilities and access to a computer.
Together, these three and their crew traveled the Gunn City landmass wastes before any city
representatives or corporations did, and apparently saw incredible sights and made brilliant discoveries
about our wonderful land.
DeGranouille documented all of it in his journal, which he called Sullivan's Quest.
However, he misplaced it, so now we don't know what he saw.
Degrenouille tried to tell everyone about his journey, claiming that the land was not barren,
but in fact a verdant paradise, but no one believed him because he seemed a little creepy.
When he died he said, "In many years, a young frog just like me will have his own quest,
and he will discover the truth behind Gun City, the things that none of the city officials
or corporations want the people to know."
Ah, the wound in my balls that is spreading to my penis, and then he finally died.
Hopefully, nothing like what he said will ever happen.
And anyone who even thinks of trying to explore anything, or uncover anything, knows exactly
what would happen to them if they tried.
The End.
Well, wasn't that just grand.
Okay, class is now over.
Take your knowledge pill before leaving and you're free to go.
Ta-ta!
I think we have to leave the school now.
Wait, don't just leave.
Try talking to the teacher or seeing if there's like a secret item or something.
I'm off the clock, Sullivan.
Oh, I think that's all she says.
I'm gonna order a pizza.
Okay, there are students talking.
See if you can listen in.
I heard the janitor got a new mop that can inflict poison damage.
Uh, didn't he get that from his wife after she passed?
Yeah, someone would have to be a real jerk to take that.
Oh, okay, we gotta go to the closet. Come on.
But, Uncle Jake,
why would they do that?
That's...
not very nice.
Well, in video games Thomas, sometimes you have to do something bad.
So you can get cool shit and use it to win the game.
Ah, okay.
I guess that makes sense.
What's on your mind young Thomas?
I don't know.
I guess I'm a little, ornizol.
I guess I'm a little, uh, worn is all.
Well, let's just keep reading the book then, okay?
Fine.
Then what happens?
Hey Sullivan, it's after class. Time to fight!
Uh, perhaps we can resolve this in some other fashion.
Fat chance! Or as my dad would say, if you tell anyone about this I will fucking kill
you.
I'm gonna pulverize you!
Ow! I took one damage, one more and I'm dead. I don't know how to fight. What is this turn
based combat I'm doing?
Hey Sullivan, need a hand?
Belinda, what are you doing here?
Saving your behind!
Look, all you have to do is select an attack, and then select a target.
I'll use my little hacker stun gun to shoot Bullyfrog.
It's easy, watch.
Yowch!
A girl?
A girl just hit me?
See?
Now you try.
Oh god.
Guess I'll select an attack.
Ow!
That hurt!
Where did you get that moth?
From a crime man in the supplies closet.
Dammit, I'm actually really sorry.
I'm not going to do this again.
I'm going to get you.
Ow!
I'm actually really strong, but I have a migraine and also my stomach hurts, and I'm really tired.
But this isn't over, Sullivan.
Wow, we won!
Wow Belinda, thanks for your help back there.
Where'd you learn to shoot like that?
Well my dad was an ex-corporate operative for ASUS, so he taught me how to defend myself at a young age.
Wow, that's cool.
Yeah, I guess. I miss him though.
Oh...
I'm sorry.
It's okay. He left my mom and I a ton of money when he died, making everything a lot easier.
Plus my new dad is really nice, and he's a feminist.
Oh, that's great.
Anyway, try to stay out of trouble, okay?
And here, I got you a birthday present.
It's a band-aid! You can use it to heal after you take damage.
Oh, thanks!
Don't mention it. Anyway, I'm gonna go. See ya, Sully.
See ya? Ha, neat-o, a nickname!
Well, time to get home. I wonder if Mama made me more spanakopita for dinner.
Why does this frog want spinach pie so bad?
'Cause it heals me.
How do I... how do I open up the map to fast travel home?
FUCK, I FORGOT TO GET THE FUCKING PIZZA!
*Groans*
Wait, you know who loves pizza?
Patches.
Yeah, that's true. He did love pizza.
Pat, just hit start and go to the map and click on home.
I mean Pete.
I know. I was just joking.
My name is Pete.
Hi, Mama. I'm home.
Oh, hi there, Sullivan.
Look who's here.
Wow, it's my tough-as-nails cousin,
John Carlo, the frog.
Hi, John Carlo.
Dot, dot, dot.
Oh.
Now, Sullivan, John Carlo's going to be watching you this week while Mama heads to Cancun.
Cancun?
You mean Cancun the desert oasis on the outskirts of Gadsville?
That's right, hun.
Your cousin John Carlo got an all-expenses-paid trip from his job doing, um, what is it you
do again, hun?
Contract killer.
Right.
And he gave it to me.
How sweet of him.
Oh, uh, great.
Well, I have to go.
The laser helicopter leaves in half an hour.
Ah!
This is so exciting!
Thank you so much Giancarlo.
I really needed a vacation.
No problem Mama Sullivan.
Have a good trip.
Oh I will.
And please take care of my special little tadpole while I'm gone.
Oh Mama, come on.
Well alright.
I'll see you in a week.
Woo!
Cancun!
Errr.
*door slams*
Uhhhh...
Dot dot dot.
Dot dot dot?
Uh, okay, um, I'm gonna go do homework.
It's nice to see you though, John Carlo. Thanks for giving my mom a vacation.
Hey Sullivan.
Yeah?
Nothing.
Uh, okay.
Dat dat dat.
Whew, well, that was a lot of homework.
I'm pretty tired now.
Guess I'll go to sleep.
[Sleeping Beauty]
Solvin!
SOLVIN!
Solvin wake up!
We gotta go!
Giancarlo?
What are you talking about?
No time to explain.
Do you have that map you stole?
Err, yeah.
How'd you know I stole the map?
Okay, good.
What's all this noise?
What's going on?
They finally came for you kid.
A bit earlier than I thought they would.
They?
Earlier?
Me?
Look, I'll explain on the way, okay?
Just let's go!
Woah!
We got Jolly Roger!
We got Jollibee agents.
Jollibee agents? But I don't do nothing to the government.
I don't even jaywalk.
That doesn't matter now. You know how to use that mop?
Yeah, yeah, I guess.
Good. You're gonna need it.
These Jollibees are pretty speedy. Try using your frog arts.
My frog arts?
All frogs have the ability to use frog arts to do some serious damage.
Neither Gun City nor the Stankums Federation of Bodies and Spaces wants you to know that though.
Just concentrate on your happy place. A place where froggies love to hop and smile and eat delicious flies.
Then select the frog arts option in the combat menu and let her rip.
Okay, I'll try.
Whoa, I just shot magic from my mouth! Nice work Sullivan, you took him out in one shot.
A mount caster. It's pretty rare.
Uh oh, watch out! Here they come!
Now it's my turn.
Woah! Giancarlo's dual magnata!
And his gun!
Come on Sullivan, let's go!
Guess I gotta follow Giancarlo!
Okay, I got the pizza
Finally, okay, buddy next time you can get the pizza. Maybe I will guys shut up. They put Sullivan on a motorcycle
Stop rocking around the sidecots not swinging your mop at the enemies coming by this is like a mini-game. I think let me play
No, I said we'll switch off after I die. Yeah, but this whole intro you're never gonna die. So it's not fair
Well then next time you can get a game and bring it to your friend's house, then you can play it first.
And then Caleb said, "I love pizza! Yum, yum, yum!"
Uncle Jake...
*Groans*
I'm starting to get really, really...
Really...
Really, really...
really really really sleepy you think we can wrap this up soon now hold on
there's just a little bit more oh it's the nightmare assassin nightmare
You're an assassin!
Sullivan, you gotta drive the motorcycle.
I'll hop in the sidecar and hold them off until we break the city barrier.
Oh god!
You can do it kid, just drive!
We meet again Giancarlo.
Dot dot dot.
What's the matter? Flying out your tongue?
This will be over soon.
The board will not stand for this betrayal.
And after all they've done for me right? Blah blah blah.
Let's get this over with.
Have it your way.
Time for my ultimate attack.
Step on it, Sullivan!
Hurry!
Here I go, here comes the barrier!
Blast it all, they got away!
Hmm, that young frog is impressive. Could he be? Hmm. We'll have to find another way.
Move out operatives!
We did it. We broke the barrier. Nice driving Sullivan.
Thanks. What was all that? Why were they after me? You said you'd explain!
I will. I promise. But we'll only be safe outside of the city limits for a little while.
Then they'll be after us again. Never mind all the creepy creatures out here. Let's get moving. We have to get to the base.
The base? What do you mean?
First we're gonna have to walk a little bit to get there.
We gotta be careful though, a lot of random encounters between here and there.
Let's go.
Why are there so many monsters?
I feel like we walked half a mile and we just had to fight like a hundred guys.
We don't gotta worry about that any longer.
We're here.
What?
I don't see anything.
Just under there.
Where?
Under where?
That's, that was good.
You got me.
Thank you, thank you.
Under where though?
I don't see anything but the wasteland that surrounds Gunn City.
Huh, the wasteland.
Look, I'll show you.
You just have to knock on the ground like so.
Whoa, the ground's splitting open.
Whoa.
Stairs?
What's down there?
Whoa, the ground's splitting open!
Whoa!
Stairs?
What's down there?
Somewhere safe.
Somewhere special.
Come on.
Oh my god.
This place is amazing.
So wet and warm and...
Frogs everywhere!
Welcome to the pond, Sullivan.
Your quest begins here.
Man, I'm beat.
That last part was tough.
I think I'm gonna head home.
You wanna play this again tomorrow?
If we have to.
Ugh.
I just wish Padges were here.
He was our most loyal friend and his death hurts us all forever.
If he were some bitter, balding podcaster with fat kids and a stupid bitch wife, he would
still be cool.
But he's definitely cooler dead, where everyone can miss him.
When I stopped recording I was hard as shit.
This is it.
People were gonna fucking love this.
Goodbye Brooklyn Brownstone, hello Westchester McMansion.
But seven and a half minutes of work was tough, especially at my age.
So I smoked some medical K2 and seized in my recliner until the sun started to set.
My eyes were rolling to the back of my head and my heart rate was soaring.
I tried to remember the last time a recording felt that good.
I thought if I can capture this feeling again and again,
I'll not only have created a great American Wangshi Shan Province novel,
I'll have found the first thing to fulfill me in God knows how long.
What to call it?
Story time with Uncle Jake?
Maybe, maybe.
The Three Gaming Friends?
As told by Uncle Jake?
Hmm, clunky. Maybe just... maybe just Sullivan Quest?
Yeah. Yeah, that's about it. Sullivan Quest. Yeah. Yeah, that's... yeah.
Yeah, that's the one. Woo! Sullivan Quest, baby! That's the one! Yeah. Sullivan Quest. Yeah.
(upbeat music)
[Music]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC]