*snoring*
*cough*
Oh fuck, what time is it?
Oh shit!
Okay, uh, okay, I gotta finish.
Um, uh, where was I? Where was I?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I see there was a frog in the...
Oh yeah.
Level up!
We're at a fizzy drink.
I'm gonna go get some.
Just hold up until I get back.
It's still my turn.
Oh, come on.
Just go on your phone, man.
I'll be back in like five minutes.
Fine.
Remember to get grape, okay?
No promises.
And a promise is a promise.
Repeat that.
A promise...
Is a promise.
That is a promise.
And committing to that is key, young Thomas.
It is how you will elevate not only yourself, but the collective as well.
It is the integrity of such...
Oh, oh, oh, well the integrity of my bowels seems to have been called into question.
I'll be right back.
Now don't you go reading ahead, young Thomas.
I won't.
Okay.
Now...
Let's see here.
Great work team! Let's keep going!
Indio, earlier you were saying that hybrid creatures are new. What did you mean?
With my friends and I jam out in the woods, sometimes we see like birds with little antenna
and stuff, or a vine covered in fur.
No scientist necessary.
Usually we're on some extremely intense psychedelics though, so nobody really believes me or my
friends.
We saw a real massive hybrid on our way here.
You saw Roger?
Roger?
That's Roger!
The biggest hybrid in the woods!
Monkey once swore he saw him while he was tripping and even we told him to fuck off.
That's insane man!
Monkey's gonna be stoked.
Did you guys see these creatures before Dread came a few weeks ago?
Definitely.
And the few we saw were always really peaceful, if a bit skittish.
That Venus milk truck and those rat things have really bad vibes.
The parts mashed together is like, like forcing a collab, you know?
Don't I know it.
There's so many extra lines in here.
Where did these come from?
Yo, Sullivan.
Hey, bro to bro, Belinda is super hot.
Nice work.
Oh, uh, no. We're just friends.
No, dude, seriously.
The best intimate coupling of my life was with this girl Sky Seed.
We stared into each other's eyes for like a week, but then she had to go back to work
doing UX design for a defense contractor.
I'm getting very similar vibes from Belinda.
Great, thank you.
Kekekekeke.
Bullet Frog!
Ah, it's Sullivan McCloud himself and his new best friend, Purple Guy.
Easy brother.
We are all children of the universe.
We travel the same ley lines as our forebears, and sup from the same mother's milk.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Why are you working for the Nightmare Assassin anyway, Bullyfrog?
How could you stoop so low?
Maybe I am that low.
Maybe I'm the lowest, stinkiest, creepiest dwerf of all time.
You ever think of that?
No! I just thought you had a bad home life.
We need to get to Dredd's lab, Bullyfrog!
We have to restore the woods!
Restore the woods?
HAHAHA!
Don't make me laugh!
You two have always been such goody goodies!
The world is a harsh place with fathers who hurt you, who call you lame, and make fun of
your creative endeavors!
You two...
SHUT UP!
JOIN
JOIN OFF
Well, it looks like the ultimate sewer hybrid is here.
The ultimate sewer hybrid?
After I told the scientist what you doers were up to, he made sure to send the ultimate
sewer hybrid your way.
Looks like I stalled for just enough time.
Good luck losers!
Ha ha ha!
Oh boy.
Here we go!
Oh shit.
No no.
Oh fuck, I don't know if I saved.
*Screams*
This thing has tons of tendrils on it.
I'll go for those first with multi-attack!
Uh oh.
That didn't seem to work too good.
Ah shit. Ah shit. Okay.
Um, fuck, fuck, thank you. Um...
Oh!
Fuck yeah!
Shaka beam!
Nice!
I'll just have Belinda stun gun the main body.
Nice, okay.
Look at all this art.
Look out!
It's shooting a sludge laser from the flower coming out of its beak!
This thing is wild!
Ow!
Okay, that was like a defense buff thing it just did.
So, that does damage and debuffs.
Alright now I got this.
We did it!
Whoa...
Uncle Jake...
Level up! Very chill!
Let's hurry outta here to the rev!
Oh wow...
This place...
eradicating my soul.
All these different creatures floating in these tubes.
This seems wrong.
This is the type of person Gun City churns out.
Profit-seeking innovators.
Broken spirits all.
No concern for how all the towns that supply their labor live.
We are tools for their complete and total exploitation.
Isn't your dad really rich?
Hey, look at this!
Look at this!
Nice, a computer.
Let me see if I can hack in here.
Oh cool, a rhythm game thing.
Okay.
Got it!
I bet his log entries can give us some more insight into what Dredd is planning.
Probably the last one is all we need to read.
Oh sick!
I can read all of these.
Seintschlug, Stardate 10325023, Actual date October 3rd.
It seems that my hunch was correct.
There is some peculiar activity in the Nono Woods that will contribute greatly to my research
of hybrid creatures.
Much of this activity is stemming from a clearing in the woods.
No one seems to frequent it, except that foolish hippie son of the mayor.
I will have to ensure that no one can enter these woods until I've completed my research.
I will ask the mayor to put the barrier up for me.
Scientist's log, star date 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, actual date October 5th.
My grad student slaves have been excavating day and night beneath that clearing in the
woods.
There is a greater source of power than I even anticipated.
We will find it soon.
Meanwhile, I have developed the first man-made hybrid, the Venus Milk Trucks.
And they are beautiful.
From extracting chemicals from the soil of the woods, I am able to create these man-made
hybrids.
However, there seems to be the occasional anomaly of a natural hybrid.
I will have to take care of those as well.
But anyway, while these Venus milk trucks will live miserable lives, their anatomy does not
support the weight of the others.
They produce a curious milk product that, when treated properly, is not as pleasant.
When I eat it, it kills my breast feeds.
But imagine a town dedicated to eliminating these studies.
This is an entirely new product stream for support premium agriculture.
The only problem is that taking care of these creatures requires a number of training efforts that my grad student slaves and I simply do not have.
I will have to solve this.
Scientist's log, start date... let me see... 100, that's fine.
Actual date, October 10th.
My work on the sewer hybrid is near completion, and the rat creatures are already scouring the sewage.
Soon I will have everything I need to control this town and turn it into an outpost for
ze board.
The pathetic mayor is so desperate to be loved he doesn't even notice this is happening right
under his stupid purple nose.
Since I was a student I've always believed in the potential of hybrid creatures.
I would draw little doodles of a dog kissing an antelope and this would make a doggalope.
Because of this my parents pretended I wasn't their kid.
Or we don't know him, he's just some little boy who looks like us and follows us around.
I was shunned by all, and it was never a horny thing.
Everyone thought it was a horny thing.
I have never been a horny.
The profit potential in this endeavor alone was enough reason to persist.
But to show those naysayers that I'm no fool, that I am a once in a generation genius, I
would do this for nothing.
I would do this for nothing.
Woah.
Gee, Sullivan, you're sure being thorough about these logs.
I think we only need to read the last one.
Oh, shut up.
Scientist log, blah, blah, blah.
I have found the solution to my Venus milk truck problem.
I will give these to the gullible ninnies who live here.
They can feed them and take care of them and once they grow irritable they will probably try to eat them.
But that's not going to be an issue any longer.
You see I am done with the board. I am done with profit.
Tomorrow my grad students will have dug up the source of power beneath the clearing in the woods.
and through that I shall make hybrid creatures that roam all of Yibam.
It will be about me for once.
Just my domination.
I shall become the Chimera King!
The power is too great to ignore.
It needs to be mine and mine alone.
Uncle Jake's gonna...
skip some parts.
Tommy!
Uh-oh.
Patrick!
Whoa!
That big monitor just turned on.
It's dread.
I see that you've been doing some research.
I'm glad that Ovishtole told me about your thing.
I thought it laughable, but he spoke of your strange powers,
and indeed the death of Twiggy Hancock had reached the board's ears.
They had sought Twiggy for the lost cause, but it turns out his discovery of the power
of these amber shards and his untimely demise has made us all very, very curious.
My grad students will soon finish their excavation and the shard and its power will be mine.
So for that I must thank you, Froggy, for going on this quest for the shards.
Because now this one's mine.
Come on man, I told you not to play without me.
Dude, it's fine. Look, I got past the sewer exit.
That's exactly what I didn't want you to do!
And for you to do that to me, when I'm devoting my time to reading literature to you, it's
just so disrespectful.
Young Thomas, I am aghast at this affront.
I'm sorry Uncle Jake.
I was just...
I really enjoy the story.
I didn't want to stop.
Well it's not always about what you want Thomas.
It is about what is good for you.
What is good for all of us in the face of declining institutions and a cultural sickness that threatens the existence of the entire project.
The second I let you play it's like, "Pete you're doing this wrong. Pete stop talking to these guys. We're gonna lose."
Yeah Pat but you are doing stuff wrong. Don't you want to win?
game cam I want to play the story and my name is P I'm sorry the youth the youth
these days I just I know you're sick we can talk about this later let's keep
reading for now is that all right whatever dude here's your stupid grape
Fizzy. Give me the controller. Yeah, okay. I'm sorry. That's enough sorries outta you,
alright. That's alright. Do you hear that? It's the sonorous sounds of the Venus milk
But he and all of his precious citizens shall soon be devoured by the Venus Milk Trucks
as they so lovingly took care of.
But you will get what you deserve for thinking so little of me and my efforts.
You see the power of the man-made hybrid creature.
You see the power of the human-made hybrid creature.
We are great hybrid creatures and you shall either join or die.
(Evil Laugh)
We have to help everyone! We have to save my father!
Right! Let's go!
(Milk Truck Noises)
Oh no! The milk trucks!
The milk trucks are attacking everybody!
This is all a part of Dread's plan!
Somebody help!
I just wanted to help!
I just wanted to help my Hamlet!
What have I done?
Oh no, you dare?
He's being swarmed by the milk trucks!
I know just how to clear them away!
Sonic Blast!
Thank you,
kind frog folk.
Son!
Papa!
Look, son, I'm sorry.
Our town, we're so desperate.
Even with my ill-gotten gains.
Shh.
It's okay, Papa.
Dr. Dredd is hiding in the woods.
I don't know what he plans, but he seemed insane.
Go to the woods, brave frog folk.
My guards will let you through.
And stop this madness.
I can take care of the town once that bastard is gone.
You can count on me.
And me.
And I as well.
I'm proud of you son.
I know.
I feel like you think I don't know how to play this game.
That's because you don't.
I beat up mini boss guy by myself.
We're finally in the no no woods.
There's a clearing a bit up ahead where my homies and I jam and saw the hybrids.
I bet that's where Dredd is.
Alright.
Hey!
Oh, oh, hey Johnny. You scared me again.
Hey Sullivan.
Oh what the crap, there's girls of you? And a purple guy?
Yes. Good to meet you compadre.
You know this guy Sullivan?
Yeah, this is Johnny Tinch. He sells goods and buys bones.
Yeah, but the bones are for the goblins.
I thought we were about to get into another fight.
Nah, fat chance. No offense, cause you're a girl, but I'm basically like the best fighter at my school.
at my school and I actually had to be put in a separate gym class because I was always
uh they were always trying to beat me up because I loved to cuss.
Johnny, can I borrow some potions from you from a spandacopita to restore frog points?
Yeah, these woods are so messed up man.
One time I was in the woods by my house uh like hanging out with the neighbor kid and
he was trying to look cool and he kept playing with these matches that have um like um well
on the thingy that holds them uh the thing had like a picture of a squid holding like
a
like potions and stuff really or a spin spanning whatever but I got some herbs
though there's a lot of good herbs here so I made some weird stuff if you want
to buy it well what does the weird stuff do I got some of it that make you make
you strong like me or it can make you fast like me and I got something even
unlocks a new combat art but those are really expensive no offense
Belinda what do you think I think we should get one of those attack buffs and
one of those speed buffs. Try to save the rest of our tokens for that special
combat art thing for next time. Okay well look lady I'm not just gonna be hanging
on to this thing for you because you know a lot of adventurers come around asking
me for crap and I need money. Well then I guess we'll just have to take our
chances. Okay okay you can have it. Thank you. Is that all? I think so. How's your
mom doing Johnny? Um well well actually I haven't really seen her in a while but
She's probably fine cuz she just sits around all day anyways, ha ha
Anyways, I'll see you around solving good luck with whatever you're doing and make sure to bring more bones next time
I will and therefore that goblins not for me. Yep
Okay. Yeah and turn around what just do it make sure you don't look because if you do it'll be bad news
If you betray me
It'll be just like last time when I was playing
Dodgeball and they made me sit in another room because I was too good at throwing the dodge ball so far
so they made me sit in the locker room all by myself and then afterwards they tried to find me...
*sigh* Alright, let's keep going.
Another hybrid creature! Do you recognize this one, Indio?
This is one of the ones I've seen, yeah. But it seems really agitated.
It probably doesn't trust anyone coming into the woods now. We must subdue it.
Okay, it's a battle. So, the controller?
Fine.
Okay, what about...
Just do Lightbringer Blast. We know Frog Arts are strong against these guys.
Lightbringer Blast!
Okay, and now Belinda will use Magikize.
Frog Art Magikize!
Okay, let me do Indio.
Fine, can you just use forage though in that case? Good chance to heal Sullivan without wasting a potion or a band-aid
Nice okay, just use light bring her blast again, and I think we got this one sure
What the hell man again what to do I dare you tell me again
So immature dude.
There is no cool shit, it is just the forest level.
All of these games have forest levels, they all have the exact same stuff in them.
Everything has the same stuff in their shit.
What?
You should appreciate the stuff in the shit while it's there, because then it's gone,
and you didn't get to appreciate any of it.
You didn't talk to the shit and ask him questions or listen to him, you know, maybe he had cool
stories okay?
Pete, what?
These things are made by like 1000 incredible Japanese guys, and we're just gonna say, "Your
is boring, you might as well be dead like Pagin.
The clearing is just up ahead.
Not so fast!
Bullyfrog?
I'm tired of chasing you losers through these fucking woods.
It ends now!
Bullyfrog, why do you hate us so much?
I know you picked on me in school, but we're not in school anymore.
It doesn't have to be this way.
Because you humiliated me!
You two, you two, you beat me up!
And everybody knows that!
Oh, Bullyfrog I didn't know that, I was just defending myself.
I didn't mean to humiliate you.
I'm sorry.
WHAT?!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, that's all.
I didn't mean to do that to you, Bullyfrog.
Come on, Sullivan, we have to hurry!
Right.
See ya, Baldi-frog!
Wait! Get back here! I...
He's sorry!
Doctor Dredd!
Well, well, well, you made it through the force.
I should have guessed you would.
Oh, I forgot.
I did.
Come, grad students!
Sacrifice yourselves!
Literally this time!
Go mine grad students
*crying*
*sword sounds*
Why am I so hard?
Ah! The grad students have laser wands!
And they won't stop crying!
Here, Pete,
battle's about to start.
Oh, what a-
Please, just play as Sullivan, and you can be Indio!
You're just gonna tell me what to do!
No, I won't, Pete! You're your own person,
I trust you.
And trust you see, young Thomas, is the cornerstone of any great organization of peoples.
But, we must be cautious.
As the saying goes, trust, but verify.
You mean that?
Yeah, whatever, of course.
Uncle Jake, can I please see the picture when the boss dies?
I know they're in the book.
Please.
I miss him too, dude.
Okay, just...
Don't get any ideas in your head.
Don't you see? Soon I will have endless hybrid creatures that I can control and love to my heart's content.
This world already has hybrid creatures! You're exploiting its wonder for your own twisted gains!
Does that not leave you ill, man?
No.
I'm gonna use Sonic Blast on the grad students.
I think they're gonna react to that.
Where's the shot?
Sonic Blast!
We're grad students.
Going to scan, Dredd.
Lil Hacker, scan!
Analyzing enemy.
Weakness to chakra.
Only energy that rejects orthodoxy.
Got him now.
Chakra beam!
Fuck, fuck, fuck you, fucks!
Grad students come!
We shall fuse by harnessing the energy of the ember shard.
I shall become the ultimate Chimera!
Oh God!
Is there anything more hideous in the entire universe than 50 grad students fused together?
A true nightmare!
They won't harsh my vibe!
Hey, let's try out some new combat arts!
With three party members, there's a lot more we can do!
Good thinking, Sully!
Thanks! Every once in a while, I have a good idea!
Cam, I don't know how to do the combat arts.
Here, instruction manual.
To perform combat art, select option for frog art with frog character, then select either
another frog art or ability with another character.
Then attacking character follows button sequence on screen in time, so it's like a mini rhythm
game.
Okay, I'm first, so I'll choose lightbringer blast.
And I'll use Belinza's stun gun, and there's the combo.
Light Gun Explosion!
You uncultured hoppity fox!
Why do you always gotta break out the slur?
Now it's my turn.
Blinding science!
Ah! We're blinded! I can't see!
Me neither!
Yet, I can see clearer than ever before.
Whoa! Indio has a new combat option!
All I can do is hear the music flow through me.
The sounds, the rhythms, the vibes.
Run away!
Nein, it's illogical, it's nonsense, it's complete, but fulminary.
It strives towards nothing.
No progress, no innovation.
I finally see. I am really, really rich.
But this time, in love.
Alright, take a look.
No!
Suck my dick pussy bitch!
This is the only way to see.
Okay.
Well, I guess it's time to eat this fly.
I can sense...
That golden gift.
You're in.
Come on!
Back here again.
This is your power, Sullivan. Your quest. The organism demands it.
New frog art online.
Oh my gosh!
The forest! It's filled with all types of creatures!
Rabbit snake lilies, squirrels that grow from tree branches, they got little leaves on their back.
It's like a massive single organism.
Intertwined.
It is an ecological, biological wonder with infinite possibilities.
When the rest of our people come to this planet, places like this will be remarkable resources
for food, medicine, lumber and agriculture, as long as we know how to live in harmony
with it.
This is really something, Sully.
Hey! Whoa!
So many critters and creatures!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
It's that big hybrid from before!
Roger! You've come as well!
[ROAR]
Whoa!
He won't hurt you, brother.
I know him.
We all know him.
Well, I'm not scared, so shut the fuck up!
Shut the fuck up!
Indio!
Papa!
You called me by my name.
It's a miracle Indio.
The Venus milk trucks have calmed themselves.
What has happened here?
Many things have passed Papa, many things.
Sullivan, I must stay here.
My people are going to struggle with these strange woods.
They will need someone to guide them.
I believe Roger and I are up to that task.
Yeah, I can't think of anyone else better to lead them.
If what your Sullivan's Quest says is true,
then we'll all have to reckon with the bounty of our world.
Our people have a way of saying goodbye.
We say, good journey to you.
And so I say that to you now.
Good journey to you.
Good journey to you, too, Indio.
Farewell, both of you.
You will always be friends of No-No.
Hey, Sullivan!
Hey, Bullyfrog.
Can I...
Can I come with you?
You're not gonna try to kill us, are you?
No, I'm not.
Well then, come on!
Yeah!
New party member unlocked!
But don't think this means you can be annoying or stupid around me.
I'll do my best!
Where are we headed next, Sullivan?
Come on, I'll show ya!
Foolish toad.
*Suspense music*
Honorable board, I beseech you.
Yes, yes, get on with it.
Quiet, member number one. Let me just speak.
We're told to talk, you interrupt every moment you get.
*Drum roll*
Go on, go on.
Looks like he wants to hear what you have to say, Mr. Sasson.
Thank you, Honorable Board and Chairman.
It seems the amber shards that Hancock raved about are real.
Moreover, a group of teenage frogs seem to be collecting them.
The very ones associated with my former colleague, Bullyfrog the Toad.
The Granwy's Journal, whatever it is that exists within it, could be the key.
Chairman, I trust in the wisdom of yourself and the board for how to proceed.
I await your orders.
Very well. I shall proceed thusly.
Blessings upon you and the board. Farewell.
Oh, blessings upon you and the board as well!
Gentlemen, it is clear to me that we must take the shards and use them.
They have tremendous power held within them.
Why not take them for ourselves?
What about the Dread Hancock?
You think that's the best path?
Surely prophets could increase 500% over a man-
But board member number 3, surely profits will only get us so far.
Now you're gonna get number 6 started.
The minions! The best customers we've had!
Face those! Face those! Face those! Face those!
And someone shut him up!
Um, yes chairman, of course.
My apologies.
We of the board are at your command.
And we members will conduct ourselves responsibly.
(music)
Yo!
Oh, you beat the chapter.
Yeah, well, you had other plans.
True. But it's all good news, I promise.
Fizzy drink? In the fridge.
Okay, so, I was hanging with Price, and he has a pretty big opportunity for us.
Something that I think a lot of people would dig.
A Patches Benefit concert.
What?
Okay dude, it would be this huge concert at the garden, we'd have all these podcasters there and some shitty bands that follow us on Twitter would play.
And then at the end we'd do a full D&D session with a Patches hologram as the DM.
Then we can end the night with the unveiling of the Patches statue.
And all the women he saved will sing "America, the Beautiful".
Woah, that's pretty intense.
It would be so sick.
Plus at the garden? We've never done the garden!
This shit would put us on the fucking map!
I won't do that.
What?
I'm not gonna do it. Do you want to talk about hologram a
Patches hologram fuck dude. I
Can't do this. I'll see you guys tomorrow. He what the fuck
God damn it. I mean you know what he means
cool, dude
Well, hope you had a good dinner. Yeah, all right. I'll see you tomorrow. Okay. All right, okay
Bye, okay, just leave I love you. Okay. I love you, too. No, you're leaving or I'm leaving. Bye. Bye. I love you
Okay. Yeah
That's my take
How will they ever resolve this I do wonder
me too
Well young Thomas another chapter done in podcasters who play video games
Another night of rest for you
Uncle Jake I
Really want to beat this illness I
Know you do son. I know believe me. I was wondering
Do you know what it's called? I?
Want to be able to put a name Oh young Thomas
Some things are not worth knowing.
It would upset you too greatly.
Cause you undue stress.
Okay...
Plus we already showed you them pictures tonight.
That's enough excitement, don't you think?
Sure...
Well, goodnight.
Goodnight, Uncle Jake.
I'm...
Horny?
Uh, I'm horny.
When I finished recording I started zoning out.
Then my Alibaba bracelet started beeping because it thought I was dead.
So I uh, crammed a few supplements in my mouth and I walked out of my balcony.
It was night now.
The streets were real quiet.
If another cataclysm comes, I don't think I'll make it.
Curiosity got the better of me.
If Caleb was here to see the other guys, that means they must all still be in New York too.
I looked up Cameron.
He's some schlock horror director now, no surprise there.
He won a couple of ten cent grants for propaganda work and could fund the rest of his shit with
the proceeds, I guess.
He always liked that crap.
That horror stuff.
I started to look up Pat.
The only thing I could find was the podcast and an album called Big Patty Style Boston Delights.
Which came out a year after I stopped talking to them.
Then nothing else.
No trace. It's like he vanished.
With my allotted Baidu time used up, I decided I should try to maybe get a real night's sleep
for once.
I headed over to the couch, and for the first time in what felt like years, I saw the picture
of my wife and I that sits on the side table next to it.
She and I were smiling.
It was at the height of the whole podcast.
I remembered when my wife was going into labor, I made sure we moved one of the tour locations
around so I could be at the delivery and then perform the same night.
Why the hell did I do that?
Nice a computer.
Sorry.
(laughing)
- Nice, a computer.