I think a burp is a better signal. It doesn't make any sense to start with a
burp, because you have to see the moment that we've had this exact. Yeah, what
do we do? You're so stupid really this exact because you go into the mic and
you're when you burp, you burp, and we make a pit bull face. We've had the
we're moving on because if you want to hear this, you can go to five episodes
ago. Yeah, right. You're already on this tier. So you like what you're hearing.
So hello, everybody. We're going to do some character creations, the Mother's
Day episode, but we're going to start by doing character creation because I got
everybody brand new, awesome character sheets. If you're on the video,
Patrick, will you show the episode right now? Pat, will you show? Stop trying to
eat me. Wait, I can show easiest, I think. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah, true. We'll post
this in the Discord, too. And straight up DM me if I forget, because I always
forget. So there's a couple of things I want to point out here, okay? So will
you please explain what you would politely say is the reason why we
switched to these?
Politely.
We've been, over the past three years,
the most recent episode notwithstanding, we've been having some...
It's just been challenging
sometimes to communicate some of the
nuances really in the game with two you guys and have that
stick with you and I so you decided to eliminate the nuance and go for things
such as the speed ability, having a rabbit on it, but a a running jack rabbit.
Yeah, I just thought that would kind of help and then you could see that
also what I think it really does help what I like here. What I like here too
is that you've completely removed the names of the stats and replace them with
pictures. So we have a and I know exactly what all the more a strong arm
of balancing guy, a guy standing on a ball, a heart, a brain, an owl wisdom
talking
also
we're having trouble. We didn't know what strength.
This is like
the fire moves anymore. This is like their own with three, but yeah, we'll
come up with moves we're going to it's going to be everything's nice and giant.
there's no way you could. I mean this literally looks like a kindergarten
worksheet. Yeah, it is. This is my first D and D thing. This is a you found a D
and D. So there did you make this? No, I wish I did. I found it online. What
were what did you look up to find? Yeah, what was this called? You have to
know. It's a pdf dyslexic D and D characters really
that
dyslexic. That's really funny. This isn't even the right handwriting for dyslexia,
but this was the best one I found.
That is so fucking awesome. It has a very specific handwriting, too. Yeah,
all the letters are slanted. Yeah, but this was the most accessible one I
found. I was really looking that up. Oh, no. Wow. For no other reason. We really
do need this, don't we? Well, so what I did is we removed skills. Skills are
kind of in the way. Yeah, think about it. Dyslexics can't handle skills. Yeah. And
then as far as the at least for that, we're going to try it for the
Seahawks. Yeah. I mean, like I think when we do a campaign that's not a
holiday special, that's kind of be a little bit loose. We'll have like more
room for abilities and some other things, but I think I want to start, I'm
thinking this is like, let's start from a strong foundation, right? Let's remove
some of those roadblocks that have been impeding you guys from taking in any
information like maybe three and which has all been my fault too is what I
realized to I did a lot of reflecting and I was like I'm the problem here. So
let me get you guys very wrong of you. But yeah, I was there's a clear problem.
Yeah, and it's not you. Well, I appreciate that. But you know, I I still
feel like I gotta do what I gotta do. You know, that's how I was raised by a
pack of nerds, wild pack of nerds. So yeah, let's let's let's roll for your
stats. Okay. And then I'll introduce the premise to everybody. It's a little bit
more informal, right? I want, well, you know, let me know what you guys think.
Let me know in the comments. Please say what symbol they are and not. So roll
for arm flex. And we're just rolling in order down the line. Oh, sorry. No,
we need three D's. Three D's. Yeah. So you only gave us two. I gave, I handed
you another one. I handed you another one. Let's roll down the line. Oh, you
didn't have two because you've got a pack. The reason why I want to roll down
the line is because it will force you guys to just kind of have the character you have
to have. Have the character you have to have. Cameron, don't worry about it, I got it. So
yeah, let's just roll for each stat instead of rolling it, putting it on the side and
assigning it. Alright, so just go down the line. Yeah, so everyone do arm. Okay, arm.
My arm is 13. Oh my god, I got a 15 arm. I got a, oh. You got a 14 arm. So you guys have
all pretty decent arm. And then what's next? Because I have it here.
Next one is balance.
Balance. Next one's balance.
Camera patches. You got to move your backpack.
Sorry. Sorry, camera.
Oh,
not so good with the balance ball.
OK, how'd you do in balance ball?
I got nine. I also got nine.
And what did you get?
I didn't roll because I was fixing the camera.
I screwed it up.
If you get a nine, this is a sign.
I got a 7. Oh God, we suck at balance but we're pretty good at arms.
Next is heart. Okay.
It kind of looks like a face. I got a 13.
Heart. I got 11. Okay. I also got a 13 heart.
Okay. It's kind of like our hearts are linked across the table.
You know what? These are kind of our real life stats so far.
We got three dice right here. You got singles?
I played Steelo the other night and I lost fucking 40 bucks.
Jesus Christ. Brain. Now brain.
brain
ten
five
fourteen very nice.
You got good. You have the highest brain all right. That's giving brains
that yeah, I went there wow. I'll only shit
okay. I got I got twelve. I got fourteen some so the maybe not so all you're
maybe a bit smart, not good at flying, but not so owl. Are you now talking
thirteen.
I got a seven. I can't believe I got a fifteen talking
okay, let's let's let's review. Let's review
let's see how so arm everybody's pretty decent right. I got fifteen. I got
fourteen or yeah, let's start with the start. Yeah, Caleb, you start okay guys.
I have for my arm. I have fifteen are for my balance ball. I have not
for my heart. I have thirteen or maybe that's a stomach. I have for brain. I
have five
and for talky
I have fifty
wow
great.
So we'll do the modifiers for that in the second. Okay,
so Pat, I have fourteen arm. I have nine balance ball. I have eleven hearts.
I have fourteen brain, fourteen owls and seven talking well.
So
but for me mine, I didn't get anything above thirteen on mine. I got thirteen
arm, my balance ball at seven thirteen part and as and ten brain, but only six
owl and my talking will be thirteen as well as the other thirteen. Okay, that's
not bad. Thirteen talking is pretty good. Thirteen thirteen, thirteen arm talking
and heart, but my worst is by far my owl fall.
this is my balance.
Yeah, my guys, my guys kind of well rounded when it comes to doing arm and
brain
but
what he has to do stuff that involves our you know, it's ball. I really my
only bad stat is my brain is fine.
Yeah, you're pretty on balance ball.
My balance balls, okay, your balance ball is definitely passed, but I got
good arm and good talky. I got pretty I got pretty lucky here with arm, brain
and owl. That's pretty, those are big stats. Yeah, those are big stats to I
got three fourteens. I feel like my character is maybe a tier lower than
you guys' character. Yeah, I think I'd have to agree. Maybe we can, maybe we
can
exploit that. Based on just, I mean based on
owl alone. Yeah. So yeah, with five brain, I think that's like dolphin, maybe
little less than dolphin intelligence in D and D aren't dolphins intelligent
or than humans. No, they're not or is that science fiction? That's
thinking
a
like and are they good at singing and they fly
but in the movie only yeah, but they're smart, though that's that's all I'm
saying is don't get down. No, they are smart. I'll get down on the dolphin on
your on yourself. Oh, no, you're a doll. You know, I would say it's much more
consulting that I had to fill out the arm brain out worksheets kind of the
idea yeah. So let's do so let's now
do initiative and armor class and bunny rabbit. So for armor class,
we're going to do
eight
or sorry, no ten plus your decks mod. So what are sorry your ten plus checks
your balance ball. Okay, so my armor class is how we come up with
balance. Oh yeah, I apologize. So yeah, let me let's get the mods in
there and the saves will be the same as the mods. You're not doing
any specialization. What do we roll? So so so for
if you have fifteen, so actually I'll just tell you guys all
so let me just say so ten is zero ten to eleven is zero
mod twelve to thirteen is plus one and then fourteen to fifteen is plus
two and then sixteen, seventeen, plus three, etc.
Then for minus... Sorry, what was that? What was eleven? Eleven is zero, so zero
mod. If a nine is minus one, we have there, Pat, and then that's plus two,
that's plus two. And what about six? So then this is... Six is
minus
two. Nine to seven is minus one? And five is minus three.
Sorry. And seven is minus two? Nine is minus one. Okay. And seven is
minus two. Damn. Okay. My talkie is not good. You have bad talkie?
I got plus two talking. I have really bad talking. Yeah, not bad for me. So
plus one.
So your armor class then is gonna be 10 plus
that balance ball. So 10 plus... Well, wait, but my balance ball is negative
one, so 10... How do I plus a negative one to it? So my balance
ball... So my armor class is 19.
So mine would be... So I would have a nine. Just add your modifier.
your
- What's Dex? - Balance ball, sorry.
- Balance?
- I gotta start saying that.
- Just the mod, so negative one.
- And then the rabbit is?
- Pat, it's minus one, not nine.
- You're looking at the thing, the other thing.
- You need to just do the Dex mod.
- Mod, or the balance ball mod.
- Yeah. - A little circle to the rabbit.
- Oh, okay. - Balance ball.
- For it, just for initiative.
- The balance ball side number.
- So my initiative is negative one?
- Yes. - Yeah.
- So you just subtract one when you roll a D20
to see if, roll for initiative.
- Now what's the bunny rabbit's name?
What is Roger and that's thirty feet is going to be your speed unless you guys
are little. I see two. I'm really little. Something just happened to my sheet.
Okay. You spit it on it. I laughed and then I spit. Mr. Patches, he spit it on
my God. Mr. Patches, I did.
I
spit it on his spit take and it inked. That's why I look like a sad mom. That's
why I brought spares. Let's just copy it onto the new sheet and try not to make a mistake
again, Patrick. I don't have enough for everyone in the class, so I just...
I cannot believe this turn. Wow.
You guys died.
Can I get an extra? I don't like how I roded my numbers.
No, let's just try to stick with what you got right now, and then we can see if we'll
see a little later. All right.
I'll call your mom. I don't care. Call my mom. Why?
Now, if you make me laugh, you know, that doesn't mean you're not in trouble.
What is my speed? Oh, 30.
What speed? I thought his name is Roger. What is my Roger?
Roger's 30.
I got a cross out speed.
Can you fix that for next time? Yeah, I'll fix that. I'm sorry about that.
You see, you're slowly resting control back. Do you like how I wrote Roger?
Yeah, I see. I had a similar idea.
I did a similar thing.
All right. Backwards letter. Now, do you like my Rs?
Yours are better than me and his is all of your hit.
Die are going to be one D10 for this.
So that is to just write one D10. And what is hit dice?
that's just what you use to cover your band aid band or dotted pill. I thought
that was yeah or a could be a nintendo switch flatbread. No toppings. I don't
know what flatbread is too childishly dumb. Okay, so what about so then
nintendo switch put one d ten just to have that in there and then there's a
little heart, little heart, big heart, maybe a butt and then a big but yeah,
what's my big but it's a heart, which one's very funny guys. So, oh upside
down. It looks like that's all right.
Quiet coyote. That's right. Okay, Max HP. That's your little heart is going to be
ten for everybody for this session. Okay, and your big heart for everybody. So
one zero thirty forty ten ten ten. That's pretty good though. One thousand. You
know, you're smart when you're trying to be funny. So the current HP will be
is
attack and a ranged attack for this one. So right now we have to say our intros? No, you
don't have to say your intros. We don't have to do that. We should do the intros and stuff
when the game starts. So what we will say is that we know that you guys are three twins
and it's Mother's Day. Who are your characters? I'm just going to be myself because I found
this guy that looks pretty similar. Here, wait, give me this camera. I mean it looks
just like and then Pat found one that looks like him too. And I found one that looks like
me. This looks like Patches when you put it next to him. Don't do that. Don't show that.
Mr. Patches. Mr. P. Mr. P. Mr. P. From Planet P. What's P stand for? Planet. Alright, okay.
Mr. Planet. It stands for Mr. Patches. Okay. See I can't even tell when you cut to that
angle because he's not even on frame anymore. Okay. You're not sure if I'm the blue alien
you're not anymore because of the angle. So that's basically who we are. Yeah.
Cool. Okay. So you guys are just yourselves, but you look fucked up.
I think that's like, you're just an armor. Can I,
can I just get into character real quick? Yeah. Go for it.
No way. Is that a whoopee cushion? Oh my God. What are you doing?
Patrick, why don't you describe what you just put on for the audio listeners
put on a bald cap that says I heart eating
you know. I thought we were going one way with this. I just got kicked out of
mom's room for you guessed it a panty raid. Why am I why is it a pain? Why am
I fucking trying to smell my own pants?
That's what the campaign was about. Whatever do well
well guys who am I
you can do it
don't make fun of patches
sorry
Okay, so you're me and I'm me. Wait, are we then you have to be me too, then? I
guess. Because if we're twins and two of us are identical, you gotta be him also.
Yeah, okay. Alright, so you don't have to actually.
You can make your own choice. Yeah, you could be three twins and just two of you
are identical.
And also, I don't even know about identical, by the way. It doesn't really
Oh yeah, no I'm wearing glasses. No, don't take that wasn't a problem. This is
gonna be now. I look just like him. I guess I'll just be Sir Lancelot.
Okay, so we got is it Caleb, Caleb and Sir Lancelot? I mean I'm Caleb. I don't
know about this guy. What's your name gonna be Pat? Because you ripped me off.
Just guess what my name is.
What? It's Caleb. Okay. It's Bilak. Bilak. Okay.
people are going to go crazy for be like so be like Caleb and Lance lot. I think
they'll make
that's going to make it easier. He fought for the honour of the title. You can't
certainly
yeah, you said,
I don't give a shit about it, so don't break my current angle and let's now, so
let's, let's come up with your attack. I do like him backwards. I do like so. So
what is, what is Caleb's melee attack backwards, walking directly at you, okay,
write that down and add one D six and add your strength modifier to it. Okay,
so backwards backwards walking directly into you.
We can have that have a we can have that have a chance to knock somebody prone
on a crit
is walking with a NG or just a G.
Have it our time. I did it with just a G.
and a modifier is so it'll be plus to your arm circle, your arm arm circle,
arm circles, your arm arm circle circle circle in the slot. I'll get to and the
damage damage. No, that's what it is. The damage your image is plus attack.
Attack is attack is is just
is plus two plus two. So it's four plus four. I had to do this. You mean twenty
two. I'm sorry.
Let me do this. This is my okay. I actually did explain. You could you not
have gotten us some easy character sheets? Yeah, I know.
The section that I was filling out, by the way, guys, no pictures.
Yeah, I don't know what this is. What were you thinking? Come on attacks?
Come on.
Why does it say my name?
Cameron attack. And I have one D6 plus two.
Yeah. Yeah.
You have to attack Cameron for this?
So, and what's your range attack going to be? What's Caleb's range attack?
It's walking backwards into you as your melee attack.
Jumping backwards onto you?
So it's range, but...
Okay, shit.
Like a slingshot or...
Ha, Hock-a-loogie.
Hock-a-loogie, love it. Okay.
So then just do Hock-a-loogie and then it's going to be...
Minus one is going to be the modifier.
I mean your attacks going to be 1d6 minus 1 because it's based on your balance ball circle.
My balance ball circle is shit.
Your balance ball circle is not very good.
And then do you want to have a special attack?
Yeah.
Alright, let's, do you have one in mind?
Pick him up and throw him.
Okay.
Pick up my twin, or one of my triplets and throw him.
I like the triplet attack. Pick up a triplet and throw them.
Pick up, how would I say that?
Just pick, uh. Pick up.
pick up, can I just write pick up and we'll know what I mean? Yeah, we'll know
what you mean. It's pick up. We won't forget it in an hour. Let's have that
be still based on your balance ball circle. But my balance ball's bad.
Can we have it based on my owl or my talkie?
Let's have it based on... On my arm? Let's have it based on your arm and
you're using them as a weapon. Okay. So it's less... So it's plus four again.
And then let's do one. Let's do one day ten.
One day ten
plus two plus two.
Yeah, I like that. And then you guys will also get to move a
little bit closer to an enemy from one of those. It'll be
there'll be some fun shenanigans there.
Okay. All right, Billak or do you want to be?
I don't know. He's Caleb.
Caleb also. I guess we're all named Caleb. Caleb Caleb also.
All named Caleb. What the fuck are you talking about?
the
All right, Caleb. Also, what is your attack going to be? I'm walking forwards.
You can't copy. No, first of all, you're copying my likeness. Let's create. We got to draw a line.
We got to draw. We're being we're being twin draw. He said you got to draw a line. Patrick
don't. Oh, Lordy. He drew. So my attack is a line. I walk in a line. You walk in a line. Shoot line.
shoot line. I don't steal something from you line rider. Hey Cameron, which what
iconic internet video should I steal from Patrick that he's made? Oh wait,
that's right.
Line rider. So what is what is line riding? I play line rider on my phone.
Is that a stupid? Okay, skip to me. Skip to you.
Bird about it. Hallbird right? Yeah, you've got a hallbird. Hallbird. That's
plus one one one six plus one. I'll add to cross plus three plus three for your
modifier because you're cross your modifier, not for your attack modifier
for your yeah, yeah, yeah cross bow. What is it balance ball minus
zero?
What's the damage one D six? Also one D six pad. I'm going to with our number
changed if it's a modifier. Oh sorry, it should be plus two. Oh sorry, minus two
- two - two - two special ability. You guys are not going to fireball fireball.
He a fireball okay
plus one hundred no damage one D one hundred. So make you know
so make that drag in stop it pet. Okay, okay, stop it
summon
stop. You can't have summons. I'm not going to let you have summons. I'll let
you shoot fireball fireball plus what
Plus three, let's say.
Damage?
One D10.
Straight.
One D10 straight, like it's a fire damage.
Okay, I'm done.
Okay.
Caleb also.
What did he write?
I have hit,
and then I have dodge.
Dodge?
You have dodge.
Dodge, dive, and dodge.
and then my special move is air fryer.
- Okay, what does air fryer do?
- I can shoot.
- Don't even say it.
- Unfortunately I kept it at 400 damage.
- Yeah, no, I can shoot fire from my mouth.
- You copied fireball, now we copy fireball.
- But only up to 400 degrees.
- Okay, I'm changing mine to lightning ball.
- He is the ultimate copier to the point
where he's copying my head.
- I didn't even hear that you did fireball.
I was trying to think too hard.
- Not paying attentioner.
- All right, so cops are hit.
attack. What about hot air? I can shoot hot air out of my breath. You can take
fire. I don't care. I'm having a skull attack. Skull attack. Why does he have
15 fucking abilities and I got dragon pit summon, but I got rid of it. Yeah,
he has the ability to summon. Then I'll write abilities. I can't use either.
Okay, right for hit. Let's add. So pat for that. Let's do plus four there and
then write one d six plus two for hit. One d six. You forgot how to write a d.
I watched that happen in real time. I drew an eye. Okay, so right one
number six, so you know, so you know that when you're looking at it,
I got busy with an eye and then one D plus six.
That is not anything that is awesome. That is really make this character
sheet path. That's what I'm trying to one D six plus one plus two
plus two. Okay, so that's one high plus six plus two, but no one know what it
one I D plus six plus two one idea
dodge. I guess is your rage to attack. Okay,
you have to you tell me. I don't know it's a car. I guess yeah, you use it
throw a car. Think of any funny Caleb abilities. You you came in here with
that prep. You could have all you spent all day writing this
on this. It's a very good joke. I found the bald cap here and I found a sharpie
okay,
so how about you sharpened an okay
I honestly wish I had that attack yeah, but mom won't let me you've got sharpie
you throw you get a part because of what I did to the coffee table. He drew on
and I drew a heart on it. I wrote four no, that's
I wrote plus one hearts mom on the coffee table and sharpie and it's one
I got banned from sharp -1 pitch.
And then special attack is what was that air fryer?
Yeah, and I can blow hot air out of my mouth up to 400 degrees.
Let's add your owl to that.
So let's do plus four, but it can probably get into 1d6.
You know, you could probably just so you know about the air
fire ability.
It could probably be jailbroken to go higher than 400.
I don't think you can jail.
You guys are you guys are so now we've got everything
settled. We've got Caleb, Caleb and Sir Lance a lot. And I'm gonna start the
campaign. One second.
Oh my God.
Can I wear that after you?
Yeah.
Can I wear that when the campaign is done?
I want your smell, Mr. P.
Mr. P.
Mr. P. I want that.
Let me sniff that wig.
I would do anything for a good grade.
it.
You look like Ricky Lake. I tried to get a
Karen wig and it's just cloud strife turns out. You guys are walking in the
class and I'm stopping you at the door like you guys have to see what Mr P is
wearing today. Damn, I can see Mr P's thong.
I heard Mr P's a stripper. No, I heard so too. After hours, yeah. Damn. After
three. To pay for school. To pay for school supplies for us. To pay for
pencils. To pay for pencils, Mr P's a stripper.
yeah and she listens to that which a finger eleven paralyzer yeah, god,
that's her dancing zone. It would be it's a great stripper song. Probably no
probably
probably a great
you guys wake up with the most epic of hangovers.
It's mother's day and last night you guys went hard. You barely even remember
know what you did, where you did it or who you did. Oh, I hope it was my mom.
You remember going to Big Mama's dude ranch in Motherland
Wyoming with your beloved mother on your annual Mother's Day trip with your mom
that you three take to get how old are we? How old are you guys?
Ten
in Sir Lancelot, how old are you?
but but fifty three from like the fourteen hundred so I was old and gray
yeah yeah you remember I'm like eighty yeah. Okay, you remember taking a trip a
day trip your impression of me my face. I'm not like that. I don't go like this.
You know that is not me remember taking a day trip to to the candy land
amusement park
and going to Peppermint Forest and licorice castle licorice. I barely know
You remember eating so much candy that you couldn't even see straight, and then you woke
up somehow back in the dude ranch, in Big Momma's Dude Ranch, but no mom.
And all of you have a distinct feeling that you did something.
I pat my penis.
You weren't going to do it again.
So before your phone is ringing, Patrick, your phone is ringing.
Before you pick up.
Say my name.
up though. Everybody get one of these. Is this an eye or a brain? Just to get two D10s. Can
I have a D10? Sorry, a D10 is a circle guy with five triangles if you look at it from
the top. If you look at it from the top you see five triangles. Okay, I have two D10s.
So
That's 29. What did you get?
58.
58. Okay, hold on.
29.
29 is Pat.
Right, you got 58.
You got Caleb.
All right, by that I mean Caleb and then Lancelot.
I thought I got a 92.
10.
4.
10-4, good buddy.
That's 14 for you.
Let's roll it again.
Everybody?
Yes, all of you again.
I got a zero.
Okay, just tell me when you get both of them.
And I got an 80?
I got 12.
84.
Or I got 210.
I got 07.
Okay, 07.
Reroll that zero.
Oh, sorry, no, just keep the zero.
I'm an idiot, I should've done that before.
You got 77.
So you actually got seven,
and you actually got nine before, Pat.
I'm sorry, I forgot.
It's just if you get two zeros and you get 100.
Oh, then I got four.
You got four?
Okay, yeah, that's my bad there.
I'm sorry, I got confused.
Then why don't you just read them as zeros?
Um, cause I'm stupid. Who's 0-4? Who got 4?
Me.
You did. Kayla and then Pat you got 12 right?
Yeah.
And then Cam you got 7.
7.
Alright, let's start here. And now I'm gonna do a little roll. And you guys can't look.
I guess I'll give it a roll.
Cam where you going? Oh he can't hear me.
Cam where you going?
Okay. I know who fucked mom.
You do?
Uh oh.
Oh, wait, we fucked mom? We fucked our mom?
Well, you'll find out in a second.
I hope it was me. I'm Caleb.
This is character assassination.
I hope that I did it, and I hope I made it stink.
Hold on. Okay, so what you guys just rolled for was on a random table of things that might have happened last night.
What the hell are you doing over there?
And we're going to find out slowly throughout the course of the adventure
what's been going on, what you guys did.
Okay.
Oh, that's a fun one.
And then pad again.
I don't understand my pantomimes.
Oh no. Okay.
That one sucks, but it's fine.
I got chat GBT to make some of these.
You can replace them if it's not good.
Yeah, I guess I can.
But I try to have the integrity of the game.
All right, I'll do that one.
I'll replace it.
It's his fault you're allergic to him.
Yeah, I'm dying.
What do you smell?
I don't know.
I get it.
OK, and then Caleb.
Yes, that's stupid. It's got a better one. Caleb. Yes. Can you turn the autofocus on
cams camera off? Yeah. It's a little blurry. Hi, Jubio. Hi. What are you up to? That's a good one.
I'm drinking water and watching the show. The show? Oh, this show? This show that I'm doing.
Okay, all right, maybe I'll fill time by singing a song. No, no, we're good.
No, we're good.
Okay, cool.
We he your phone is ringing Pat Caleb. Okay,
it's your father. His name is just Caleb. Don't say Pat Caleb. My name is
Caleb twin say so. So Caleb, your name's case. You guys, his names are
They're both Caleb. Okay, Caleb. Yeah, Caleb twin. But the Caleb I'm looking at.
What? Your phone is
not bad. Your phone is ringing. Do I sound like a frog? Hello? Okay, wait,
Peck. Peck, go again. What?
This does not sound like me. What do you want, dad? Fuck you. Son. I have a
piss poor attitude. I did not ever have a piss poor attitude. Growing up, I was
sweet as a dandelion.
Hi son, just wanted to see how you and your brothers and mother were doing on your dude
ranch vacation.
I love when you guys go away right before Mother's Day and I don't know what happens.
Um, last night we uh, there, um.
I was just wondering where your mother was.
I've been trying to call her for a little while and she hasn't picked up so I was wondering
if you guys knew.
I think she's dead.
No, she's not dead.
Dead, dead.
She's not dead.
I, I, uh, she's not, this is the other Caleb by the way.
Oh, hi son.
She's not dead.
Yeah, she's dead.
No, she's not dead.
We don't know where she is.
She's dead from bullshit.
This is not, he's acting weird.
Okay.
She is.
And I hate my-
I am Sir Lancelot.
[Laughter]
This is what my voice sounds like.
Okay, so basically.
[Laughter]
Me, Caleb, and Sir Lancelot. We woke up, we have no idea where Mom is.
Oh no.
Bob's a bitch!
We basically don't even remember what happened last night.
You guys eat too much candy again?
Yes.
(laughter)
Maybe Sir Lancelot did. I barely had any candy last night.
I expect better from you, Sir Lancelot.
I'm sorry, Dad.
It's alright, it's alright. Just, if you don't know where your mother is, I need you guys to find her.
Searching.
(laughter)
when I say that I'm walking around the room. Sorry, does dad I that really
feels like a job for the police. Not really three kids. Well, who? Yeah, I'm
50. I'm 10. If you're the Children of the month, you have to find your mother
on Mother's Day. I'll call the cops. Okay, just at least all right. Can't
paint over at least just, you know, I'll call the cops. No, I'll report.
Well, she hasn't been gone more than 48 hours. So yeah, it's true. That's part
of the issue. All right, so I guess I'll go. I'm done with the robot voice,
Dad, the house stinks. You are in a hotel weird. Do you mean hotel rooms
smells and you're not here? It doesn't look anything like our house smells like
fucking clams and shit. Sir Lance a lot.
You feel a rustling in your pants.
Well, okay, and you're wearing arbor in your grieves my grieves. Yeah, you have
chain mail on underneath that. You just hear sort of a banging going on and roll
a constitution saving throw. Oh, whoa, sorry, what I'm sorry roll a heart roll
and then add the circle heart.
That's an eighteen add circle heart yeah give him a second. I did oh, whoa,
you did that in your head fast. My circle hearts one. Oh, you feel a sharp
bite on your leg.
it's Tom and Jerry, but you're not so you're you're you're feeling a little
woozy right now after that bite
you the dad says here your dad hears you go be ouch. He goes Sir Lancelot,
are you all right? Yeah, Dad, I just fell down the stairs. All right, well,
be careful because you haven't taken the armor off. We in that penthouse bitch.
So yeah, there's an echo on my voice too, which I'm not going to put on the
soundboard, but I'm so I have not raised my my visor.
Look, just let me know where your mother is so that we can have a great Mother's Day back
home.
I can't wait to see all three of you and your mother again.
I'm addicted to you, Dad.
I love you.
I'm addicted to you, too, son.
I love you so much, Daddy.
I love you, too.
All right, kids.
We're that kind of dad and kid who kiss on the lips.
Yep, we are.
I love you, Daddy.
Dad, what channel is Cartoon Network on in this TV?
Last time I watched it, it was 32.
It's not on 32 here.
not on thirty.
It's fifty seven
Xbox into the TV idiot.
I'm trying. I've never seen what we
have. Cartoon Network saved to the
Xbox. Oh, I forgot.
OK, Daddy, have a good day at work.
I love you. Love you.
What's up? And you just stay on the
line.
Yeah, I can just hang out for a
little bit. You guys are probably
really nervous.
My first hotel stay without
Sir Lance. I roll another
constitution saving throw.
OK. OK, Daddy.
that's a fifteen. Okay, you feel another bite
on your inside your greaves starting to sound a lot like Tom and Jerry. Hey
daddy, yeah, something's biting his wiener.
Daddy, don't listen to him. There's nothing wrong. I think it's a
I don't want to worry. I don't want dad to worry about my
mommy.
It's where he has enough to worry about with mom. I just don't need him to
know about my wiener bite. Okay, daddy, there's nothing going on with Lance's
my wiener doesn't hurt daddy. Did you pay for xbox live this month? I did yes.
Dad, did you pay for loot crate? I can you got change? I don't remember what I
don't remember.
I don't remember what
it is. So
hello fresh this month. Can you get the hello fresh sent to the hotel? Daddy,
none of us have any money. How are we going to eat? Do we have frozen mac here
dad? Do we order room service? Daddy, I got room service for you guys.
this morning.
We hang up on yeah you here
at the door. I answer the
oh wait, no, I look through the people who is a and I put the chain on okay,
that's got to be that's got to be owl yeah. I was looking yeah. That's a good.
I mean it's an owl. It's owls fuck dude. You look through the people, but I
still don't raise my visor okay, yeah, you have to roll for this so far. So
far you're just being a person, so you you look to the people
when you see a guy in a fedora and a big gangster is most suit that is not room
dad and he's doing sort of this kind of thing way wait. It's mom open the door.
I knock back
can I come out?
Can you let
oh wow that's a
never heard of that.
Can you open the door?
hello, we're waiting roll a d four
one
oh boy, this guy hates us yeah
open the door. You son of a fucking bitch and you hear a gun of what a gun
being pulled out. I'll have you know that fucking bitch is missing and the
police are on a trail roll dexterity saving throw
so what sorry roll a circle balance ball roll the dice and then add your circle
balance ball balance ball circle. You mean subtract my balance ball, yeah
subtractor yeah for you, yes, what you got eight okay
you got a one yeah, I did so a spray of bullets comes
the door. I'm wearing armor with Tommy gun, ten and you take one damage from
he's coming out through the door and damage lowers my heart. It lowers your
lowers your big heart, big heart, your little heart stays the same. He's I'm
going to get you so Lance, you son of a fucking bitch and you guys hear that
going on from outside like a hole. I'm going to total de munch guys. Oh wait
guys. I have an idea open that door and I will backwards walk directly.
okay, oh yeah, he's going to think that he's going to think that it's a
door.
He's going to think that he's chasing me, so he'll run after me. We'll meet in
the middle and then we can close the door on his face. Okay, I'll count to
three open the door one
on
the
okay, fling the door open, okay, and I start walk. I start backwards walking
directly at him. Okay, roll. I guess I'm just gonna skip an issue. Roll an attack,
roll. Sorry. Sneaky. Roll the 20 die and add your... He's the biggest one. Yeah,
you'll roll the biggest die and then add your top common attack. Add your top
common attack modifier first. 20. Okay, wow, that hits for sure. And then roll
one D six. So it's a square yeah and then add plus two
that's a sit nice very good. So yeah you walk backwards into this guy while he's
spraying he's spraying bullets. You just see him like spraying bullets and like
it's going to pass the camera. I don't think you just see you walking back.
I would like to add directly and directly it's a backwards directly. You
see the profile of this moment of you just slowly walking back. You just he's
this
to show show everyone is like, but my arms are still swinging
walking backwards, and this is also my face the
as I walk directly backwards. This kid's insane and that's the face that I make
you knock into this guy. He takes some serious damage for him. Yeah, no shit. I
walk backwards in him, so he's he's he's like what the fuck was that? Who are you?
You're supposed to go to have to turn around to talk to you about that.
And he, you see him, he starts to get up to take out his gun again and start
shooting it at you. What do you want to do? I am going to use my sharpie.
You're going to use your sharpie? Okay. And I'm going to try and throw it
directly into the barrel of the gun. Nice. Okay, roll the biggest die and add
your circle balance ball. Plus two more.
you get a one yeah, you got a one okay man you write I heart eating shit on
your forehead. What the hell? Oh no,
no God, what happens? Yeah, it's got to be actually bad. That video was a
natural one
natural seven came naturally to one maybe okay. You natural million views
plus you throw you throw you throw the sharpie at
Okay, yeah, you throw the sharpie and it gets inside of Sir Lancelot's armor and
Sir Lancelot, you're gonna- it's like stuck inside your helm right now and it's
just rattling around in there and so you're gonna have a disadvantage on
attacks, but you're up to Sir Lancelot, by the way. That's the order. Hey, who
turned out the lights in a- in one sharpie shaped area? That's what I say.
Okay, well, also- sorry, roll another constitution saving throw. Oh. 'Cause
you're not taking care of what's in your pants. What's constitution?
Sorry, roll heart, roll 17. Roll real heart, not fun heart. Realistic heart.
Realistic heart. Let's just call it stomach. Stomach, let's just call it
stomach. It looks more like a stomach to me. Yeah.
17. 17's boring you too.
So then you, yeah, you're fine. You get bit again by whatever is inside your
grease. We need to take that thing out and throw it in his face. Okay, I
rummage around in my penile area as my brother wants me to it's called a
crotch. Okay, find a big snake in your greaves actual fucking
trousers.
I'm scared
I
damn nice fucking boner
is big. Well, my my armor also has a huge cod piece. The one that like the
medieval ones where it looks like a giant dick. Yeah, yeah, so do you what
do you do with the snake
jacks it off. You jack off the snake. I'd point it at the guy and I'd swing it
like a whip. Okay, let's - cool. Roll arm, add arm, and then add arm circle,
and then add two more. Okay, 19. Okay, and then - cool. So then roll one
round triangle. Yes, the good. Yeah, roll that triangle twice.
The single triangle or the double triangle? Single triangle. Okay. Seven.
Nice. So yeah, describe the way that you dispatch of this gangster. Well,
honestly,
that's gonna be nasty, but the snake doesn't even touch him and just the whiff
of the groinal stank funk that has been brewing in that armor for 53 long years.
You've never taken it. I don't know what a shower is. I don't know a bath never
taken off the armor.
It is. Wait, what's your deal? Why are you in this world?
I don't know. It was kind of an impulse thing after I found out that there was
gonna be two of the same guy. I was kind of planning on just being me, but then I
was like, I don't really know what I'm supposed to do here. I kind of got
thrown in. You're also all trifling. Well, you're already- A curve ball. You're
pretty sir. You think you got there on a curveball? Look at him. Does this look
good, by the way? He looks like a curveball.
So you just, the groinal stank. Yeah, you watch this, yeah, it's Raiders of the
Lost Ark, right? Like his face is melting.
It's like a power wash video. Yeah, and he's like, "I'll get you for this,
watch out!" And he just like melts. How are you gonna get us for this? You're
fucking dead. Wait, his whole body melts? Just his face. Oh, okay. Can I loot him
immediately. You can loot him immediately. I shit on his bones. Okay,
yeah, you get $77.
Where do I write this? This guy was rich as fuck. Wherever you want.
Am I allowed to cuss? Yeah, you can cuss. Yeah, you write, you get 77 bucks.
You get his, his, you know, his ID, which says Tony Spumoni. I mean,
it's fucking, he's just some gangster. This says it's some fucking gangster ID.
Yeah.
This gangsters attack like yeah, yeah, walker gangster.
Can I say that word? Can I steal his clothes? You can steal his clothes.
Okay, it's a really big suit on him and he's an adult. Oh, can I have
one? Can I have a sock?
Hand raised. You want one sock? Can I have one sock? Yes, you can have
one sock. I already have a sock. What else does he have in his inventory?
Put it back into my pants. Argyle pattern. You put it in your pants?
Well, I put the snake in the sock and I put it back in my
pants. So the snake can't bite me through the sock. But you still have the
snake.
He's like putting, yeah, like he's, like it's his golf club. I tie off the
sock. I know the snake's gonna get out of the sock if I turn upside down.
Okay, you're gonna turn us upside down. I put the suit on. You see the snake,
it's like foiled again. I put the suit on, I say.
Guys, look at me, I'm a preacher. Nice. What else is in his inventory? I
grabbed, actually I grabbed the Gideon Bible from the hotel room. He has a
at
the dingleberries. Plus one, it's going to be on that. And then that's going to be a
2D4.
Real quick, I'd like to see what he's working with downstairs.
2D4 plus.
Sure.
Or minus.
Nothing, just 2D4 straight.
Nothing?
Oh, no wonder this guy wanted to kill us.
He's playing.
No, it's like, I don't know, like, it's a little bit below average, but...
I knew it. Spamoni.
Not startling, but like a little...
I would like to interrogate him.
He's dead.
don't care. I would like to grab him. Sure. Where the fuck is my mom, you
stupid son of a bitch? And so, you know, you're shaking him. I take his,
like, you know, the skull falls off. What else is in his inventory? He's
avoiding the question. That's about it. I mean, his clothes, his money. Oh,
you know, I didn't even think about that. He has a flip phone. I take his
flip phone. Nice. And I call the first number on speed dial. Oh, no, yes,
hit redial, hit redial. Yeah, hit redial.
Hello. Hello. Hello. Hi, Mom. Do what is the my head is flying off Antonio?
Yes, it's me. My head is flying off and melting.
Antonio, so silly. I'm actually we killed your son. Yeah, it's actually
three random. I killed your fucking son. Happy Mother's Day.
And we're from the fart Department. Yeah, we're checking in on your
the far
yeah, this is actually the part apartment. You hear a heart and I
start just pressing buttons on the phone like
bitch yeah, she's dead on the other. Okay, so then I crack my knuckles and
okay guys. I think I'm ready to find mom and then I all right, so I'm going
to hit the next number. I'm going to hold down to on speed dial. See who
is
just roll d twenty. I'll come up with one based on the dural like I like that.
What do you get fourteen? Okay,
you got
the it's a guy named
Dino Dino Bianco. Okay,
really breaking out my racism here. Okay, yeah, Dino a Dino Dino Dino where you
been? I thought you were done with that night already. Oh, this is ups and we
and you're and where you're waiting on a package to be dropped.
You have a stinky package.
Your kids need to be dropped off at the pool.
Yeah, the Cosby kids.
Tony, Tony, what the fuck is this?
Hey, did you order?
This is the fart department and we are.
Did you order one million farts, sir?
You know what?
Call me when you fucked up fucking killed that night.
You got that money.
Oh, Donald Trump.
What's going on?
Calling on behalf of the fart department.
I'm calling because I want you to be the treasurer of the Fart Department.
Roll talking.
Okay.
Which I would, which roll?
The big one?
Yeah, big one.
Okay.
Big one talking.
14.
Nice.
Okay.
Oh, Mr. President, I'm sorry, I didn't realize you, how'd you get Tony's phone?
No, never mind.
Forget I asked.
It doesn't matter, don't worry about it.
I won't.
The thing is, I want you to be, I want you to lead up the new Fart Department in my administration.
In Miami.
(laughing)
- And I'm going to, I'm not gonna buy your ticket.
- Oh my God.
- You gotta buy it yourself.
- I will reimburse you once we--
- I'm moving to Saudi Arabia.
- Yes. - Eiji!
Eiji!
- What?
- I'm gonna run the fart department in Miami.
(laughing)
- That's just my burp.
I burp like that.
- I burp like-- - That's amazing, Mr. President.
- I burp like three little boys laughing
on the other end of a phone.
A lot of people tell me this.
this
yet to go on to face book your face book page
you know i'm not that united
near alright long island dad against dot is dating
the thing that you have to write on the wall that's what i would tell you that
the kids dot is dated as a set of post on that group and i got to say i like i
I got into that group through the Knights of Columbus, actually.
Yeah, you have to say, "I'm okay with my daughter dating a black guy."
Oh, Mr. President.
I mean, no offense, you've done so much.
Do you want to be the head of the fart department?
Or do you want to stay in Long Island forever?
Or else you're going to go to jail.
Or you'll be in jail.
And one more thing.
Do you want to be the head of the fart department or you can go to jail?
We'll check up on you later.
I will, I mean.
But one more thing you have to do.
It sounds like there's two of you talking to me.
It's an echo.
Don't worry about it.
People say I'm so talented like a bee.
Two places at once people say that.
Listen, I want you to go to PennIsland.com and I want you to fill out, there will be
a form there.
It's just a little, you just have to do it, okay?
It's a little application.
You already got the job, don't worry about it.
But I'm done.
Also, you got to go...
And stay on the line while you go to PennIsland.com.
PennIsland.com.
I'm writing this down.
Okay, then the next thing you need to do, you need to go into your family's Facebook group,
you need to go into the Bianco family,
Bianco Family United Facebook group and you have to write, "Mama's meatballs are
not good." And also you have to... Oh, Mr. President, I can't do that. Also,
you have to go... On the day of all days. You have to go and get
a silly haircut, then you have to keep it for at least a month.
You have to serve and be realness.
you have to put a silly haircut with a funny hat. Yep,
and you have to wear it to work. Then you have to get a tattoo of a Dorito.
Okay, bye.
Okay, yeah. So you guys did that? Yeah, yes, you guys can go. Okay, I'd like
to step over his body. I would like to leave the charge. Wait, wait, wait,
what?
We didn't hang up and he's still on the phone.
And we hung up. I already said hung up. We hung up.
We just hear him.
What would happen if he didn't?
Outside of his house.
What would happen?
Outside of his house, we just hear just a mob of his own family and a bunch of
Long Island dancers.
Get your fucking ass out here!
What the fuck you mean black guys?
I would like to, I would like to hold my brother's hands because that's how we
get everywhere.
Okay, cool.
And I would like to walk up.
When you do that, your walking speed increases by five feet.
Amazing, because I only have 25 feet.
I would like to walk up to the receptionist at the front desk. All
right,
all of
that's not gonna make sense. Yeah, why not all of you roll a D four
okay,
tiny triangle three one one three eleven
we just we an amber ray appears. You see the receptionist and he just starts
to like kind of like
back away and kind of like start to go under a desk. Hey,
fuck face
What do you want? A hundred dollars? No, no, no, no. You already asked me for
that last night. We're from the fart department.
Where's that gangster that came in here?
Because I'm wearing armor, but I'm Donald Trump.
I look like three guys, three little kids. Hearing Donald Trump's voice
coming out of armor.
Listen, okay, so I need one thing from you, my friend.
Where's the, where's that, the, the, the, the, the, the swarthy fellow who came in?
Well, yeah, let's just say you'll be sweeping his fucking brains into a bin
later on. Okay. But listen to me,
what happened last night? Because I can't find my mommy.
And if I don't find my mommy on mother's day,
I'm not going to be too happy.
Okay. I'll try to tell you what happened. Um, all I know is
in order. Don't be jumping back and forth mementos like I would never
ray don't and do not whatever you do. Do not tell it through the medium of a
disposable camera and
I do not want to see Polaroids
everything that happened last night. He opened his drawer and he closed it up.
And it better not be and better not have a
heart topping song under this montage. Do not play I'm blue and I'm feeling
all right. Do not play that song. Okay, he puts away his iPod. Yeah, do not
play. He's really strapping him right now. Okay, well, all I know is that
you three came in last night
with your mom. You were all
very, you were very much, you were on candy. You were on a lot of candy.
Candy flipping.
You
Caleb, you were wearing like a robe, like a black robe.
We did karate.
And you...
Caleb.
Yeah, we're both named Caleb.
We're identical twins, idiot.
No worries, no worries.
You got up on the desk and you started telling jokes.
I think you thought they were, you were kind of slurring your words a lot and
uh, everybody was laughing and I was trying to tell you guys to please go to
your room and um,
you just seem kind of, uh, agitated.
He can't hear you so well with that.
Yeah. Put your, put your mouth up to the, the ear hole on his helmet.
Okay. Yeah, I'll do that. Um,
You can't? Oh damn, that would be funny.
So you, well, you seemed kind of agitated and you kept putting your hand down
your pants.
Oh, I figured out why that was. We solved that next.
It was a snake.
And now he put a golf sock on it.
And when I told you guys to please, please go to your room or I'd have to
call management, you tried to pay me with some sort of jewel.
Can I have it back?
Oh, boo hoo.
I mean, you didn't give it to me. You said you kept doing, "Here you go," and
then eventually I was like, "Okay, I'll take it," and you pulled it away.
Wait, Jewel, the object...
That was crazy.
I knew that was... I could feel it. I could feel that coming.
And then you had just the craziest twist on it.
No, I meant the singer songwriter, Jule. Jule the object. The object.
Wow. I think so. He said... Jule was here. He looked blank in a
way that he couldn't even... Didn't know he could look blank at someone.
And then he says, "Yeah.
Holy shit, you guys.
I mean, you feel in your pocket now and as you pull it out, you see a tiny
jade monkey, but like made of pure jade with diamonds in its eyes.
And roll owl circle.
Okay.
All of us?
Just him.
Just Caleb.
With the biggest dice?
Biggest dice owl circle.
That doesn't count because I dropped it.
I know, I know it doesn't count.
Well, it was the same number.
What was it? Holy shit. Is that a four? Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. Well, with that whole circle, plus two is six.
Roll hit.
Roll big dice, big dice.
Add four.
That is a ten.
Okay, roll damage.
That's the next column in the common attacks.
Six. Okay, plus two, right?
So it's eight.
Yeah. You hear
and then you just punch this guy in the face. Whoa. Without like you black out
for a second and why in the face and he's like,
what are you? What are you doing? Caleb?
I don't care. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
And you I meant to do that and you notice that you are wearing those black
robe still and that is where you pulled that monkey. Oh, I'm gonna well, I have a
Tommy gun now, right? You also have a Tommy gun. Are you gonna Swiss cheese this
guy right here right now? I was thinking about it, but no, I think I'm just gonna
check my own pockets more. Guys, check your pockets. I check my pockets. Nothing.
I have, I don't check mine. It's a waste of a check. I have cloth pockets,
- You, you, but yeah, when you, the guy,
like he's holding his nose, he's not looking good.
- That's a lot of damage for like a regular NPC.
- Yeah, no, that was crazy, a lot of damage.
I thought that was damage happening to me.
- No, no, no.
- I was kind of excited.
- He just goes, okay.
And then yeah, you did something similar last night.
Your eyes glowed green for a second.
And then you guys all went to your room
and I saw your mom wander off and then I went home.
something said he punched you last night and have you had a long rest since then.
Yeah,
just checking. Okay, so you're not dead. No. Okay.
And then yeah, you guys went,
you guys went to your room and your mom said she'd meet with meet up with you
guys and then she fell asleep in the lobby of and I went home.
Our mom fell asleep in the lobby. Yeah, the dude ranch lobby. You have security
cameras in here.
Um, yeah, we do. Okay, I'm going to need you to take me to those post-haste. I don't know
if I can. Guys, this is like a lot. Have you ever seen a Tommy gun? You know, from one
of those like old school like movies? No, I don't know. Have you ever seen a skull attack?
I pull out the Tommy gun and I just shoot into the roof. I have seen a skull attack.
Have not seen that. Let me take you to the cameras. Okay, let's go. All right, so he
goes to the back room. He goes to like the CTD cameras. Okay. I hate skipping ahead,
to rewind to the very, very first minute you have recorded
of the of like the first day you guys opened
that was we okay. I'll go back to when we first got it like nineteen seventy
okay, like one one one fine by me yeah. You had a security camera in nineteen
seventy very advanced. Yeah, we were the first dude ranch to do that
yeah. You just see now are right on thirty five mill.
sorry,
takes up like forty five minutes to get it all set up all right. He's like
he's like that you don't hear anything. Yes, you just see like a celebration.
Play some fucking piano while we watch this
yeah sure one second. He takes out an iphone app and he's like a
playing. He's just playing
yeah, wait, let me show you something
wait. I got one too
do do do do do do do do do do do
yeah yeah yeah okay
all right now i now that i've gotten a suit of armor
now i've gotten
i feel like i've gotten sufficient backstory i would like to see my mom get
let hurt yeah or let her show me crank it faster. Show me when you when it
faster and it turns into a computer and he starts to and you see you see
you guys coming in and you see you see you are wearing this like black robe
that you are wearing and you're like holding your hand tip. You're holding
your yeah, you're you're you're sure
you're holding your hands up and it's a small penis speaking in tongues and
walking around you and your suit of armor, you're reaching into your pants
and trying to find whatever's happening. You keep looking over your shoulder
also and like you keep you hear somebody very faintly. It's like you would,
I guess you can't in these ctv cameras. You can hear you hear somebody like
yelling after you. You are talking about a great set great set and then you
start to get up on top of the thing and you start doing kind of like a
rambling stand up set that doesn't quite make like anything. You're kicking off
the notebook off the thing and your mom is just cracking up. She's cracking up
and then you were making mommy laugh. He was rising up mommy. Yeah, and then
big surprise and then yeah, you then the thing happens where you just like
punch him in the face. I don't know where what's someone doing outside trying
to come inside. They're not allowed to come in if they want and then he's
trying to come in. So when we know you punch this guy in the face and when you
do, you also look directly at the camera, Pat, like your eyes are just green for a
second and then
yeah, your head's now in the way of the camera as you're doing the stand up and
then, then you guys, it's like that kind of just happens for another like 20
minutes. He like fast for like this kind of just happens a lot. He fast forwards
a bit and you guys start you guys, you get down off the desk,
you start floating back to your room and then you guys follow you got ability
and then oh my God, I can wait wait. Can I try it? Yeah, you try it now.
Oh my God,
I got so long.
I even realize there's some stuff's worked out with your figurine there, but
and you see your mom kind of go like oh no, like I'll see you guys later. She
kind of like waves off. You see the guy fast forward, you see him going home
wiping blood from his face, you see the mom like passed out, you see your mom
passed out on the couch, and then you see a dark figure in a hood go up
and like grab her.
You said in a hood? In a hoodie, like a hoodie. A dark figure in the hood.
No, you didn't say from the hood. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
nothing like that.
Like just like in a sweatshirt and a hood. He's still in the Long Island
character. Yeah
and
you see them like picking up your mom, walking out and she's like and she's
like kind of passed out and then like leaves and that's what you see
and guys like, oh God,
can you rewind all that
from the I have to pee real quick. Me too. Let's do a quick pee break. Okay,
I'll be to
okay. We're back.
Oh yeah, so you guys saw your mom get sort of abducted or carted away by a strange figure.
What are you two laughing at?
I make Cameron laugh.
Okay, very funny. We have cameras on us. Really fucking funny.
I can't see the screen so I never know.
You gotta look at that one.
Okay.
patches. You can look into that one.
It's just not working. Okay, just continue. Let's go. Okay. So what you
guys want to do? You guys were just giving this information. Okay, so
where I'm going to run a database search for everybody with a hood.
Everybody wearing way. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, you are wearing black
robes. Does your black robe of a hood?
Does it does have a hood? Wait, put the hood on.
Okay, I would like to
I would like this. I would like to set him next to the basically. Yeah. Okay. I
know. Yeah. Mom,
did you fuck mommy?
I'm Caleb and I fucked mommy. No, you don't know though. You didn't fuck
mommy. I can check his wiener. I did. I checked my wiener. The first thing I
woke up brothers, wait brothers. This is nasty. But Caleb, you need to smell
Caleb's wiener. I checked my wiener as soon as I woke up and it was sticky.
Okay. I will check his wiener because, but just because I'm a good,
I can't say who fucked mom. Just wait, check my wiener,
but do it as Donald Trump. So it's not weird. Okay. That was a central mystery.
Okay. I'm going to completely look at my brother's permanent.
My brother's penis. Check your wiener, sir. They're looking at my wiener.
Okay. Okay. I can't, I have to be normal. So it's not. Cause then if you look at it,
then it's Donald Trump's wiener. Okay, I'm looking at your penis. What am I seeing?
Mr. President, you ruined Kemp's camera again. No, I didn't. He did. Fuck you. You kind of
look like Donald Trump with that wig. I look like Donald Trump and I also sound a lot like
Donald Trump. My Donald Trump is not that good. He's not as good as yours. He has bugs.
I have bugs inside of my Donald Trump. I'm talking about his wiener. He has bugs. He
does not have bugs inside of his wiener.
I'm saying he has bugs.
There's a cockroach on my penis.
There's a cockroach riding your penis like it's a rocking Bonko.
He fucked a bug.
I might have fucked a bug last night and it made me just so hard that I fell
asleep.
A bug that takes a human cock.
We know that the other Caleb stole mom, but where would where would you?
Well, we don't know can we can't we can't see the face right?
Okay.
Wait, hold on.
Hold on.
Wait, let me I'm going to do something really quick and hands.
it. Oh, sorry, yeah, it enhances. Okay, and you can't see the face, but
what about the build
roll brain circle with a big? I should not roll brains. I roll brain. I have
a really bad brain circle. Okay, okay, okay, you pick just pick one person to
do it. I will roll brain circle with a see if I remember it's himself. See if
I remember if I did that. See if you can enhance better. That is a fifteen.
you know it's not him. Okay, but okay, you know, but it's the same the same
clothes, same wait a minute and I checked the tag.
You check the tag of your robes. Yeah, no, there is no tag.
Receptionist
receptionist. Tell me,
did we give you any indication last night of where we were coming from?
Well, sort of.
You kept talking about a great set. You kept muttering about the circle.
Oh, the circle. Let's go back to the circle.
I don't know what that is though.
Okay.
But it seemed like you guys were coming from some kind of festival or something.
Oh.
You kept talking about the festival and the party.
There was a gathering in the woods last night, but other than that...
There was? What woods? Can you tell us where?
Can you tell us where?
Sure.
Well, it's the Big Mama's Woods, nearby the Big Mama's Dude Ranch, which is where we're
on.
Some people were prepping.
There was sort of a pre-party.
There's a big...
Well, Vile Cacaille is jumping over a huge bus today.
And so there was like the finish setting it up and then they had a big...
That's the biggest stretch of a name you've ever...
Vile Cacaille.
It's pretty bad.
Vile Cacaille?
you don't like vile kakail
sit that bad to that dog shit. Definitely not good. It's me on the
Amtrak coming back from work
like vile kakail.
What about bad Chad?
Could have done bad Chad, but it won't it wouldn't be the same. You wouldn't
immediately know it was no yeah, but also it also wouldn't be horrible. Is
you know that's true. I've done horrible and couldn't evil okay, because I
already had an evil steel, regardless of so there is a big characters,
terrible name. I would like for you to take us to these woods right fucking
now. Oh,
you still have the gun. Okay, yeah, so this guy, this receptionist and I'm
looking in down the barrel of the gun, yeah, he leads you guys to the woods
and yeah, you go faster.
It's moving as fast as he can
faster and
clank like like right behind him
and yeah you get to the woods. You get to this clearing where there is this
like huge. It's not six buses in a row. It's a bus. It's as long as six buses.
You see a bunch of people gathered. You see people with beer. It's going to be
the first like this guy jumping over this huge long bus and there was a
party last night about it, and so let's roll.
let's roll a general. Let's roll D fours. Everybody to get a general sense of how
you handled hanging out with people last night to okay. Another one of only
ones two one four. So we're looking at not great, but not terrible. Not that
bad. Not that four is good, though four is very good. So like with a one that
was very bad. So two it's kind of leaning on everybody hates Sir Lance a
lot.
Everybody hates his fucking guy. Sit down. So you're sitting to see everybody
So you, yeah, they see you in the robe and they go, and you see a vile Cacayo sees you
and goes, "Caleb!" and he comes up to you and he's like, "What up?"
You are a fucking legend.
Sounds like me.
I love you, man.
How are you doing, man?
Last night.
Last night was mad real.
Sunglasses and Advil.
Yes.
What's the other, yeah.
That's something that the pastor don't preach.
Yeah. Thanksgiving disguised as a feast. He was doing that all last night. Where did he
go? What's up? Hello. You. Oh. I told you not to bring him here, man. He's whack. That's
my baby brother, yo. I'm no whack. He's just in armor. Hey. You almost ruined this entire
event. Kyle today. Tell me you weren't that much of a help. I mean, I wasn't
great from what I understand from my role, but two out of four, that's 50%.
I don't know what you're talking about. Listen, where was okay. So hypothetically,
he was a one last night, right? Yeah, I was. He tried to ride my bike. He got on
my bike and pretended it was a steed and tried to drive away with it. He's lying.
sounds like he was the life of the party and you're being a bitch. The life of
the party. Oh wait, I never told you that was a dare. I did
bro roll roll talking, talking with circle
great one. Wait, wait,
that's a crit one minus two. He just missed picking up the negative one.
That's so bad. He goes, why are you trying to cover for him?
Because he's old and my brother.
So I'm basically the cooler Caleb now.
Because of that whack ass role.
What do you guys want?
What happened, what, okay so what I was getting at is if he was a one and he was a four last
night and I'm a two, what was our mama?
Your mom was cool, she was just kind of hanging out with Drake.
Cool enough to fuck?
Did she seem slutty?
Yeah she was hanging out with Drake a lot but other than that.
Drake the rapper?
You don't know him?
Drake was here last night.
I know, I know, I know.
I know Drake, personally.
No wait, Drake was here for real though?
Yeah, Drake was here.
With our mommy?
He was hanging out with you guys too.
He was laughing when you were riding around the motorcycle.
Were we popping champagne?
Do you like me?
I don't know if he liked you.
Yo, chill, chill.
Drake like me?
Last night?
Chill.
Chill, bro.
Chill bro.
Drake was laughing at my antics last night everybody.
Chill.
You're going to look like a fucking dork in front of everyone again.
Drake could not get enough of me.
I can't say that you're drunk as an excuse anymore because now you're sober.
Okay, wait so did Drake and my mom kind of hit it off?
Did Drake hit my mom?
Off of the...
(laughing)
- Sorry.
I didn't see him hit her.
- But were they getting along?
- They seemed to be getting along.
- Okay, a couple more questions.
Why the fuck is he dressed like that?
- Oh. - New thing.
- I don't know, he showed up like this.
He looks-- - And why am I dressed like this?
- I don't know.
You're-- - Medieval vibe.
- I'm gonna, you gotta get this guy outta here.
- What? - I'm done.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, kitchen! - We have to,
We're piecing together the puzzle parts of last night's adventure.
Do you guys not remember anything that happened last night?
No, dude, we got fucked up on candy.
And we were roofied.
By you!
And I'm only ten years old.
So you better tell me everything I want to know.
You have to tell us everything, because we're ten years old and we'll tell the cops.
We'll tell the cops.
And here's my ID that says I'm ten years old.
I didn't roof you guys!
Okay, well somebody did, or we had too much candy.
- Sounds like you guys had a lot of candy.
- Or we just were really tired.
- Yeah, if you didn't ruin me,
why'd I fall asleep, motherfucker?
- Guy came here, it was like 2 a.m.
- Okay, but did you see anybody else
with a robe like that on at the party?
- Well, now that you mention it,
there were a few, oh, sorry.
- Bless you and don't let it happen again.
- Yeah, yes sir, sorry.
- Don't throw up.
I saw you, I'm piecing parts of the last night are coming into my mind.
No, you're not.
It's the premise of the campaign.
They're coming back to my mind.
Yeah, I just remembered everything.
I just remembered the whole plot.
Now that you mention it, there were a couple of like kind of weird people in robes shuffling
through in the woods last night.
Oh wait, the roby shuffle.
But I wasn't like thinking about it, but you were, you kind of came in and just brought
the house down.
The black roby shuffle.
you know this guy this guy first of all stopped him from riding off with my bike
okay all right then you you made it float in the air with your mind
crazy I do watch this somebody in the back oh shit it's a kid with mine powers
I'm trying to float that guy up right now. Do I roll to see if I can float him?
You can't. You're not able to do it right now.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
You look upset, but hey man.
I'm looking like this.
Yeah, I know.
All right, yeah.
Did we give you any indication of where we were coming from when we arrived?
Not really, no, unfortunately.
didn't say like yo, we was at the
foaty foaty club. We was at the club,
bottoms up, went.
Did we at least play my party playlist last night?
We did play your party playlist. I wanna party part two.
Out now. Version two. Version two. Version two. Yeah.
Can we put that in the episode? Can we just, can we hold off? I gotta do
this jump. I've been trying we hold off on this for like five seconds. Yeah,
I
please fall, please fall, please fall, please get on his motorcycle and he goes
up and you hear ladies and gentlemen, the guy with the worst fucking name of
all time, vile, cacile is about to jump over the world's longest name was a
stone, but
bus and you see him revs up his motorcycle goes up world's longest bus
world's long. How long is bus it's like
ninety he said six buses long yeah right. It was a hundred something feet. I
don't know how long a bus is. How long is a bus? A bus is probably twenty
thirty. Twenty feet right, so like probably a little over a hundred feet
and he
revs it up. He does the motor. He rides his motorcycle. Oh, he revs up his
motorcycle. Okay, it's time for the motorcycle. It's time for the motorcycle.
Okay, guys,
Whoa. And he revs it up and he goes up to the ramp and he clears it. He clears it perfectly.
I just rolled. He cleared it perfectly. The crowd is going crazy. There's more where that
came from. You keep, you keep listening to pal D and D. We're going to have way more.
Okay, all right, that's enough. Hey man, come on, you're spoiling it spoil.
That's the crowd
and he lands it and yeah, he rides over to you guys says, all right, I remember
now.
Yeah, there was a gathering in the woods. You guys kept saying that you had done
like a killer set there or something and
you were given some kind of you're given a oh my lectures.
What
you're a weird 10 year old. I got to say I do lectures on how to grow your
income and then now I think about it. Drake gave you his pet snake.
Wait, what does it say about what does it say about Drake that his pet snake
is all in a bite and nuts and shit. Hey man,
I'm not gonna say it. Drake a conda. Y'all I got Drake snake, but I didn't
know where this gathering is.
I'm sure if you guys...
It's microchipped, you can't put it on eBay.
I took out the microchip.
Okay, we're getting some eBay money.
I'm sure if you guys, you know,
you could probably track in the woods where
it happened, probably follow your own trail of candy.
Oh my god,
I just noticed this whole time.
We've been following a trail of candy on the ground.
Okay, well, we're done talking to you and I'd
like to follow this trail of candy now.
Alright.
I'm glad you guys didn't do anything to fuck you to all right to crafter cool
faster. Oh yeah, the receptionist is still there. Find the candy for us.
Okay, okay, okay, but don't eat it. He's leading you because I need to wake up
fucked a little hair of the dog. I've been over. I eat some candy and I feel a
little better. I eat an acorn.
That's not candy. Caleb
shut up. He's leading you through the woods and you move further and further
into the woods and you see this cave. It's like a little hobble, little cave
hobble
and you see a couple robes lying outside of it. I'll pick up the robes and then
give them to them to okay cool. You guys are now wearing the robes.
What about the receptionist? I'm a girl. What about the receptionist? I take off
the first look at me. I'm a girl. You undress the receptionist. Please stop
please.
Just let me go home, whatever, but I don't know why I just did that hold on
and I try to put the clothes on, but I'm I'm just making it worse. You put on
worse and naked pants on the top shirt on the bottom. It's on the top looking
like a fool with your pants on the top on the bottom pants on the top
and as you guys and had turned sideways still you guys go into the cave. The
hats on the bottom shoes turn sideway
that might be the next time in your mouth. Call yourself a cool cat.
You guys go into the cave yeah, immediately okay, cool, it's a goon cave
You walk into the cave and as you're walking in, you start to hear...
Big boobs?
You hear huge boobies.
I hear big boobs!
Wait, can you do a double echo because you're in the cave?
Wait...
Last name Elphort, first name Kratos, like a spring ankle boy, ain't nothing to play with, started out local, put things to all the haters.
hear the sounds on a first name basis of Drake and you see and you said he faded
out the brown. You know, you see Drake performing for a group of people who are
wearing these dark robes and in the middle is your mother.
We found you, bitch. We go find you.
We're doing a competing. Mommy, Mommy, boys, boys, help me.
Drake is trying to use me to summon something. Okay. Oh hell no. He's
gonna summon something. D's nut. Oh you're so funny. Hit him with the dam.
Okay wait. Wait say it again. Yeah he's gonna summon something. D's nut.
*Bang*
me. Yeah, we just walked out. I'm upset. Wait, Drake, why are you upset? What happened? Why
are you so upset? You're the fucking best. You're the fucking best. Thank you, Drake.
Thank you. You think we're the best? We're the best? That doesn't sound like you're that
upset? I don't understand what you said of we're the best.
Where are you in love with our mom?
Oh, no, he fell.
He's our only link. Okay, can we can I just try to run and grab my mom?
He's back. I don't give a fuck if you're upset Drake. I'm keep playing your song.
I'm going to take my mom and we're going to leave. He shakes his head. No,
that's his mom. Now he says that's his mommy. That's your mom. Your mommy.
That's our mommy. Wait
four brothers, one brother being Drake. Honestly sounds better than having you
as our brother. I pull the Tommy gun out like a sword and I present it to him and
I say, "We would love to have you be our fourth brother and our big brother."
You can be the big one.
And it works.
Okay, so we've made a peace offering. He takes the Tommy gun, yeah. Yeah.
he started nodding to himself. Yeah, I love it. Oh yeah, go drag
doing a little bit now. Go drag. Okay, so we're going to see all the
cultists though. They're like, what are we supposed to do? Oh, you're going to
follow us to
roll for initiative with the cultists. They're all wait initiative. I thought
I just said that they're going to be our brothers to roll for exclamation point.
You mean and is Drake on our side now? Yes, to drink. Oh my God. Yes,
16, 2, 12.
That's not Drake.
I don't know why that's on the soundboard.
Thought he was gonna,
would've went to his part.
Okay, what'd you guys get on
the exclamation point? I got a 16.
I got a 2. And I got 12.
Okay, we got 6.
6 for you, right?
I got 2. You got 2, sorry.
Who got 6? No one got 6. I got a 16.
Maybe you got a 6. No.
And then what did you get? You got twelve, right? Twelve. Okay. What did Drake get? Nice
job, Drake. Twelve. Did not expect you guys to turn Drake. It was so easy. We gave him
a gun. Yeah. He just wants to be hard. So that was -- true. All right, cool. You're
going to go first, Caleb. Okay. I guess I'm going last. So you're surrounded by the
cultist right now. Put your guys in the middle right now. Okay, you guys are in
the middle. We have a Drake action figure. Let me see if I can get one for us.
Cough with the echo on. Echo's not on. That's just what it sounds like when I
make a noise. Wait, cough with the echo on. Drake is a jelly bean? I guess so.
Where'd you get this? It's kind of dope. I don't know where that is.
Press the button. Press the button.
Really?
Whoever gave me this at the LA show,
this is one of the best gifts I've ever received.
You guys right now, your surrounding mommy.
Whoa!
Sorry, who needs to be protected?
Mom!
And then cultists.
Oh shit.
Oh no. Patches did a spill.
By the way, the two white claw policy for patches has now been downgraded
to one. He gets one just needs to not be around me. Not
yeah, but that's the entirety of hotline bling. Yeah. Why are you still playing?
It was
over the whole. You can look at the time on it and it says like three minutes.
That's the entire song. That's pretty. He downloaded an album. Yeah, this is
the sound bar, but I forget. Okay,
You're up me. Okay. I think that I would like to do my pickup ability.
Okay, who you gonna pick up? Well, I can only pick up him if you
remember the entire fucking move. He said all your brothers. I thought
or just me.
Cool. You pick them up.
Throw him at you surrounded by like like
you're it's like kind of a group of cultists, but they're kind of like
I don't throw him. We said that we use him as a melee object.
Okay, cool. So roll. I would like to basically do a tornado. Okay, do
it. Roll for roll for arm
for that. Great one. Crit one really? Yeah. We've had three crit ones in this
fucking session. It's been very bad. That's crazy. So you throw, you try to
pick him up and throw him. It's that you end up dragging his face on the ground.
And you,
you take three damage. Okay.
I accept it.
I accept my fate. That's really adult of you. It honestly is. Alright, and now
it's Drake's turn and Drake's going to use the Tommy gun you gave him to start
spraying it into the Colt. I fucking gave Drake my best weapon.
Not your best man. Drake did a great job.
I would give Drake the best of anything I had. Best you ever had.
If you would have fucking bet.
Can you hit the echo real quick? Drake got a...
Drake sprays it into the crowd and kills a few of the cultists at once.
and now it is their turn, though, and they're going to try to grab you,
Caleb, because you're wearing the well, actually, you're all wearing the robes,
just realized. Yeah,
grab anyone. Yeah, because they were going to try to target you. Probably go
after you because you're the biggest target because you're a big night man.
Don't go after me. I'm just a kid. They miss, though. They try to grab at you
and they miss
a ring. The robes over your armor. I guess I were up now
the Lancelot. Okay, I think I'll use my am I near them?
Yeah, you're all near them. They're all kind of crowding around you guys. I'm
going to use my Halbert attack and I'm going to cleave them in twain. Do it
that's fire sick as fuck. Thirteen nice that hits
seven wow. Okay, yeah, you cleave a group of them in twain. Oh, my God, he
always cleave them in twain. Consider yourselves cloven. That's my
trace yeah. I do the dab on it. You dab on it yeah. He dabbed
all right and now it should have been one of my attacks.
All right, you're now I really wish you had oh no, I'm dying. I know I was I was
I would have put it on the sound board. No, I'm dying. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
All right, roll for it, bro.
All right.
Full 400.
And that is--
I'm fucking wasting my time.
It rolled a dice, buddy boy.
What'd you get?
I got a 9 plus 4.
Oh, OK.
That's not bad.
Right, yeah.
Nice.
Wait, do I roll a d20 for that?
Yeah, you did that, right?
You're doing everything correct right now.
Yeah, because you had an owl, because we
wanted you to do owl for that one.
1d6 plus 4.
Yeah, it's a big damage for you.
Oh my god, it's a 10.
yeah, you spray while you guys are doing great actually yeah, you're
saying I want to hold this except for your one. So you're doing really well.
Somebody here's a better Caleb. So here's a bad sport and now we're back
to the top of the order and it is your turn again. The coldest are thinning
out. They're getting freaked out right now. They like
I would I will roll probably wigged out because Drake betrayed them. Yeah,
I would I would freak out if I was betrayed. Wouldn't you be going to
I heard you wig out. Yeah, I would wig out around Drake. Of course,
yes, I will.
I'm going to do pick up again.
Okay, can I do it even though it's my special attack? Can I do it twice? Yeah,
of course, okay, well, of course, I'm going to fucking do it again and that
one is a it's a very nice. Sixteen plus four. Okay, oh my God, we got a dirty
twenty, dirty twenty. You definitely hit them roll
a D ten
Yeah, where is it?
35.
Nice.
Cool.
Yeah, you knock into a few of them.
They're staggering back.
They're freaking out.
It is now Drake's turn.
He's going to take out his Tommy gun again.
Wow.
He's doing great.
He might stop them before they do their special attack.
Whoa.
He won't, but he got very close.
Drake the MVP.
They're doing very badly.
sprays into them again. What are you doing with your mouth? I got a bit of my hair in
there. Oh you did. My mommy hair. The cultists now, they say, even without our leader Drake,
we could still summon something I'm sure and they all gather in a circle. Summon my balls.
And they're doing, they're kind of like going back and forth. They're talking about the
six. They're doing the whip. They're doing the whip and they, yeah that's what they're
you're doing. And that's what you're about to do. Yeah. And they they they
summon
the anti mommy.
I nope the fuck out of this
fire doesn't kiss your boo boo doesn't make food. I don't kiss her boo boo
either.
Caleb Come on, we got to finish the episode. But I was really I was
genuinely pretty worried about this. I was like, they're not really gonna like
this. Okay, I'm not happy about it. So wait, is the auntie mommy not just the
daddy? No,
no, the dad. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Auntie mommy. I'm the auntie mommy.
I call daddy. I call daddy. Yo, chill.
Okay, you call daddy. That's true. Yeah. Hi, what's going on? You sound like
you're in a cave fighting an auntie mommy. What's going on?
That's exactly what. Oh, you're doing the shaggy voice again. Daddy, daddy,
My Game Boy is out of charge. The charge is gone and I can't find the charger. Daddy,
I want to play Kirby's Dream Land.
We had some other problems, but focus on this one first. Once you figure out this Game Boy
charger thing, well, you can help us with the other shit.
Okay. So did you check your bag?
Yes, but I only had the one that goes in the car.
Okay.
Do we have an adapter?
did you actually sweep the hotel room before you left? No, I thought the
made sweep it. No son, you know what I mean or maybe you don't you mean. Did
you really check under the bed? Did you check in the oh no, I didn't look under
the bed. I bet I put my charger under the bed to protect it. Well, do you have
the receptionist there?
Yes, I think so. Oh wait, the receptionist has been here the whole
time. Yeah, we can go back and check the bed. We can go check. We okay, let's
go do that right now
and Drake is like
Oh, he wants us to stay. All right, we'll stay with Drake. Oh, wait, Daddy, one more thing.
Yeah, what's up? Can we have a new brother named Drake? Say yes, say yes, say yes, say
yes, say yes, say yes, say yes, say yes. Daddy, if you say no, I'll kill myself. It's a big
responsibility. For you or us? I think he's like 40. I think you guys are ready to take
take care of another brother? Yeah, especially a rap wash him.
We'll give him a bath every day.
Well, when you put it that way, Drake, okay,
okay, so now we can kill Auntie Mommy Daddy. What does mom hate or love the
most? Why she loves you three? Oh my God, an anti man and Drake.
she hates also wait. I guess maybe a better way to phrase the question.
Daddy would be what is mommy strong against
what's her strongness?
What are mommy's strongnesses?
What are mommy's arms? What is unable to defeat mommy easily?
Well,
unable to defeat mommy easily. Strongness is her secret strongness. Well,
So mom's just oh my God, mommy is weak against chocolate.
Mommies are weak against chocolate. So Auntie Mommy would be we don't
strong
against chocolate. We don't want to know what she's arm again. We want to know
what arm against chocolate, but what's the opposite of chocolate vanilla
vanilla
vanilla is Auntie Mommy's weakness. Well, if I couldn't have said it better
myself. Oh my God, and if she's wait and if my mommy's like daddy's, then
auntie mommy's like mommy's
and hey daddy. So we probably use mommy like a bat. No show like that,
because she's a lesbian.
So and daddy was a lesbian
which I think it's a kind of animal animal. Yes,
there we get one as a pet.
We promise we will wash it.
You better wash it too.
Wait a minute.
Candy.
Vanilla.
Vanilla candy.
Vanilla Tootsie Roll.
The blue one.
The cyan one.
I don't like it.
Because the blue one is blueberry.
Anti-mommies don't know how to love their babies.
Anti-mommies hate their babies.
So who do they love?
Their babies.
their dad, their adulties, their adult and their parents. Oh my God, and we
have the perfect adulty right here. It's Drake
and
our brother,
getting ready to talk. Look, wait guys. It looks like Drake's thinking
that's it okay, okay, that didn't really help us at all. Drake
what
led to my TV. We have to pick up Drake and use them like a bat against
Auntie Mommy.
We need
okay,
Drake, I'm going to be real with you. You're not helping
that are you just kind of way to
know we will one day we will speak. We will teach you to speak English. We will
speak you in
okay,
all right, I'd like to gather up all the vanilla candy that we have that we
yeah yeah guys. Oh my God, I realize the reason that we were leaving a trail of
candy is because we didn't like the blue rapper tootsie rolls. We're dropping
them on the ground. That's true. I hate those for flavor to zero. They're bad.
It's true. You see the receptionist go yeah. I noticed it was mostly vanilla
wait. What is your name receptionist
wait a minute? I'm having a brain blast mark mark vanilla. Yeah, it's mark
vanilla. So
what do you taste like? Pick up? I take a bite of them. Pick them up. Pick them
up.
it's like vanilla. It is like vanilla bro. You go in and auntie mommy's mouth
right fucking now. Don't feed me to the auntie mommy. Please ever drink.
I would hate it if you fed me that boy. Okay, Drake, wait,
wait, is she trying to trick us? Auntie mommy use sarcasm? I don't think
no, no, because mommy's just mommy loves sarcasm. Okay, mommy. It's true.
I love sarcasm.
not because that isn't sarcastic. We don't have sarcasm. Okay, so we're
let's all grab one limb of yes of blur vanilla and throw him into Auntie
Mommy's mouth. You do it. You throw you pick this guy up. All of you roll
by the all of you roll arm and add circle arm.
Oh my God, I got a 19.
Nice.
16.
Okay, Drake is another one.
Drake got a four.
Well, Drake, but we got 19.
I got five, so I'm not the worst brother.
Okay, and now Auntie Mommy's going to try to resist that.
Can I pick up his head and throw him?
Okay, Auntie Mommy did not get a high enough really to resist
that. So you guys all together shove
the mark vanilla inside of auntie mommies now.
Yes,
I was being honest because I don't know sarcasm like mommy
she explodes. Oh yeah, oh yeah, and mommy's so excited.
She gives you all a big hug and she loves you guys and she's so happy, but
wait
who fucked her
sounds pretty right in front of her. Let's lie. We fucked last night.
Why did you have sex with your own son
mother's day
because it was mother's day? It's because it was mother's day. Oh man, my
press.
Why would you get a present? First of all, I was giving her a present. Your
present to her was you had you fuck your own mom. Yo
Oh,
that Drake's all of us that he was.
Drake wanted to do it.
Yeah.
Drake, you can do it too.
Let's all do it.
Let's just do it.
That's the end.
Yeah, happy Mother's Day.
Happy Mother's Day.
That was a really sweet ending.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
(static)
- If you two are so good at thinking of a restaurant
to come up with,
tell me two things.
- Okay.
- Number one, the theme.
- Theme is casual.
- Yeah, casual Friday theme.
- Yeah.
- Oh, man.
- And the chefs don't wear outfits.
- There's already a casual Friday theme restaurant.
- You can't tell who the chef is.
- There's already TGIS.
- That's, thank God it's Friday.
They still wear clothes and stuff.
You can show up. This is EDIF. No, every day is Friday. This good day is Friday.
Every day is Friday. And the chefs and get this, the chefs and waiters,
they sit at the tables too. So you really can't tell who anyone is.
Because there's a... Why? Why are they sitting? That's the theme.
That's the theme. Where do they sit now? And this is a thing that we thought of.
This stands. A thing that we thought of that has never been done in a restaurant
before. They cook the food at the table for you. Table. But only at some tables.
Yeah. Benihana is what you're thinking. No. No. You're doing Benihana. He works
there. Who's he? Benny. Benny works at the, yeah.
Okay, so that was my first question is the theme. So I guess the theme is that
it's always casual Friday and the waiters are are blaming it.
The waiters are, it's indistinguishable. And also they cook the food at the table.
That's also why we have to have the biometric thing, because I know we're
going to run into problems where people come in and pretend to be waiters.
Yeah, and I'm taking people's orders.
So I'll cover the dead giveaways that I have no hands.
I'm going to hold the fucking place.
First week, first week of your like the first week that you're an employee at
EDIF's.
EDIF's?
Yeah, every day.
Oh, I thought it was EIF. RFID chip right there.
Uh-huh.
And if you, we call it an EDIF chip.
It's proprietary.
That's why it's so big.
It needs to hold a lot of data.
It holds your entire, it's it holds every every, so it's a whole stick of
Graham. So what's to stop me?
No, we're mining, we're also mining cryptos in all of our employees' arms.
What's to stop me?
That's how you tell the employees when they walk around, you just hear like...
*laughter*