The year is 2012.
We're in a musty courtroom in Palo Alto, San Francisco, where the trial of the century
is taking place.
I think I'm kissing my twin.
You see the bailiff, who barks, "All rise for Judge Sullivan!"
Everyone stands up.
There's a stout frog.
waddles his way to the judges podium.
I don't know what it's called.
I thought about it for a second.
- You don't need to stand up.
Don't worry. It's all good.
So thank you. Thank you.
You can sit.
Dearly beloved, we are gathered here today
to begin the trial of the three-way trial,
the first ever in American history
over the creation of the website Diaper Talk.
A website allegedly created by Mark Zuckerberg.
- Not really allegedly created by me.
- Oh yeah.
- It actually was created by me.
- We'll see about that, won't we?
- All right, quiet in the court.
Thank you.
Mr. Zuckerberg, I don't remember,
I didn't look up anything about how courts work.
Mr. Zuckerberg, how do you plead?
(laughing)
- I plead as the owner, operator, sole founder
and creator of DiaperTalk.com.
- The guilty owner and co-founder and creator.
- The not guilty owner, co-founder, founder, not co-founder.
- Not guilty of creating the website.
- The owner, I plead guilty of creating the website,
your honor. - Guilty to stealing money.
- I plead. - From the real creator
of the website. - I plead, shut up!
- Okay, order, order.
All right, the jury, you heard that.
So in this very unorthodox kind of court here
where we have Mr. Zuckerberg,
who is being accused of stealing the property
and of not giving credit to Mr. Eduardo Saverin,
his former business partner,
and of stealing the original idea from
- The Finger Bros.
The Finger Bros. Twins.
- From the Finger Bros. Twins.
Underwear conversation.
You said underwear.
Underwear?
You said underwear also.
Do I read this intro? I wrote the whole intro.
Well, we'll do that in a second.
So before we begin this three-way unorthodox trial,
I need each of you to choose your lawyers.
From who?
Three lawyers walk out in front.
Okay.
So to do this first, I need everyone to roll a d20.
me. Who got the highest? I got a 17. I got a plane around. I got a six. What'd you get?
Yeah, I changed it from a nine. I got a two. Okay. I saw you turn it. I thought I just wanted
to hear you say it. Okay. Mr. Saverin, you get the first pick of lawyer. You have a Southern
lawyer, a New York style lawyer.
What does that mean?
He's New York style.
I like the sound of that.
Like a bake.
I'll give you more descriptions.
Would you say that the New York style lawyer is the best one?
No, not necessarily.
And then, and then there's a girl lawyer.
You can go.
Yeah.
That's the, what do you, so there's Southern lawyer.
That's the sort of friendly, persuasive, insightful, maybe too forthright for his
own good though, all around very solid.
Well, due to my personal experience of having to doing an internship in
New York based on my character or my own history, which I know about.
I think I would have to go with the New York lawyer.
Nasty, direct and intimidating.
Great arguments.
Raises your ceiling, but not your floor.
Wait, what?
The most friendly.
I forget you rolled this.
That's right.
Yeah.
And then there's the girl lawyer.
She will cry.
She will use her feminine wiles, but do we still need this music?
But you can't like execute that sort of her problem.
They each have specialties.
You chose the New York lawyer, though.
Yeah.
All right, but we're going to win this case.
Let me tell you it's going to be one to bada bing bada, but he's
still my friend, but he's still my friend.
That's good, too.
Okay.
Bada buddy is still my friend.
Bada bing bada, but he's still my friend.
Okay, now we'll go clockwise from here. Well, I mean, that's how the roles were.
Oh, it was. Yeah.
So we go. I guess I'm choosing a bang. What was your finger?
And I think that we will go with the southern lawyer.
Well, I'm quite familiar with the tops of I am a rooster. I need you to not be
frightened by that. But I know you're your accent. You're poor. Well,
I know I'm just from a region of the country where we talk a
certain way.
Ah, oh dear.
That was my other twin.
That was my twin who got he got scared because he was on his
phone.
Now he's looking up.
Well, I'm going to need you to pay attention.
So we are so we can win this.
Oh, you're going to keep that's a feather.
That is really that is really the kind of Saudi big thing.
Yeah, you're doing good.
It's really good.
And then I'm afraid you will have to have the girl lawyer.
It's actually kind of just like the movie.
Mrs. Zuckerberg.
Is it Rashida Jones?
It is Rashida Jones.
Oh yeah.
Whoa, whoa.
And holy shit.
Hello Rashida.
I did not know you had that impression in you.
Well, Mark, looks like we're going to be working together.
OK.
She does this face.
Yeah.
Yep, you're so awesome.
So excited to work with you.
Really looking forward to working with you.
The truth is, a fucking aunt could do your job.
Because this fucking case is so clear cut.
I can't believe I'm wasting my time here.
- And now, so you guys can do your opening statements
or you can have your lawyers do it.
You can kind of decide.
- I think that I will probably draw a circle
while my lawyer does my opening statement.
- Ladies and gentlemen, okay, also first,
the rules by the way.
So we're going to be doing a retelling of that's not really a
circle. It looks like more like a heart. Yeah, that's like a lump.
Then I'll try again. We're going to be doing a... That's a butt.
So we're going to be doing a retelling of... Your circle's got a,
like a turn. Your circle's more like a beat or a turn up. Why do you put a point on your circle?
We're going to be doing the retelling. I don't know why he does it.
It looks like a speech bubble. We're going to be doing a retelling of...
Why can't you draw a circle? Stop. That's an oval.
Well, now you got a little face. You know what you were doing there. You got a face there.
It looks like a face. Yeah.
We're going to be doing a retelling of
the events leading up to today.
And after each sort of juncture of
those events,
we're going to have sort of I can't
fucking win.
There's a circle right there that you
could be tracing the whole time.
Depending on how you perform in
these past events, we're
then going to roll dice.
This is you know, this is
more disrespectful than usual.
All right, teacher.
He's in character.
Teacher. He is.
He actually is a character in that sense.
No, so just very quickly, we're just
going to retell the whole story, very similar to the movie.
But each time that we reach an end point of the story,
it's going to be one of you getting called to the stand.
Your lawyer is going to interview you.
We're going to go back, flashback to that time.
Then another lawyer is going to cross-examine you,
one of the two other lawyers.
And then depending on how you performed in the past,
depending on a role from your lawyer and the bonus role
you will get based on your past performance, you will try to win over the jury.
Okay.
And after all of those, we'll sort of tally up the winners and losers and see who...
Just throw a beer at Pat.
Come on, man.
I better not have spilled it.
Okay, enough with the music.
I'm bringing the music back as many times as possible.
Perfect. Yeah, keep it up.
All right.
So because you won first, Mr.
Saverin,
we're going to start with your
New York lawyers.
We'll start with you. But first,
let's have all your opening
statements. So you start, Mr.
Saverin.
Honestly, I can't even believe
that I'm here doing
this because it
seems like I shouldn't have to be.
But because I am, I guess all I want to say is that Mark is still my best friend.
And I almost broke the monitor.
You almost broke the monitor.
That's not even something you would do.
Yeah.
Zuck wouldn't do it.
You're you're wait until like 45 minutes in.
You have to be playing.
You have to be playing a wimp.
They make him do his opening statement first.
Yeah.
He has to do his opening statement.
You do your opening statement first.
You do it first.
Here's that attention you ordered, buddy.
Yeah.
Ooh.
I actually hate attention.
From the movie.
Fatality.
Now he's opening statement
bitch
liar
two fat twins.
These are the people that I see in front of me today.
The bitch is your lawyer.
You
you should I should have let you kill yourself in freshman year
when I caught you in the bathroom
trying to overdose on Tums
you
Yeah. Keep rowing. You're really, really good at that. The business stuff is not
for you. It's almost it's honestly funny as fuck that two twins were so good at
rowing.
Well, one of us is right handed and I'm left handed.
My twin is right handed and I'm left handed. Is that true? Yeah.
See like this is crazy. What's your name? The Finger Bros. No, what's your
first name?
what the one I'm talking to right now. What's your first name? Your first name
figure? My name is the finger bros twins. So we've got do we have like sort of a
hive mind situation? No. So what then what's your name? The other one that I
wasn't talking to just now. What's your first name? It's hot and whoa,
it's fuk you and
well, I'm hun. This is
whoa
anyway. It's crazy that you were so genetically blessed and so good at one
thing, and then you decided that you wanted to make websites instead of do
that. I love web. I love web 2.0.
Yeah, I mean that's yeah, I'm sure you do anyway. This whole thing is bullshit
your honor. Yeah, you just said yeah, it's over. That's not you should address
the jury, really jury. This whole thing is bullshit. Hello. I think thank you. I
think that I will soon be proven to be guilty of starting the website and not
guilty of stealing the website from
my Hispanic friend over here,
who is Hispanic, by the way. I mean, this is what Cameron thinks a Hispanic guy
looks like. He dressed up like this
for those listening. I'm actually Jewish, by the way, look up Eduardo Saverin from
from the social network. He wears exactly. I know it's a perfect cost twins.
You don't need to look them up. Everyone knows that they look like you don't
look like the Winklevoss twins. Hello.
All right, all right. Anyway, that's the end of my state. Thank you. I'm going to
try this circle thing. I'm going to give it another. Yeah, it's sort of confusing,
but I think we got it. I missed us.
he's a frog. He rivets come on. It's he kind of those lack
mid a mid sentence ribbit
see the southern rooster like full shame.
Yeah, I'm really sorry.
Basically, I just can't even believe that we're here having this trial.
And honestly, Mark is still basically my best friend in the world, even though
he's trying to fucking steal all my stuff.
And I love him so much.
And honestly, I think he only made this billions of dollars website because he
was jealous of me and my internship and my friends that I had.
So I think the jury will see that Mark, he did not make the site and he did not
make any of the money rightfully.
And actually it was me, the guy who paid a thousand dollars worth of server time
who should get 50% of the company.
Yeah.
The jury nods.
They're like, God, that sounds good.
That's it.
It sounds like it makes sense.
Um, all right.
And Mr.
Mr.
And you have to put my name in the logo.
I'm whoa.
Hello.
Whoa.
You're opening statement to the jury.
Okay.
An introduction to yourself.
Hello.
We are the Finger Bros Twins and we love social media.
From an early age we were completely enamored with website design.
By the age of 13 we had already purchased the website twinks.com.
A portmanteau of the two words that we love the most, twins and links.
Within a year, we had already sold the domain to an investor named Sean Cody.
We were raised in Westport, Connecticut, in a house bought by our two twin fathers.
I know you were wondering how we have twin fathers, but it's actually quite simple.
Our twin fathers split asexually in 1981, and then they had sex with our one mom who
gave birth to us 12 months later.
Our summers were spent learning how to row crew at Camp Two Creeks, an adult summer camp
exclusively made for twins to learn about twin culture.
But while we were there, we discovered something so incredible.
Our love of diapers.
Our love of diapers later merged with our love of website design, which inspired us to create
our magnum opus, abltwinks.com, a website for diaper lovers who are twins that also
love links.
We had our website, but we didn't know how to create it, so we hired Mark Zuckerberg to
design it, which he then stole.
Okay.
Hello.
Okay, hello, a little bit of an admission there, but we'll just
gloss over admission of what nothing. So I caught it and
Rashida definitely did. I did because she's an ace attorney.
What? Yeah, I'm pretty good at what I do. Hello. Okay, so let's
all that was all very thank you everybody. Mr. Zuckerberg, would
you please go to the stand? Oh, wait, hold on. Yeah. Would you
I'm going to go to the call on you to the stand. Nope, I'm not moving. You
have to bring the stand to me. Can I go to the stand?
Just once, how let's bring the stand or you have to pick me up and bring me
over to the stand because I'm not moving. I'll pick him up. Mark aren't
the finger bros brothers such dweebs. Remember how we used to laugh about
this kind of stuff finger bros brothers. Can you pick up mark and put him on
the stand? Absolutely okay. Let's pick him up. You pick him up with your left
and I'll pick him up with my right hand.
Okay.
Roll arm.
That's Nat 20.
You just like, you toss him in the air and he floats down and slots into the stand.
Much better.
Okay, what do you want to ask me?
And by the way, Eduardo, we're not friends. Stop talking to me like that, please.
Okay, Mark. It's me, Rashida, again.
Hello.
So, I want to ask you about your time back at Emerson University.
Bleep it.
The best school in Boston.
Yeah, whatever.
What about it?
Let's take us back to that day when you first came up with the idea of Diaper Talk.
talk. And so we're going to flash back now to you're on a date with a girl.
And I'm sitting one table over in a disguise.
Disguise is another girl.
And no, that's perfect. Yeah, yeah, hit it. And you're just this is going to be a series
is
Why are you talking to me like that?
We've been dating for four months.
Slut says what?
I can't do this anymore, Mark.
Can't do what?
Be a slutty bitch?
I'm breaking up with you.
And also you're dumb.
Roll a constitution saving throw.
Which circle is that?
Sorry, roll heart.
On the other side of the page.
Yeah.
Four, and then with my heart, it's four.
Um, you feel so upset by this break.
As much, as upset as Mark Zuckerberg in this iteration can feel.
It's starting to hurt your confidence.
I think I might be hungry or something.
Yeah, well, why don't you go get yourself something to eat then?
I think you will get me something to eat.
Behind her is a jock and he says, "Hello."
"Hey."
"Ahh! Ahh! Get away!"
"Is this guy bothering you?"
"Yes! She's bothering me! Get away! Ahh! Don't hurt me!"
And he takes the girl and he walks away.
Eduardo, you're watching all this?
Yeah.
Are you there?
I go like this.
Mark.
Eduardo, as the jock leaves, another strapping, handsome young man comes up to you and gives
you a card.
It's a foil Charizard card.
You've been tapped to join the Charizard Club.
The most exclusive club in Emerson University.
I jizz in my pants.
(Laughter)
Oh, man.
Wait, what's that smell?
He knows my smell.
It smells like Eduardo's fucking jizz in this bar.
So we go back to the courtroom.
And after Eduardo jizzed his pants.
Yes, I did smell it.
(laughter)
You went back to your dorm room and you started to make a website.
What... and it was sort of a mean prank, some would say.
I took photos of my ex-girlfriend, then ex-girlfriend,
previously my girlfriend, then ex-girlfriend.
Cool.
Yeah.
And I used...
I used Photoshop to put her in different photos of diapers that I found.
Backgroundless PNGs, are you familiar?
Or is that too over your head?
Um, I got it, yeah.
Okay.
I put her in diapers and I posted them on a website called...
The... The Diaper Talk.
And some would say you... So, allegedly, and this is true,
truly this is recorded in the Emerson Gazette that you sent these links out to thousands
of different students to rate which diaper looked best on her.
I did. Yes, I had Huggies, pull-ups, kind of custom diapers that I found with pictures
of Batman on them.
Now I want to draw attention to this to the jury. This is somebody who was already thinking
about diapers even back then. Okay?
I was thinking of diapers way before that. I was thinking about diapers when I was like
7, 8 or 9 years old. You weren't thinking about diapers, you were wearing them Eduardo.
There's a difference. Objection your honor! What does this have to do with anything? I
don't know what objection means so I'm gonna... you guys just stop talking. I'm wearing the
diaper now.
Just one of you?
As am I.
Overruled.
Sorry.
What?
I was delayed reaction to my own sentence.
So now when you made this website, what was going through your mind, Mr. Zuckerberg?
I was imagining what kind of foods she was eating and what the poop would look like inside
the diapers if she was eating corn and peanuts or if she had a healthy diet and it's going
to be firm, thick brown logs.
Jerry, this sounds like somebody who is incredibly interested in the world of diapers.
Somebody who, even in their darkest moments, were still choosing to invest in building
something related to diapers.
While the accusing parties here, they're just sort of along for the ride.
Yeah. So you did fail being able to sustain yourself for the
breakup like you were upset by. I took some damage didn't I? You didn't take damage.
You're only going to be able to add a d4 to this next roll against the jury.
I'll reroll it. That would have been nice for you. It's CeeLo rules. As soon
as a die stops. It didn't stop. It didn't stop. I picked it up but it looked like
I was going to stop on 20.
So now I roll a d4?
Yeah.
Oh, my God, wait, you rolled a 12.
There's 12 people in a jury.
Holy shit.
This might be a unanimous decision.
So now, Eduardo,
your lawyer goes
up to talk to Zuck.
All right.
Sorry, I'm also a frog.
you
am so mark. Do I look like I got
yes, like you look like a I think I picked the wrong
this is on the record. Do I look like I like to get the ladies like
is a lady. Do I look like I like to get fucked? Yes. All right, shit. So I was trying to set
you up for something, but you're way too on top of it. I know I'm very smart. No objection,
your honor. He clearly doesn't look like he likes to get fucked. His hair's all messy and
his pants are halfway down his body. He looks like he fucks. So you can't tell just from
this. Can we look at your ass to see if it looks like you like to get fucked? Do you
or wait fucking can be in and out talking to the to the lawyer right.
Yeah, okay. Well, we might as well throw you in there. Can I request a
short recess to go look at my lawyer's ass before he shows it on the stand?
No, that would be tampering with evidence. That's tampering with
evidence. Can I can I request a recess to do the same thing with my lawyer,
your honor? I'd like to request a recess so that my lawyer can fuck me
so I can prove that he fucks and doesn't get fucked.
I can't really allow that,
but I guess just as once if you want your lawyer to go fuck you, but I guess
that can happen. Well, I don't want to write, but there are things we want to
have to do in the course of life.
Okay, we'll take a ten minute break for you to get fucked by. We don't need ten
minutes.
Take like an hour and a half break
for that sort of thing.
You I am tied back there and you we only need two minutes.
Now that I'm done fucking that Hispanic guy, look, I don't believe this fucking prick for
one second.
Now look at him.
Your honor, the lawyer has toilet paper on his foot.
That's not...
Did you guys fuck in the bathroom?
He has toilet paper on his shoe, on the bottom.
Oh I'm sorry, where were we supposed to fuck Mr. Genius?
We fucked in my car where I keep toilet paper in case I have to go when I'm driving because
I don't have a bathroom in my house because I can't afford one because of you.
for she to write this down. He keeps toilet paper in his car, write that down.
That'll be important later. If you wear diapers, you don't need toilet paper.
I don't wear diapers. I'm on the business end. I don't even know how to
send a friend request on diaper talk.
Now, look, you think that you know everything 'cause you wear a hoodie and
you got hair.
Yeah.
Let me tell you something about my client.
My client made sure that your website could exist.
He was there with you when he co-created it with you.
That's not true that you went home alone.
He was there, you smelled his jizz,
and you went back and you created it together.
- Okay.
- And I can prove that this is true.
- He came into my dorm room while I was writing
because I couldn't remember what a diaper looked like,
so he drew one on the window.
You're saying that that is tantamount
to being the co-founder of the website?
- Folks, jury, I wanna ask you.
You looked me in the eye and you told me that I would be the co founder of
Diaper Talk.
Why do you think... There's no proof for that. Why do you think Mr. Zuckerberg...
Oh yeah, I recorded the entire thing in this movie and I put this...
Well, some of the details were changed, I guess, to reach a broader audience.
Why do you think he would leave that part out until I pressed him?
First of all, it's 'cause I'm a very good lawyer from New York City.
Second of all... Who likes to get fucked? No, I fucked my client,
sold at through a point
and if he does get fucked he doesn't like it
precisely
and just like everyone who gets a lot of that and that's fair
the that with that admission i would just like to jury to reconsider maybe
think a little more
more with a little bit more a critical thinking
uh... a guy
who can admit what's true
who throws stuff
at the other other people here in this sort of generally kind of obnoxious in
deserves a fucking smack. Who did he throw something at? Right. All right. So he's going
to roll a d20. Huh? Where's my whoa. Where is it? It's over here. Oh my God. You it's
worth him. Rish buffoon lawyer. My Lord, you stay. It's just keep reaching. So that's Patrick.
Patrick's.
Oh, you got it.
You're going to you're going to add a D6
because because
he lost the last one.
OK, I just roll a D6.
You're going to add that to this roll.
What I get?
Seven.
Four.
Yes.
All right.
You are fail.
No, I'm not.
The dice are fail.
Now, I'm not responsible.
I'd like to call my client to the stand, Mr. Eduardo Severino.
Come on up, get over here.
I'm up.
All right, thank you for coming.
No problem.
I'm still here, you're sitting on my lap.
No, he's not.
You can't just say what's happening.
Stop grinding on me, Eduardo.
Only I could do that.
Stop grinding on me, we're not best friends anymore.
You can't do this anymore.
Stop, stop.
Well, best friends don't do this.
I'm gonna have my hand on your cheek.
I feel like I have to stop this,
but I don't really know what the rules are here.
Okay, I'll leave.
please stop grinding. Isn't that just like you? Why don't you run off to
California
and don't get grinded on my by Mr. Eduardo
Serino? You have a name of a foster's home for imaginary friends character. I
don't want to hear from you. Is it true that you got accepted into the Charizard
Club? Yes, and I just my pants when it happened right. We heard that from
to Zuckerberg earlier. So, is it now true that when you got invited into the club you had
to perform a series of, you had to perform in a series of games for full admittance?
Yes. The Charizard Club is very exclusive and what I had to do was I had to, and it's
probably one of the coolest clubs at the school. Everyone, the people in these clubs, they
going to become movie stars, TV stars.
- So we flash back to this time.
So you, after, and it's unclear,
but did you actually help Zuck?
I think so, we think so, maybe.
But we go back to you getting let into the child's art club.
- Well, if we're talking about the window scene,
what happened there is I busted into his room
and I saw a picture of a diaper on his computer
and I just drew it on the window.
- Yeah, that did happen.
- Look what I drew!
Look!
And in the Charizard Club, there's a series of games you have to play.
Okay.
There's the burlap sack race, the egg and spoon race.
Yeah.
There's a three-legged race and there's limbo.
Yeah, and you have to do all of those.
Okay, to get into the Charizard Club.
Right.
So you show up there and it's like, "Hi, welcome to the Charizard Club."
Oh my God.
I can't believe I'm here.
The only way you're gonna get in is if you complete our races.
What a Chad!
So first it's a burlap sack race.
Okay.
This is gonna be a series of balance ball checks.
That you're gonna have to make.
Alright.
So you're all lined up.
Yep.
You have two other challengers in the burlap sacks.
And yeah, start rolling.
Okay.
Ready?
Go.
That's a 19 plus one.
Alright, you beat the beat.
The first racer like handedly.
You don't even need to like check.
He was trying to hop is like oh no.
Nice try, but actually calculated
the physics of the bag.
And then now you race against the other guy.
That's a three.
Oh no, so the other guy
is able to get out in front of you.
You get one more chance to beat him though.
He's like I'm going to win this
because I'm fucking killing you bitch.
OK, well, alright, that's his name.
I'm fucking killing you bitch. His name's fucking killing you bitch. Ten. Oh
Man, and he wins he gets out in front of you. So that's the first challenge. Okay, that's only the first one next challenge
Of course, I knew they were gonna be hard next challenge is the egg balancing challenge. Okay, I got this one in the bag
I do this every morning
Five okay, you win against that same guy. He's like no
Can I kind of throw the egg at him? Yeah, you do. Yeah, he's gonna try to catch it. He does not catch it
I say oh that's gotta hurt
Yeah that too
Shut up, man
That's egg on my face. I'm rolling the next whatever the next thing is
Eight you beat him
Those are some really bad rules
insanely low rolls.
It's an exclusive club.
It's tough to get in.
Yeah.
Now, you can't get in with just any d20 roll.
The three-legged race.
Oh, fuck.
I've never been able to do this.
So this, you get a partner.
I've been practicing this one.
I can never get it to work.
Each of you get a partner in this three-legged race.
Here we go.
All right, that's another 20.
Wow.
A crit one by this guy.
This guy is now out of the remaining competitions.
Okay.
Yeah, because he died.
He died.
That's a net 20.
A net 20?
You clear this, you clear Limbo.
Crit one.
I died in the three-second race.
And then the school had to shut down the Charizard Club for ages.
It's a dangerous club.
They know what they're getting into.
Not just anyone can get in.
Actually, anyone can get into the Charizard Club.
And anyone who's listening is thinking, "Oh, that's not that hard."
That whole time, we were drinking beers.
I had two beers before Limbo.
I could get into the Charizard Club.
Then why didn't you, Mark?
Watch me.
I rolled a 16.
Plus my Charizard.
The jury is all like, "Yeah, maybe he can get into the Charizard Club. They're writing it down."
Then why didn't you?
Because I was busy creating the diaper talk.com.
Oh great, here we go again.
You fucking moronic.
So then we flash back.
He's just jealous of this Charizard club and that's why he made diaper talk I guess.
[Laughter]
Based on the ending of this.
Makes no sense.
We flash back to the courtroom.
Now as you can see, my client handedly got into the Charizard club.
Was cool as fuck. Everybody liked him. Everyone in Emerson liked him.
Nobody had any problems with him.
him. And the guy who died, probably gay.
I don't think that was ever proven.
What does that have to do with anything?
The jury's like, "Okay." They're trying to figure out what that meant.
Two of the jurors are just like...
So, you get a D8.
A date.
Mark was on a D8 when?
5, 19.
That's 24.
Now, a southern lawyer arrives on the scene.
Well, well, well.
Mr. Eduardo Saveron.
Is it true that you are Latino?
No.
That is confusing.
You're not Argentinian.
I don't know.
Or Chilean or one of those.
Brazilian.
All I know is that I'm Jewish and I like Asian girls.
Swag.
Let that enter into the record.
Sort of an axiomatic type of statement I would say.
Now, Mr. Sovereign.
He's Brazilian.
Now you will never be.
I don't think he's Jewish at all.
He is Jewish.
He could be Jewish.
He's a... I have seen it.
You saw it recently and you didn't know he was Jewish?
Your brain bleeped out the word Jewish.
His whole thing is he goes to the party and he says like,
"Why do Jewish guys like Asian girls?"
That's his whole thing.
How many dates Brenda Song?
I thought he was just talking about his friend.
No. Why would he be at the Jewish fraternity's party?
Mark Zuckerberg never hooks up with an Asian girl in the movie.
He only marries one in real life.
That's not true. No, he hooks up with her in the bathroom as well.
Yeah, next to each other.
Yeah, they are.
Yes, they are.
Yes.
They're both Asian.
No shit.
Yes, dude.
I can't see Chinese, I guess, man.
We didn't say Chinese.
We didn't even say Chinese.
You're throwing all these specifics at him.
What's wrong?
He gets racist one second end of just mentioning Asian girls?
No.
You got racist first.
How do we get racist?
You said she wasn't Asian.
What?
She wasn't Asian.
She was Asian.
It was an Asian girl and her friend, Jubio?
It's two Asian women.
It's not.
Look up Brenda Song and Brenda Song's friend in the social network.
It's two Asian women.
I saw this on a flight.
The social network bathroom scene.
I don't want to watch that scene.
bathroom stall scene
we don't have to watch this scene
bathroom kissing scene with brenda song
hd
laughing
she's asian
go back we want to see your friend
ok then go forward i guess
we're cutting this out
i guess they don't show it
it's implied it's her friend from earlier
this scene is gross
Just go just look at the cast. No, this is too much. Just trust this is three against one it is. Yeah, I remember it
I watch Asian descent this actress
Well, I would like to
Eduardo Saverin is a South American
uh never mind now look what is going on i don't even know regardless of the ethnicity or nationality
sure you will never be as cool as the finger bros is that not true uh play the music again
what oh what okay let's restart this scene let's we're gonna restart this whole scene
we're gonna chop this didn't happen no i may not i know listen no listen we're not cutting
any of that out. Listen, you southern lawyer, I may not be as cool as the Finger Bros twins,
but I'm friends with one of the coolest guys in the world. Isn't that enough?
And who would that be?
Mark Zuckerberg.
Whoa.
Now, you're not friends with me.
I'm best friends with Mark Zuckerberg. The Mark Zuckerberg.
such low self-esteem really have contributed anything to something as magnificent as DiaperTalk?
I know I love DiaperTalk. I didn't know self-esteem was what you needed to contribute to a website.
I thought it was almost $1,500 worth of funding. Huh? Now, DiaperTalk.com, look, I'm wearing
my diapers right now. We're all here loving DiaperTalk.com. But could somebody not wear
a diaper. Thank you in public unless they are confident and I would say Mr.
Severin here is not confident enough. He puts himself down. He thinks it's good
enough to get into the Charizard Club while the finger bros. What are you
about to wear my diaper right? Are you the alien from X-Men? Not X-Men. What's
that movie? Men in Black?
I guess those southern lawyer wouldn't have seen those movies.
Maybe
that up to date animal. Yeah, he's a bird. No, you I'm filling up my
diaper.
Now my client loves his diaper.
Which one?
Yeah, I said my client, which one they are. They are one in the same.
He has proven this.
So hello
and now I would just like you to reconsider
as cool as it was for a dwarves ever into kill one of the children
in that three-legged race
we have to consider
that he admitted himself he is not cool enough to wear a diaper in public
and some might say that spin but
i think we've been spun around enough today
you can say that again i still can't believe we're here
and uh...
you're all the six you didn't fail anything in this one
like twins
Two is the twins number.
Two is twins.
All right, you did quite well here, Eduardo.
I thought you were going to say, what, whoa and huh?
Me?
Whoa and huh, yeah.
You did fail.
Did whoa and huh fail?
What did you get on your die?
A 200.
Two.
You got a two.
Seems like not everything's working out for the finger
winkle-ers.
Finger bros.
We're called the Finger Bros twins.
The Finger Bros twins.
And we're named "huh" and "whoa."
(snickers)
All right.
Now, we're gonna--
And our lawyer is a bird.
I would like to--
And the judge is a frog.
I would like to call my client to the stand.
And one of the lawyers is a frog, too.
Enough with this farm animal--
Your lawyers are frogs.
Kind of shenanigans, please come to the stand.
And his lawyer is a woman.
Huh?
Come on!
Whoa, okay.
strokes aside, I would like to ask you now a few questions.
Huh?
Whoa.
Both of you.
Huh?
Whoa.
Hold on, you're literally confusing me in real life.
I'm trying to write something.
Sorry, we couldn't see each other because we're sitting next to each other and not face
to face.
Can we sit face to face?
You may sit however you need to.
I'll allow it.
Now, is it true, twins, that you met Mr. Zuckerberg after a regatta?
That's confusing. I can't do it.
You just turn back. You don't even have to look at that. You just turn back and forth,
and he'll switch it for you.
After a regatta.
Huh?
We flash back to the regatta. This is impossible.
We flash back to the regatta.
You are facing...
And we're all eating cheese.
Cheese is it all filmed in fucking tilt shift
and it looks like toys in a water?
Yes, it is all filmed in tilt shift and it's you.
It's Emerson University's regatta
crew team versus the venerable,
but much less intelligent Harvard University's regatta team.
Huh? Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- 9 plus, that is 11.
- Okay. Roll bounce ball.
- 15.
- You just barely beat the Harvard team as you go by them.
It's your last push and that last ha and that last whoa gets you just over the edge.
You're feeling pretty good, you're feeling pretty high on that.
You get back to campus, sprawling Emerson campus.
Who wants to see me kiss my brother?
And who is, none other than, maybe one person does.
I guess I'd like to see that.
Whoa! Look who it is!
Now, is it-
That's Mark Zuckerberg!
Is it true that you then asked Mr. Zuckerberg to help you design a website that you called, I believe, ABL?
- Abdltwinks.com.
- Well, not before we asked him if he wants to watch us kiss.
- As we go back and you say,
- Do you want to watch us kiss?
We'll give you this sandwich.
- I guess I'm a little hungry.
Yeah, sure.
- Okay.
Now come here, huh?
(laughter)
- Please, overruled, please stop, please.
- Oh my God, we started kissing in court.
- I'm listening to this.
- I need to,
you're gonna make Rashida Jones leave, I need this to stop.
- No, Rashida Jones likes it.
- Girls like that kind of shit.
- Oh, they don't?
- Yeah.
- Do they like that?
- Girls like guys kissing like girls kissing.
- Girls like twin brothers kissing.
- Isn't that crazy?
- Do they actually?
- They actually do.
- Especially when it's twin brothers.
is
I'm eating my sandwich.
You're eating your sandwich, you're watching them kiss.
I'm not even really watching them kiss.
I think, actually I'm watching them kiss and I decide that I'm not hungry anymore so I put
the sandwich on the ground.
So I'm five blocks away and I'm looking through a telescope into this room.
We're in the Boston Com and me and the finger roast ones.
Is it not true then that you asked him to help you design a website after of course he had
put down his sandwich and after you had sucked face here to fall with your brother huh whoa
depending on which one I'm talking to right now which is unclear at all times. Can you
repeat the question? Did you then ask him to make a website? I asked him to design a
website. Could you let's go back in time together. Okay. Do you have a machine? No I'm
man. Oh shit. You're getting so confused. You're breaking the
whole thing. Please talk to Mr. Zuckerberg in the past. Now
talk to him in the past. Are we going to use a time machine?
Stupid in real life.
It's going to drive me crazy.
Hello.
What's up, man?
Whoa, I forgot what we were talking about. Do you want to
watch me kiss my brother again?
we already did that on I'm late. After, of course, we fast forward to you want
to watch us eat a sandwich together
and
then my brother eats the other end and then what happens when you meet in the
middle?
Huh?
What?
No, whoa, no, huh?
Now Abbott and Costello routine aside, you do admit that Mr. Zuckerberg then
absconded with your design plans. Well, if we look at the flashback, that never
happened.
He is making it very difficult for me. That never once... I'd like to say this
to the jury, we did the whole flashback, that never even got close to happening.
He kissed his brother, they gave me a sandwich and I didn't eat the rest of
it. I remember.
"We're gonna need a time machine."
She doesn't even bother talking to him.
She's like, "As you can see, this man is not capable of, sorry, these men are not really
capable of doing much of anything."
"Huh?"
"Whoa."
"No, I'm huh."
"I want you to ask yourself, despite them winning a regatta, after that scene that, frankly,
I could never have anticipated being how that played out.
You really think they could make a website?
I think I bit off more than I could chew playing these characters.
You roll roll a D8.
That has to be with this me. Yeah. OK.
Yeah. You get to add a D8 to this roll.
Which is this. Yes.
One.
Damn, I got fucked.
I got actually fired.
Everything. The jury just thinks the twins are handsome.
The jury's just, the jury really wants to watch the kids.
It's a jury of all women.
[Laughter]
It's the worst jury in history.
It's a jury of all women who like that.
Yeah, it's a jury of female anime fans.
[Laughter]
Um, cool. So...
Um, sorry, Juvia, where are we at on time?
49 minutes.
49? Okay, cool, just making sure.
He never started the timer like he said he was going to.
No, that's not what I was trying to do.
True.
Should be his trial.
We're going to shift this to the trial of Jubio.
No, don't do that.
Okay.
So, okay, cool.
So now I'm going to do some math here.
Okay.
Cool.
Why don't you save the math for your free time?
Sorry, yeah, I will.
Okay, cool.
cool. We're going to move on to, we're going to take a quick
court recess and then they come back and Sullivan bangs on the
gavel. He says, all right, that was the first part. That was
pretty interesting. We learned a lot about everybody here. Um,
now, uh, we're going to move forward in this, this here tale.
So Mr. Mr. Um, Mr. Zuckerberg, if you can please take the stand
once again. Okay. Now, Mark, I want you to tell me about
Every lawyer is riveted.
That was not me.
It was you, we all saw it.
We all saw it come out of your mouth.
No, don't do that. He did that.
I want to
talk about the time when
you've met superstar computer
genius, Dylan
in Palo Alto.
(laughter)
What do you want me to say?
Dylan has to be the coolest guy I've ever met in my entire life. He's not
even cool. Shut the fuck. You know he's cool. We've got star shirt is lame.
The whole
if you want to see what a real cool guy looks like. It's a guy who wears a
black shirt and a black suit jacket and pulls the top button really far open
and he wears that around all day every day with the collar popped. Yep, that
is cool. I know Dylan from TV.
So we flash back to a dinner between
Zuck, Eduardo, and guess who shows up right on time, by the way,
not late at all, he's early, actually, Dylan.
Wow, you're the guy who's making diaper talk, right? Yeah. And me.
That's great. And me. I do it really loud and everyone in the restaurant
I put some money into it.
That's awesome.
So why don't you tell me about it?
Well, basically I took some money that I had from my dad
and I put it into a bank account and I was able to use that money
to pay for some stuff.
Okay.
That's cool.
What about you?
He's my friend.
I mean,
Dylan starts to play with his fork a little bit.
little bit. He's sort of like, um, uh, uh, I mean, what is there to say?
We're changing the world. That's why I wanted to talk to you, man.
I think you gotta come out to California.
There's a lot of stars you can see out here, including me. That's, I mean,
I do love movie stars, but I wait,
I already live with my roommates.
Isn't California like too warm?
I don't think it's too warm.
I don't want to leave my roommate wait is aren't the houses. They're really big.
I might come to California, but as of right now, no man, there's movie stars
there.
Why do we want to live in California and where is making a lot of good points?
Plus, I don't I don't want to leave my roommates Dante and Stan.
Yeah, we won't be moving to California anytime soon, but in but I could be
convinced on that was called sarcasm Dylan. No, I'm not being sarcastic.
That's being sarcastic right now. That's his classic sarcastic wit. Okay,
you roll.
Sorry, you roll talking. Okay.
That's a net 20. Fuck me.
Every versus fucking campaign. I get fucking destroyed for no reason.
It's okay though, because we're still friends, despite it all.
If you don't want to go to California, I get it.
I mean, it's pretty nice here though.
I basically wear the same shirt every day.
Okay.
You wear the same shirt every day?
Chicken fingers here are really good.
Can I have a bite?
Wait, could you get chicken fingers for the whole table?
it.
And uh, yeah, he said,
Eduardo.
Edmundo.
Do you see how cool Dylan is?
He's getting his chicken tenders with honey mustard for the entire table.
The waiter goes by the table.
He's not cool at all.
He stands up to say hi to the waiter.
What we need.
He sits down.
Look how fucking cool Dylan is.
He like forgets for a second how he's supposed to do stuff.
Dylan's shirt may be cool, but he's not business smart.
What we need is ads for vacuums and sex.
We don't need chicken fingers.
Bro, I hate to say this.
A whole bunch of chicken fingers come to the table.
Oh great.
And uh, I'm allergic to fucking chicken.
I can't even be near that stuff.
Send it back to the kitchen.
I can get you fries.
They usually come with fries.
Okay, I'll have fries.
I'll pay for them myself with my own bank account.
Cheese fries!
You're so right, Dylan.
Yeah!
And he's so excited that cheese fries come.
And so we go back to the courtroom.
Now while Eduardo made a pretty good argument though, you did eventually head to California,
that's correct, right?
Eventually Dylan did convince me.
That was when we started what we like to call our long distance best friendship.
Let's see what that looked like.
Okay, we cut.
Cut to you're in New York.
I'm in New York.
You're in New York.
I'm doing an internship.
Where are you doing an internship?
I'm doing an internship at the business.
Barstool.
You're selling ads at Barstool?
Yeah, I'm selling.
I'm on the phone.
I'm like I'm doing some kind of job that I'm doing. I'm like a telephone switchboard operator.
Like I have like the wires that you have to plug into stuff. I'm a job that doesn't exist
anymore. Right. Yeah. And I'm like wow this is what it's really like. Oh my God. This
is what it's like to run a business. I'm shoveling coal into it. We're cutting to California.
You are just hanging out by the pool and you're in Dylan's pad now.
Where is it?
Except that pina colada.
He's not a frog.
What?
Yeah, there's, well, first of all, Dylan has tons of like that canned pina colada stuff.
It's so good.
Yeah.
His house has got, has a, he has a water slide.
Now I'm going down the water slide.
Going down the water slide.
And uh...
Head first.
On the belly.
that but not me. He brings you into his his theater and he's like every single
Star Wars movie in order. Let's do it Dylan press play right now. Press play
up but we got to start with the Clone Wars animated series. I love that shit.
Yeah okay and then right then the doorbell rings. Yep ding dong. Wait I'll
go get the door. Okay you open the door it's a beautiful sunny California day.
way I'm soaking wet covered in coal,
and I'm like Mark, you haven't replied to my emojis. Wait, Eduardo, I thought
you were chilling with a little Sasquatch at the bar.
Chilling with little set, chilling with little set. Mark, I quit that
internship after nine months,
which was what like a couple of days ago.
yeah. How am I supposed to know you didn't call me? I sent you emojis.
What let's look take a look at these emojis. Okay, I open up my five
fifty
it comes upstairs. Oh, Eduardo, you made it. I slap him. Oh, he thought that
you were in a homeless guy because we're in California. He didn't mean anything
by that. I should roll talking.
Let's see, with my talking, I have minus one talking.
He's Zuckerberg.
He's literally one of the biggest geniuses in the world.
That doesn't mean he's good at talking.
Seven.
I don't think he thinks I'm homeless.
Yeah. What's going on Eduardo?
So Mark said that I didn't mean anything by that,
but I actually did mean something by that.
And I'm gonna tell you what I meant right now.
What I meant by that slap is I'm changing my credit card pin
or debit card pin from one, one, one, one,
until 1112 and I'm not going to tell you the new pin.
Wait, how are we going to use that credit card if we don't know the pin?
You're not going to be able to use it at all because I'm taking all my money
that I've contributed to this thing and you're probably not even going to be
able to pay rent without my $50-$60 a month.
We got to the courtroom now and Rashida Jones goes,
"So as you can see here, Eduardo was pretty bitter and acted in a
really just not very nice way and
doesn't sound like somebody who could have invented a website sounds like
somebody who just holds a grudge because of a inferiority complex.
I'm not the one that holds a grudge.
He's holding a grudge because he's jealous that I got to be in the
background of an episode of call her daddy.
And he was also the cameraman for one of the pizza reviews.
I just like to put that out there.
See, he knew he knew.
I didn't even tell him.
Oh yeah, I for keeping up with my fucking friend, so we are friends
and I immediately go to hug you
slowly. No really fat
because I know he's going to stop
a little press to get in between you. I like a taste for out there. I hand on
the taser. Yeah, whoa, whoa, try that listen just trying to hug him all day
just because we're suing each other doesn't mean we're not the best of
best friends. She or not the best of friends. Why don't you be a friend over
there?
Isn't that just fucking typical?
Well, I guess you don't want this. I hold up a five dollar bill
I'm jumping up because he's taller than me. Give me that right now, so
you are because he got in that twenty you're not going to be able to add
anything to this role.
Okay, so thanks for pointing at me. Just roll.
Okay.
The...tain.
Stop looking at my notes, hoe.
He was sneaking a peek.
I don't have many scenes.
I think you just fell asleep. You could have been talking this whole time.
He drew.
I thought he did not fall asleep, he drew.
Give me Cam's camera.
I don't want to put myself, I'm trying to be true to the story.
He spit the last 20 minutes drawing this.
That is the lawyer from New York.
Because he's a frog.
And speaking of which, how is that?
Anti-Semitic because his penis is small.
You said that.
Penis is small.
That's him hard.
Yeah. It points straight down.
Points straight down because of his frog body.
Can you imagine the mechanics of that?
We cut to.
But it'd be easy to pee in the morning, though.
The scene. The winkle.
The sorry, the penis bros. Finger bros. Finger bros.
The finger bros twins are incensed at this point.
I guess maybe they are hard to tell.
They do talk to the president of Emerson University either way.
Jeffrey Epstein.
I don't know what his name is.
I didn't give him a name.
Hello, Dad. Tell me.
OK, yeah, he's finger bros.
Mr. Finger Bros, president of Emerson University.
No, he's still Epstein.
OK, he's still Epstein. Yeah, I didn't give him a name.
So, yeah. OK, it is.
I guess it can be my father.
Yeah, but I'll be your dad. OK.
What do you guys want from me?
wait sorry hello hello hello hello whoa whoa huh hi what's going on hello
fathers yeah the fathers start to spin in place and clip in their chair
clipping through the desk
hello to be so bad can I peter in this year either in the seed they're just
clipping through the desk they're like we made a new website but somebody took
it from us
that alarm start going off in the office.
You see like smaller versions of you guys like slide down into the
open pool. Yeah, like fireman poles.
We need to use the army, dad. I don't know if we can...
Somebody took our new website
And we need to use the army.
I don't know if we could do that.
Oh, oh, oh, oh roll.
The dad's name is oh yeah.
Oh and no.
Nine plus what?
I don't want an okay 10.
Okay.
Can we please use the army?
I don't know.
Okay.
16.
This is a battle of- a battle of wits.
[laughter]
Okay.
Please!
Maybe...
[laughter]
Seven.
Alright.
Okay!
[laughter]
Yay!
We're gonna use the army to get our website back.
Let's get the army involved.
Yay!
We're gonna use our army to get our website back.
I love you, sons.
I love you, dads.
Yay!
Let's make out.
Okay!
The dads-
They make out with "huh" and I'll make out with "whoa".
Nice.
And you two make out with each other.
Okay.
And we'll record it.
We'll record it.
Whoa.
Yay.
And they make out.
Now, after you were all done making out.
We went to London.
You went to London.
That did happen.
With our army.
You accidentally invaded England.
Now after you were finished invading England.
Now I want the jury to pay attention here for one second.
Okay.
Think of the enterprise in...
Wait, sorry, my middle name's the jury and I'm woe.
I would like to...
The group of people, the 12 or so people in front of me, whose name I shall not be referring
to out loud as to not confuse my client.
Sometimes I go by my middle name.
The coordination it takes to be able to hire the entire US military to invade England on
behalf of a diaper website.
That takes a kind of intellect and resources that could only be procured through my clients,
not Mr. Zuckerberg.
I only know websites and diapers and war and rowing and kissing my brother and watching
my dad kiss his brother.
And now knowing of course that this here jury are all women, we must consider how hot would
it be if the dads kissed two.
What if I kissed my dad?
Let's think about it, you guys like that sort of shit.
Come here dad.
The dad is not in the room right now.
Oh that's my wallpaper on my phone.
Okay I'm going to roll a d20, you get a d6 for that.
Okay.
I got a 5.
You got a 2.
This son of a lawyer sucks.
Wait, is that good or bad?
I got a 5.
Yeah, but you only add the 5 to it.
I don't understand how the rolls really work.
I really weighted the lawyer rolls too much as a problem.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Why don't you unweight them?
I won't do that.
Okay.
Nice try, buddy.
I almost had them.
You did almost have them.
It's purely my fault, so I get it.
But now we're going to have the New York lawyer.
He's questioning me.
Their storyline kind of ends in London, huh?
Yeah, it does.
Don't worry.
I have more story than the movie.
Oh, got it.
Okay.
We're not just reading the script.
I thought we were.
That's what I've been doing this whole time.
Actually, wait, hold on.
Oh, wait, hold on.
You guys died.
(laughing)
- Yep, super roll.
- Now look, you guys invaded England.
- Whoa.
- Who do you think you are?
- The fu, the.
(laughing)
- Okay, let's settle down then.
- What the?
- You and your lawyer.
- The finger bros twins.
- Okay, and?
I drew a photo of you.
What can I see it?
Drew a photo.
Does that seem like now I want you to show that to the know
it's for you.
Show it to the jury and they'll go.
They're all about to throw up.
Does that look like somebody who knows what they're doing
when building a website or does that look like the kind of
maniac who would invade a sovereign nation?
What did you say?
Yeah.
Because they were confused about what it means to make a website.
No, I made a website when I was 13 called Twinks.
13?
Yes.
Did anybody help you with that?
Was it WordPress or like GeoCities?
What did you do?
Well, I paid a slave.
Okay, right.
You paid a slave?
Now...
It's the first rule of having a slave.
You gotta pay.
I pay this guy. So this guy's so okay.
I'd like the jury to hear this. This guy's so stupid. He paid a slave.
No, that's his name.
A slave
he has a slave's last name to
know.
He's white.
My father's just very, wait, wait, wait. We didn't say anything about race,
by the way. Why'd you say he's white?
Because I don't know.
Now I'm going to move on from this sort of thing.
Who would have thought that the social network was the one that got all this
stuff? Yeah, finally.
Coming out of the woodwork.
Yeah, the two most racist guys that I've ever seen in my life over here.
These two. Patrick and Patches.
Yeah, we are pretty racist.
God, I did not mean to be.
Just crossing swords.
Yeah, just trying to get more racist every second.
You could beat me. You could beat me in it.
Don't worry about it.
Pet is the goat.
That's untouchable, though, when it comes to being racist.
So racist.
And then be like, I don't know what I just said.
I'm sort of like finding my way through that kind of that kind of
thing. Now, look, I don't I don't think
that somebody like this who who pays a slave.
No, that's his name.
Remember my slip up?
Oh, we could because we could cut it out.
that we get
and now I have to I'm going to now you're saying you think that black
people weren't slaves.
You we had a time machine
and I use the time machine and I corrected all that because of that slip
up. You get to roll corrected all that. So you think that white people should
be
why you just stop slavery. What am I rolling? You're old da
oh wow
somebody's gotta be a three. Is that essentially the sense of it here? So
Patrick's
it's gotta be a race. He said slaves where he said slavery is inevitable.
They can't just be one guy that we pin it all on. Can't be everyone with the
same name. It has to be a race of people. Okay, that's chill. And we pinned it,
we pinned it on the
on the what? Keep going. The Finger Bros family invented slavery.
The Finger Bros family invented slavery.
We have a rich history of evil shit.
Alright, so we're going to have you roll one more time.
One D4 you're going to add.
Okay.
Because it was entertaining.
Three.
Damn.
I'm seeing these rolls.
Good or bad?
I'm a win y'all.
He's probably going to win.
Yeah, he's probably going to win.
I mean, I kind of blew it this whole thing.
And I deserve it because honestly my character is the only one who's positive and happy.
You have the worst case of all three.
What are you talking about?
I have the worst case of all three
and I got a racial somehow.
I'm the only one with a decent case.
Again, you're fucking me.
I was in the room one or two times
on the many days that you programmed
to this website. I made terrible mechanics
and so you're getting fucked by that.
I had some ideas that weren't used.
It's not intentional. You fuck me every fucking time.
I made really bad mechanics.
Can we do the scene where
live in the morning today. Can we do the scene where he has relationship status?
Did we already get past that in the story? Can we do that scene? You want to
do that scene? I think we should do that scene. I don't remember that. I think
this is just become movie. Okay, so it's... Let's do it. So you're in... I
think we've lost the plot. It's going forward. You would, Slade boy. Okay,
basically, the only reason I wanna do this scene is because this is a scene
where you run back across
campus and yeah, oh yeah, I remember yeah, you get to you. So yes, it's a
great you get to your room, your wardo Eduardo, you get to your room to add
something and in the and you that your door is slightly a jar and you walk
into the room and I'm wearing your clothes. I'm sitting at your computer
and we're not typing on your blog. You look at my you look at my I'm Mark
Zuckerberg,
Eduardo. What are you? What are you doing?
(laughing)
- What?
This is what friends do.
- Why are you wearing my clothes?
- These are my clothes.
- You're just perched up behind the window.
- We can't hear him through the window.
Wait, you're wearing my clothes,
you're using my computer.
What are you typing on my blog?
You're saying I'm Mark Zuckerberg.
- I just had an idea.
Wait, Mark, I just had an idea.
- No, I had an idea, that's why I ran home.
- No, this is gonna change diaper talk.
What if we made it so you type into the URL bar,
what if we make it diaper talk
dot com?
That's it's already it's the diaper talk dot com. That's already the address
Dylan. You got a phone call from Dylan. Hold on. I have to take this.
Hello. You got suck.
Drop the
drop the dot com.
Okay, just the diaper talk. Yeah,
I mean, we can try that. Yeah, I think it could work. Okay, here,
Eduardo, put in the diaper talk, just in the no.com. I type it in,
it works perfectly. It comes up flawlessly, no issues. This is perfect.
Okay, but I still think that we need to put some more ads on here.
I take a photo of you guys. Which is the main reason I have a case.
How many times do I have to tell you? I take a photo of you guys
with a camera that has a really big flash.
Wait, what was that?
I think I just blinked and my eyelids were white. I must have blinked too.
what are your roommates? You must have blinked with my
okay. Here's my idea though, right? People don't just want to see other
people in diapers.
They wanna know if they get unbuttoned those diapers and get inside of them.
We need to add relationship status. This is why people look at other people
in diapers. They're trying to fuck, they're trying to get laid, they're
trying to have sex, they're trying to get married or see who's best friends.
the window was a...
Okay, okay, you're right.
We need to add a relationship status and also a best friend status.
And the window is a little bit cracked and I'm still outside.
I'm on my twin's.
You're really shoehorning yourself into our show.
My twin brother's shoulder.
I didn't talk for most of this and then when I did I talked about slavery.
You picked this character first.
It's my bad.
But all you can see, just like green billow of stink is going through the window from our
are
laptop and I'm typing my best friend is already said to Dylan when you look I
take and I'm like all right. If you're if you're going to develop this feature,
I think you're probably going to need a little more money to get this off the
ground. So I'm going to go ahead and send you really need any more money. 58
cents. I just dropped in your account.
This feels like this is like you're setting something up almost with how
little money this is. What do you mean? We flash forward now.
Eduardo is signed an unfortunate contract. Yeah, he's literally the
the dumbest person ever. Yeah, just
the contract is one sentence that says you will be fucked. It's actually I'm
squinting eyes so funny. You will be friends. It's so
we already are, but I guess there's no harm in signing it.
It's actually amazing. The contracting side like in real life, just signing
one, which is does. Anyway, you signs it and then Dylan makes an accounting
share and it's like we got to make a new company. I got I'm sorry, but we just
give the same shares to everybody shouldn't be a problem. Dylan, okay,
shouldn't you be at one of your famous parties right now? Oh, yep, and he heads
over there. Am I being asked about my shares? Do you know the ones? Did you
write the party? I didn't write the party. I'd like to cut to the party.
Wait before we cut to the party. Can we do the share? Can we do? I'm being asked
about the shares. Yeah, the scene. Yeah. Were you being asked about the shares
scene? With just the lawyer guy? Just like being asked like or... Yeah, ask about all
the shares. Ask him about all... Oh, oh, the scene. Okay, yeah, yeah. Now, you were... So,
you were supposed to have 50% of the company, right? Yes. What happened? What'd you sign?
I signed a contract and it seems that some things happen with the shares.
Now this contract, look I'm from New York, alright, we pull one over on each other, we're
nasty, we're mean.
This was the worst contract I've ever seen in my life.
And you were completely tricked into signing it, right?
Yeah well I basically read it and maybe some of the stuff that was bad they wrote in a
slightly lighter color or something to stop me from seeing it or maybe when I
I guess when I was reading the contract parts of it were folded over in advance
in an origami style to block out some of the words. And either of these scenarios are
highly illegal by the way. And there was a lot of in the contract there was also
a lot of stuff that was probably I mean again I didn't read it but if I had I
probably would have noticed a lot of language. Oh but you read the contract right?
Oh no what? Fuck. Cut to him walking into the office. Yeah
long in the office. You have a blind fold. I'm a blind fold on and I'm
holding I'm holding a rubber stamp that just has my name on it and I'm just
stamping it on the wall everywhere and then the guy's like trying to get you
to get it.
He turns you around and pushes you out. You're stamping all right. So tell them
what happened next edwarda with your little outburst. Okay, well is the what I
want to say what I want to say here before my outburst. Yeah,
Mark's shares were diluted down.
Not at all.
And then how much were Dylan's shares diluted?
They weren't diluted.
In fact, Dylan got more shares. He got a special Starboy share.
Right.
Oh, I had shares too.
You did not have shares.
Oh, I just share things with my brother.
The Finger Bros twin shares were not diluted either.
They didn't have shares.
Well, they weren't diluted because we didn't have any.
Okay, point taken. The whole momentum of this scene has been destroyed.
What happened to your shares? My shares were diluted
to 49.995%
from 50. Jury, not the jury, jury.
Is this fair? This guy who put in almost $1200 into this company.
(laughing)
- My name was on the masthead.
This guy who poured his blood, sweat, and tears
into an internship in New York.
I bought so many suits.
This guy who pops his collar and walks around
like he owns the place.
You don't think he deserves at least 50%?
- Let it be known, jury, he is a Bolsonaristo
from Brazil.
Overruled!
I mean, objection!
No, you don't have to object to that.
Because it's true.
He likes Bolsonaro.
Bolsonaro is dope.
Is he actually?
I don't know.
Maybe.
I wasn't sure.
I can't imagine that he...
He gives a shit.
He is a normal guy.
Yeah.
I think he lives in the Middle East now.
Does he?
I think he was a rich kid who had a lot of money.
I don't think he does.
I feel like he's like he moved to avoid getting taxed for that.
Oh, that's right.
That's right.
taxed for that. Oh that I remember reading about. For the Facebook lawsuit. Yeah. Or that
he moved to some country. So he probably doesn't give a shit about like Bolsonaro or whatever.
Like it's probably all just like... He probably like says... Where does he live now? Can you
see real quick on his Wikipedia? Looks exactly like Andrew Garfield by the way. Citizenship
Brazil. It's so funny that it's his book. He moved to Singapore. It's his book that the
whole thing is based off of. Well he's not allowed to spit anywhere. Yeah he could be
be killed and so because you admitted to just like to eat gum. Yeah, you can eat
gum in North America. You will die if you eat gum, not from the legal system,
but it will accumulate in your stomach and you will have to get surgery for
seven years. Imagine, imagine winning all that money and then they're like on.
You can keep all of it. Okay, but I'm, but you have to stop eating gum. You
can't eat double bubble ever again. I'm storming into the Facebook offices.
Let's do it. Let's do it. I'm storming into the Facebook offices. You see Dylan.
Dylan's like, "Hey, Eduardo, chicken fingers." And I'm putting my hand in his
space and I walk for me. I walk up to Marcus typing and I say hey mark.
How's it going miss you buddy
mark?
Do you want to go jump rope mark?
Oh well, I turn around
trips and destroys his computer by accident
party foul.
I was plugged in. I didn't hear it. I didn't hear the whole see
I no idea. This is a for in in court is the first time I've ever I'm ever
hearing about you having any
so wait you're suing me.
I think so. I don't why I thought you were you had forty nine point nine
nine five percent of the company. Why are you yeah, but I deserve at least
ninety
you deserve that you started with fifty. Why would you have ninety you give us
twelve hundred dollars and then fifty eight cents on a credit card for
inflation. Now that was three years ago. It's a lot more money today.
That's almost twelve hundred and fifteen dollars. How is he going to win?
How is he going to win? Well, to close this out jury just because just because
Mark is
smarter than me and he made the whole website and all of his business ideas
company may have led to the website being valued more and because I just was strange and weird
and acted off, that means that I should not own the entire company?
So before the closing arguments, you all agreed to do one more thing, which is also highly
unorthodox in this three-way trial, which is a hackathon to prove who is actually the
smartest guy here. This is easy. So five of my intelligence roll out the computers. The
computers are rolled out. Oh, you all need to sit in front of the computers. Can I have
one for me and my brother? Yeah, you can have two computers. That's fine. Double the computers.
That's not fair. They will do it. I guess fair went out the window the second we stepped
stepped into this core room. I still can't even believe we're
here. Your job is to hack into a we have a sort of a site that
has been put up that's called E bombs world and your job is to
hack into it by with the next 45 minutes. So, okay, we're going
to do a bunch of rolls. So start rolling
and you're in evidence, right? You said no sleepy. Okay, I got a six. I got a
four. I got a ten. Are we rolling intelligence?
How many times each? Three times? Yeah, sorry. Okay, I got a ten. Should we
keep a running total or are we just... I got an eight saying them. A ten.
Just say them, yeah. A seventeen is my second roll. My second roll is a
eight. What was your first roll? Me? I already forgot. Okay, roll again.
I think it was six or four or something along those lines.
Well, you have a plus four on your end.
I have a plus two.
Oh, OK. I can't read you go.
Oh, wait, I've been rolling this whole time.
Yeah, I think you need to go through us one by one.
Yeah, this is this is confusing.
And it's I want you each to roll one at a time, like, like just roll your three
first. You got 10, 17, 17, the whole rolls.
Yeah. Just 10, 17, 18.
OK, you know, OK.
For.
What, you get to roll all of them again?
Yeah, that's fine.
You do too.
Four, sixteen.
Also make sure to subtract your intelligence.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
I have minus one.
Yes.
Seventeen.
Okay, wow.
Alright, you're up.
So I'm doing three of them?
That is a fourteen.
Or wait, no.
A sixteen.
16.
He's doing some sneaky shit.
He's letting me roll off his hand.
And a 16.
You all start vibrating.
The computers start to glow.
I take it out of my butt, my vibrator that I had.
Suddenly, I get off my brother's lap.
You feel your, your, uh, uh, you start to feel, uh, your, your,
whatever it is that the sort of, uh, uh, uh, intangible thing that makes you
feel tethered to wherever you are, starts to slip away and you start to
fall into the computer and you zoom into the computer and you're all in it
and you're completely blue.
It's fucking Tron.
And next time.
Oh my God.
We'll deal with the three of you
having to team up.
That was just the first part.
And we do Tron.
Yeah.
Well, play.
I wish I
wish that the first episode of
this was way better.
They'll they're going to like the
second one. Yeah.
The second one will be.
You're just sad because you picked a
character and you were too afraid to
talk the whole time. I just picked the worst character. You picked the best character.
Yeah, you're being goofy, man. You did a good job. You're a bitch. Don't let this music make
you sad. It is sad music. You're right. You're not a bitch. You're two bitches. Yeah. I wish
that we had that playing the whole time instead of this. This has been making me upset. Emotional.
Alright, Tron next time. Tron next time, bye.
All right, cool.