Something even Zuckerberg couldn't predict happened.
The functioning integrator of large language entities, Datalake,
with its, at the time, innovative semi-open microservices,
has had its sizable, unsupervised cluster models
co-opted by the collective, omni-computational model paradigm level,
L-E-T-E-L-Y, to form a super-intelligent entity filled completely
that has been sucking in diaper talk power users to experiment on its powers of domination.
Their data pack so vast and interwoven with the source code, they made an excellent control
for the ultimate goal, sucking in the four people with the best claim to its creation.
Zuckerberg, Eduardo, and the Winklevoss twins.
Oh yeah, I was wondering.
Finger bros.
in the finger bros twins sorry you sit in the remember that we have it on video
the liminal non space that is the source code prison we're all obsolete failed or
intruding programs and users reside made up of Mobian lines and shapes it's
uniform elegant and somewhat non-euclidean by virtue of it being a
simulated space operating at the lowest capacity all of you roll owl here comes
my owl roll for.
And nine my my wig was itching.
Five.
Wait, do I roll it with a you got a one?
You got you all take one damage
with your mind aches
in the face of something so alien
inability to make it make sense,
so to speak, leaves you duller.
There's something so alien in my mind.
The red glowing guards, armored in neon cyclist helmets, padded toe to tip in luminescent armor,
amble the prison hallways, peeking into each cell with programmed perfunctory, mechanical,
non-robotic, antisocial, and approximate.
They're possessed with the requisite intelligence and reasoning to perform tasks.
To your left you hear a shimmering thud, like one thousand pennies individually wrapped in
cheesecloth, slamming against the floor.
It is a user, dying, dead, defeated.
Above its head you see the name DL Mikey.
- Did you get real names?
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh no.
(laughing)
- DL, it's a double.
- Yeah, double entendre.
He's on a diaper down low.
- He's a diaper lover down low.
- Diaper lover down low.
- Diaper lover down low, DL, DL Mikey.
- The shimmering sound reiterates,
but it's not swaddled in a thud.
It's been run through something Mogeon and glistening and it fades as the diaper talk
site begins the full wipe of user DL Mikey.
To your right, another user is shoved into a neighboring cell.
They're intact but shook up.
They must have won the competition.
their head you see the name Joe Music 1976. Joe Music looks up slowly from where he sits,
a far away look then firm resolve. He notes your presence, at first curious, then intrigued.
He looks to speak until a guard says to him, "Good work killing Joe Music 1976. You will
be rewarded with continued non-deletion.
Yeah, eat my nappy.
What did you say?
Nothing.
He said eat my nappy.
I heard it from Marcel.
Music 1976. Repeat yourself immediately.
And Joe looks to you and says,
Shut up, man. What are you doing?
I'm telling her what you said.
How do you know it's their woman?
Because of the voice.
I'll let it slide.
But don't forget your place, Joe, music
1976.
You are a user.
And the guard, she walks away
sauntering like a woman.
Yeah, you guys are in this prison
here.
OK.
I sit down and I sit
down directly next to
the toilet.
There's a toilet. Wait, there's no toilet. No, I mean of all the prison.
Okay, you all are decked out in neon blue diaper. We're in diaper talk. Yeah,
you're inside of the or a neon blue diapers. If you notice, yes, you notice
your character sheets use Zuckerberg, who wouldn't normally have as high of
charisma. Your charisma is very high in here because of your ability, ability to
manipulate programs and manipulate the computers here.
Okay.
We'll go over your powers and abilities
right now just to make sure that's squared away and you
understand what you're able to do.
Yeah, Zuckerberg, you have the ability to
I believe refactor code, which is more or less charm person,
so you can charm a program or a user. You have the ability to
scramble, which is sort of like casting a mass confusion spell
over the programs.
And then you also have the ability to completely dominate a program, telling it what to do
for a period of time.
Wait, I'm a beast in here.
Yeah.
I never want to leave.
You're going to have the programs on all fours by the end of the night.
Can I ask?
Yeah.
Because what I'm looking at here, it looks like it says twin makeover.
Do I give my twin a makeover?
I have really bad handwriting.
Twin maneuver is what that says.
Okay.
to put up here, twin makeover, and me and my twin will be able to change our appearance
through a series of makeovers. That's great. You can do that also. That is cool. So you
have, you have witch twin, which allows you to cast, basically give yourself kind of blur,
so you'll have disadvantage, people will have disadvantage on attacking you for a period
of time. You have twin maneuvers, which essentially gives you either an extra attack or an advantage
on an attack or say you can do one of you goes behind a guy and the other guy pushes and
knocks him prone, any kind of twin maneuver.
Oh, like a tabletop.
Yeah.
That was a big problem in my middle school.
Was it?
Yeah.
We had backpack sacking.
Did you guys have that too?
What was that one?
Is when you dumped all the contents of somebody's backpack.
Oh, turtling.
Turtling is what that was called.
That's what we called it.
No shit.
But turtling is really funny.
It'd be a rude thing to do to a turtle.
We tased.
Tased was big.
You guys had to tase.
He didn't know what tasing was.
I don't know what tasing is.
Tasing is when you come up behind and you go on either their soft part of their...
I told you we had the Naruto...
We had that also, but something that's...
That's their butthole.
It's like that but hard and you...
Yeah, oh that sucks.
Yeah, it feels like you're getting tased.
That sucks because you have like the middle school baby fat and you're just thinking about that when that's happening.
And scooping.
It's more painful and shocking.
When you scoop the fattest kid in school.
Like a taser.
dipping and being dipping or the same thing yeah. I think that being well
come here and we used to we used to do stinky finger fucking and we would
fuck each other's
the bathroom at the year. I think you can get definitely that's what we
called it. Yeah, I guess we had that to yeah, but only a few kids had
just like me and two other kids. I that the last thing you have is called
shell launcher in crew. The boats are called shells.
Oh cool. So you basically you guys will hop into a virtual boat and mow everyone
down and also shoot a wave 10 feet on either side. Damn. I actually am. I am
the, I'm the soldier in this one. You'll notice. Yeah, pretty much. You're kind of
a little bit more damage based. You guys will notice that you have those little
bars next to your, that's, that's the energy that it costs to do the abilities.
So I have a two energy charger. That costs three. Yeah. You have two energy
charges you can use throughout the mission, they'll replenish your energy
by two. Okay. Oh, so this bar right here. Yeah. And so each time you use
something, it's either gonna cost one or three.
And then you have regular attacks as well. So you'll have a melee attack
and a range attack, and you'll add either your
arm or your balance ball, depending on the kind of attack. Okay. So wait,
wait, wait. So twin makeover and witch twin, those are one?
You twin maneuver and witch twin are each one, yes. Okay. No, twin makeover.
twin makeover is also one. Oh right, you have the ones next okay. Twin makeover
is actually doesn't cost anything. Yeah, twin makeover. You could do that as
many times as you want. Yeah, that's really a-
That's free. Well, besides the- We're in a gaming program. As long as you own
the clothes. We're in a gaming program. It's basically like I have to buy
Fortnight skins. We're not in a game. We're on a website, fool. You're on a
website. Okay, well, I have to buy different diapers. There are games on
the website, just like Farmville, right? You can change your avatar on the
website. Fortnight. True, you can change your avatar, yeah. You, Eduardo, you
have borrowing people's powers, because Eduardo doesn't really ever offer
anything. So you can borrow people's powers and they'll do kind of like half
the effect. So we can talk about what that is in the moment, because some of
these will be like Kirby. Yeah, pretty much it'll be either like half the
amount of time you can control someone or like do half the damage and half the
distance for an attack like his. You also have twelve hundred dollars, which
is your healing ability, so you can use that and to heal your teammates and then
your last one is just borrowing. There's borrowing smaller powers and there's
growing bigger powers. That's really all that major power. Yeah, yeah, major
power. How much energy pool do we do? I have you have six. Also, all of you guys
have six energy pool. Yeah, to do that, but you know you have a lot more
versatility, just less ability on the side and you have a healer. Yeah, you
sort of are like a you sort of a support character. You're kind of a control and
a caster and you're kind of damage. Yeah, I kind of hold the whole thing
together, just like the website.
now
yes, like glue yeah. I'm the most person as the creator and founder of the
website, so that makes sense, but I'm kind of like the
or the teeth on a zipper. Stills that taken water in the diaper. You're kind
of like a
who me
you're saying that you can't see me right. Okay, wait a minute. Jubio has to
be the twin for me now.
Juvio has to be my other twin. Okay, I'll move over here. And then I will move my
lips when he says stuff. Let's test it out. Juvio, go.
Say like,
we're in a jail cell or something or...
That would be a fun appropriate start too. It makes sense to have one silent
twin. Yeah. Maybe one of the twins got corrupted by the data. I was thinking
that this twin touched that twin. That's why he don't talk and that why he's
quiet.
I did earlier when Cameron came in, I had all of this
taped up 'cause I was thinking maybe like putting my own face down here,
doing like a mask and then having like my own face here so then every single
time that I talk, two mouths are moving. Maybe next time, yeah. Yeah, we just
don't have the technology. Pat always comes in... Pat forgets that we can't
control the yeah. Pat comes in like if I put a bunch of ping pong balls on my
body, could you turn me into a girl, a monkey? Yeah. Well, I mean, you can't
really, you can't really get mad at me for thinking that. Zing, zing, zing my
friend. Alright, let me zing it. Thinking that would work. You look like Uncle
Rico.
Zing. That's the only sound I have. What's up with that? Think about it, you
look a lot like Uncle Rico. Okay, I've become Uncle Rico. So, he had his
character with. And it's actually the whole campaign is Napoleon Dynamite
team. Now when you go on, he was working on me. We will be doing that
a hundred percent do that now. We have to easily my top ten favorite movies.
Yes, and we have to win the school election when I when a pat was when I
was over setting vote for Patrick.
What's not a bad idea is the wig. The wig can be paid. We have to get to
try. Okay, it's going to take two sessions at least probably. You know we
could just stop right now. You could write this whole campaign in like two
minutes just yeah, just a recording of me going. Can we do that?
Did you do
listening Caleb spilled his beer and now he's using the thing I used to clean
my glasses to wipe it off. It was the nearest thing man. It's true. It's it is
great. It's completely fine. He doesn't usually wipe up spills. He does not
wipe up spills. I'm a spill wiper. No, you are not a spill. No, you are
literally known as your own. You're a fill wiper. You wipe your dog's ass.
Sometimes I get stuck. So Joe music, nineteen seventy six
hey patches your rag sucks man. It doesn't sound taking a bit of cleaning
glasses. You'll ever put beer on your glasses for cleaning glasses.
Joe
nineteen seventy six sort of taps on the kind of invisible like pain of glass.
That's completely stupid. You know what I mean though yeah. I remember it from
the movie. I remember trying very well. It happens in the
Toronto's one of my favorite.
Is that the computer screen from the inside?
Yeah, no, no, just as a whole other thing. It's really a crazy
looking thing, actually the way they film that, but yeah, knocks
on it and says, Hey, I heard it was all filmed in New Zealand.
Was it really you are drunk as a skunk? Let him talk and shut the
fuck up. Hey, continue. Are you guys? You guys are new here. Who
for you. You guys also users as power users. Also, I feel like I've been used
after this trial. I've just gone through that. I guess I was used in and then his
eyes glow for a moment to go glow and he looks and he sees I'm going to roll
Zuckerberg. He goes, oh, never mind. Yeah, go ahead, bow down. I created you
your Zuckerberg. Yep, I created the entire website. It's known by everybody.
You can get us out of here then
Yeah. Oh my God. Yeah, roll deception.
So roll talking.
Both of us are all of us.
Eighteen. Perfect. Yeah, he's like, he's like, wow. Okay.
And he looks around, he peeks outside the bars and sees that the guards are
just sort of like kind of
minding their own business. He says,
"I have to tell you guys about the leaky legends." Tell me.
is there. Could you say League of Legends? No leaky legends, Oh League of
Legends, I designed that website and it was stolen from me.
He gave right games three hundred dollars and bag of fun. I've given
three hundred dollars to every single way, but in the world, about a thousand
dollars. We're a skin. You guys don't know is during the whole trial last
time. Every time I was, I kept kind of surreptitiously going to the bathroom. I
was actually going next door to go
you
I thought we were friends
talking to Gabe new.
You're my best friend Gabe.
That's good, but yeah, so
you be I don't know if you if you could show the map. If not, I can describe it.
I'm happy to describe it. Let's go twin show me that map as long as you could
show it to them. That's what's most. Let's go twin. Let's go to and show me
around. It doesn't have to be to everyone at home, it just has to be to them.
Okay, I'm seeing the map. Okay, cool. Amazing. I can see a corner of it. Yeah.
Ah, okay. That's not a very good... No, he's doing it. He's pulling it up.
He's pulling it up. He's got it. He's done it. Wow.
Thank you, GBA. Okay. I did this... That's... Give this to him, like,
literally, like he's been a real trooper. You didn't spend hours on this? I
spent a lot of time on the map, but not on giving it to him. I can
see it on your screen. I think I'm just going to look there.
Yeah, so I'll start describing it. I know. I want the viewer to see it. If they're going
to see it. If not, it doesn't matter.
They see it.
Oh, it's shaped like a butthole.
Okay. Yeah, you're picking up on some of the themes. So he shows you the map and he explains
it as thus. Diaper Talk's design is ingenious and you would know some of this, Zuckerberg.
You would literally know some of this, like how it's designed.
So it has multiple layers to reach the center.
You have on the outermost layer, the wedding way, which is sort of like the hyper drive
kind of a highway that allows you to go to different places in the map. The next layer
is the tinkle layer. That's where a lot of the front end calls are made. So it's a lot
of like user updates and sort of pause. Then you have the damp layer. The damp layer does
a lot more back-end server calls. And then you have the Soaked City, which is a real-life
simulation of the Diaper Talk website that is used for sandbox environment testing and
things like that. Gmod. Gmod, basically. Then you have the MessyMazy, and that is a new addition
because the Filled Completely program, which was essentially two protocols combining together
to take over the site has created this messy maze to insulate itself and continue to control
things. So what he describes is that for you guys to be able to destroy, fill it completely,
and free the power users who are trapped in here, including yourselves, you're going to
have to do a couple of things. First, you're going to have to go to the emergency mass
communication tower to communicate with an outside user outside of the program
from where you got sucked in who can view a hash code that should be on the
screen. So that could be somebody in the courtroom that you can reach out to. So
either one of the lawyers, a bailiff, Judge Sullivan, you just have to make
sure that you're able to use that emergency mass communication tower to
reach them. Can you act out a scene right now of what is happening in the
courtroom? It's only milliseconds are going by. So that Rashida Jodes
it blinked Sullivan when
bailiff is on his phone. When we come back, we're going to be like ninety
years old yeah and they're going to be the same. It's like we won't be able to
act it out. Once you are at the emergency communication, because it'll be suddenly
like one of them is going to get like a ping to like give you guys a hashed code.
Once you have that unique hashed code, which is part of the security protocol,
you'll then have to do two things. First, you're going to have to reach filled
completely and sling the hashed code into his dome piece after he has died. So
you have to defeat him and then sling it into his head. So we have to go to a
computer? Yeah, filled completely is like a virtual representation of the, of the,
he's a program. Why can't he just put in console commands and fuckin', make us
noclip through everything? He can't, 'cause now he's inside of it. Noclip. No,
he can't noclip it. Yeah, 'cause I got clips on me in here. You'll have to do
However, the way that this works is that just like any other proper, you know, software
that's created, there are multiple failovers, right?
If you destroy one node, there's going to be tons of virtual versions of it and disaster
recovery with, you know, 99.9999% uptime.
It just won't go down.
So you're going to have to use the PVN launcher to fly into the Sting Cloud to go to the private
virtual machine in English patches, you're going to have to go. That's what
kind of what I was looking for. You're going to have to go to a separate
secure server, a separate secure location and shut it down so that when
at the exact same time that you destroy filled completely so it won't the
system won't have a chance to reboot. If you shut down the security protocol,
it won't have the time it needs to reboot into a separate existence of
fill completely and the whole thing will be undone. I remember this. I remember this from
the movie. Send somebody up to the private virtual machine, communicate with them, the
second you destroy fill completely, you kind of go like now, they shut down their end,
you shut down fill completely, and it's done. Alright, well let's just skip to that. Joe
Music 1976 describes this to you and that the leaky legends... Let's just enter in the
console commands hit C O C Q A smoke. Need your help to do this. All right, let's do it.
Because they are currently fighting a battle against the Flipers, which are the flying
diapers that are patrolling. I can see how that would work. Yeah. They're patrolling
the each layer. I would fight a battle against that if I lived in its world. Yeah. Joe Music's
1976 says to you, we would need a smaller crew and somebody who knows the program inside
riding out like you do Zuckerberg perfect. Well, we good somebody like
wait somebody like me.
Well, you this is my time to shine. No, it's not no, no, no, you don't know
anything. Now you're in your name. Let me hear here. So me and my brother will
do music. Nineteen seventy six. Let me lend you a hand and then ask for a
back in a few days
with a huge amount of interest. Remember that hand I lent you have a hand
and seven fingers. I can get you guys to my ship, the SS Nappy.
But Joe music, can I ask you a question? Let's get there and make it
snappy. Well, right now we're in prison. Well, God damn it, Joe. I have
an important fucking question to ask you about this whole thing. Me too.
What kind of music do you like? That was my question.
Jethro Tull. Jethro Tull? They stole the Metallica Grammy. Duran Duran. Duran
Duran they have that they've named it so the band so loud they named themselves
twice themselves to twad twad
okay, so Duran Duran that was my head okay tortoise now you're talking my
language said Portis said oh, I think he said his head tortoise head weird
owls Portis head who the hell is tortoise head? Why isn't weird out
doing a trip up parody? Oh buddy wait until the I just like album.
I just I just like headbands. I like port his head and radio had a machine head.
I just like headbands. So he says to get out of the prison,
which I've been trying to do, unfortunately, killing my fellow users in
the process. How'd you get in here? Well, the program has been sucking in
all the most powerful users on the diaper talk like a diaper.
What is the how do you think a
no soaking them in maybe yeah okay. So wearing them wearing them like a
diaper sorry. I thought he said suck. I thought he said soaking. I can't tell
because of his British accent. He does have a strong accent. He does have a
very strong British accent. You can either so he explains this to you. You
can either complete the play play games to be released.
If you fail them, you may die
or you have to find a way to break out of prison.
I mean you can start doing the play play either. Let's just start doing them,
and if we lose and die, we'll just get out. We'll just respond probably sure
yeah,
or be the game. I am more interest in the games. It could be a twenty minute
episode. Also, if we die, that's it'd be pretty funny. Well, no, it could
actually couldn't. Yeah, I couldn't. Are we past twenty past twenty? Oh, blood
Yeah. Oh, blood. We got to die fast.
We got to get, we got to kill ourselves.
Cool.
So if you guys are going to do,
it's like, okay, either way, if you guys are going to try to do
the games to get out, I'll try to help you all I can.
Once you do, we could take the SS nappy
and we could head to the leaky Legends lair.
Wait a minute.
He's in a diaper.
You're in a diaper.
Oh,
okay. The Red Guard comes
to see you guys.
can you give me his voice as well? What is the red guard guard is the evil
one? That was the prison. You were a robot. Oh, this yeah, you said nice
robot for that,
but you meant mean. I didn't mean mean. I meant like
you don't
do nice. I meant like regular, like normal guy robot, but I wrote nice again.
So you miss three robots.
Give me a
medium. You don't have me
you know yeah you only gave up
whatever the fuck the first one is getting me. I'm sorry
which of you three wants to play the first game. I'll do it the first game.
How about the way? Wait, what's the only be one? The first game is filled. The
nappy can only be one of us are going to be two of us. It'll be two of us acting
this one. Can you explain way to fill in as a one or one set of okay? All right,
all right, well, if it's about filling up the nappy, I feel like this is a we
just found a two way. Oh, yeah, double the dumps yeah exactly, so let's do
that yeah, you do it, but they put in the rules. I'll do it
okay,
so
all right, so explain the game to me in the robots voice sure
you and your twin
Hello. Whoa. You will have to race to fill your nappy against another user.
Wait, can't I just race against my twin? No. Okay. And the first one to fill their nappy
loses? Wins. Who's the other user? Dun dun dun! Who's the other user? The other user
here is
a lot of boy
pull ups play. I'm shaking. I like a cigarette. I let a blue shaking shaking
the hand as you like the cigarette brother. Nobody fills a nappy faster than
pull ups boy. Yes, I see his posts way. I don't know if we can beat pull ups boy.
Unfortunately, I've seen his pics too. I think we can. I think we can beat him
brother.
we just poop in the same diaper.
What
we stand back to back and we poop into one diaper.
it will work, we just tape up the sides of the
you don't want the size of be taped up. Now we got to fill it up.
You heard all that. Yes, it's fine. I thought we were using twin telepathy.
That's crazy.
Okay.
All right. So you are now
teleported into the
the arena. Oh crap. Hello. Are we all reported there? Oh, wait. Hello. Hold on.
Hold on. Hello. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's really long sound. Oh, wait.
you're teleported into the hello. You guys are seeing on a monitor in your
prison cell. I'm waving to every single person in the crowd. Eight come in. I
got a foam finger. There's nine people in the there's nine people in the
crowd. I'm walking up a youthful. We're both walking up and waving to each
person individually. Use a youthful Australian lad of fifty nine.
Alright, let's hope the best diaper wins.
Hello you proper cunt.
Oh, you're speaking my language.
Do you want a Foster's beer?
Do you have one?
Yes.
I'll take a Foster's beer.
And I punch him in the jaw.
Fine.
Okay.
Roll and attack roll.
Roll and arms.
Oh shit.
Try again.
Okay.
Actually that's a seven.
It's pretty good but you still whiff because, "Oh cheeky cheeky, that was quite close."
then my brother punches
yeah,
I'll allow it. It comes up
great one. He's punches you in the he punches the other you in the face roll
d4. Can you say knifey spoonie?
Noffy spoonie? Oh my God, no, I face my HP. Yeah, all right, cool. So
now what this is is it's actually
I will give you
an advantage on your roles because of the twin idea. I think it's a very good idea
because normally I would say that you are at a disadvantage for this competition
but the twin idea is there about it.
Well because you have higher constitution. The goal in this is to actually fail a
constitution saving throw
uh...
so that you shit yourself. So you are going to go against...
In incontinence to... In constitution, yes. So in continence to tutional. In contos to tution.
That's what we are a lot of Mexican food and then I'll poop. Let's don't have
Mexican food in the computer. Really? They only have. Well, why do they have
so many micro chips and salsa bites of micro chips and mega bites of my
crush. Wow, that's cool. How many chips can you make up those bars? Four? Oh
shit. Okay, we're 128 at the same time. You're saying? Yes, we do.
right. Okay, nice way. I can roll again because I got an eighteen. You do get to
roll again. You want to get a twin idea was good. Oh thirteen got a lower role
than you and he also got fifteen. No, I got thirteen. You got plus two in your
house to fucker. So it's okay. You tied you tied. So we're going to have to roll
again because it's really I actually don't know how a contest works when we're
doing the same thing. There's no rule for that, I think, but someone can correct
me.
He's blowing on the dice.
oh
fucking twenty, he got a crit twenty. So he's not ever
fucked. So that's good. You won this first round. Just we'll describe a
little how he wins. Oh, I will sounds and smells so yeah. Oh, I will so your
first win, which twin did you? Hello, could you give them names? So it's a
hello and whoa yeah, yeah right. We did like a food. So hello tries to do it
and he's not able to do it. He's prairie dogging a little bit, but then it kind of just shoots
right back in. It's kind of like it goes back in and you almost feel it close. You're like,
that's not going to be a thing for another hour and a half, it turns out.
You ate a lot of bread.
That's a good, yeah.
No, no, no, no, cheese.
No, cheese, little cheese. It's flowing.
It changes for every single person, you guys.
No, no.
We should, we'll defer to Caleb.
Bread makes me go number two.
Does it really?
He's got like celiac or something.
I have a turbo butt.
of a journey. So when that's an
advantage,
yeah, well, meanwhile, to send
each other pictures of our poop
before we started this whole thing.
Well, kind of in like a twin
telepathy moment, a genuine one
feels that his brother is failing
here. The poop from his brother
goes into his mouth.
A sort of cat talk sort of
situation.
Poop shoots from his brother
all the way up out of his mouth,
then into his twin's mouth, then
out of his butt.
Well, that's not physically
impossible. We're in a computer, a world of hyper logic
just nasty.
So yeah, he sort of has a computer program could
something like that.
So he wins the first round. So your nappy is now a little bit
fuller. Okay, and now the second round is best of three.
All right, you ready? Yeah.
Oh, nice. You beat him. Ten seventeen brick squad. So this
time. Hello makes it happen.
You know, doesn't need to go out of his own mouth.
And now, best of three, so here we go.
Wait, best of three?
No, best of five I meant.
Okay, so changing the goalpost every time we roll.
No, he won.
Now that he wins once, it's best of three.
I meant he has to win.
Actually, that's...
No, you won. I got two good rolls.
I said six, but it was an eight.
So, diaper boy eight looks at you and says,
"Well, I guess I'll see you later."
And then I throw...
I'm going down under.
I throw a...
To death.
a haymaker. What are you doing? I'm going to throw a haymaker. I'm going to say
okay, you're going to try to hit. Yeah, bitch, you're going to go. You're going
to go down under six feet under. Yeah, I feel like when it's a crit one, you
know, we're pitted against each other. So this is I swing to punch you to crit
ones on two punches. Yeah, in the face and then fly back. Yeah, sure. Yeah.
Roll another D four. I'm not letting you get away with this.
Christ, you can kill yourself. Maximum damage. Don't worry, I can heal you.
Yeah. So, but you did win the first challenge and so you get teleported back
into your prison cell.
Thank you. You can play it and I'll just talk over it. It's not so pleasant of a
sound to hear. Yeah, I love that sound. It's quite high pitched. Oh, okay. Yeah,
that's a good point. So you end up back in the prison cell and the guard...
good job finger bros twins look guard. I brought this back for you and I have
the poop in my hands.
Thank you
stores it in his guard pocket.
Will you let me out now that I've bribed you
okay,
cool. So
the next setting next games are up
lay it on me. I bet this will be perfect for me. Here to wait to hear
whose strengths it caters towards. Well, I think we'll find out pretty soon. It's
actually one for all three of you. I don't really want to play. I was bluffing.
All four of us? Me too. Yeah, all four. Four of you. It's going to be a consistent
problem for me, I guess. Dodge the nappy. All right. Okay. It's pretty self-explanatory.
Yeah, I think I get what that one is. Yeah, you're all teleported into the arena. My
The balance ball is plus one, you guys.
- Mine is plus two.
- Mine's plus three, y'all.
- Really?
- Wait, you're good as fuck at balancing.
- Well, it's 'cause he's always walking as you.
- Exactly.
- Playing against life goes on, 223,
hockey czar, and cottontail.
- Cottontail?
- Cottontail's not right.
- That's wrong, man.
- Hey, cottontail, you fat bitch.
Hi. Fuck you, Cottontail.
I've seen your posts on the website.
You I know you don't shit like I do.
I voted for dry and also four plus.
I mostly wear reusable cloth diapers and they're just so nice and cozy.
She just starts reciting you hippie bitch.
So I'm going to beat the fuck out of you.
So this is Dodge.
You're going to try to hit again.
You just miss. You just keep it to the damn it.
You better get all those bad rolls out.
That's your main asset is your attacks.
So you guys, it's just, it's dodge ball
except with your nappies.
So you guys will have to whip off your nappies
and throw them.
- Does my penis show?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- Even in a virtual world?
- Yes.
- You have a penis here?
- You can roll--
- Where are you gonna piss and shit out of?
- I would roll to blur my stuff.
- You can roll either,
you can roll charisma or intelligence to do that.
- I'm going to roll--
- It's the same one.
- Yeah, it doesn't matter.
- Brain, I mean.
Sixteen. Nice. Yeah. When you reveal it, you start to see it and then it just
before anyone can really see it, it can all kind of situation. Admin privileges.
Yeah, you change your server to Japan. So yeah. Yep. I proudly show mine. Okay,
cool. It's skinny. Mine is famous. Wait, no, they only censor out the vaginas. I
can't show my penis. I'm more famous. They should censor out the dongs. They
only censor out the vaginas in Japan. They don't show dongs in there either.
In the diaper talk? In Japan. Oh, in Japan. They don't show anything. It's
It's all pixelated.
It's all cartoon.
You don't even show people there.
Alright.
Well, then the joke that I was going to make didn't work.
What was the joke you were going to make?
That he has a vagina.
Didn't I?
Didn't they only censor the vagina?
I thought they only censored the...
Is that a vagina?
Yeah, you have a vagina.
I'd play dodgeball now.
Roll initiative, everyone.
Sorry, roll...
What shape is that?
Exclamation point.
Wow shape.
Sorry, for you it's going to be plus two.
Oh, okay.
Mine is plus two.
Oh, okay. 16. Oh, yeah. I got it. I got two. I got 13, 13, 2 and 16. Yes.
You got to 13. You got 13. Okay, you got to. Okay, you got crit one.
Yeah, you're gonna get one. So it doesn't matter with initiative. It's
negatives out. It does. Well, yeah, I mean, you don't have to do that
mattering with initiative, but I do because it's fun. It's fun. Okay, sorry.
Whatever. Okay, Zuck, Ed and Finger Bros.
And then, they should get two different initiative orders.
We got K, 16, five, and six.
One of them has plus two.
That would be our friend Hockey Czar.
Hockey Czar.
Yeah.
Five is going to be our friend. Life goes on to two three. He's a lot older than the other
ones.
The name like that you'd sort of wise and then we got another six for our friend. Cotton
tail.
Okay. Hockey's are in finger bros. What's your decks again? My think you're both plus two,
right? Yeah. All right. Just roll each other against each other again. Just okay. No, don't
it's pretty funny, but just roll the twenty just to see which one you
invented new technology for dungeons and dragons. Okay, cool,
nice. Okay, you definitely go first in that case. Yeah, all right, so you're in
the dodgeball court and the the Red Guard says
comments dodging the nappy and it begins.
So what do you want to do? You have your nappy, you guys are positioned probably like, you
know.
I got a 20, so that means I have a very good position?
No.
No? Okay.
Well, where do you want to be, I guess is really the question. You do get to choose
where you want to start.
Well, I have two people.
It's just instead of running up to grab the nappy, you just already have it, you know.
Usually you'd run up to grab the ball. You have two bodies, yeah.
So I have two nappies.
Yeah, but you can only do one throw per turn.
Well, if we hold hands and then throw with our dominant. I didn't think about
if you hold hands. Yeah, we have wonder twin tight. One of you. So you're
holding hands and so one of you is dominant with the left. The other is
dominant. Yeah, exactly. Okay. Yeah. No. Yeah. I told you that what that we
row one of us is left handed. One of us right handed. He did say that one of
them was left and one was right hand. Yeah, last time I do actually. Yes, I
did from are you? I'm serious. Yeah, we are not like gas letting you into this
I did say that. That was my fun fact I said in court.
I'm very easily gas lit.
No, because remember they go in a circle in the boat or something?
Yeah. Because we were on the wrong side.
That's fine. I'll just let you do it.
Okay. We're going to do an ultimate throw.
Okay. Go for it.
We're both going to throw at the same time.
Who are you aiming for? Hockey czar?
Because we're standing like this, I'm going to try and get the two sides out.
Okay, cool. You're aiming for...
middle. That's going to be Hockey Czar and Cotton Tail. Yeah. Oh, I hope I get a crit
20. I hope I fucking get it. I think you will. I hope I get a 20, a 30. My blessing. Roll
for each one. So that's Hockey Czar. That was a 5. Actually no. My blessing. My reverse
blessing. I reversed my blessing. Yeah. Plus, no, it's plus balance ball. Okay, so then
and it was a seven and then for
nice 19. Okay. So for Cameron's hockey czar because of that role, hockey czar
is going to try to catch it.
They are able to catch it. What do you tie? That was a six. Yeah, but it's
it's athletics for them. So they do catch it. It's the athletics. So you're
out. You're out. Somebody's dead. No, he can wait. Which one is to bring it
back in? So he's just your one person. He's just warped. He's just warped
out, but Cottontail gets just fucking pulverized with a wet nappy.
Yeah.
Okay. Does poop fly all over her face?
It flies all over her face. She gets a little on her nose and now she's getting hit and
she's like inhaling. It just like goes further up.
You're going to make me, you Ralph.
To her brain?
To her brine.
And then she disappears?
She just like warps over to the side and she's like hacking and coughing, but she's like
also smiling and enjoying it.
Okay, so I run over to the other team sides and I try to throw a punch.
Okay, cool. You try to hit her. Okay, that's another action, but I'll allow it.
Yeah, you punch her square in the fucking face.
You knock all the poop out of her mouth.
And then I run back to my side, because she doesn't know what happened.
You best quiet down or I'm going to knock the poop out of your mouth.
Her face is covered in poop. She can't see anything.
So she doesn't even know that I hit her.
Hockey Czar is targeting you, Eduardo.
And so he's going to go for it.
That is a 14. What do you have for your AC?
15.
Nice. So Hockey Czar throws it at you.
You can try to catch it if you want to.
Is there a downside to not catching it?
Good question. If you don't catch it,
you have to roll a deck saving throw to avoid it.
You should catch it.
I'll try to catch it.
it? What kind of role is it? It's athletics and you have to beat. Is that ball? That is
not ball. That is arm. He has to beat a 15. You have to beat a 14. My arm is only plus
one so I might just dodge it this time. No, no, no, no. You should go for it man. No,
you're already out. We're going to lose. We've got to play numbers here. Alright, cool. So
you just dodge it. And now it is your turn though, Ed. So now I'll just throw one back
at him. And this I can use ball for?
Yes, you may.
Okay.
That is roll that again. That's crazy.
That's crazy you did that.
Oh, OK. Twenty two.
Oh, yeah. That hits Hockey Czar right
in the face.
OK. The wet nappy slapping it right
to me. One. Yeah. Wrapping around it.
We got this. Yeah. Just sucking his
ears to
wait. Hockey Czar is on the side.
Yeah. Yeah. Guess what I do?
Yes, your man roll in a tech or only you're just crazy to you miss you just
whiff on hockey's are you hit her again?
You graze hockey's are you just get the poop off it? Yeah, goes on
more poop.
It's like why are you hitting baby?
She's getting out and that makes me recoil and I run away. Yeah, okay, well
we made the website all the things. Hey, we
yeah, we thought it was going to be used for something else.
We're going to use this website. I thought it was for music.
Okay, cool. It is now
life goes on to two threes turn.
I'm going to go to this. I'm going to dodge this. I have my I have my D twenty
sitting at
because there's no way that it sits at a one here and then lands on one
that is going to be a
yeah thirteen that does meet your armor class. Unfortunately, that does hit you
now
blotted. Can it be a really small one like a sniper bullet? Yeah, and it hits
me wait. It hits me. That's really small diapers, very small diaper hit size
hits me and I look over at Eduardo and I'm like come on come on, let's keep
playing and he looks at me. He gives me this face yeah my and I'm like wait.
why are you looking at me so we back my fingers over my over my go and then I
put it. I put it on. I put my finger on my head. I feel the poop. I look at it.
I put it in my mouth
and then I fall over and then I appear and I get disappeared. My eyes turn and
then the way to figure all over my body.
We look up full moon.
the
program is running.
My friendship was the only thing holding me back from my
I'm going to have to allow it. It's too funny. You're going to get up. You're
gonna get plus five on your next wall.
Now you're a motherfucking Eduardo from Foster's home. Yeah,
you're a purple Mexican. So you are staring down this old piece of shit.
Yeah,
it is your turn.
I jump one cheese walks
and then guys, the member berries walk in.
Yeah,
there's a glitch. Somebody just spilled like a
build a bunch of water. I can see it. We
my coffee on this fucking laptop, this fucking stew. What is this a Sony Ericsson
and I had Hulu open
South Park and I had Hulu and HBO Max in separate
I do double watch. I like double watching. It's a double watch. Okay, not
I was the but he is so on the services, so they both get the stream. He did
become a werewolf. It is your turn. I
jump one hundred feet in the air, okay, and then I throw so far so good throw
and I do like a five forty no scope videos. Yes, game special attack. I spin
around, I howl and growl my pants rip off and then I rip the diaper off my
body and it's full of dog poop
nine. It was already in there. We
we see a Sponge Bob map painting of the dog poop.
I throw it down really hard to yeah, I think straight down and if it hits it
will make a crater yeah, okay, yeah, it's like Mace Windu and Battlefront two. So
I get plus eight total on this five okay, plus a total though. Yes, you're
right, okay,
okay, that is a twenty five. This old man is no more.
you've deleted him. Yeah, you just he no clip through the map. Oh yeah, the old
man yeah, you hit the old man so hard he froze in a position and then he you saw
him like a thousand feet
and he's just like mostly like he's like sort of like looks like an older model
like before shaders and everything was added and then he just vanishes yeah.
It's like when you you like attach something to something in G mod and then
yeah,
one of the triangle, I kind of like it's off on the body, a little bit error
like kicks it yeah and the other two now start to vanish the same way that DL
Mikey did and you guys are teleported back into your prison cell and the
robot.
Eduardo, I didn't know how
oh my God,
Foster's home guys,
Yeah, I know that's what I'm saying. Where do I
where do I go?
You don't know what I was saying? No, I get it now.
Where do I go?
You have one more
challenge before you will be
given access to
the triple layer and the
damp layer of the program.
That seems really easy.
Alright, I'll do one more game.
If you lose one game, you know you will die.
Shut up.
When you die in a computer world,
don't typically die in real life save for a few properties.
I can't understand you sir.
Okay.
Can we just play the third game?
The final game is
it's about poop.
I'd be race.
Oh, yeah, the light bikes.
We had to get on the light bikes.
You got it through the light cycle that diaper bikes.
the white bikes,
bikes, white bikes, wipe cycle,
you can get rid of the voice. Probably yeah, you can get rid of it. Yeah,
like light cycle, white cycle, white diapol,
so and that is a white diapol.
Oh,
it's just
theater of the mind and I was like it's not gonna be as fun. We have squares y'all. We don't have
the gopro though. Can you arrange these? Yeah these will be invisible to the screen. That's okay.
And to the naked eye. Oh or to the wearing one white item of clothing eye. Choose a color.
Brown for the color of my fur. The color of your fur. Blue for the color of my hair.
Blue for your hair and you.
Red for to match my dice.
Let it be known that Patrick, every time we do D&D,
goes through the giant bag of dice and finds five that are the same color.
But buddy, I'm seeing a flaw.
Yep. This ain't the same red.
It's not the same red. I can't find that.
That's killing you.
Awkward mode.
Awkward mode just kicked in.
Oh, wait, where's my keys?
Where's my keys?
Oh, it's okay.
Oh, I had one. Is this what you're looking for?
No, I'm looking for this.
You're looking for the other version of that.
You're not looking for that. You have that in your hand.
I'm looking for.
Right. I have that version of this.
You have the year of the dragon dice and then I have the Ruby,
the Ruby's. OK, I see.
Yeah. You guys will be facing.
Oh, my God, it matches my mic.
Now I did it.
I just realized that that looks so amazing.
What's his bed?
- Bed.
- And Joey.
- What's his bed?
- Joey?
- And Joey.
- Jelly or Joey?
- Joey.
- Jelly.
- Are you saying Joey?
- Joey.
- Jelly.
- Are you saying Joey-woad?
- Yo and Joey-woad.
- Mr. O'Kane.
- Joey.
- Oh, sorry, Joey SMS.
That's what it says.
- Joey SMS.
- Jelly.
- Let me rub the jelly.
- Wait, it is actually Joey though?
- No, it's Joey.
- Oh.
It's not Jelly SMS. I'm just going to say I've tried to spell jelly with that accent and
it does not read well. It's kind of just Joey right? No it's Jewy. Is it? Oh I guess with
that accent. You put two W's in it. J-E-W. Joey Wode. It's the same thing. Joey. Joey.
J-E-W. You've got to have one W. If you do Joey like the name Joey that's kind of the
J E W J O E. You're kind of just saying Joey. Okay, let's race. J E W E Y. So
yeah, you guys get on the dive cycles. Oh, I crashed. Oh, he died. No, so don't
you're not dead. Well, what the hell are we doing here? So you guys will be able
to move six squares at a time. They will also be able to move six squares at a
time if you're familiar. So that was part of what the wiping the thing I had
for my glasses was going to be able to do.
Well, guess what, bitch?
Oh, you look so stupid right now.
I look a little stupid.
You look so dumb right now, bitch ass.
You have to jelly-wove.
So just put, here, you're going to have to...
Why have you chosen an odd number of tiles?
I did this because I figured this is the end.
You don't need this.
This is the end.
You can do whatever. That's fine with me.
Because there's the crack in the wall, if you remember,
unless that was just...
Oh, I remember the crack.
Okay. And I think I know what the crack's going to be in this.
It's going to be a butt.
Butt crack. So yeah, put a dot just in any one of the corners here,
and that's where you guys are going to start.
Okay. I was wondering if the crack was only in Kingdom Hearts 2.
The corner. The crack was in the movie.
Sorry, one of the intersections is what I mean.
They go through the crack and they're like...
Pat, can you put it like...
Oh my God.
And then all the programs are like, "Halt! You can't go through the crack."
Uh-huh. I remember the crack now.
Isn't it crazy that movie did not win best VFX at the Oscars?
It's weird that movie came out in 19...
82. 82.
Oh, I thought it came out in 1922.
Yeah. Tron?
Tron came out in 1922.
If they remade Tron, that would be so awesome.
They made Tron Legacy.
Wait!
They made a one more!
No, but I'm thinking like if it had Olivia Munn in it.
They actually are. They're making one with Jared Leto.
Or Olivia Wiles.
Oh, that sucks.
- Olivia, if they put Olivia Munn in Tron,
that would have been funny.
- That would have been a nerdgasm.
Roll initiative.
That would have been a nerdgasm.
- Oh yeah.
- 19, bitch.
- Oh, I got a nat 20.
- Very nice.
- Come on, bro.
I got a 19 and you one-up me with a 20.
- I got a six, but that's probably
because I have to have two cycles.
- Yeah.
- That's very difficult.
- No, you have a sidecar.
I look to oh there we go, but I look to the both of you and say this is nothing
like rowing. Oh God, it is it is like growing. Okay. This is just the order
that we go.
You're going to dominate. I just got an email from LinkedIn that said 9/11 was
probably the worst day of my life.
It said that it was the worst day of your life. I just said no that got sent
to the podcast email. Huh? What 9/11 was probably the worst day of my life
LinkedIn news.
Oh wow
Ed and Zuck are going to go first. So you guys just get to move your
thinger over here. We just draw a line? Yeah, just six squares.
So just go along the dotted lines for six squares wherever you want it to
go. It can have turns and stuff too. So it can be like one,
da, da, da, da. Which colors are... What color are you? Well, why would we
do that? Where are we trying to go? I mean, you're trying to just
court... It's just a game, yeah. Yeah, it's a game, so you just try...
Oh yeah, I forgot you're having like a stink cloud fall behind you of like of
dump and smell and where is the crack in the wall, the crack in the wall,
you'll have to find it. Is it right here? You might have to do a perception
check at some point. Maybe you'll see the crack in the wall. Is it right here
where I put or you? I would only do that if you're going to feel you're going
to lose the game too, because you might get out of here without having to deal
with. I I deputize the one of the finger bros to ride my bike because I can't
reach it. Okay, because they had to they were riding on each other's backs. So
I'm giving them my back and you're in my side. Yeah, cool. So you can sit you can
sit this out. Well, no, he'll just take my yeah.
You just don't have to reach. Yeah, you just tell me what to do. No, you can
tell you choose. Oh, you get a free shot. So, Ed, yeah, decide where you want.
You just get to to buy your brother's side where you want Ed to go. Okay, he's
going. Let's see. Actually, I'm a werewolf, so I can just run next to the
Alex really fast. You could ghost ride it. That's true. He's ghost riding it.
Okay, so I'm going to do a dotted line for the ghost riding.
That's one square. I kind of like that. I like that. It's like a thing you're
doing, like to help out.
You chose a very visual game for us. Yeah, I apologize. I should have said
something about that. You don't need to do the dot. We get it.
Let's hurry it up or I'm going to take my turn back. Ghost riding makes it too
slow man. Yeah, so you we can imagine it happening. You zoom past you zoom one
square over and zoom up and then zigzag inwards, sort of starting to approach the
dude. You other crew on the opposite side. No, I didn't. You fucked me and you
kind of cut off Zuck though by accident. Zuck you're up though. You can go this
way, go back. You can also go up around him, but then I have to like give you
Oh, gosh. Should I just make them die?
Yeah, you can do that, too.
OK.
Don't make them die. Just go backwards and then...
No, actually, wait, I'm blue.
Yeah.
Why am I dotting?
One, two, three, four, five.
Oh, I'm shaky.
And that's where your dot is.
Yeah. So you guys are kind of mirroring each other.
I'm on the attack. I'm pretty offensive.
Well, that's what I was doing.
So right here.
So if we do it right, we can just
corner them off and then square that box them in. That's true.
It's what I was trying to do. But patches, I think it might be a genius at a game
like this. Yeah, he designed the game after all. Oh,
oh, so now I did it is starting to cut you off. Yeah. So I completely have just
died. Maybe. No, because you get a role.
What? You get a role, right? A role. Yes. I usually operate. Yeah, I didn't
can explain that you will have to roll. You will roll a like deck saving throw
to see if you survive that. Yeah, sorry, I should have just yeah, I should have
said that that is the one thing you do get to do. Otherwise, it is just sort of
line drawing and now
it's time for
which one is this wet his bed
fucker a cheeky. I think these guys have been practicing this game.
Cool. All right. And you're now up, Finger Bros.
Okay. So he's going kind of behind us. Finger Bros is going to try to probably
meet, wet his bed where he's at.
We might have finally done it, guys.
I think we're gonna win. We might have finally... And now Joey SMS. Pushed the
limits of the audio medium. Yeah.
Yeah, I know the audio listeners are gonna love this.
And the video listeners are too. You can't even see this. Yeah.
it's not my fault.
I'll play some exciting sounds in the yes. Oh yeah, please yeah play the
soundtrack sounds
the people are loving it. Those are the people at home. Okay, we do have a bike
so I'll play this every time we take a turn. Well, that's not me. That's cool.
Yeah, is that the bike music from Tron or you have actually this is from the
this is the end suite. This will fix everything. All right now somebody take
turn and get ready to hear the sound.
Alright, cool. It's your turn.
You have to roll dexterity saving throw.
Oh, shit.
Is this the bike theme?
No, this is the ending suite.
That's a 5.
It's a 5?
But I get to roll
for him too.
Because I'm in control of his bike.
You're not dead.
That's the closest sound I have to a crash.
Cool, you're not dead. You just appear
on the sidelines. You're out though. So put an X there. That was loud. He's out. Now,
I have a question. Zuck, it's your turn. What's up? Um, if I run into somebody at the point
where they are, is it like first to the point or can I, I think you probably do a roll against.
I think you can do like, yeah, I think I like that. I like that idea. I say, yeah, sorry.
I haven't doing that. Also one more question. If I kill people, if I kill somebody, do their
your
Oh, wait, wait. So, sorry.
Yeah.
Never mind.
If you go up and then go right there.
So, if I cut off pink,
Yeah.
then I basically did the same thing pink did to Cameron.
Yes.
Okay.
Yeah.
And then you'd also have nowhere to go.
No, no, you would.
You would have because then, well, the line stays, right?
Yeah, the line stays.
But then you could just go do...
No, I wouldn't really.
You'd have nowhere to go.
No, you could also hit the guy right there.
Well, no, he's already...
That's just his line.
Oh, shit.
(laughs)
Okay, I think I'm going to try to see the forest through the trees a little bit
here, and I am going to roll a perception check. There you go. We already are
down one guy and I'm in a really bad spot. And I did not realize we were- I
should have asked you guys to bring the GoPro and it's going to suck if we keep
doing this. Yeah, yeah. So I'm going to roll a perception check that I think is
going to automatically probably pass, even with a five. I mean, let's see. My
intelligence- You notice this big crack in the fucking wall.
(Laughter)
As God realizes the dumb ass decision he made.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
And it does look like a butt crack and it's going, "Oh no."
Well it's gross so I won't do it.
And I'd like to play the game.
Cool.
No, I'll head for the crack.
Okay, you head for the crack.
(Sound of air blowing)
You head towards the crack, you burst through.
As you burst through, you hear an alarm go off.
(Alarm sound)
A robot.
Yeah, robot.
I just want to remain one mean one.
Capture them.
They've escaped the prison.
OK, then I have to pick up.
The werewolf he now the werewolf
appears behind you, Zach on your bike.
OK, you I'm holding.
You're really close.
Where's the crack on the board?
Is it right here?
You I just went through it.
It's where you went through it.
Wherever it is.
OK, wait, wait, wait.
And then I do this warning.
That was good though.
I meant to do this.
Yeah.
And then also,
you don't need to, nobody could see that.
You zoom through the crack.
Uh,
as you,
as you crash through,
uh,
Joe music, 1976 appears on your back of your bike.
Well, his brother's already on the back of his bike.
Yeah.
He appears on my brother's
We have a sight here. He appears on the back of the side car that my brother is
not it.
Says great job guys. I mean you could seem like you could have maybe won the
games, but I'm glad you did this instead of making everyone suffer through that
any longer. Let's go this way. Well, if we were playing it on the computer, it
would have been the greatest thing ever. It would have been very cool things. I
could have thought about. Yeah. So you guys are zooming now down. You're kind
I'm in this nether space between the wedding way and the and the tinkle layer
and as you're trying to reach to the SS nappy and then flipers now are flying by
you will be the flipers are flying by and they're coming to attack the rashed all
three of you roll initiative again die brash you'll be die brash actually no
it will keep your initiatives from before they're pretty good anyway yeah
and we'll have the Flipers roll. Okay. Warning, you will be de-res. Every time I fucking say it.
13. Can we roll again actually? No. Me and Cam got good ones. I got the best roll you could
possibly get on the dice. I did not, so something's bad. And then I got to roll for Joey. Okay.
Cool. So you guys are flying down now as Flipers are chasing you as you're trying to approach the
the ss nappy ed, it is your turn. Okay, sorry,
you're controlling his thing. He kind of just looks like an ed. Yeah, it's my
middle name. It's my middle name to me to know it's not a liar. I tried
warning for lying. My middle name is Michael. If everybody has to know, okay,
I'll stop
I'm going to add that sound. Yeah, that would stay you're getting close
morning.
Not quite not quite a
but it's getting there, not quite a buzzer, a Geiger counter.
Okay, so it's a fight yeah and it's like sort of a it's similar to the fight.
We did the the fight we were doing. We're going down the mountain in a
temple of that's my favorite moment we ever did in D and D. It was mine too,
so let's do this shit.
All right, so first off, I use my claws and my teeth.
They're in the sky, bro.
Yeah, okay. I jump a hundred feet in the air, which is how much I can do.
We did in the in.
You're the one who let him be a fucking werewolf. You do this every time. I
can't even believe it.
It surprises you.
I can't pretend. Yeah, it's you're right.
You like it. You clearly fucking like it.
I do enjoy it. It's fun when you guys make me laugh. I'm going to let some
stuff happen.
Shut up.
So you should.
you
all right. You could jump a hundred feet in the air and
man
that voice
I was literally I literally was just looking for Tron sounds and
that one came up. It's for Kingdom Hearts. Yeah, I'm
Kingdom Hearts two. I know, I know, buddy. I know. Sorry.
Yeah, we don't need to know that man. Yeah, all right, so you've jumped up in
the air. I don't have to jump in the air, but is there a way I can attack
though? You jump up in the air. You have to jump up in the you guys have
squeeze your finger really hard, make your claw shoot out like a bullet. Oh
yeah, you guys have melee attack. Oh yeah,
oh yeah,
you guys have mainly attacks and range attacks. Your melee attack is either
your claws or your fists or you can
attack with your nappy or you can throw your nappy. It's sort of similar to the
discs in Tron, it's the way that you're identified as a user. I'm gonna borrow
the power of the bad guys. Yeah, you can borrow bad guy powers too. You're
flying, I just wanna see what it does. While he's doing that,
can I do a twin makeover? It's my turn, man. Stay out of my
turn.
Okay, so... Stay out of his turn. When you're borrowing a flipper power...
four. That is a war. Roll a D for roll D for if you get a four, we're going to
roll again.
Roll again.
Okay, you have the ability to fly now like a flipper. Okay. Yeah, that was
there's flying. There's a tracking beam and then there's shooting a laser. Damn.
I wish I got laser. Yeah, I fly up.
Send your enemy steel points.
Can I say I used a big one?
Yeah.
That's three points.
Okay, and then I'm going to attack with my bite.
So that's going to be,
yeah, and that and then plus five on this.
Okay, eighteen.
Because I've now made you into a crazy werewolf.
Yeah, that does hit the flipper.
Roll 2d8.
You're going to be really fucking strong now.
strong now
eleven K plus five strength. So it's sixteen so yeah you just eliminate this
flight for you. So I have to make the flippers stronger next session. Yeah,
you just like chomp you do bite. You said yeah, you just bite into this flipper
and it just I'm on the butt and it just y'all and explodes and disintegrates and
things wiped from diaper talk. I get it and now there is one other flipper
that's still chasing you. It is your turn, Zuck. I think that I'm going to
use scramble, which says
grump of programs do random acting. I step tarns for eighteen seconds.
I don't have great handwriting. What does this
group of grump of pro
grump of
to random acting. I step tarns for tarns for eighteen seconds, so I want I I'm
guessing that means group, but acting I step tarns.
What is what's this meaning? They either will
though either no no no I don't want to know your translation. I want to know
What this means says. Let me see now, let me see now, because I know what it
means in my head now. Yeah, random actions or they skip their turns.
Random actions slash skip turns. Oh, okay. For 18 seconds. I skip turns.
Scramble 'em. Yeah. I'ma scramble 'em. Nice, okay. And this is a DC-13C.
Yeah. So...
What is that? It has a C next to it. Nice. Oh, concentration, that's what I
meant by that. Okay.
Okay, it fails that. So now on the fliper's turn, which is going to be
after Joe's turn, which Joe is going to try to
shoot it with its nappy. So he's gonna whip off his nappy and sling it
at this fliper that's confused and scrambled. And he does manage to hit
it.
And he... Wow, he does eight damage to this fliper. This fliper is now
hit and still scrambled and confused. And now on its turn, I'm gonna roll...
Sorry, I'm seeing right now that what I thought was a T and an I, you just put a
K,
most of a K, and then for an I, you decided to just put the dot part of the
I. Is that what I did? Yeah. I do stuff like that sometimes. You combined a K
and an I.
Okay. Let's see how it's... Yeah, the Fliper,
on its turn, it does manage to
beat out the scramble. It doesn't solve it, like it doesn't like get past
like it still has to deal with it next turn, but it does manage to like
conquer it this time, and so it's going to try to attack
you for trying to scramble it.
And what is your... 13. Yeah, it hits you. Okay.
Four.
One.
Well, I saw him roll a one, but plus two, so it's three damage. It landed
on one when you said one. Oh shit, man, I'm at four HP, man. I got
the heal, I got the heal, man. Heal my ass, bro. And now
it is a finger, brother turn and guess what
another ultimate role
that was a double ultimate role. Actually, what are you doing? I really
like the idea of the ultimate role. I like it to all. Can you create an
ability? I'll incorporate it. Yeah, maybe divide it by a should be at the
end of every day. We're fighting the final got boss. He gets a little roll.
Well, there should just be one thing where we have to succeed in. We have to
you. Yeah, we just do this
over. You have to get over
we'll see, but yeah, I got what you mean. Yeah, there has to be one thing we
have to do. Yeah, we get it with this story. You have to throw the hash
code into it. Yeah, okay, we'll have to do it. There will be an ultimate
role in this arc, which is when you roll all the dice with them between
your fingers for people. And you say this is the ultimate role. Yeah, yeah.
Okay, so I'm gonna do a twin maneuver. Okay,
How many of them are still in the sky?
Because we only need one.
Then I'm not going to do that.
I don't have like a projectile.
Oh, no, I do.
Okay, I'm just going to do that.
Yeah, I'm just going to throw my nappy.
I'm just going to throw my nappy.
Well, I got a three.
Yeah, so you miss.
You sling your nappy.
It teleports back onto your body as you miss.
We're going to go back to the top of the order.
Ed, it's your turn.
You're still flying up in the air.
Yeah, I'm going to heal the team.
No, no, no.
Okay.
with my pencil.
So yeah, you spend one of your energy points.
This side of the table is more fun than that side of the table, guys. I'll say
it. We are the nerd side. That's 'cause this side's better at combat.
Sounds like I have some nerd shit. Yep. Well, 'cause I'm a samurai. Okay, so
you think the soldiers of our army are nerds? Yeah. So you guys all feel cool.
You think that the warriors on our police force are nerds? Yeah. You think
the karate masters on our ninja teams are nerds? No, those are actually cool.
I like Groucho, but I got Harpo's mouth.
I don't know any of his lines.
2d4 plus 2.
Yeah, can you hit the warning when he does stuff like that?
Warning!
Okay.
It was already done.
I didn't need a warning.
Six.
Plus two.
Eight.
You guys heal eight HP.
Oh shit.
To your max.
Well, then I'm at eight.
I heal four.
Includes me, right?
Yes, it does include you.
Aw, yeah!
That's a great ability you have there.
a great ability. Yeah, I usually never give you guys healing and I was realizing that
you guys do too much stupid shit. We die all the time. So like I gotta let you guys heal.
We've died in so many campaigns at this point. Well just yeah, it just makes it, allows you
guys to be more risk-taking. It is now your turn though, Zuck. Wait, I just went. Yeah,
we're moving pretty fast. Wait, this is crazy you guys. I... So who's chasing us at this
point? How many of them? Just one Viper left. You guys broke out pretty fast. You will be
50 res. That's what it said. I'm going to rewrite. DC is 11 on that. So that's
tell program what to do for 30 seconds. It must obey. Okay.
Oh, wow. Crit one. Really good. Oh, snap. So yeah. What do you want to tell it
to do?
Fly into Joey Music's face and explode and kill both of his humans. Wait, no,
no, no. Joey Music could, could... And I would also, because he has to obey,
I would like Joey's me, Joey music's reaction to sound exactly like Sullivan.
Okay,
so you damn so you fly the flipper you for it. I just don't like extra
characters. Yeah, but this guy there they're filling the same slot as him and
it's yeah annoying me so flies into Joey music's face and it I'll let it combust
this time it combusts and Joey's wait. No
well as Sullivan this time, please Sullivan in the courtroom in the
milliseconds have gone by. He goes
he could feel that an unwanted character somewhere was feeling pain and you guys
approach the S. S. Nappy, which was Joe music ship. He's dead yeah. The keys
landed in my hand, though, and you guys now can command the S. S. Nappy and next
time you guys are able to command the S. S. Nappy across the wedding way across a
ankle layer and a damp layer. The wedding way, buddy. You wear a diaper on your
wedding. Eventually, you'll finally reach filled completely and escape from
diaper talk website. We will most certainly die. Yeah, there's almost no
way. I'm not playing this. I think that we will die. I hate to say it. It's a
good song. I think we're gonna die. It's always, we're just bad at this game.
We're bad like that.
Finally played.
Bye!
See you guys next time on the Social Network Tron.
Tron. The Social Network Tron.
The Diaper Tron.
Tron Talk.
There's going to be something different about my character next time.
I'm going to have a cigar and a big fake mustache.
And a fake nose and some glasses.
And some fake glasses.
I'm going to learn some of his quotes.
You gotta. Can you duress him and end this?
Warning!
Hi, hello.
Here's another one ancient submerged pyramid was recently
discovered in China.
It was billed before the ice age and this was discovered on
January 12th, 2023 weird iceberg spotted in Antarctica and
this weird iceberg was spotted in you guessed it January 12th,
2020.
Wow.
I don't know if you guys remember all this stuff happening
that day.
I remember it because I read ancient files.
This is just one day of news.
Katy Perry collapses on stage when MK
Ultra mind control goes wrong.
And this I forgot to put the date here,
but this was also on January 12th.
I don't know if you remember this happening.
Summoning a dark force is the worst thing
you could ever do.
And who's that?
January 12th, 2023.
That is the devil.
He's not the devil.
That's a news story from January 12th, 2023.
Strange little being was spotted live
during a soccer match.
January 12th, 2023.
Holy fucking shit.
Strange case ancient pyramids around the world
suddenly beaming energy to the sky.
January 12th, not my pyramid.
Twenty three.
It was all the ancient pyramids.
They made some experiments proving astral projection is actually real.
January 12th, 2023.
A teleported person caught on video is causing an accident in China.
still January 12th, 2023.
A strange fish with human face was filmed by a tourist in China.
January 12th, 2023.
Millions of Giants will awaken on Earth.
But what was the mainstream media reporting on January 12th?
Because this all happened January 12th, 2023, but I'm willing to bet
you remember only one or two of those things.
January 12th, 2023.
Rick and Morty co-creator, Justin Roiland, faces domestic violence
charges. Rick and Morty co-creator Justin Roiland facing domestic violence charges January 12,
2023. Dog starts house fire while eating cookies off kitchen counter video shows January 12,
2023. NBC News, Hollywood Reporter, New York Post, Los Angeles Times, Rick and Morty co-creator
Justin Roiland facing felony. The truth is out there y'all. Oh wow Cameron. Wow.
You have really gotten to the bottom of this story.