Last time on the Diaper Network Tron, Mark, Eduardo, and the Finger Bros were sucked into
the computer into the Diaper Talk site, now run by the villainous self-replicating program
from filled completely who has been sucking in diaper talk power users.
Also, he can I'm just waiting for you. I'm not doing anything. You do seem
tense. Just relax, man. Chill out. You want a beer? I'll go get the beer. I
don't want a beer. I want a beer
who has been sucking in diaper talk power users. Also, he can try to destroy
his creators, which would be you three
after sucking you in you three found yourselves imprisoned in a in a cell in
the website where you met the power user Joe music. Nineteen seventy six, who
sought your help in destroying the field completely programmed. Then you then you
three were forced to participate. It's so quiet
then you three were forced to participate in the play play games where
compete with the fellow power users for supremacy and access to the next level
of the diaper talk site. In this case, the Tinkle layer.
During the final round of the games, the diap cycle race, you almost died.
So you opted to escape the deadly games free aided by Joe Music,
1976, who began to lead, escape the deadly games aided by free,
He did by Joe music 1976 and begin to lead you to a ship the SS nappy
pursued by two flippers flying diapers that hunt those who disobey filled
completely.
You three just barely made it look like a bass player in like a seventies music
video to the wedding way.
You got to talk into the mic if you're going to, um, we're talking,
we're having, we're goofing off.
You got to goof off into the mic. So don't I look like a bass player?
And like, uh, when you see like a new wave music video,
He's like the ugliest guy in the world.
You look like Christopher Gass in Spinal Tap a bit.
That's pretty good.
Yeah.
See the...
Pursued by two flippers, flying diapers and hunt...
Where the fuck was I?
Oh, yeah.
You made it to the wedding way where you'll now be able to
travel all around the website and enter the Tinkle Air.
However, you made sure that Joe Music 1976 died.
He told you how to defeat filled completely and on his ship
there is a navigation panel that can help lead you to key locations.
Turkey locations?
I heard turkey locations as well.
No, tequila, tequila.
Tequila!
Tequila-cation.
Ooh, that's what I have, like echolocation.
Dream of tequila location.
Which we will go over now. So, it seems like I got, I got about 33% attention on it. Do you guys need me to repeat anything?
Nope.
I heard every we were going to the place and then we got interrupted.
We're going to we have access to the hamburger.
You're like 300 and there's hot dogs.
There's hot dogs and hamburgers that are flying over for us.
Yeah. Sure. Yeah.
But now our objective is to now we have to kill the king.
Pretty much. So what you have to do is it's a couple of things.
This is from last time.
So, uh, you do have to get the hashed code from an outside user to do that.
Uh, Juby, did you have the map still from a little bit ago?
I can, I can re-send.
Oh, I'm running a minute.
Okay.
I'll keep talking in the meantime.
Um, so you guys have to go get the, get the hashed code, which you have to go to
the emergency mass communication tower.
A hash coding slasher.
When you go there to the tower, you'll be able to contact somebody on the outside.
You eat pepperoni who will be able to provide you there.
It is you eat with the hashed code.
So where you guys are right now is you're at that ship.
You guys see that on the map?
What? Sorry. What's the ship?
The S.S. Nappy. That's Joe Music 1976 ship.
Oh, the the thing that those lines.
Oh, it's a fucking toilet bowl, isn't it?
It goes from it.
Wait, that's a sperm going into an egg, bro.
it's a fucking toilet. It's a no look guys. It's a sperm going into an and
we're going to Japan. It looks like that does that is the Japanese flag is a
Japanese flag. You were in Japan and you left so by the way, Japan, Japan,
whoa, good job with that flag man. Not
you can't call them that I did not. I said Japan. I was going to say Japanese
and then you cut me off of the whoa. We have the map back up.
Okay, so you guys made it to the ss nap. You actually have two of your dipe
cycles on there too. So you guys can ride all around the wedding way, which is that circumference,
right?
Well, where's the hash code?
The hash code's at that emergency mass communication tower.
Oh, then we're going there.
So here's the thing. The SSNappy will allow you to ride the wedding way across all the
perimeter, but it can't let you penetrate any further into the website.
So you'll have to go around, but then you can park yourself there basically and then
Make your way through the Tinkle Lair to the Emergency Mass Communication Tower.
Okay, let's do that then.
Okay, cool.
So, as you guys are riding the wedding way, on the main comms screen of the SS Nappy,
you see the screen comes up.
Here.
Joe Music 1976?
Are you there?
Hello?
You're not Joe Music 1976.
He couldn't make it actually.
He died from cancer.
And by that we mean he's out in the yard.
playing. He died from bowel cancer. Roll, I guess, like one of you roll, all of you
roll deception. All you roll talking and we'll just sort of figure it. You got 19.
Plus you're talking. I got a 13. I'm talking. I got an 18. 12. Yeah, that all
passes this person. Oh, move the how terrible. This isn't going to be useful.
I think you should roll it on the table.
I
well,
were you guys his friends in prison?
No,
we didn't like him at all.
So we killed him.
Shut the fuck
with kindness.
I killed one of the twins.
You kill one of the twins.
Okay, eat one of the twins.
There's one of the roll.
What do I roll?
Roll to eat?
It's also talking talking
because it looks like a me out.
That's an 11. Can you roll to not be eaten?
Seven. All right. Which one gets eaten? Which one?
Which ones are there?
Whoa. And hello. And hello.
OK, if I roll 11 or higher, I'll eat.
Whoa. OK. One to roll.
I want to use some abilities.
The other one. No, wait, don't don't do that because I'll lose abilities.
I'm making it easy for you.
No, no, no. Because I have the role of my head into the system.
All of my abilities, all of my abilities are twin based.
least I'll be your twin yeah. That's my plan. You if you agree that you are my
twin now, okay, you can eat my twin. I rolled a thirteen. What did I say that
man said? Whoa gets okay, why? So okay, so now this actually would make it to
our to make more sense as a character. So he's now just because he's a werewolf
yeah exactly. Oh yeah, I forgot you're a werewolf. You forgot you're in charge.
Yeah, I remember that's why it's been a while.
Whoa! Bye-bye!
Now it's just hello?
Bye-bye, whoa!
Describe your kill.
I open my mouth and I swallow him.
He opened my mouth.
I open... yeah.
So, meanwhile, the person
on the comms says,
"I'm Sissy Boy...
where is the name? SissyBaby34."
This guy doesn't even know his own
fucking name.
How did he get this job as an announcer guy?
I'm not an announcer guy.
I'm a member of the Leaky Legends.
I was Joe Music's 1976's contact.
- Whoa, my brother is gone.
- Hello.
- What up?
What up?
Listen, Joe Music, all right,
we didn't want to tell you, but he did die.
- I know you did tell, you told me right away.
- We killed him with kindness.
- No, we killed him brutally
by throwing him off of a motorcycle.
- Oh, yes.
- Why?
because he wasn't that fun man.
Are you you better be fun or we'll do the same. Tell me a joke. Tell me a
no, tell us a joke. Tell us a joke you turn crazy. Tell us a street to see
baby thirty four turns the comes off
calling back. Wait here, call back yeah.
I'm a woman
hello. I'm a woman doesn't pick up shit man. Why did we do
Okay, I throw the twin back up. No, you guys ride. Hello, you guys ride around.
Hello. Whoa, shut up. You guys ride around the wedding way. Okay, until you
do reach
right outside of the
emergency mass communication tower.
So, to get through to there, there is a
sort of layer of... Well, I'll describe it to you.
So there's yellowish waters with sparklish glint.
- Sure, waters.
- This is where many of the microservices
that make up the diaper network make API calls.
You'll notice the many shimmering glistening glares
that spark through.
- Oh wait, I have a twin over there.
- These are the data that fly across the globe
replicated 1,000 times per second.
Occasionally you'll find a floating garden
with whirling machinery.
These are nodes where worker programs
man the microservices.
- Could've had that the whole time.
- One for updating user information,
sending a message, one for up-diping, down-diping, one for translating diaper
comments from sissy to bull. So...
Sissy to bull?
What's bull?
Bull is in the diaper world, I think is like a tough guy or something.
Now tell me why you know that.
Because I freaking went on the website.
Check it out. I made a profile.
So you guys are...
You made a profile ten years ago, maybe?
No.
Back when you were in diapers?
Sheesh.
[laughter]
I wasn't in diapers at thirty five man
so you guys are we'll be back in them soon enough. So you guys are sort of
looking out at this layer, this tinkle layer and you're seeing you could see
the communication note. It is this sort of like blue cone that's like pointing
upwards and inside of it is the terminal that you need to use to communicate with
somebody on the outside to get the hash code. You're going to need to go through
this like sort of like swim through this like tinkle layer and there are flippers
trolling the area. So you have to be careful.
We have to swim through the P. I thought we were on a ship. I didn't say it was
P. No, the ship can't pass through. What about the motorcycles? You can try to
use the motorcycles. Okay, I'm gonna try that then. Okay.
And it sounds like I just successfully used it. Done. What you can do is you
can... Well, hold on, don't just roll. I'm just... I put some triggers in my
brain to hear certain words. One of you guys can roll an intelligence
check to see if you can like okay, basically, I think I have the highest
and tell like what his name does in what Jeff Bridges does what's wrong where he
programs plus three mine's plus one. I ruled in my entire yeah, but maybe my
character is a little more heart. Okay, I'm gonna roll now.
You should have rolled. Yeah, I got a five. Okay, so you sort of assess the
motorcycles. Now we can keep we can go down. He can roll with advantage because
he's the smartest. No, we can go down. You try to assess the motorcycles and it
seems like code that you probably didn't write something I filled
completely might have created. So this has to be the code that I wrote.
Let me take a step. If you didn't write this, this is probably some of
the code I wrote. You can take a step. I don't think you wrote any
code. No, I wrote code like A equals one, B equals two, C equals three.
I don't think you wrote that. I wrote that and I put messages to
you. Did you ever read them? I guess I don't remember reading these.
oh, they said things like hello, friend, hi, friend, lovely, hello,
friend. Oh, that's a net twenty wow on didn't even get picked up with a
cop. I'll move it over see
this is a lost cause yeah, it's nothing
so
you got in that twenty. So yeah,
a torto wolf man. This is very much the only piece of code you wrote yeah was
to make dive site. One of the many piece of code I read that had like nothing
you wrote. Why do you write our website to have motorcycles in it man?
My uncle had a motorcycle. I always thought it was kind of cool, but it's
not
fix it. Just do I check this out and I press a button on the motorcycle and it
a bunch of screens pops up and it starts advertising cat food. This is actually
great because you did way that could earn money. This is actually earns us
about point two cents a day. That adds up. Whoa, this is your business savvy.
This is good. This is good for you because there wasn't there was a you
found a good way to suit. There was a
well. I'll explain to you after this is done. This is a very smart decision. So
So you have these really good motorcycles now that are able to travel across the
Tinkle layers. The wheels go on sideways.
Yeah, they go on the side. That's actually bad.
Yeah, I go, "Check this out, guys. I wrote this code. I know how to modify it."
And I reach out and I grab the wheel and I go...
[laughter]
I turn it all the way sideways.
So the thing is, is, you know, what you'll give up in like the stealth of
like slowly moving through, you'll more than make up for in the speed of just
darting directly to the
emergency mass communication tower. I like speed. Oh, did I just say that
whoa?
Did you just say that you guys I guess are writing the same motorcycle. Are
you guys writing the same motorcycle? Because you I'm on the back of what he
threw our motorcycle. Yeah, he threw up that he's making us
rattling to motorcycles. I was like
you wrote a piece of code that gives you like a
like you remember the fucking the
platforms that Buzz Lightyear walks
across in Toy Story 2.
You're standing you're standing on
just like a little hover disc next to
us and just like
most motorcycles.
And I have both my I have my arms
around each of your shoulders.
I wanted to eat one of those.
So me too.
Oh, my God. They looked like
Mentos. Delicious.
They looked like Mentos.
And I like with an electrical
charge.
Past the some of the flippers
that were before they even can get
to get like pay attention to you
when you arrive at the emergency
- Nice, mass communication tower.
- He's getting so good at that.
- Again, it's sort of like blue,
like multiple triangles kind of folded into one another.
Not quite like a pyramid,
but more like a sort of a weird cone shape.
- And then you see an advertisement for a hot dog.
- And there's a small door inside.
- And you see an advertisement and it says this.
- Time to eat hamburger.
- We all kind of stop and we're transfixed.
- Time to eat that hamburger.
- And actually when you guys arrive there.
time to eat that's hot dog ketchup. You hear Sissy Baby 34 in the distance like a
"Come here!" I yelled that. Well Sissy Baby doesn't quite notice you because he's in the
I don't know why he made this sight. He's in the middle of fighting a fliper.
He's half made this sight.
So he's in the middle of fighting flipers and you see them in the background.
So you guys can either engage with that or just sneak in.
I want to kill that fucking baby.
I drive directly into the baby.
I'm nuts. No, you're not getting off that easy, sissy baby.
I'm going to drive directly into you and I'm going to bisect you.
Okay, so you're gonna kill him.
I mean the sound effect said that it happened.
So just keep in mind, Sissy Baby is fighting the Fliper.
So if you attack Sissy Baby, the Fliper...
I don't care man, I'm in a rage.
You don't care either way.
I'm gonna rip his arms off.
Okay, so why don't you roll an attack roll.
(Screams)
Eight.
And yeah, so you run up to Sissy Baby, who is in the middle of fighting a Fliper,
and you just miss. You just sort of go to grab...
I try again.
Yeah, and you don't try again.
That was a 20.
That would have been nice.
Bitch.
That's a 20.
It has to work.
Instead, initiative starts.
Did you guys follow him or no?
No.
I'm on the back of both their cycles.
Yeah, we're doing our own thing.
Well, you wouldn't have parked your cycles at this point.
Well, yeah, we're watching the hamburger ad.
I jumped off of my shit, though.
I guess I'm a bloodthirsty animal of the night.
I want to kill this fucking communication tower or you can fight them.
I think I'm going to go to the communication tower while they fight the baby.
Okay, cool.
And I'm going to get the hex code and save the day.
So both of you guys roll initiative since you guys are fighting sissy baby and now another and a flipper five
Eight would you say that the this battle is explicit in nature
Sexually no not necessarily you're talking about are you saying that it's sexual?
Nobody can see you're so stupid man. How is it? No it'll all be revealed a d20 for me
You're just dumb. So I have like 2 d12s and 0 d20s.
Don't slap my dice.
Wherever you put it, you had one for certain.
I'll snatch your wig.
Don't you dare!
Will somebody get patches of an extra d20? He lost his.
No, I did not lose it.
[Laughter]
Jesus Christ.
Where is Sissy Baby's stats?
[Laughter]
Sissy Baby is fast.
I forgot.
Okay. I was doing a drag race impression. Sissy baby. I was acting like a gay guy.
Okay cool, so sissy baby's gonna go first. What type of gay guy? Just one of those ones that dresses up like a lady but isn't a lady.
Sissy baby's gonna go first. Sissy baby's gonna go, "I knew you were a program. No way the great Zuckerberg would do this."
Come here!
Oh yeah, right. So, and Sissy Boob's gonna try to attack you.
Why?
But he misses terribly. He goes to attack you with his rattle.
I look so sad.
He just misses terribly.
Why don't you fucking... What are you doing, man?
You attacked me.
No, I wasn't. I was trying to... You dropped something. I was trying to pick it up for
you.
Roll deception.
It's an 11. No.
But you add your talking to 14.
I'm... I don't know. I don't know.
of opportunity I rip his head off.
It is, it is. First it's Ed's turn.
Okay, so I go
trip attack,
bonus attack,
action surge,
lacerate, bonus attack,
shove.
This guy's been playing a lot of Baldur's Gate
over here. Well I've been playing Persona, I use
Maracuja. So you guys can't do either
of the things you're describing, you have to use
the very simple attacks.
Okay, simple attack.
Duh.
Five.
Okay, yeah, you miss Sissy Baby.
Um, the Fliper is now gonna go,
and the Fliper is gonna go after Sissy Baby also.
Yes, let's--
-Good job. -He misses terribly.
You will be dereg.
And, Zuck, now it's your turn.
You're gonna get advantage on your attack on Sissy Baby.
I'm so sorry that you dropped that coin earlier.
I had this huge, uh, misunderstanding that was--
I got an 11 plus my--
Yeah.
-I hit. -Roll for damage, yeah.
Come here!
That's not your damage die.
What do I roll? Damaged dice. It's going to be a D6 and then we're going to add
your arm.
I got a six. So five. I have a negative arm? Yeah. What did you do to him?
Rip his head off. Actually, you know what I do? I do end of inglorious
bastards where they stab Hitler's face a million times and... Or maybe that's in
Pan's Labyrinth, that's what I'm thinking of, where they take the butt of a gun
and they just beat the guy's face in until it caves in and it's like this
prosthetic and they're like shoving his nose into his own face. I do that to the
baby. You do that to the baby a little bit, but not enough to kill him, but
enough that the baby's face is now inward. He's got a different voice and
everything. Okay. And I'd like to trip him as well. Cool. What if he sounds
like this?
And can I spit on him?
He hung up.
Can I spit on it? He wants to spit on. Can you say, Hey, baby, can I spit on
it? Inside the emergency communication tower. What do you think you do in sex?
Warning is
Don't worry I've been keeping
I'll tell you what I think you're doing sexy
Put your hotdog in her hamburger
And she'll make ketchup
I've been keeping track of everything
sexual that's been said
Did you throw
I crossed it out cause now he said
something sexual
Did you actually throw up woe
or did you keep it in your tummy
So hello and woe
Hello and woe
Tupac. They caught the bastard that did him.
Tupac, I saw that. So, hello, I was like, you guys walk into the
emergency mass communication tower.
I was so scared. I've been up at night since then. Every day I
haven't found a way that Tupac, the killer of Tupac is still at
large. I'm sure I'll walk this earth another day.
And in the center of the emergency mass communication tower is some kind of
program that is the avatar of Dylan, who was one of the people who funded
Zuckerberg's enterprise. Dylan, Dylan, Dylan. So you could see he spins to go
see you, 'cause he's sitting in sort of like a circular chair and he goes,
"Oh, hey, what's going on?" "Whoa, Dylan, it's hello and whoa."
"Oh, hi." "Hi."
"What do you guys want?" You guys sent the worst guy in here. Okay.
We need the hex code.
We need a code.
The hash code.
Oh, you want to get a hash code?
We need the hex code for the website so we can make the whole website a different color.
Yeah, sure.
I can help you with that.
Is it #000000000?
No, no, no.
All you need to do is -- You did an extra zero.
Well, I guess not if you want the alpha channel.
All you need to do -- I want the alpha channel with the code.
quote is tell me who you want to communicate with outside of the in the
courtroom where you guys were sucked in.
Okay.
I want to talk to myself.
And you were obviously you remember the people in the courtroom 'cause it was
only two months ago that we recorded that episode. So, Rashida Jones. It's
Rashida Jones and then the Southern lawyer, Sullivan lawyer, New York lawyer.
New York lawyer and very bailiff.
I want to talk to the
okay
Dylan does a little bit of programming and you see like a beam of light pop out
of the top of his perfect haircut and in the courtroom now only like point one
milliseconds have gone by like no time has gone by. Everyone is just suddenly
reacting to you guys being sucked in and then
the computers, all three of the computers, because you guys were about
to do a hackathon light up
and it goes bailiff
Bayleth, can you get the attention of Dylan
a
one is over
so
the bailiff wanders over the computer. You see the judge judge solving being
like this is very unorthodox. Where did the and like and but the the bill goes
shut up and then walks over to the computers and he starts immediately
knows what to do and he starts typing in to the computer. The hash code that you
Thank you. He finds it. It's copied to him. I was going to try and get him to
get Dylan's attention so I can ask him for the hash code. No, Dylan is reach
Dylan communicates outward. He knows him and he's yeah. I wasn't sure which
he's being funny. I'm sorry. It is funny. What are you talking about? It
just that is funny. He thinks he's being funny. Just let him do it. Sorry.
He's telling it his kind of idea of a joke. So his second weird idea. And so
the bailiff sends down the hash code. You Pat, you bombed. It's okay. It's not
got a bomb. You killed it. That was funny. You have the hash code now in
the form
of Patrick. I'm sorry of a sorry that you bombed so hard. Sorry for what
happened of like a frisbee, like in the traditional tron sense, and so
Dylan,
and Dylan turns to you, he goes massive bomb. So yeah, I guess if you
want to shut down the whole thing, this is what you would use
and he gives it to you and
yeah, we're going to go back outside now to you. You guys are in a little fight,
sissy babies turn cut back to me. I'm having a heart attack.
Sissy baby attacks, you
attacks you Zuckerberg. What the hell would I do because you went and attacked
him
and with his punched in face
oh yeah, this is because this baby is
yeah baby with a caved in brain is going to hurt me yeah for real. He does six
damage. Oh, you got fucked. Wait, I got I got two HP. This baby hurt me badly.
You got destroyed beating you in the face with the rattle trying to do the
same thing to him that you did. I pretend it doesn't hurt at all. I don't
I defend myself just go like yep yeah. This is fine yeah and you at is now
your turn. I have to make a death saving throw. You got a heart attack for real
okay roll roll death saving throw
okay. It's a success. Okay,
your computer program having a dead sick. I got a heart attack.
Okay, cool the flipper sir. The flipper is going to try to kill you because you
are on the ground having a heart attack. Wow, kind of shit. It misses, though,
just like cross battle ever.
It was never done. It's your turn, Zack. Now
I'm going to kill that baby. Okay, go for it.
Oh, wait, do that.
Oh my God, strategy.
Unlocked 19. My roll roll camera thinks he's the blower for
Okay, cool. Is that four total?
For real though?
Honestly, out of the four of us, I am like the blower.
No, it's 19 and then it's 19 minus one and then four, right?
18.
No?
No, minus one strength. So three.
So Sissy Baby's not looking good.
But he's still not fucking good.
How's it 19?
Sissy Baby misses on you. You're pretty lucky.
Thank God, I have two HP, man.
It is your turn. Roll another death saving throw.
Why did we pick this fight?
Okay, another success. You're doing well.
The fliper is going to join well y'all.
The fliper is going to...
The fliper misses you again.
The fliper is just the worst fliper.
Just missing you completely.
And now it is Zuck, it is your turn again.
You're just having a hard time.
Alright, I think that one more melee attack is going to...
You know what to do.
Four.
Okay, yeah, that misses for sure.
The average is still pretty good.
You now are outside and you can kind of come in and help I would say.
day. Can I just hold up the disc and shoot out a giant beam? Is that how that works?
That's from the cover of the movie. That's from the cover of the movie, so I imagine
that you could do it. That's probably one of the only things that can happen. No, you
could do... Oh, I'm going to throw the disc. No, no, no, you have to save the disc for
the end. I thought that the whole movie was about throwing discs. Put the disc on ice.
Yeah, but not right now. See if you can do a front flip in this world. Okay, you know
what? I'm going to have a makeover party. Before I do anything, I'm going to have a twin makeover.
All right, you and the twins step outside, see this battle going on.
Juvia, can you search on YouTube makeover music?
Do not.
Yeah.
Okay.
Do your thing.
We're going to have a little makeover session.
All right.
We'll see.
Songs for doing makeup, chill music mix.
Okay.
Whoa.
Hello?
Before we go to battle.
Yes.
There's something we need to change.
Okay,
okay,
we should change our hairstyle. Yeah,
describe what you're changing hairstyle, but describe how it's changing.
We paint us a picture with words. No, with
okay, you turn this hair back, backwards, the long parts on the front.
Okay, now maybe I have a little bit of a sexual scene tension wise between
you and your twin and then while my twin is putting makeup on my face,
I kiss him.
(laughter)
- You do the thing at breakfast club.
- Yeah.
- And then I put my hand down the front of my twin's pants.
Wait, can you go grab my twin?
(laughter)
- All right, show us on the doll where you, okay.
And that's that. And then we go to battle. Okay, you put his foot in your mouth all the
way and then you're ready to fight.
So yeah, I guess, I guess, roll for initiative to enter the, please get the head sitting
next to you.
I'll hang out.
17.
Okay, cool. You're going to go, you're going to go. So yeah, what do you want to do? Now
you've, we'll just let you do that.
As soon as I get in there, I hit my shell launcher.
Okay, nice.
Which I, what do I do?
So it's when you and your twin get inside of a boat.
It looks like it says lunch is a straight line.
Launch is in a straight line, sorry.
Lunch is a straight line.
Lunch is the midpoint on a straight line.
Three feet, 10 feet water damage crowd.
Yeah, you're gonna fuck up everybody.
It's gonna cost you three.
Okay, wait, if I'm gonna fuck up everybody,
he has two HP, I'm not gonna do that.
Yeah.
Then I guess I'm going to do twin
maneuver.
Nice. So this is where you get to do
sort of an extra maneuver where you
could have one of your twins go.
Like you just described to me what
you're going to do and we're going to
figure it out.
I guess what we're going to do.
Think of a twin antic then.
I don't know why I haven't had
this on me the whole time.
What I'm going to do is
I guess it's a leapfrog style
attack. Oh, you know what?
What?
Tabletop. We're going to tabletop.
I was hoping you'd say that.
we are going to table top somebody. You're going to Eiffel Tower somebody? No, no, no,
no. That is different. One of my, one of, I think, hello will go behind. Eiffel Tower
would be somebody standing behind them and you just push them into them. So roll, or
something. Roll stealth first. Or it could be something else, I guess. So that's balance
ball. That's a five. Okay, so your twin is very obviously. Actually, that's a seven.
Your twin is very obviously going behind sissybaby34. And then you're going to try to push him into
this. You're going to push them at disadvantage, but you can still
potentially do enough damage. So roll d20. What'd you get?
Crit one. A 20. You got a crit one. Yes, I got a crit one. You
a hug, SissyBaby34. It's okay. I wasn't going to fight you. And
in, oh yeah. Oh, okay. Roll, yeah. Roll, roll speaking. That
is a 15. SissyBaby hugged you back. This fucking baby's so
so hard to kill. This is so sweet, smushed in phase.
Yes, I understand exactly what you're saying. Yeah, and it is now Ed's turn
you are yeah, rolled in the death saving throw. Okay, fail. All right. Okay,
that's the first. The flipper is going to try to shoot you now
and a crit one. Wow,
this viper, it's the worst flipper ever.
you're the fliper charlie browns away, just like depressed, like
just like you can't fucking do shit.
Fucking more shit sucks. It fucking works and he just leaves. So it's just you
guys beating up this baby now. Well, the baby is now on my side. Baby's also a
man, but it's a man. I don't want to kill it anymore. It's a man using a
baby avatar. Yes, I mean I could, but how old is that? Can you show us a photo
what
your kill? I rip his arms off. I rip his legs off. I rip a hole in his chest. I
put all of it in like a bouquet of flowers. I rip his head off. I put it on
top. Wait, wait, wait. Throw the bouquet behind you. And then I throw it behind me
like a wedding. And who catches it? Cameron, roll. Yeah, well you two. Oh,
wait a minute. Who catches it? I can't catch anything. Well, you can still try
to catch it. Well, yeah. Can we roll to see if it lands on your dying body? It
could land on your dying body. Ready? 321419. He the twin catches it. I'm
having a heart attack. 20. So maybe okay. So which way he does. Okay. So hello
catches it. Nice. And then what happens and you two maybe look at each other a
little knowingly because you know that you're gonna be now you don't make out
with your twin. Why not? Because we let that happen for one second when the
music was going. We got caught up in the music. But now the music I think that's
the only time it can become sexual. I agree. I'm having a dream about being
trapped in an auditorium with a shooter and I'm dying. Describe your dream.
Describe your dream. The world is falling apart into pieces. There's
spider webs everywhere and there's an active shooter at your school.
Lightning is following me through the ground and I saw a baby bear and then
the mama bear came out and was killing me. And then is this a real dream?
You know, there's now there's a three guys who have guns and they have masks
because of COVID. Your character's having this? Yeah. Because of COVID-19. Because I'm dying.
Oh, okay. I have heart attack. What if you go to a Tony Soprano realm? I don't know if you want to
see what Sissy Baby's profile is. I really don't, man. Oh, I really do. Yeah, I'm not sure I do
either. I'm done looking. I'm dreaming of this in my brain. Whatever is on the screen right now
that I'm not going to look at, this is what's going through my... this is my last thoughts.
Well, no, because we're going to get you up right now. Sissy Baby's
My life is flashing before my eyes, me designing Facebook, me writing all the code for Facebook,
me putting all the money up for Facebook, me winning the court case, me escaping from
Tron World, me and you having a platonic friend wedding to be permanent friends. I'm from
from hand to hand. I'm sure you are now friend and friend. Sissy Baby's last
words is... That's the most recent post. No, it's something else. He dies.
So you guys killed the Sissy Baby, but you did get the
disc you need, the hash code you need. So...
You guys, you got the hex code. With the hex hash code, damn it.
With that, you also can go to the next layer of the...
Oh, wow. Bitch, I'm going in. I'm going in. You only just saw that?
- Yeah, he's got a weird, strong baby.
- That's the classic baby.
- Doesn't look like me.
So the next layer is the damp layer.
And that's the layer where you can do--
- Maximum damage?
- No, so here's the thing.
- Crap.
- What you can do is the damp layer
is the sort of backend code layer,
and in there is the PVN launcher.
The private, or PVC launcher rather.
The private virtual cloud launcher.
So if you recall, what you guys have to do to break out of here is you have to, one person
has to be in the private virtual cloud and at the exact same time that somebody throws
the hash code into the, into filled completely's defeated husk, somebody has to shut down the
backup.
Spoiled it, we know he's a corn.
Somebody has to hit the backup code so that they sync so that there's no redundancies.
these. Okay, where's the backup code? You have to go to the PVC launcher. So
somebody needs to stay behind. Somebody's gonna need to launch into the cloud.
It was supposed to be Johnny Computer. It was supposed to be literally anybody
from the Leaky Legends crew who you have just, I guess, also started a war
against. Not a war. We killed a baby. I don't care. Yeah. Killed also Joe. Joe
was an accident. Well, I didn't know if anyone was gonna ask or even care.
But I did survive my heart attack. Also, how fast does Word spread in this town?
it. But, well you told Sissy Baby on the comms that you guys killed Joe Music. So this guy
believes everything he hears? Yeah, I mean that was pretty clear from his character,
right? No. Does he, did he tell everyone? Did he have enough time? Because he was fighting
a fliper. We can, we have this disc now, we can just hack into anything. No. The disc
lets us do anything. The disc lets us do whatever we want and hack into whatever. We can hack
to
They know who he is for sure.
They know who he is.
Celebrity status.
Probably Edward.
They might not know exactly who killed Joe Music 1976.
They might just know that Joe Music 1976 has been compromised.
Okay, alright, so we're good then.
Well, where, then we need one of them.
So where are the Leaky Legends abound?
There's a Leaky Legends lair, which is also in this level here.
Can we...
We'd like to go there.
Can we shoot a beacon into the sky that says...
like to go there. Legends,
the poster of Tron, you cannot do it right now.
You keep mad, you keep trying to do the poster, the dream
is up. You already are a werewolf. You can't also shoot a beam. I shoot a
werewolf. You gotta pin werewolf shoot beams, but you gotta shoot a
moon. That's one of the werewolves thing. That's not one of the werewolves
thing. Werewolves do that in lots of movies. I'd like to I'd like to turn
tail and run directly to the triple l. Okay, cool. So you guys hop on your
motorcycles, which are now hover bikes and you guys, you guys are running to
the to the the cycles. I'm like guys, can you slow down? I'm not supposed to
run right now. I'm having some issues with my heart. He has agita. Oh yeah,
for you're just out that whole thing. Is that the thing? Is that the old
italian agita? He has agita. I may have survived my cardiac arrest, but that
doesn't mean it won't have lasting complications. Okay, well, then you can
ride on my bike. Whoa! Friendship perhaps repairing? Our bond growing closer?
Hamburger?
Yeah, you guys ride away around the Tinkle Lair towards the Leaky Legends
Lair, which I realised also while I was riding, I was like, "These are gonna
sound similar," but it did happen. So
yeah, you see there, it's sort of like a hoveled out
crystal cavern kind of a sitting amongst the alongside the between the between
the the tinkle layer and the damp layer and sort of a little hovel with like
little nodes and and then sort of like you know mother boardy kind of wires and
sparkies and knock on the door. There's no door. They just see them there. Do you
knock on the ground? I knock on what I think is a door. Okay, so you're going to
that's what do you think is the door? Can I roll to see what I think the door?
Yeah, that yeah, I'll just low low. It makes them think that I have a
disability. Yes, you're high.
A door appears. Okay, I get a net twenty a door
materializes. Yeah, you probably would have done that regardless. I'm going to
be honest. I'm a friendly guy.
get one so
you I mean you just like start clipping through the ground.
Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, you're going to take some damage roll
one D six
or you take four damage from clipping through the ground ground and coming
back up. Okay, let me handle this
guys. Hey
leaky legends, somebody killed Joe
or Joe exotic
or what's his name? It was Carol.
Somebody killed Joe music at nineteen seventy six and the fucking sleepy baby
and now it's just sleepy baby is dead.
Yeah, so guys, we have to happen. We have to
buy a bunch of flyers so
fucking
covered in blood. I tried to save him. I tried to save him, so I'm trying to
save the sleepy, the sweetie baby. Look, I saved his skull. We saved his skull
because you guys thought we thought you guys might want it now. Now now hold on
whoa. My name is warm feeling
okay. Hello,
you're telling me that sissy baby's dead
sleepy. I can't believe I'm saying this right now, but honestly, this is the
first we're hearing of it too. Yeah, we like just found out from some fucking
bitch.
Yeah, he's fucking dead.
They're all deceptive of course. But that's a pretty good lie. Yeah,
it's a good lie.
It is a good lie. Nat 20, naturally a 20. I saw it, I saw it. You show the
world though, yeah. Oh, you guys thought Caleb couldn't play D&D.
Look at my dice.
You see warm feeling and he goes,
God damn it.
You see like, you know, it's a bit of...
I hug him.
It's warm.
I clip back up under him.
You do what?
I like clip my...
I clip back up and I'm right in front of him like Skibbity Toilet.
Please tell me there's no Skibbities in here.
And you see warm feeling.
Honestly, I'm not on the floor enough to know if it's good or bad.
It's basically the worst fucking thing ever if you have a camera for it.
enough of a no, if it's cringe or based yet, because I do think that the
younger generation when it comes to analog horror, they're making some base
shit like the back rooms. This is this is stuff where it's like
it's a scary house. That's only rooms, the back room. This is the back rooms on
fucking crack. What if a house was only rooms and
no furniture? Nope, I mean noping the fuck out of there. Yeah, the furniture's
so scary, warm feeling gives you gives you a big hug. I missed you man.
You're honestly me seeing a wall kill it with fire. This is this is a travesty.
It is a travesty forced and you see in a hulking
user come who forced forced his name's forced forced. What F O R C E D forced
gump. His name's forced
forced to go
gump in his diaper
forced chose to chose to live forced to go
God.
That's good. You see forced he's like
hello forest. He's like so angry hello all right. We need to accelerate our
plans. Yeah, we have to Joe music. I've been saying the same thing a lot. Yeah,
Joe Music had told us that he had some useful allies inside the prison.
It was us, man.
All right.
Look at this disc.
It has the X code.
Joe Music.
We need to head to the private virtual cloud immediately.
It was fucking crazy, man.
Let's round up the troops.
Some psychos pushed him off a bicycle or some shit.
Hockey Czar, Mechanic X, Life Goes On 223, Pull Ups Boy 8, Joey SMS.
Is anybody here just got a normal name like Charles?
Now I did it.
Is there any person of this
now I did it now I did it's crazy bed. Let's go. You see a whole crew of power
didn't we kill a bunch of those people wait there. What's his bed?
Wait you killing those guys that we killed a bunch of those people. Now we
killed. So we just beat them so bad in a game that it yeah. Yes, they're here
though. Okay, they're here. So they come back in there and now you guys are ready
storm the capital, the private virtual cloud. So you guys ride Intel with them.
They have their own SS and oh yes, that's from Pokemon.
That's from I remember that SS. I was wrong with nappies. I'm sorry. Yeah, I'm
sorry. I haven't played Pokemon in years. I forgot about it. They would never let
you on the ship unless you had the ticket to get the ticket. You had to go
to the every ship is like that dumb ass. You had to go to the fucking own the
shit like me shit. He said shit. He said shit. Yeah, like own the shit like you
could own you own shit really seem like you meant to say ship and you yeah.
No, no, no, I'm a deal. Oh shit. Did a reverse target commercial. I don't own
you. I flush it away. You're charactering a heart attack. He's having
a stroke. I'm doing a stroke.
So,
we have a stroke too,
the fuck. So, you guys ride through the
with your new crew who you convince with that nat 20 ride through the damp layer
where the tinkle layer is bright and yellow we find the damp layer me the
damn player murky browns and chug this is the back and murky brown watching
murphy brown with its dreary murphy and brown you said i'm murphy brown call me
murky brown i'm murky and brown it's dreary logic and a thin layer of
compiler sick it's murky doodoo canoes glide on a black easy waterway
it
in each coming the damn player with a black Uzi
rest a single gold.
Yeah, I got a single gold coin that authenticates each user as they log
into the diaper network overhanging our stalactites that stuck that suck up the
coins as needed and spit them out on the next one. So reusing those tokens on
either side of the Black Sea lies thick steel docks or programs create the
and stick each little coin inside it.
These programs sweat and ache
and work hard to make this beast run.
- These are doo-doo canoes?
- Mm-hmm, more flipers exist here,
along with the flipper captain.
- Warning, you will be derezzed.
- The flipper captain resides in his brown citadel,
well, citadel, where the PVC launcher rests.
Well, you'll have to either beat him,
you'll have to sneak by him, maybe.
- I will sneak.
I don't wanna beat anymore, I'm done beating.
- You are rolling through with a crew who are intent,
they wanna like storm it so you guys can try to sneak around.
Can we hang out?
Can we like meet at the back? We will create a distraction with them.
Can we guys try to like say to them like, "Yeah, we're all in."
Yeah, that's right. Yeah. Can we be like, "Oh yeah, let's go. Oh yeah,
we're almost there guys." I have the perfect distraction, guys.
We don't need to distract, we just decided. I have the perfect distraction
though. Okay, let's hear it. Okay, you might convince me. Guys,
I'm not feeling so good.
He just had a heart attack. We have to attend to him. My stomach hurts.
Wait guys, you guys go ahead. Wait guys, I'll create a distraction.
my stomach.
Warm feeling. Wait a minute. We have a tummy ache on board. Are
you doing? All right?
Honestly, I think I'm not doing that good. God damn it. I just
want to get I just want to use the hash code to shoot a beam
and get out of the website. Would you two be able to stay
with him and make sure his tummy's? Okay? I mean if we have
to but I'm so bloodthirsty to kill the Flyers. You've a promise
there's three of us and get revenge for stinky baby. Are you
not even looking at me?
Which one said that the other one what I did which one said
did that
yes, we can stay with them. Okay, no, they should go with you wait
no, no, no, we have to
both of you roll deception. So you win
is it talking for me yeah talking
six eleven okay all right, so they win this time. No wait wait before you guys
leave. Do you have any money or something? If we need to buy medical
supplies. Of course, of course. Oh, thank you so much. When you get to the Soak City,
you're going to probably need this. Do you have weapons? Oh, well, the weapons that we're
using, but... Can you give us all those? And probably you have to use those to storm. Okay,
can you leave one and give us the rest? We can give you one. Is there any kind of...
No, you have to give us three. How many of you are there? We'll take the money, we'll
take the money. Here's the money. And he gives you guys, he gives you guys each 100 tokens...
Oh yeah. To spend when you're in the Soak City.
And he says,
"Leaky Legends, charge!"
And him and Forst and the rest of the gang, they all storm.
I was kind of hoping to send them on a suicide mission.
And they all charge.
That's the second time that you've played that.
And I thought the world was ending.
Oh man.
Wait, that's cool.
That's how they run in.
And the fight begins.
And so they are now fighting the Fliper Captain.
It sounds like this. Yeah.
All right.
So you guys now have an opportunity to sneak around, get into the PVC launcher
and just fly right through to there.
Here's the thing.
You'll still have to leave one of you there behind
unless you take one of the guys with you.
We actually need it actually takes three guys.
Wait, I need you.
Or you leave one of the points at one person.
We take forced. Yeah.
For maybe not forced.
he seems now because he won't speak. I bet him vibes though. Yeah, we were on
the same wave. Like they were on the stage
situation ship.
We've been sending each other and emojis.
Okay, maybe you should say baby. What are you eating?
With the pig
I'm eating cheese
if I eat you first
what do you eat?
Are you
talking said knowing for someone for like two weeks?
I
want to come hang out with me. Do you want to come to my apartment? My skin
got ripped off and I must go
so for stays with you guys. You guys sneak you guys are trying to sneak in
all of you guys roll balance ball. How do I do that? Nat twenty nine?
I'm in probably two hundred five in a row.
It's been pretty grim over here.
I've rolled so many fives today.
What'd you get?
Got like a 13.
Okay, the twins rolled a 20.
Yeah, we roll for fours.
Wait, what is this for?
This is a sneak.
Okay.
Well, I actually got a critical one.
Oh, well, it's a dirty one.
What'd you lie about?
Nice.
No, no, it's not a, it's a natural one.
Oh, a natural one?
Yeah.
That's very bad.
And I have two health points.
so forced in the twins easily make it by this guy, the battle to
get spotted by the flipper captain who goes
try to pass and he swipes away at the leaky legends. He was fighting and you
two have to roll initiative while you and forced can start to travel to the
network. Okay, okay, seventeen, eleven, should I wait actually eighteen up to
Make up your mind, man.
18 for you, Zuck?
Yes.
Remember, you do have healing, Ed.
And I need that badly.
What did you roll to, by the way?
11. I only have 2 HP, man.
I'll heal right now before initiative starts.
If it's not, you can't.
Nice try, Buck.
I'll just take one turn
before the order starts.
Zuck, you do get to go first, though.
Okay.
fucking you say, but fucking, but fuck the animal in front of me, whatever it is,
but fuck the diaper. The animal in front of me. Damn. That's a JPEG mafia line.
I would like to, I would like to click rewrite and tell the program what to do
for 30 seconds, which is five turns. Tell it to kill itself. Okay. So true. Yep. I
know. Okay, bad writing by the way. It shouldn't be 30 seconds. That's so long.
Yeah, it is five turns. Believe it or not though, for some reason, you don't spend
any resources. It just doesn't work on the Flipper Captain. You don't know why.
What's the next thing you can do?
We're in the real world and we're in a simulation of a Squid Game style show to
pretend we're inside a computer.
Wait, that means that somebody else wrote this code.
Roll wisdom or owl.
I just figured it out. I don't need to roll this shit.
No, you should roll owl.
Okay, shut up bitch.
Fucking nine. Fuck you. Okay. You can't quite tell but something is off about the Flapper captain
He's a girl
Okay, Flapper captain goes now. The Flapper captain is gonna start spraying at you too
Yeah, me? Oh you too. Mm-hmm. I meant you too T-O-O. Okay, he misses.
Spray again. Crit misses. His guns get jammed up. He's gonna only be able to shoot once next turn. You are now up
up.
whole party I guess. Yes it does. How much? Okay that's a beautiful 4 HP to
everybody. That's a dude that's a lot of my HP on this. To me too? Yeah. I'm not good.
Who's the squishiest here? Nice. I got 10 HP. This guy over here is the
squishiest. Oh it's making him cry. Oh sorry. Shit. You think he's the squishiest?
Trying to give you a massage. It's not working. Before we go back, before we
I put my hand on his thigh.
Yo bro, how did I know you were going to take it there?
Forrest goes like, how did I know you were going to take it there?
He's like very happy.
And I say, Forrest, you have to jump on the back of the Viper captain and rip his head
off or else you won't get this.
And I showed him.
What do I show him?
Do I have anything in my hand?
I don't know.
talking with advantage.
Show your body.
Show that trump is a thing.
That is a 15.
With advantage, yeah.
And a 13.
I'm being hypnotized by this entire video.
Forrest nods and like looks you up and down and nods.
And then runs to attack.
So he's going to roll initiative and enter into the fray.
Okay.
And I'm going to save a life.
Oh my God, that's playing right now.
Yeah, as he runs and attacks.
Wow, good hit.
This might be the last time you see Forst.
Wait, turn that music up then.
Yeah, slow motion. Forst goes like
like jumps on the flipper captain and grabs him from behind and starts to
like bite its neck and you two have a moment you can escape if you want to
forest wait I'll never forget roll for damage for force he did he did for damage
but I have to get out of here I can't hurt this guy he did none of my programs
work on him we can't fight this truth I'm leaving wait wait but before they go
So can we call one more person?
I was going to say, you will have to leave one of them behind.
Why don't we just bring Forrest with us?
Well Forrest is now biting the guys.
So just get him off of it.
Whose fault is that? Why don't you send one of your fucking twins?
I thought that maybe it was going to be...
You thought it was going to one hit kill? You thought an NPC was going to one hit kill a boss?
I thought that you guys were going to continue to fight and that I had just given you an advantage.
Dude, I can't hurt him.
I said you could, well you don't know quite if you can't hurt him.
That means I can. Okay, I fight.
I can have you you can roll insight again on him by the way to try to understand
What's if I can't rewrite the code then I definitely can't scramble and refactor the code you also have hitting you're gonna do that's what
I mean, I'd have to just normally attack. Yeah, and I'm not gonna do as much damage
We'll just do it. I know that's being mean whatever I fucking hurt him
Mm-hmm. I
got a 13
That hit let me check his
It's a one.
It does not hit.
Shit, dude.
I told you.
It does not hit.
You didn't roll well.
Well, one of them is a werewolf.
And now the Flipper captain is going to try to grab.
Remember he's gunned down.
He also has disadvantage, yeah.
So he's going to grab, try to grab Forrest and throw it off, throw him off of him.
So it's going to be a little strength contest.
Oh, crit one.
And he does win.
Why did I get a crit one?
What?
No, he got a nine and Forrest got a crit one.
Oh.
is forced off back towards you, just like throws him back and that's when he sees you. So you
roll initiative now. Just to join the fray.
18.
Okay, nice. You'll go early on next time. You have more balance ball, right, Zuck, than
him?
My balance ball is at plus one.
Okay.
And his is plus two.
Oh, so you will go first now.
Oh, okay.
Next time. But cool. So that's his turn, though. Ed, it's your turn.
What is my attack? I have nothing on my sheet.
Well, you're a werewolf, so you have claws, biting, scratching.
I gave you more attacks now. Now you have like attack plus your arm and it does 2d4+2 I think is what I had or something like that.
Well, yeah, I don't know. I'll trust you.
Yeah, I think that's fair because you're now a werewolf and I'm letting you. I think that's fun.
Five.
Damn, you missed. You just whiffed.
Excuse me, I'm sorry, gang.
It's not so pathetic that I missed because I am still recovering from a
pretty crazy medical emergency. I call out and I say,
"Edwardo, you're doing good with the situation."
Forced does hit. "All things considered, you're doing amazing."
I'm glad you're considering everything because a lot of people don't. Nice.
Okay, forced does hit. So forced is the only one really doing damage so far guys.
Maybe if you stop lowering our rolls. Thank you.
It is now, though, your turn.
I am going to do "which twin" on this fucker.
Okay, what does that do?
That, for one minute, enemies have disadvantage.
So he still has disadvantage, or...?
No, he would just have disadvantage on attacks against you.
Okay, so he has disadvantage...
On attacks against you.
...confused by the twinness.
Confused by the twinness, we look at him and we say,
"Hello!" in tandem,
so he thinks we're both named "Hello" now.
Oh, so he doesn't know. So when he's using his targeting program,
targeting hello, he doesn't know who he's targeting. Exactly right.
And then what's my like?
Well, the shell launcher would hit everyone, would it?
Not necessarily. No, it just goes in a straight line.
OK, well, well, I'm going to do a shell launcher. Cool.
That's going to use up most of your.
Well, I'm good. I can also refill it later.
So I'm going to do that right now because I haven't used it.
OK, go for it. Shell launcher.
It is a Mike.
That was an 11 plus.
Oh, sorry, yeah, no, it's what's your balance ball?
Oh, OK, then that is a 13.
Nice. Does that hit?
It does half damage. OK, so what's the damage on there?
Did I put that on there?
Damage is 48 to D6.
What? That's what it says.
My crazy.
I am crazy. OK.
D eight and two D six yeah, so it's got
whoa.
I think I thought oh, I thought the ways would do two D six on the sides, but
still crazy amount of damage. That is crazy. Oh well,
can I get two more D eights? You can't roll multiple times. Oh yeah, yeah,
yeah, okay,
twenty well
ten
eighteen eighteen eighteen
Eight.
Eighteen and eight.
That's twenty six and that's
thirteen.
So, yeah, you do some serious
damage to this guy.
You and your brother fucking row
your shell boat through him.
He's not looking too good right now.
You guys doing a good job.
It is now
your turn, Zuck.
I mean, I guess I'll try to.
Fuck, man.
None of my. I don't have any damage
abilities.
Which kind of stinks.
Didn't he get a weapon?
What weapon?
No.
You can just use attack right now.
Pick me up and use me like a...
I'll just attack.
From what you can tell, this guy is somehow not a program or resistant to it.
Crit one.
This is somebody from the real world.
Another crit one.
Can I examine him and compare my celebrity memory?
You can in a second, but it's actually his turn first.
My egg is itching me.
So he is now going to attack the twins, but he is going to have disadvantage.
So, what's your AC?
My AC is 14.
Okay, he does hit you.
What?
It was 13, but he adds plus two.
No, he doesn't.
No, he does. I'm sorry.
No.
So that is not too bad. That's six.
And now he's going to do a little bit more.
He's going to try again.
disadvantage, so he misses. So you only take six. And now, now, Ed, you can try
to, you can try and place his face. Yeah, roll, roll, yeah, and then we'll add
intellect, brain, intellect, brain. Fifteen. So you realize why, and it's
because this is the user, LittleAndAlone, who's somehow been corrupted. What?
How could you corrupt Little and Alone?
Snap out of it Little and Alone! Snap out of it!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up!
Roll Talking.
Eleven. Oh my god, he's got stitch slippers.
Like from Lilo and Stitch? Yes. I'll show you guys later.
Why would you not do one Lilo, one Stitch? You got eleven? Eleven? Okay.
it's like I
didn't notice he was doing that before men in black sort of like a alien guy
like fucking almost snapping into it, but not quite yet, but now fuck the
soofy. It is your turn, though
is forced somebody talk to him
forced. Here's you say that and and well, he forced hears you say little and
alone and he goes like
really can treating him. Was that a girlfriend as
I was a your diaper diaper friend and the fiber captain starts to transform
into a werewolf like me. It's your water wolf. No for a second you think
you might have a peer yeah
you have to transform back into a user, but he's like halfway transformed. It's
not quite there yet. He's like kill me okay. Well, that's what we've been
trying to do man. Stop fighting back then asshole. Forrest is like give up,
give up right now. What'd you get? What was the first roll? Oh, I didn't know I
was rolling. I was trying to get all my bad rolls out before I get a,
before it's my turn. So I have to roll. So now I'll roll. It's my
turn? You weren't done with your cut scene. It's not your turn actually,
sorry, it's his turn. Exactly, I'm getting my bad rolls out. You're getting
your bad rolls out. Alright, you're up, you're up though. Okay, it's my
turn. Yeah.
That is a dirty 20 because I just go over and I, or we do a, I pick up my twin like a bat
and I swing my twin at him.
Well, that's cool.
Yeah, describe your kill on this guy.
Yes.
Head lobs off like it's a t-ball.
I go shoot, throw 420 feet away like it's Fenway Park.
420 feet, that's funny.
No, that's Fenway.
Oh shit.
Yeah.
Flawless victory.
Well, there's some flaws.
Yeah.
Yeah
It probably would hurt does his head disappear head
Yeah, his head flies off like it's going to go in a left field. It's going past the green monster. Oh, yeah
Wally the green monsters in a diaper in the
Body the green alien sure
Yeah, this guy's dead and you see the the crew
Many of them are battered and broken the leaky legends and they look and they realize who it was and they're like
Crestfallen and they know he said to kill him
y'all and warm feeling says
You guys have to go go to the launcher, okay
We're trying to go that's literally we're trying to meet you when you're fucking friend here decided
He wanted to start a fight your friend
but your lacking friend, your friend, you all come with us because we're going to
sacrifice all of you.
Okay, no, no, no, no, no, no, we definitely need somebody to say they're
going to the soaked city and they said they'll meet you guys there. So you
three enforced can go and fly into the cloud. Let's do it right now. Let's go.
Okay, so the three of you, four of you rather get into the PVN launcher and
it goes like countdown five, four, three
and then you guys launch into...
It whispers.
It launches you guys past the code.
You can almost see the full makeup of the website.
And then you realize you're in like a private
cloud server. Makeup.
Makeup song.
Sounds like it's going to be next.
So the makeup of the website. Yes, good call.
And you're in
the stinky cloud layer now.
Floating in the air. Eww.
A green matrixy stream of
code swirls and congeals into foggy tangibility with tendrils of lingering
binary flavor. In what flavor? It's the stink of the stink cloud meant to hold
all PII and PCI user data. PIIs. Mm-hmm. Encrypted and hashed and rehashed and
blockchained and scrambled and all these things. You guys are now barreling
through to get to the private cloud server itself and
and mess balls now are flying through.
You guys are going to have to start dodging these things.
These are balls of mess.
Scrambled poop.
Come off it.
Yeah.
Barrels of scrambled poop.
So, deck saving throws.
Let's go.
I got a 13, man.
I got a 2.
I got a 17.
But I get two rolls because I'm a twin.
No, but you do get to add two to it.
Okay.
I got a 4.
You take four damage.
And four saves.
And I'm going to go ahead and roll.
I'm going to roll a 10.
And forced, oh yeah, I have to roll for forced as well.
I have 3 HP.
Where's my... where's the fucking d20?
Ugh, forced. Forrest, what have you done?
I look like Patrick Pespo's right now. You do, he's
missing. Oh, is he really? Yeah, he's missing. That's sad.
Him and his wife, both missing. I bet you know where I bet he is, in Hollywood. Again!
We can only hope.
Dexterity saving throws again.
Damn.
There's a crit one.
Fuck me, man.
No, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, another one?
That's a three.
It's still a crit one.
That's another one we have to roll?
Yeah, I got a four.
Oh, that's a crit on.
Eighteen.
Okay, what'd you get?
Crit one.
Crit one, what'd you get, Zuck?
I got a four.
You take nine damage, Zuck.
Whoa.
I'm fucking dead, bruh.
You take five damage.
I'm dead.
He got a crit one?
I'll just heal both of them.
I'm gonna heal both of them.
damage. I'm gonna crit one. I'll just heal both of you guys right now. I'm
dead. Okay, I heal them.
Okay, you guys land. Wait, wait, I'm healing them. Another campaign where we
just die. That's all we do. We just fucking die and heal them.
Eight damage. Eight forces healed back. I'm back to full. I'm at eight. You
guys are healed and then I take two energy chargers. Yep. I pop an Adderall
that I had in my pocket.
That's awesome as a power up like Mario, like Super Mario. That's fucking sick.
So you guys land on the private server. Yeah, that's good man. I don't know you
were do you focus you've a lot of focus. No, because I don't have ADHD because
I'm me and my twin don't have a d. You're just you're just we we stand up
we we
now that I've taken the Adderall, my brother's name is now we no bro. Don't
bring we sent to know not we send we can't go on this. No, we're saving. We're
saving. We're saving weeks for the next campaign. And yeah, you guys approach the
private virtual network. So one of you forced can stay behind and you're going
to have to tell him forced. You will stay behind.
Okay, and force will stay behind. Somebody has to communicate with him.
So forced. How's my phone? Now? I see. Give me your phone. How can we call him?
if you have you gave him where's your phone to you have a phone yeah. I've
had a phone the whole time. I've been a phone. I developed this.
I have a draw. I all have ways of communicating with each other. You can
just tell him to like you will communicate with him. The second the
hash just thrown in will communicate with you every second yeah.
So now you guys need to
fly back through the cloud and into the portal and you'll fall through directly
It's a soaked city. But before that happens, oh wait, I do another makeover.
This is the sound for flying.
Pretty cool. And then play the makeover music.
It's over. It's over? It is. It's over for you. Oh, okay.
The episode's done? No. Oh, it's just over for you.
So we fly and we get you guys into Soak City.
Geez.
And next time we will.
Oh, it is over.
It is over.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, sorry.
Next time we will explore.
I was just saying it was over for Patrick because Julio wasn't playing the music.
You had an amazing read there, my friend.
Yeah, it was a good read.
Because we got, we got, we have.
Julio left the computer.
Yeah.
I think Julio fell asleep.
We need to check on him.
on him. Is he sleepy? Hello, are you there? You there, buddy? Julio. He's completely gone.
He's gone. He left us. There's no way. We're going to have to stop the recording manually.
Great. We just have to press a button. How much fucking work does he make us do? I know.
Bro, we pay you $200 a month. Do I look like the Beatles or maybe? You do. Say Ringo. Ringo.
- Oh. - Ringo.
- Ringo.
- I smoked weed in Japan. - Well.
- Paul McCartney got caught with pot in Japan.
- Unbelievable episode.
- Pot, he was caught with pot.
- I'm gonna stay completely neutral on the two.
I'm gonna say my first memory with,
I think the first memory I remember
is the shadow of a hot dog poking out
in my bedroom when I was a kid.
I saw the shadow of a hot dog on the wall.
And it was kind of like a come to G like a Batman type moment. Come moment.
Nope. Come to Jesus.
Are you saying you got molested? I'm saying I saw the shadow of a hot dog.
Are you trying to say seeing a shadow of a bat?
Are you saying shadow? Oh, did he see the full bet?
I don't know. I thought he saw the shadow of the moon.
My bad. So you got attacked by a hot dog.
No, I was attacked by burgers,
but I saw the shadow of a hot dog that saved me.
And there's nothing about molestation in this.
Why are you bringing up molesting on the hamburger versus hot dog debate?
Well, you brought up the shadow of a hot dog on your bedroom wall,
which kind of makes it it feels like that's what you're getting at.
It feels like you're trying the way you were kind of laughing when you were saying
it. No, I was imagining a hot dog style Batman.
But what is the shadow?
Why would you be a shadow?
Is because Batman is a different hero.
That's a shadow.
- What do you mean?
- A shadow is Batman of the night.
- Also, what are you, you're saying like,
like you, bats are to Batman,
like hot dogs are to you?
- A shadow is the Batman of the night?
Is that what you just said?
- Let's just move on.
- Wait, I just, we're not gonna get anywhere.
- We're not even gonna get anywhere.
This actually makes the most sense to me,
is what I was trying to say.
- This is what makes the most sense to you?
This is what you're trying to say,
is that a hot, a hot dog as Batman on a plate?
You're making no sense.
- You're, something is wrong with you.
- I feel like I just went crazy trying to puzzle out
what you said.
Can you answer, did you actually say a hot dog or a shadow is the Batman of the night?
Or did I?
Was I like falling asleep?
I heard that too.
(explosion)