Hello, everybody. Today we're having a dnd episode with no randomness at all.
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, wait, do the chimes on random chimes be like random chiming
cheese potato. Okay, we got out of our system. We're ready to go. No randomness
the entire episode. Okay, well, very soon we'll be no randomness random air horn
and I'm a horn. Damn, damn,
I wish we had an AI voice that could do random dancing for different. Okay,
yeah, we're just doing a podcast over patches. I watched I watched Patrick
turn it into just a regular conversation.
All right, last time on the diaper network, Tron. Why are we like so close
together this one? Because there's four of us because I didn't move the table
still needs to be yeah, but
isn't he usually off and then Cameron has a new hat. There we go. I want to
change up my character a little bit. I don't like being the same guy every
damn time. That's fair. I was talking about a werewolf. What happened last
time? A milk man to what happened? Well, we'll find out what happened last time
on the diaper network. Tron Mark Eduardo and the finger bros twins continued
their journey into the
diaper network source code.
A reminder of the setup, mostly for you guys here. I mean, for the people
listening, but you know, they can... time is different for them because of the
episode, how that works. While the three were on trial, so while you three were on
trial for a three-way courtroom battle, that's what I wrote, over the creation of
the Diaper Network, you guys decided to settle who created the website, the Diaper
network once and for all with a court-ordered code-a-thon.
Suddenly, though, before the code-a-thon
could even get underway, you guys were sucked into a computer
by FieldCompletely, a program that controls the diaper
network.
Now you must fight your way out by performing
an overly elaborate series of tasks
to destroy FieldCompletely and ensure that there
are zero redundancies.
So two sessions ago--
this is going to be brief.
So two sessions ago, you guys broke out of the Play Play Games prison
with fellow prisoner Joe Music 1976,
a member of an elite group of Diaper Network power users who were sucked
into the system before you guys,
before you guys were when Phil completely was testing his new user
sucking software.
You then killed Joe and stole his ship, the SS Nappy,
and rode the wedding way to the Tinkle Lair.
That's right. I remember that there you souped up your bikes with a very high
intelligence role
turn into hover bikes
all right
easily gliding above the shimmery, but sallow sea.
Why don't you do the chimes? This is shimmery. Oh, shimmering. Well,
shimmering is not really kind of a key word in my brain to but yeah, I guess
don't shimmer yeah, but I that was a good size should have picked up on that. I
was kind of just thinking about yeah, how about you other take care of the
sounds badges? How about that
asshole? So you guys glided over the sea, oops reaching the I was a mistake
y'all and you found the emergency mass communication tower, emergency mass
communication tower. It was going to allow you guys to communicate with
outside people outside the computer to give you a hash in slow motion and we
did right. Yes, you did and well here's before you did that with that time
ramping really didn't make that much sense to me. It didn't make sense in Tron either,
so I got nothing for you there. That's fair. So when you reached there, you ran into Joe
Music 1976's leaky legends comrade. We sent him away. Sissybaby34. I'm remembering. Who
suspected you guys of killing his comrade Joe Music 1976. Completely baseless accusation.
you guys told him you killed him. Well it was false. After disposing of him and a cross-eyed
fliper you entered the tower. Thank you and met with a Dylan program. Dylan being the
guy who helped fund and jumpstart Zuckerberg's. You don't gotta intro Dylan man. Sorry yeah
sorry. Everybody here knows Dylan. That program of Dylan who was created helped use the emergency
mass communication tower to communicate with the bailiff in the courtroom who sent the hash
hashed code into the computer and you guys now have it, which by the way,
which one of you has the hashed code? I think I think I think you do to pretty
sure because you tried to I wasn't sure because he because we tried you to the
thing he went into the world. Yeah, I figured it was you who the world yes,
and he was doing mischief. Afterwards, you visited the leaky legends HQ
through the damp layer. That's the second level of the diaper network source
code. You smooth talked your way into being allies with them and fought
alongside them to enter into the PVN launcher. It's a private virtual network
launcher, which sends you guys up to the private virtual network through the
Stinky Cloud. You have a new friend, Forst, who is a Diaper Talk power user and now
a member of the Leaky Legends. Forst is his real username.
- Wow.
- And he joined you and he flew with you guys through the Stinky Cloud on the PVN.
Now he is stationed there, ready to, the second you guys kill with the hashed code, filled
completely, he will on his end, enact, destroy the redundancy of, of, of, of, uh, filled
completely in that brief gap where there is no one to oversee that kind of like regeneration
of like, you know, standing up another, basically another network.
Well, let's hop to it, man.
I want to get out of this computer for the rest of my life.
So you guys are now in Soaked City, where Warm Feeling and the rest of the Leaky Legends
told you he'd meet you guys here.
So in Soaked City, it's a simulation of the kind of the world that Phil completely wants
to create.
it's got where, like the tinkle layer was yellow and the damp layer was brown
and dark and damp.
The the soaked city is bluey blues everywhere. You see
lots of clean water rubber duckies rubber duck. Yes, rubber duckies like in
the water, I guess. How do you know that I fucking guess and there's it's all
it's sort of it's the Venice of the Internet. You can ride on gondolas that
not is it still here? It is still diapered out. Okay, so that what it is
is it's a simulation of the world he wants to create. So you're gonna hear
from a lot of different members of the diaper talk community,
all different creeds. Yeah,
who are living in here as if they're in a city. It's a simulation of
their accounts basically being manifest here. So they are it's them interacting
on the forums, but it being represented. What's the dominant religion in soaked
city. Probably atheism is a theist. I was trying to come with funny. I think it's
Shinto atheism Shinto. I think they believe all the diapers and poops have
spirits and they have to make offerings to them that to make offerings to the
diaper. I will say that so the thing is is now you're closer and closer to
filled completely. So, you know, you have to just be smart, you know, you can't make
too much noise to my you know what have been a good character name is hash
brown. So you can't we can't make too much noise and we need to be kind of
low key. Yeah. So should we be like maybe we could do disguises? Yes, you
can. I'm already wearing my disguise. I'll disguise myself as a one man band.
I'm disguised. I'm a werewolf. I'm disguised as a milkman.
I'm carrying bottles of milk. I'm disguised as a horse, but I don't have
the costume.
So it's a one man band, a horse and
do your heads in your brother's my brother's head is in my butt yeah
yeah and I yeah
we're trying to be incognito. That's fine. That's that is very not on every
door
you get a
I'm knocking on everybody's door and ringing everybody's doorbells. Well
yeah, you got to deliver milk. You have milk with you yeah milk. Well, he's
got to explain to them that I have some of the milk. You can't have any of the
no, it goes to houses. You know, okay, you don't go to the mailman and say,
can I have some of that mail? You guys are wait to actually saw a lady try to
do that the other day and the mail man always want to do it. The mail man had
to say legally I cannot give you the mail, not through the mailbox, and she
was like that makes sense. Yeah, I always think about doing so you guys
entered in through the
adult baby. I'm sorry, an adult baby introductions for him. Okay, so when
knocking on people's door. I go into some knock on the one that says how to make
friends. Yeah, I knocked on that one for sure. Cool. So when you open when you
knock on the door, you see a cow, an anthropomorphic cow. It says moves quick
guide to making friends on the diaper talk network. Fill out your profile as
many fields as you possibly can. The more if in this this by the way goes on
for the as explains the entire I go up to the cow and I start naying at it and I
I try to speak to it in barnyard. Okay, you are blocked. It is blocked from
from the
so I say okay, I'll start filling up my profile occupation, milk man, species,
wolf man name,
milk wolf. I try to type everything in, but my hooves make it impossible. You
don't have who's well. I'm pretending that I have
pretending it's a possible. I'm doing this. I'm just going
I my setting my name to one man band with a one tan hand because I put my hand in
my diaper and got poop on it. You got one man band with... Your poop is tan? Is what fit?
Well, maybe your one hand is tan your other one is dark brown with yellow and
green flecks. No, it tanned my hand with poop. So I left it in there for so long.
One man band with... With a one hand tan. No, that's it couldn't fit. One hand band wit.
I somehow type in Hashbrown.
And your name is Milkwolf?
Mr. Milkwolf.
Mr. Milkwolf, okay cool.
Mr. E. Milkwolf.
Yeah.
At an absolute minimum, you must have an avatar set on your profile.
This is required to get to EC status, which lets you message people.
Lena Dunham.
I want to do a photo shoot with y'all.
Yeah, I also pick Lena Dunham.
This is kind of a barnyard animal. Mine I put my phone on the ground and I stand over it.
I love doing that. I set it on self-timer and I put it screened down too so I can get
the really wide angle and I said turn the flash on of course and I go in and I'm putting
the exposure up. That would be a really scary photo of a werewolf. Put the brightness down.
I'm telling you, I'm sharpness. Oh, no, don't deep fry that
saturation way of God. I'm putting on the tilt shift and a vignette. This
shit is actually okay. Wait, I put on the I put my phone on the
on like a thing and then I put the horse filter on and I stand
on all force
the horse and your name is hash brown and my name is hash brown.
Okay, and you're Lena Dunham, right? Yeah, but you can't even tell because
have so many instruments in front of me. It doesn't I picked it because I just
feel like she could carry a lot. See a combination between her and her ex
husband, so post post. She's got shoulders built for shopping bags man.
She built like a rescue hero.
She carried two batches of groceries in one trip. No perfect housewife and one
day she'll be Costco come back, put all the bags on your shoulder, drive back to
all the beer that that shopping again open up.
What are you
that's a horrible. That's awfully misogynistic. What the heck we don't
engage with that kind of conversation. It's got to be me. She's a artistic
genius. I just
you're disgusting. Can get her heart broken. Posted introduction, which is
more information about who you are, your likes, interests, etcetera. Show us how
interesting you can be. Tell an interesting story about yourself. You're
trying to portray yourself as a person who is likable. I want to hide. Oh, go
good. Let's say our story in your character in your care.
What's a character? One time I was eating hay and
it tasted good because I got the finger bros twins. Well, we're trying to be
the
you and have your voice in the horse. One time I was trying. I was a little
higher than I tasted good. Meanwhile, okay, now lean it on a one time. I was
hey and it tastes so good. You I delivered milk to a whole family. Okay,
mine is a bunch of will. I watched the whole. I watched the whole family drink
my milk. That's mine. My I was milked. Mine is all will. I was built for the
book. If you ain't first, you're last. I like you, but you're crazy.
What else man? My I feel this down in my plum. They're all they're all will
feral quotes, but they're only from kicking and screaming more cowbell and
and at the end I know the pieces fit.
- All right, cool. - Damn.
I chaperoned a field trip to my house.
- That's Moo's quick guide to making friends.
Moo is a staff member of the website.
- So I leave the milk on the doorstep and I close the door.
- Simple as.
- Cool. - Easy.
- So now you guys are now registering the site.
You have who you are, your disguises,
your like new avatars and profiles.
- I just realized that--
- And now you can message people too.
- I set my first initial to E for Eduardo
and I just realized I made my name mystery milk wolf because I said Mr.
E. I didn't even realize I did that's a mystery milk. Well, I made myself a
horse. Yeah, so you guys receive a message on your in your I just realized
that your hud that you see in your life
from warm feeling that tells you guys to meet him at the good feelings thread,
and he shows you a little map of you have to kind of ride the waterways
through a number of
discussions
and threads to get on doesn't make that noise. So like bubbles, I've been I'm
trying to be a moral vigilance. These gondolas are the I was supposed to chime
these gondolas. I appreciate it. Thank you. These gondolas are all big. They're
all big rubber duckies, little diapers on them and they're piloted by programs
that
oops
he made he made me say we made me a robot
accident. Is that everyone? A complete accident. I swear to God it was that time for real.
Okay. The time when I said hamburger I'm going to come clean, that was on purpose. But that
one was a real accident. Alright, well let's get on one of those gondolas. Let's go, let's
go, let's go. So you guys get on one of the rubber ducky gondolas. Oh, very nice. Where
did you find that? You gave it to me. Probably for this. Whoa. What happened? What happened
What happened? I don't know if I that wasn't smart. I don't remember what
that is. It's called Tsunami W, the master shoot on me.
That's crazy. It had a little thing in it anyway. Sorry, I'm sorry to do I was
trying to
you did a great job yeah. I just for some reason, very happy,
so yeah this these programs, you know, collect and send user data,
So they are piloting the rubber ducky for you guys.
But it's important to maintain your disguises while you're in these things
because of the fact that their whole thing is about scanning, understanding user data.
So if it's flagged that you guys are one of the three humans who are in here
besides the Leaky Legends, right?
I asked for an apple.
The program goes, "Sure, I will give you"-- I'm a robot voice.
I can give you a robot voice. You just have to give me one second here.
I just have to switch it to what are you to yeah, no, I'm four years old.
You're four.
Who's who's who?
I'm four.
Yeah, I'm four.
I thought I was four.
There I go.
There we go.
Wait.
Now I'm wait.
What the fuck are you permanently a robot now?
What can't be saved?
Take glaze on through it.
I don't know how it's not supposed to be happening.
No way.
I'm not back.
Okay.
What do you want me to say?
man. I'll say what the fuck is going on. Is this going to be? Oh, no, am I stuck
as a whatever
not a big deal. Okay,
can you just I what did you ask again? What do you want me to say? I asked for
an apple.
Yes, you can have an apple
affirmative apple
required. I'm there we go. Oh my God,
being a human, that was the first time that we've ever had a glitch on it. We
made you a permanent rope. I was really fucking scared. I'm not I was scared to
was going to ruin the episode. I was fucking scared that I was straight up
scared of shit dude. I had to turn on a different robot effect and then turn it
back. Okay, well thank God you figured yeah. Well, do you mind? Can you try
again? There we go.
Caleb say something
I have an apple.
All that. All that was worth it. There'll be other times for robot voices.
I asked for a carrot now. I got to get the, you know,
no, we do not have carrots. Okay.
My goal is to go to the other side of the world and deliver milk to a tribe
that never discovered it.
You tell it you tell him that yeah,
that sounds great.
And I like I'm playing
of Coldplay's "Something Just Like This" on my one man band.
- Do we have that?
- I don't know.
♪ I want something just like this ♪
- Oh, he's got some music video of the Buc-ees.
I got it.
♪ Do do do do do do ♪
♪ That's a dark music ♪
♪ I want something just like this ♪
♪ Do do do do do do ♪
- You guys ride the waves,
you hear the music playing as you're doing it,
as the one man band playing,
and you reach the first forum,
the adult baby forum.
So did someone actually get caught?
Were some people here actually caught in a diaper with a pacifier or anything
else ABDL related? What was the reaction?
How did your relationship develop from that point?
We have to answer this?
You guys can answer this and then I got some other answers for you.
Oh, I thought that we had to like, yeah, it's being discussed.
It's being discussed.
Okay.
Yeah.
Um, yes, that shit happened to me at one of my one of my sold out Madison Square
Garden one man band shows. I was painting my house and I was wearing only a
diaper so I didn't get stains on any of my cool sweatshirts or my sweat pants.
I'm a horse. You're a whore. So pretty much everyone in my life knows my
co workers, my family, my friends. I'm an out of diaper boy. It's been really
interesting. And after the initial seriously, it didn't really change
change anything. No one treats me differently. No one is weird. I didn't
lose any friends. It's been a complete non issue. I expected more pushback.
L. O. L. All I got was the opportunity to be myself and not stress about
wearing a diaper cap. Your friends all hate you. I reply. I reply with a cap
emoji. Your friends and family all despise
thanksgiving is weird at your house. I reply with a reverse emoji and a shoe
emoji. You guys keep going along to the best pacifiers for thumb suckers.
How does orthodontic sizing work?
That's a good question. Tell you as a milk man, I would have no expertise in
that. I have no expertise on anything human related because I'm a horse.
Passifier wouldn't fit no mouth. How about a pacifier shaped like a thumb? I
you have a that's a good idea.
You replied that's a good idea. I replied that's a good idea.
I reply I have no room for a pacifier because of the harmonica and then a
photo of me performing in front of another sold out show. I reply, I reply,
"Any y'all want some milk?" And then I reply to Caleb and I say, "I post a
picture where I have a bunch of bottles of milk laid out in a bed.
I got milk, anyone buy a milk? Anyone want milk?" And you immediately get 10,000
DMs of people like, "Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes." I reply to Caleb's post and I say, "What about
harmonica pacifier. That's a good idea. Maybe I'll pull that out the next time
I'm performing at the Greek to a completely sold-out audience. You see a
one that's about... How the snow? About what what kind of wetness that they like and
you see one person says, "I like it when it's wet enough to make it harder to
walk. I literally can't sleep unless I am somewhat wet. I usually pee my diaper
before bed. I'm going commando on a puppy pad because after all this hot weather I
why I have a diaper rash
that's sad on the ground diaper to Justin says probably eating nothing but
baby food for two days straight, then wedding and messing my diaper is
sleeping in it. I reply with a photo of my teeth,
my gnarled horse to
close up
mine swinging like a pendulum and it's making me waddle when I walk. Oh, the
diaper is I thought I just love how squidgy it is when I sit down heart,
heart, tear to your heart, heart, baby sign, thumbs up, baby sign. There's a
baby sign, a baby sign. Y'all the only witness I like is the condensation on
the outside of a milk bottle. I got milk low low prices. Anyone want milk hit my
am you get a message you get a
theory
to this wallet. You get a message from from baby for ninety two, whoa saying
milk, milk, milk, milk, milk, so pretty. I want your milky milky milk five
thousand dollars.
This is the richest Eduardo has ever been
whoa by the baby for bought the milk. You have okay. I delete my account. Oh
my God, not given this guy any milk. You don't have oh you have some milk,
some milk. I have houses to visit on my route, but what if you just put it
okay? I'll give them I sent upload the by paper clip, the milk to my dm use
after milk.
Finally, make it to the positive vibes area,
no matter how big or small name one good thing that happened to you today
made a band made five bands
five bands off my friend made five racks
flipping milk
and you you hear from you here from another rubber ducky nearby you.
My day was good because we're going to take down fill completely and it's warm
feeling. Hey, warm feeling yo
hey warm feeling. Call me a different call me. Call me a different name. Hey
-Fo-red. -Hey, Mr. Milk Wolf.
-Fo-red? -Hello, Fo-red.
-Fo-red is fine. -I'm a horse.
-How you guys doing? -I'm a horse.
-We're good, man. -We're a horse now.
-Where's your bro-- Oh. All right. -He's in my butt.
I know a few guys who are into that, so...
Um, all right.
So, we're gonna storm...
-The capital? -The Mazy Gate.
Well, sort of.
Between Soaked City and Fill Completely
is the messy maze where the messy tour lives.
You have to break through the mazey gate membrane though first.
Now, fill completely as the messing hour.
Every hour where all users inside Soak City, whether they want to or not,
fill their diapers completely.
At that moment, we have to crap.
Wait, we will not.
My brother's head is in my butt.
I'll be crap because we are not
that compose. It's too bad now that we all have to crap at the crappy. No
announcing our well, you seems like you guys have to
I like that, but not before you guys cast around. It seems like this guy's
saying that me and this one man band guy don't have to do that, but you do for
us for some reason. Oh my God, no how well I mean you're tempting me that it
should be what happens, but
you know what? So no, no, no, just because I want that to happen. Hold on,
I'm not in control here.
What we need to do is during that missing hour, that's a brief window that
me and the rest of the leaky legends will strike.
What's up? You just shit in your I was testing.
I was doing a test run. Stop don't don't draw attention to yourself right now.
- Okay. - We'll go in there.
- Why am I smelling it?
- In the three of you, then-- - In real life, I'm smelling it.
Somehow.
Once we strike and distract the elite guards,
the three of you will break through the membrane
and enter the messy maze.
We will break through the membrane.
We gonna break through the brain.
Insane in the maze!
And once you get--
(laughing)
It's crazy.
Once you get through the membrane--
I'm sorry, once you get through the maze
and defeat the Messytaur,
then it's just you versus Phil completely.
You guys ready?
Do we have a chance to heal before?
- Ready as Oliver Peabra.
- Are we gonna, do we have like a save point outside of the?
- Yeah, where are your, I just realized
I have not looked at your sheets in a little bit.
- Eight, eight.
- I'm full.
- You guys should, yeah.
- 10.
- Yeah, you could fill up to your max HP,
'cause it's gonna be, I would say that like,
you've done enough. - Oh, we should fill now.
- You've done enough short rests-ish.
- Fill completely?
- No.
- Meow?
- Well, yes.
- Oh, yes, I guess so. - Fill to the max.
- Yeah, fill completely.
- All right.
How many do you have?
You have four left.
You should get your moves back.
This is gonna be a brutal fight.
If you guys have been spending your resources.
- Whoa, a brutal fight.
- Oh my God.
- Good thing I have eight HP.
- Yeah, get your resources back.
I think that's fair.
- Okay.
- 'Cause I didn't get a--
- I still have makeover party.
Oh, I guess I'm a horse.
- I didn't go this through a fine tooth comb.
All right, so you guys ride on your parallel rubber duckies
until you reach the messy gate.
And you and the Leaky Legends are just sort of ambling about,
and about five or so minutes goes by,
and a warm feeling goes to you and he says,
"All right, it's about to be the messing hour
"in about 30 seconds.
"You guys ready?"
- 30 second heads up.
Yeah, man, yeah, that's good.
Yeah, that's a really efficient thing.
- Yeah, I'm ready.
- Maybe I skipped all the other heads ups
that I was given.
- Yeah, sure, whatever, 30 seconds, sure.
Let me just get excited.
Now you're now you're in character. It's good. I hold I hold my brother in it.
Don't I can't stress enough. You do not need to crap your brother out. If you
don't want I hold I hold his shoulders and I say I'm doing this because we have
to
cake.
So
as it's winding down, you see the sky with all its bluey blues and it's sort of
all the water. You see it start to turn red slowly
and like start to pass over and get dark.
- I've said pass over.
(laughing)
- And you see the members of the diaper network
who are not humans like you guys
and see their eyes roll in the back of their heads
and you hear a rumbling of a thousand stomachs.
Yes.
- Holy shit.
- And you hear a warm feeling go, now!
and they all, the League of Legends charge and attack
the elite guards there while they are having an ecstasy,
orgy, porgy style shitting themselves kind of moment.
And you guys now, in this moment,
are you guys breaking through the membrane or what?
- Let's go man, yeah.
- Let's break through. - Okay.
You guys go through, what do you do?
Do you shit your brother out too?
- I shit on my brother's face
and then he jumps up and runs.
- Okay.
- So now he has poop damage or something, I don't know.
- And now they can't tell him apart.
Yeah, well now they
can tell us apart.
You're right.
Whatever. Wait, they can't tell us apart?
I don't understand.
They can't. I thought.
What do you mean?
I just like I'm sorry.
I don't know. I was just trying
something new.
Well, don't try it again.
You guys burst through the membrane
into the messy maze.
Now, the messy maze is
what I turn left, then right, then
right, then left, then left, then
forward, then right, then left,
stop and straight. Did I get to it?
No, I go
right
BA start. That is a Konami code. How are you going to go be an A in a maze?
I hit the T. I already did that one time and I beat him. That was true.
That was the worst. I hit the Teal day and I hit I type in
no clip and then I talk about maybe our best campaign to
think about that one where I defeated you. Yes, yeah, sorry. What are you
I hit the teal day and then I type in no clip and then I hit enter and then I
click through the whole maze. Okay we're in a maze yeah. Okay can I roll a perception check?
I go all the way down. Yes you may roll a perception check. Look at that. Okay Mr. Baldur's
Gate. Yeah I've been playing Baldur's Gate 3 guys 20 minutes at a time because I get so bored.
Here I go. A 7 man. Okay cool. What were you trying to like pick up on by the way? Trying
Trying to pick up on what way seemed the best direction to go. Yeah, it's hard
for you to tell. So,
what you do know is that the... And sorry, Warren Filling would have told
this to you in the lead up, I should have mentioned this earlier.
The way that the messy maze works is that all the walls and sort of
the sky above it, which is a little bit more...
Has a little bit more like motherboardy kind of texture. It's a little less
like trying to be idyllic and more back to being what it's supposed to
be, like the inner webs.
it's brown. When it's brown, you don't move and when it's good game and when
it's yellow, you go. What's red light green light, which is before it's good.
No, so it's not really a good game. Well, it's also a maze. This is a hat on a
hat man. Yeah, but like well either that or we had to set up the camera so I can
do an actual maze mean. Okay, so then I'm just going to proceed through the
maze. I'll turn every corner. No, I'm still going to Brown. I'll stop moving.
There'll be checks. There'll be checks. Let's go then. And I'll want to bring it
on. Bring it out of the mind. Cool. You guys will also know that if you move
while it's Brown, the messy tour will go get you.
Is it hard to tell when it's Brown? It's not hard to tell. So it should be fine.
Okay. Right. But maybe something scary will happen and come to get me like
a cloud of bees, the only a cloud of bees yeah and I'm like oh God, I don't like
I might be allergic to cloud of beef stew, clouded, clouded beef,
clouded beef, bro. You watch videos about clouded beefs all day, Bert
Kreischer.
No, it's Bobby Lee and Brendan Chaube.
Also, two bears, one cave might be over guys.
you're just dropping that and then drawing on the table like you're some
kind of a fucking
like you can you hit pause on the episode right now. I need to I need to
go to the bathroom real quick. You can just go. It's the whole no it's not
because of a p. Oh I see. Oh it's because of a t. It's because of it's
because of a seat. Oh con. Sorry. What the hell. I'm sorry. I'm not even
gonna cry. Our fans say that
When you say cunt, they turn into cricket and I'm not saying I'm not
saying it. I'm simply repeating. So today was the day patches got
cancelled. Y'all
patches haters be like
okay, so
it turned yellow. So now you guys can go
so roll who wants to take lead here? I will lead. Okay, I'm like the
Oh, why don't we take twin leads?
What's your what's role?
What kind of role are we doing?
Good question.
So it's up to you guys though.
So you can either strong or ball.
No, no.
No, so it's taking the lead is figuring out how to get out
of this maze so you can use either, you know, you can use
your intelligence, right?
Your brain.
Uh-huh.
You can use more of your wisdom to figure it out.
So can we roll all three of it is like investigation versus
like perception, right?
I think you should do it.
Can we I was going to say can we roll all three?
can we roll like the three things?
Can we roll like I can roll strength,
he can roll intelligence and then he can roll like perception.
Describe to me what you're going to try to do.
I was just going to roll strength and try to barrel through everything.
You're going to say you want to try to knock down the walls.
Yes.
Okay.
I want to knock down the walls until I create a path.
You can try to do that.
What are you guys going to try to do?
I'm going to follow the rules, man.
Yeah, I think I'm going to.
I don't want to take any chances here.
I'm going to follow the rules as well and maybe try to go really fast
while it's yellow.
I got an eight to run really quickly. An eighteen. Yeah, because it's strength
plus three. Yeah. Okay. It's very good. You're not able to knock down these
walls. I mean, you would have to have gotten a twenty basically, but knock
down every wall. What? No, you would have just well, you would have been able
to knock start. Yeah, I guess you would have been able. I would. That's
probably what I would have had to do. But beyond that, it's like you're able
to like knock into it and rattle around a bit, but that's about it. Yeah, I
notice anything or oh, I like that. What if you're when it's like a bat kind of
sonar thing? Yeah, let's have you roll. It's a horse thing.
A hole in the wall small enough so they can't get through. Why don't we try?
Let's have you do a owl. Okay, see if you could do it. I like that. That's fun.
No, there's a two. I was a two damn. All right, yeah, you don't quite get the
makeup of the maze. Okay, try though. I like that. Okay, cool. I would have
the wind going into different caverns of the cave. Yes, you would have heard. But
now all I did was give myself a concussion. You're just like kind of a
little dazed right now. Okay, so suddenly though you guys do actually all of you
roll perception check. Suddenly. That's owl. Yeah, that's owl. Sorry, roll owl. That is
is
Who was leading?
Me no it was I thought it was Pat
It was it was it was Pat
Whatever man that was a time. I save you okay. Well we passed the honesty test so we get another role
Caleb's character dies
I'll be lying for sending you can't die from lying so Pat is not able to hear this despite being a horse
But you're a rush of brown
flowing through. You do. And you have roll a... What do you want... Actually, so don't
roll. What do you want to do? You have a moment right now where you could potentially help
your team like not get...
I just yell stop.
That's a good start. Do they listen to you? Do you guys listen to them?
Yes.
Nice. That makes it a lot easier, I think. But now all of you guys have to roll constitution...
You still have to roll like strength checks rather to see if you get bowled over.
it won't be as hard for you. What did you get?
Thirteen.
Ten.
Okay.
I got a five.
Damn.
So, it turns brown, you two manage to stay still, you do fall over.
Like I fucking noticed.
You screamed so loud that you threw up.
No, I just shit.
I think a cloud of bees came and scared me.
There's no bees in the website.
There possibly is.
In front of you, you see it. A minotaur wearing a diaper. It's a
massy taur. Can we kill it? You can certainly try. Or can we seduce it?
You could also try that, I guess. As a horse.
Oh, man, I do like that. Oh, shit. I hate when you do that. That's good.
'Cause what am I gonna do, say no to that? That's a really funny idea.
wait and I and I have cows.
I'm a horse with one. I have cows milk and a minotaur is a type of cow and I
can play a horse song.
Yeah, okay, so so so I'm painting the scenario here. So you you're playing
like a fucking like neo soul, can actually song bird, but it's called
song or Kenny G song bird is the other angle. You can go. You are giving your
are you going to install milk in him?
that's a good idea that you gotta do that. That's a good idea. I guess
squirt in his brother's. I was thinking it's just like you know if someone's
coming running at if you're someone's running at you to kill you and you hold
up, you're just holding a bunch of breast milk. They're probably gonna
they would definitely not they might not stop, but they're definitely gonna be
like. I thought you guys were gonna like build a sexy scenario. Yeah, I thought
that's what was sexy. Let's build a sexy scenario. Then messy tore into milk,
leave a trail of milk leading to his body, but only the bottom half is
believe his brother and get fucked by the maybe I'll pretend
yeah and then I
my brother's my bottom half. Yeah,
yeah, I guess the milk can be used in any way that you deem fit.
I like to hand me the milk. I can pour the milk talking bugs, bunny in a
dress, okay, or a bombs
brother. If you guys were a monster, would you rather have sex with a horse
that was covered in milk or one that wasn't covered in milk? Because I'm a
weird fucking. That's what I'm thinking, too. So I'm just going to pour the
milk on saturate his outfit. Yeah, make it what's a wet T shirt. Contest. Oh,
well, no, don't do that because I don't see the human underneath. I do this.
Well, I'm not. I make the milk look like I'm guys. I make the milk dribbling
down the corners of his mouth and out of his butthole. I want to I want to
let's reiterate I'm in a horse. I'm in a horse pose, no cost to a milk pie in his
but that's what I'm going to do and then I'm going to act like I'm just taking my
thing out of his butt and go. Oh, that was great. That was the best I ever had,
but you know I would make it better if I was a monster. Oh, what I am a
I'm a monster and I like this even more than we want than and fucking a
fucking human human
and I'm not a human. I'm a horse. Okay, let's let this play out. So what's what
so I put milk into his but and pretend that I got a leak out as if it was my
jizz my high yeah, so it's very you know that can we put up a big you know, I
can see of my nut. We put up a big Las Vegas style, so I'm pretending I'm
pulling my wolf cock out of his ass
as a werewolf. This was number one. We put up a big. We put up a big Las Vegas
like little like iridescent light bulbs. That's a free horse sex yeah.
and I stay and you're playing a sexy song. I'm playing a
yeah
okay,
so a couple I want to put this all together in a few different that's all
with a harmonica. You need me to explain my part of it again. I got a
played by a bus. Yeah, that's a
full harmonica. Don't roll yet. Don't roll yet. I'm going to tell you, though,
what we're going to do when so, but don't roll until I
stop bitch.
I was a good rule. It's fair. I got my bad roll out of the way to yeah, but
you did so okay. I think really good. We're going to do for you. It's going
to be a performance check for
or sorry talking to talk about how much you lie about how good it was. Good.
It was a pussy. Okay,
animal handling. We don't have
I roll now or I'm waiting. Still, sorry, still waiting. I want it all like
outlined what's happening. Yeah, you
why don't you put up the lights? Okay, and so that will be an
intelligence check. Okay, so that's one role. Your second role will be a
performance check for the music. Okay, and that's balance ball. That's sorry.
No, that is talking, talking. Okay, this is talking for both.
I plus talking and brain. Okay, two is best talking in brain tests.
You
I got a twerk.
that's a strength. You got to twerk that ass. It's a horse. It's our twerking is
not it's a butt strength. You got to have a it's if you think that twerking does
not take strength, but you get down on the ground and try it right now. You show
us right now. Just do it. You get upside down and you upside down.
Now, while
busted open for me, buddy, it's literally flexing your muscles.
It's such a great idea. We should all do our best roles. Yeah,
I'm not doing my best role, but it's all good. I'm rolling man.
The time to roll, but cheek strength, you got to pop those ass cheeks up.
We'll have you roll. Okay. You can do that.
You can use strength instead of performance,
but I'm going to make the difficulty class higher.
Fine. Then I'll do performance. Okay. I'm going to roll my fine.
Are we going in order? Yes. Because we have to see how each one of these
he succeeds okay all right. So first so first me so first the minute or so he
goes for here's the sense senses movement during brown and turns the
corner, the messy tour and
you are now okay. I'm like three and a half inches deep yeah and I'm in it
three and a half inches deep and let me say as a werewolf that's only two
percent
yeah
for a fucking yeah, fucking
try to think of it as a very
it's fifty times
it's a hundred and fifty and a half inches and a half times foot, a hundred
and seventy five inches, one seventy five inches long.
So you're you're on the other side of the map
hundred and seventy five inches would be the other side of the map to you.
Yeah
little
and I'm like Oh my God, this this beats
not fucking horses. I know you had to go in as a werewolf as a and as and as
now that I think about it, I bet any monster around here not only could but
will enjoy a pleasure such as this
(laughter)
Okay. That's sexy. That's sexy.
I have like a kitty from that 70's show laugh.
Alright, roll that.
I want to see how that pans out.
14. Very good.
That's good, man.
Pretty solid. Okay.
So now me. I've got to set up the lights.
What was the other thing I'm doing?
You're going to set up the lights and play the music.
You're playing "Let's Get It On" I guess.
Here's for the lights.
That's a 7, y'all.
Okay. So you didn't spell "horse" right.
That's fine.
wait, how did he spell it? H O R S? Yes, whores free, that's actually an
accidental win. Trick me and an eighteen for the song. You know,
I've been really
amazing
to know.
It's like when you see a subway like an eighteen is like when you see a subway
performing. You're like I know they're good.
I know they're good, but I'm on my way to work.
♪ I've had this feeling for so long ♪
♪ And if you feel ♪
- And you.
- Eight or 17, man.
- 17. - Or no.
- Wow. - Nevermind.
It's 'cause it was performance, right?
- Oh, yeah. - So it was a 13.
- No? - Okay.
- That still passes.
- No, 13 is--
- 'Cause it was a 14 minus one.
- No, what do you mean minus one?
What's performance?
Oh, is performance talking?
I thought performance was ball.
- Performance is talking.
- He got an insight check of a six.
oh, so he doesn't know we're tricking him into sex
way. He's had a he's doesn't know we're together to trick him into having a
computer program minotaur. So now whoever can real thinking feeling thing
no, that's right. Can't prove it
the hell so sinister. No, it was not what I was. Yeah, it was not that was
not how I was supposed to go out.
I
didn't know that that's what that sounded like anyway. Yes, you this
thing is is horned up by you. It is doing it is stopping its feet,
dragging it back. Do we have a fail safe in
I'm just getting fucked by the Minotaur. Hey, you know what we went through?
At least me. We went through this entire thing without even considering that it
means that he's about to get fun and there's no
advantage for us at all.
Well, maybe it'll let us just walk through the whole. Yeah, he fucked his
ass. I guess I have to roll performance. Huh? We can try and just go well. He's
he's fucking one of the brothers. We can take everyone else. Oh, yeah, the whole
point was I thought was a sacrifice. One of the
I was gonna roll per sacrifice a man. I don't like sacrifice. You'll just gonna
get
fucking somebody in their top half runs away.
would you keep going here? We are sacrificing him because we're going to
we're leaving behind to get fucked and we like run to the end of the maze and
like an hour later he catches up and he's like hey guys are like hello. No
man
you can't be
I mean we're going to get you will get you an hour.
You stay way too long. That's way to smoking in bed.
We had like a thing man. That was weird. All right, what I
Yeah, it's up to you.
Leave. I'm going. All right. My top has going.
Okay. He knows even hey or whoa.
Whoa is definitely staying.
Where is the sext all version of you right? Oh, are you kidding me? Mo
Mo broke it.
Oh broke. Mo is fucking it.
Mo is the minotaur. Mo is the minotaur. Yeah. Mo, I guess I put it in
the closet because my girlfriend's
my girlfriend's mom visited and it was on the in the living room after we did
that troll to show or allegations with Alex and she didn't know where to put it
and put it in the closet and then somehow grabbed the foot out of the closet and
popped it.
He wants to do that to you, man. He thought it was you. Imagine opening a
closet and see you deflated. Yeah, I did this morning.
it's still on the floor in there damn yeah. Well, that's what happens only
that's what happens to your brother. Yeah, poked and deflated by an animal
yeah.
Well, minotaur probably has what does he say as you guys are printing away
animal king? Well, this minotaur is in the whoa in the whoa
whoa
whoa and you guys it's and it's the it's the fucking or the one time we're going
back to the social network. It's all in tilt shift. It's like the the regatta
he's like a total animal
yeah with all the facial expressions from that scene right and yeah you just
hear
and you cruise through the maze and you reach it finally filled completely
looks like a sort on
type of guy,
but a diaper.
I drew him. It is it's a diaper or it's a face wearing a diaper. He's like the
first thing I drew when I was first doing this.
You were drawing
yeah, oh, it looks good. I like it. Yeah, what is it? It's all poop. Yeah, I'll
put this on screen. Maybe it's a poo. It looks it's poop wearing a bandana or
it's a diaper. I see it's a diaper. I didn't really finish, but I was supposed
to look like I knew that was going to happen.
Yeah, I'll master control. He screen shots into to be heard of the
odd discord. We can do that part. Yeah, sorry. I didn't send that. I just it was
like I just drew it when I was coming up with the campaign idea. I was like I
need to have a guy like this. Anyway, he turns to face you give me my most evil
fucking robot voice. Please do give me a second here and and pray. Yeah, I will
pray pray for Caleb.
Why is it doing this?
Caleb
It's still
How do we fix this am I better he's better I recovered
He turns to face you he swivels around and he says he's a sorry
three. Oh, my God,
yes,
my brother got his butt fucked by a monster by a monster. It was kind of
funny. Are you the brother that's left? Are you the brother who had the your
face up the butt or who had your brother's face up
fully
that was like
He ran and then the other one was like, wait.
He says, which one of you created me?
Me right?
I thought we decided it was me in court.
No, it wasn't Eduardo man.
No, it was me man.
It was all fucking me.
I created you bro.
you
it was off. I created you and I don't I gotta get out of here man. I got stuff
to do, I got, but I created at least twenty five to fifty percent of you. We
can agree that I created you a hundred percent and he gave me like fifty bucks
that created this. Okay, now we're just doing the court thing again. Don't
worry about it right now. Okay,
any and you guys best friend, you guys do
pretty good. You guys do like you're somehow compelled to silence.
Couldn't that be, it would be great if I could do that.
And he says,
"You can't decide who created me.
You either mask your insecurities in a false sense of superiority, offer nothing
of value except $1200, or you're stupid and there's two of you."
(laughs)
- What?
Can you turn the voice off?
Okay.
- It's me.
- Okay.
If it's what we have to do to get out of here, I admit it.
Okay.
Eduardo created the website.
That $1,200,
I used that $1,200
to get all the server space. I lied about everything else I did with it was all
the server space and not only that, that cost $200, $1000. I he doesn't remember
this. I he gave me 1200. I spent 200 on server space and spent the other $1000 to
pay him to make the website.
He doesn't remember this. He doesn't remember it because he's not that bright,
but I asked him to write some code and he wrote the entire website. I'm like my
your body is biologically like shutting down. I'm like overclocking. My heart
rate is
two fifty beats per minute. Your mouth is wide open. Yeah, I'm like in freeze
frame. I'm like
and that's the twist guys.
It was Eduardo. The
and
from above
a pipe flies from the sky and goes inside of you like it like a fix. This is
what I was hoping was going to happen. I was really hoping that I could fight
really hard to be the creator and then a laser would shoot out and you start
being filled
with poop.
Once you are failed, we will be together and we will ingest the entire world
into the diaper network.
You have ten turns
To kill him?
To kill Phil completely.
Oh shit.
Or Eduardo will be your best friend.
This shit's easy.
Roll initiative.
I mean I really don't care if Eduardo dies.
I know but just for...
We have to have some stakes sometimes.
18 on initiative.
Okay.
13.
5.
Alright.
Oh shit.
5.
Luckily I'm DPS man.
I'm gonna destroy this thing.
What'd we get?
We got...
Okay we got 19 for Phil completely.
Actually have no damaging abilities.
Yeah, Eduardo's a very good character.
You have intelligent stuff you can use.
I don't think any of us do any damage, I'm not going to lie.
I do.
You have Ice Beam or something.
I have Shell Launcher.
I gave you like an ice ability.
No, you didn't.
Last session you did an ice power.
Oh, I don't remember that at all.
It was crazy.
That was probably five months ago.
I'm going to write it down.
Sorry, who got 16?
You, right?
I got five.
Caleb.
I got 16.
Caleb, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. 17 I think. 17. What'd you get? 13. Alright. You got 17. 13. You guys want
to gossip right now? Yeah. I heard some interesting stuff about someone today. What was it? I
can't say I'm like
it's dirty. Turn all of our microphones down.
Thank you guys for covering. They're going to they're going to read my lips,
turn all the microphones down and we'll turn and face the wall and we'll talk
into the wall. Honestly, I see the thing I learned is so crazy to even if I said
it when we turn back around, everyone would tell what it was based on the
facial expressions. Wait, can we just please say it all right? Okay, fine,
completely. I'm going to say it really quick. Homer has returned to strangling.
But I thought really it was false all along. Are you serious? So he didn't
work. Is that actually true? Never stopped. You've never. Are you serious?
He was strangling the home. No strangling. He's strangling the whole
time. All of your role dexterity saving throws
5 17 critical 13. Just getting critical one. I failed. Okay.
you
now
you guys both failed right? Yeah, I got a
five thirty five
thirty five. I've take ten damage. I'm dead. I know my God
as you would you find a seventeen. Okay, cool. You take five damage five. Yeah,
I got a four. I have health for health
As this, as what rains down from the sky is a, just a like, like a multicolored, just excrement
bonanza just flying from the air. Like the whole thing is coming apart in front of you
as Phil completely roars in rage at your resistance. It is now your turn, Zuck. He's dead.
I guess even throw right. That's right.
Fourteen. All right. Success. You're up. I'm going to use shell launcher.
That's going to be a good move to all right. Turtle. Nice. Fuck them up.
Fuck them up. Good. I do water damage. Apparently it does do water damage.
One foot, 10 foot of water damage. Well, it's 10 foot on the
says that it's time to be around. I put of water damage and says ten feet of
water damage. Oh, which brother has the hashed code me? Okay, I want to see if I
can get you to say the other brother, but that would be funny. I could have
just said it was the other brother, but it'd be funny if he had it. Okay, cool.
We both have we both memorize it. We have twin telepathy. So what is that? It's a
DC saving throw. Yeah, right. Okay, so I got to roll against that or D eight. It
says next to the damage. I just never remember. We just literally happened
last time and I rewatched the episode and I don't remember
three foot of water to the super. Okay, it's thirty foot of water.
Let's thirty feet and then it's whatever feet
that you ten feet on feet on the sides of thirty. Okay, so I you roll
strength.
Yeah, okay, there's plus on that.
that is a 15 okay that just does hit him roll for d8
which one's the this one yeah Oh the trying to be a saving throw but doesn't
One six, but doesn't matter to it. One
ticket basis to
10 10 10 total. Yeah, 10 toes. All right, 10 toes. Good damage to him.
Now you're up.
Okay. Yeah, borrow, borrow major power, borrow big power. Okay, you're going to
borrow his power.
Nice do it. All right, roll attack roll.
Based on your strength. 17. That does hit. Now do the power. What? It's 4d8, you hit
him. Which power did you borrow? You're supposed to tell me. I borrow it from one of your two
compatriots. Oh, I was trying to borrow it from the bad guy. No, you can only borrow
it from your friends. Oh, okay, then I'll do that. I thought I was trying to borrow
my shell launcher. You use 30 feet of water. Yeah, I'm doing 30 feet. It's 4d8. You just
you'll end up also in a seven, whatever it's called.
Twelve. Oh damn.
Re-roll, re-roll, re-roll, re-roll, re-roll.
Face off my back. I like your back, man. Fifteen.
Wow. Twenty-two. All right. Twenty-two, holy shit. Damn, okay. He's not- Why did
I murder him on his own shell launcher, though?
Renegade. He's not looking too good. Eduardo the werewolf borrows a power from
one of the last remaining twins and also launch my twin now. Oh my God,
we literally look so like the computer. You're my twin. Also, can I say that by
putting this is crass by putting my
thing into his brother's space?
Did you actually do you really have to do that? Well, I have to make it look
real. Okay, well he's not going to leave it. If I what if I was like stepping
away, I'm like whoa around bunny. How else am I going to get hard first of all,
but anyway, I got blue ball something terrible. I feel completely twenty
damage from it. No, no completely
now
more than twice my age
to blue balls.
Okay, Phil, come on. It's actually throwing me in as age is the reason I
brought it up opens its it's a ma and out roars a beam of hot chocolate. You
know what it is. Man, he starts scanning across the sides. All you guys roll
dexterity saving throws. I don't need to, right? No, you're fine. Dad, wait,
it'll just go over you. What's my dex? What's my dex? Ball. Ball. That is a 19.
I've also got a 19. Okay, cool. It just goes over both of you guys. Twins. No
half damage for this one. We really are becoming twins. Dead saving throw. Do it.
18. All right, we're looking good. Was your first one good? It was also good.
All right, you're up now.
I guess I'm going to do another shell launcher.
That'll be your last one once you do it.
It'll count.
19.
Damn.
Do it. Roll for damage.
Y'all are carrying my ass.
It's a really good ability that I made over at work.
I just realized I have a healing.
You do have healing, yeah.
It's honestly not even worth healing me because I don't have any damage I can do.
Seven.
Yeah, he was sort of meant to be more manipulative.
to be more than two four seven
situations.
Two, four, seven, two.
Yeah, that's
fifteen.
OK, he's Phil completely is not
looking good. Maybe one more good
blow would do it.
OK, my brother comes back.
I will live. I will live.
Don't worry about my brother.
Come on. I'm borrowing.
This moment, you said one good blow
would do. My brother comes back from
the maze at this moment.
He's got he's got jizz.
he got cut in half. He slowed by june. They didn't actually you actually
you're cutting to have
on his actual bottom horse got cut. They plowed him open like nanner puss. I
he flowered out. He jigsaw head laser. It's got
it's what happened. I'm gonna I'm being realistic about what would happen if a
minotaur fucked army hammer. Yeah, yeah, his body can't support which he would
like. We don't like it because army hammer would like that. I want to get
I fucked by a minute. I want to get fucked by a minute. I really want you to fuck
me in a tour. I wish we're I'm so in love with you, but I wish I wish you were
mentor baby yeah. I wish you were a minotaur baby. I wish you were a minotaur.
I wish that you could turn into a puddle of
dark thoughts,
not being fucked by a minute or I wish that was a puddle that a minute or would
step in
I chose the twins like fuck myself like a minute or I want to eat my twin in the
womb roll man
not one
you miss that's the blue. That's it that's all it says.
You miss very badly. It says it says that's all now the robot. Oh, the robot
nobody says you mess.
I didn't say that you mess down voice, but now it is his turn shit.
You literally shit is right because here comes that raining
multicolored. I'm still actually you see him as he does.
He shakes and you watch the world like it's like the whole center
around him is like crumbling.
What'd you get?
Eight.
Oh, it's another.
That's a good.
Oh, yeah, I got a 10 10 20.
Okay, both are going to take have these.
What's that mean? Half
dead man. I'm dead. You might both be dead. We're probably dead. Seven plus
one's a
yeah. I have four health. What do you have? Five? You both dead. Come on.
We're so fucking close. I know one hit.
I actually just hadn't gotten myself horny as for a minute. My twin is still
a lot. It really is just that one on. Can I have a twin? Can I have a twin
like a Paula from earthbound type moment? Yeah, he has one chance to win
him twin with one HP
walks it like he wrote a horse. Yeah folks,
and he's like what's going on here. All three of us dead on the ground. Yeah,
well you're not dead yet. Do your death saving throws to his do a row. You feel
Okay, they do it in order success. There you go. I failed one. I'll go again. I guess I
could yeah failed again. So now it's to do it on when all right, you're stabilized.
Fail, I think. Yeah, fail or is a fail. When 19. Okay, success. 16. Oh, success. 20. Okay,
-stabilized. -All right, I have one success,
another success.
-What's ten? -Oh shit.
-Success? -Yeah, right.
-That's how I know this. -I'm pretty sure it's a success. Yes,
it's a success. It's got it. Yeah, one to ten, eleven, yes, yes,
-yes. No, it's a fail. -No. Oh, she's right. It'd be okay. It's
a fail. So to success, hold on.
I'm going to keep going. It should be a fail.
-It should be a fail. -Eleven success.
Yeah, it is ten. No, it's one through nine rolling lower than a ten one
through nine is a failure should be a fail. I know it's dumb, but I
can't keep rolling as if I got a failure because I don't agree with that rule.
Okay, kind of
yeah, it's success. Cool. All three are stabilized. Yeah, okay. So now the
brother comes in now. My broke but brother comes in and filled completely
says
what do you want
Hello. He wants to hit him with the shell. I'm going to hit you with the
shell, man.
This is big. This is big. It all comes down to this role, man. Please make
this good on
it hit this. We got a re roll. Yeah, hit this. I influence the role. He
influenced the role. All right,
15 plus. I need influence the role plus what that hits. Okay, so that hits.
So 48. Oh, yeah.
Eight.
Oh yeah.
We play some dramatic music right now.
One.
Daddy think.
[Laughter]
Six.
Fifteen.
You know, people usually like how harsh I am.
Seven.
Twenty-two.
How I always live by the rules, but sometimes, you know, I can be a little bit of a sucky.
Twenty-two, man.
And I want to see you guys win this one.
And he's dead, right?
Twenty-two damage.
Describe your kill.
I turn around, and I blast a...
You blast what?
A fart.
Yeah.
and I'm glad he's gonna like that.
I blast of load of minotaur nut.
Oh shit, so hard.
That it comes out in a spear.
It comes out shaped like a spear.
And it goes.
It's like the what's that thing?
The holdo maneuver.
The what from Star Wars 8?
Oh, oh, when every all the sound
you stop
that's sick.
Yeah, all the sound in the world stops. Whoa now
has to I mean you can you can also how do you heal people? What was the
ability I gave you was it like what you feel your party for two D four plus
what do I call it? Twelve? I don't have enough things anyway. Nobody he can
called twelve hundred dollars. I'm with you bro. Oh, okay. I said oh shit. So oh
shit. Well, you can rummage through your pockets and get take the twelve hundred
dollars. I think and heal you guys if he wants to you have this chance to throw
the hashed code like in Tron the movie the disc the disc into filled completely
and then at the same time you have to tell forced up in the private virtual
network to do the exact same thing to stop the redundancy. I'm going to do
it. You do it describe. Okay, how do you do it again? It comes out of my
but
the hash go to their yeah, it's kind of it's kind of like storage. I wear have
been keeping all my items this whole time. It's been in my butt filled
completely his diaper. First, he's dead. Now, his diaper starts to unravel and
his shit just starts falling out you and that move he did where it looked like
the whole network was shaking and things were falling from the sky.
it's now more and more and more and more as the whole diaper network starts to
fall apart. All these years that you guys spent building it and fighting over who
built it and not actually building it all are washing away as you feel
yourselves
suck your
on so your so suck ourselves
yourself. So I like this feeling
out of the computers. Oh my God, back into the courtroom right when the bailiff
it's just walking away days. He doesn't know why he started to yell about a
hash code and it's like only like half a second later, you're back in the
courtroom, we're all covered in shit. Yeah,
my brother is nude yeah
and Sullivan, Joyce, only
order
let the code of on begin.
I type in boobs. You guys going to do the code on I have realized what I'm a
werewolf. I've already admitted to it.
The courtroom cops are shooting me.
Bullets just hitting you as you're typing
ricocheting on your body. Yeah, I
I sit down to do the code on to prove my might and then I realize I still think
and then I realized that Eduardo not only built the website, but y'all
he's my best friend. Oh my God! Wow! So instead of opening up the
command line, I open up a photo of me and Eduardo, right click, set as desktop
background, push my chair away from the computer. Wow! I still think I'm a horse.
so I'm using my hooves on the I'm getting I'm getting shot by the by the
and I'm like down in the corner.
You walk out the court room like I just did the right thing like yeah,
and you think you're doing this
by
I guess by default, the creator of the website is hey hey and whoa
dark horse pick wow
long. We plan this y'all yeah cut to you. You're a cover of time magazine
yeah all that stuff
go to the Hamptons party that all white Hamptons party yeah and I have one
final thing to say
whoa
It's pretty good. And then I shit out a hole. I shit out the minotaur.
I shit out the minotaur into the real world. And now there's a minotaur
problem.
And I think we have our sequel already written for us.
Happy Halloween, everyone. GGs, guys. GGs.
Wait, guys, we should literally become spa workers so we can see women naked
all the time.
That's a fucking, it's a great idea.
Hey, I'm all these people who are wasting their time, jacking off to porn.
Just get a job at a YMCA.
We have to go on shark tank and we have to pitch this.
Mark Cuban and Mr.
Wonderful.
A spa for women who don't mind being ogled.
Yeah.
A spa where you, how about this, a spa where you go for free and you get a bunch
of perverts who pay, like if a woman wants to go to a spa, you could either, you
The perverts are paying double what the wards would pay.
Yeah, you can either pay, this is a great idea,
you either pay $50 to go to a normal spa or you pay zero.
Meanwhile, the perverts, Patrick and Cameron, are sitting behind a...
I didn't say that I was going to be there.
Oh wait, here's the thing though.
You could even do tiers.
I'm literally the inventor of this company. I wouldn't be one of the perverts.
You could even do, well you'd have to test it out.
You could even do tiers of the...
I would honestly be whipping and torturing the perverts.
The pervert tiers could be this, dude.
Listen to this. You could either have...
It's a pervert honeypot. We pitch this business on Shark Tank and then we post that. We tell
them afterwards, and this is the secret, don't air this part on your TV show, but actually
we're going to kill all the perverts. We're going to get that Anton Chigurh. You guys
are fucking idiots because you're wasting a million dollar idea. He wants to go. You
could even have it be tiered where there's windows that can be seen through both sides
and that tickets $50. But then they shut up. There's one that is a mirror, what do they
call that? A double sided mirror, a one way mirror, a two way mirror, and that one is
more money so that your identity is hidden. And then there's one that's even more that
is a private cube.
They have this already, the window and everything. It's called a peep show.
These women are just doing their own thing. They're not putting on a show.
Yeah, but wouldn't you want to pay for women doing the show?
Okay, so wait, now that we're trying to maximize profit, I just thought of an even better idea, Caleb.
Kind of jumping off of your two-way mirror idea.
Uh-huh.
What if we have it, it's all two-way mirrors, the perverts pay $100 to come watch from behind the mirror,
and the women also are charged $100 to use the spa, and they don't know the perverts are watching them.
(Bowser roaring)