Lying. Backstabbing. Arson. A fall from grace. A dark secret. A comedy scene torn
asunder. March 31st, 2020. There was one name on everyone's lips. Greg Peppers. The day
before, nobody had even heard of him. What drove this middling open mic
comedian to the top of Twitter's trending page alongside topics like Jason Lee and
Happy Birthday Kaden. Why do some claim he's the devil or El Diablo? What did he
do that dark winter's night? Before we answer any of those questions though we
have to tell the story from the beginning. But that's easier said than
than done. This is the Greg Pappas story.
Welcome to a very special episode of podcast about list. Yeah very special
edition. Today we do a deep dive on the life and times and crimes. Yeah mostly
of Greg Peppers, one of the most notorious
Boston stand-up comedians of all time.
Yeah.
What a story we got for you today.
It's gonna be insane.
Yeah.
Basically, we're just gonna tell you the story
as it stands now, everything's subject to change.
We have--
That's the nature of journalism.
We have a bunch of interviews
with some people from his life,
and some audio that's been recovered
from the scene and such and such.
- We won't tell you what the scene is yet.
- Yeah, you gotta listen to the end.
- We'll get there.
- You gotta listen.
- It's gonna be a wild ride.
- So let's just start at the beginning, right?
- Yeah, childhood.
- Greg's childhood.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Greg Peppers was born in Hampton Beach, New Hampshire,
to parents Mark Peppers and Nicolette Peppers-Rodmina.
Nobody is quite sure what year he was born,
and Greg, a pathological liar,
gives a different age every time he's asked, ranging anywhere from 50 to 70.
He has a younger brother, Walter "Brother" Peppers, but we'll talk more about him later.
Greg Peppers had a tumultuous and interesting childhood that was pretty well documented
thanks to newspaper articles, neighborhood anecdotes, and his late mother's diary, which
we've gained access to.
So let's talk about what Greg was like growing up.
What do you guys think about that?
Yeah, um, what was Greg like growing up?
know he's a mysterious figure with a lot of our records from Greg or on Greg's
childhood come from posts that he made on the website ebaumsworld yeah the
early 2000s sort of a precursor to the chive mm-hmm he had a lot of he also had
a he had a very very well documented very like he updated it often it was a
Geocities website that he had. It was actually dedicated to the
character Tifa Lockhart from Final Fantasy 7. It was called
gregpeppers.tifalockhartboobs.sunsetstrip.geocities.com.
Yeah, he has a lot of posts on there that are really enlightening as to his state
of mind growing up. Yeah, it's really interesting kind of combing through his
web history because much like Adolf Hitler he was an artist before anything
else and it turns out we've discovered that he was actually the guy who made
the realistic Homer Simpson picture. Oh wow. Well actually I didn't see that.
Oh yeah my team of sleuths discovered that and he actually he was he served as
the inspiration for the realistic Marge Simpson picture. I walked around his
neighborhood in Hampton Beach just to kind of get a feel for like where he was
living and I talked to some families and I met this guy who knew him growing up, this
guy Tyler Abu Dhabi.
And he had some really interesting stories to tell about the games they used to play.
They used to play this game called Find the Guy.
Yeah.
Find the Guy.
What did they...
Find the Guy?
No, I have no idea what that is.
I actually went to Hampton Beach a lot as a child.
I think the guy that they're talking about is, well as you know, Hampton Beach, 311 does
come around there a lot.
They do play a lot of shows on Hampton Beach.
I think the guy that they're talking about is actually the bassist from 311, Peanut.
It is.
That actually is what Tyler at Bobby told me.
Okay.
All right.
Wow.
Yeah.
They would run around and try to find Peanut.
When they found him, they went, "There's the guy."
And you don't even want to guess what happened next.
Yeah, you could tell who Peanut was by his tattoos.
He had a very, on his calf, he has a very large tattoo of Mr. Peanut, the planter's peanut.
Wow.
Yeah, it's actually, it's very detailed.
It's actually more detailed than, I think he actually used an older image.
Wait, so is that where Greg Peppers got the idea for his Fry Guy tattoo on his leg?
The McDonald's Fry Guy, do you think?
Maybe inspired by Peanut?
Oh my god.
Oh, I thought it was Frylock from Oppertine Hunger Force.
Oh, okay.
He has Fry Guy on one leg and Frylock on the other.
He has one of the McDonald's.
And he has Fry from Futurama on his chest, I think.
He has a lot of tattoos of just various people named Fry on his body.
very strange very strange very strange man yeah I know we're sort of putting
together the puzzle of his life yeah no that's that's the thing about this guy
you you start like talking about him you start to asking people about his life
you can just kind of like piece together other things about something that I
found really interesting was through sort of contacting his old classmates and
and just old school friends I found out that you remember those books sideways
stories from Wayside School. Yeah. Uh-huh. So it turns out Greg Peppers went to
the Wayside School. Oh my god. Oh wow. Yeah, the one with the missing
11th floor. Yeah. And they had the teacher that turned the kids into
apples. Yeah, the teacher that turned the kids into apples. Mrs. Gorf. Yeah, it's again just sort of
like I think when you're talking about these
sort of criminal entities like the Menendez brothers or Casey Anthony or
Greg Peppers you you you start to sort of I don't want to say empathize but the
more that you learn about where they came from yeah the more you can understand
sort of how the math adds up absolutely okay okay here's a guy went to wayside
school you know here's a guy who his first crush was Nala from the Lion King
and here's a guy whose second crush was the girl hyena from the Lion King and
maybe that's why he ended up you know the way he did. Yeah no I mean actually you
can draw a really clear line like you look at like oh he went to a sideways
school and that could be a big reason for his infamously sideways penis that
yeah many people do talk about. Yeah his penis is like a burrito taped to a
And I actually I actually I learned a lot through his chatter bait that he
Actually, he what he does is he takes a magnet and he puts it into the neomodium magnet
And he puts it into the in his meatus and he actually takes another stronger magnet and puts it at the bottom
Towards his kneecaps and he just kind of yeah, he lets it hangs. He lets it hang and he comes that way
It's he's really a fascinating guy. Yeah. He's also a bit of an amateur scientist. Yeah
Yeah, he loves chemicals and magnets and materials
Yeah, Greg Peppers and his dark material. Yes. I think I actually have a line here from his mother's diary right here
Oh, oh, yeah
Mother's diary it was actually it was at a it was at a Salvation Army. Yeah strange
Yeah, yeah, it was in it was in an old an old box for some Jordan 11 space jams
Yeah, and they were behind the counter. We were just trying to buy a pair of Jordan 11 space. Yeah. Yeah the originals
So yeah, I do have a line
Kind of that refers to his his addiction to science
And I mean I figure I I don't really know what her voice would have sounded like but I can do as faithful a recreation
As possible I suppose
Yeah
Greg was playing with his science set today
That kid is such a fucking freak. I hate him so much
So that kind of is provides a little background maybe to
Uh-huh. Yeah again again. It's it's it's making me feel you know
I do sort of empathize with him. You know you yeah, you think that you can't empathize with somebody this like
You know just just this is just abjectly evil
But his his mother goes on to say um
Today he mixed together some strange chemical that filled the entire house with a green cloud and when I woke up it was the next week
That's pretty good a pretty interesting event
He actually came up he it's one of the biggest scientific breakthroughs in modern history
But it was wrongly attributed to a different scientist, but he actually came up with the big green cloud
Yeah, and you know I I do
I do think that, I don't know if you guys,
I mean, I don't know how many mics you guys went to with him,
but he did say that he invented the big green cloud
to me in passing, and I just, I kind of wrote it off
as just another one of his lies.
I do think, I think he had a bit about that on stage.
He did, his big green cloud bit.
Yeah.
Yeah, but he did it in the context of, you know,
slipping a big green cloud into a woman's drink.
So it's much--
Which was what he was trying to invent.
Which is what he was trying, he successfully,
little did he know there's tons of sort of medical uses
for the big green cloud as an anesthetic.
He, again, everything that he does, he uses it for evil.
What's happening forum?
Probably get his dad on the line.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, we should probably call, I mean, we have,
his dad's been on the call the whole time.
His dad's basically just been waiting to talk.
Oh yeah.
Cameron is he had to leave to go
watch a movie but
Mr. Mr. Peppers, is that you - are we correct? Are you on the line? Colleen Peppers? Is that you? Hello? Yeah, that's me
Colleen what am I reading? Am I saying that correctly or is it Colin? It's more as a Colleen. It's more. It's mark
Okay, then. Okay. So great. Yeah. Wow. Yeah another one of another one of Greg's lies
Well, you know, that's just kind of how the boy was in many ways
Can I ask you one question just right off the top?
Caleb and I Caleb Cameron and I
We all thought he was somewhere between the ages of 60 to 85
I do can you yeah, can you clarify his exact age? Oh Greg? Oh, let's see. He was born in
1994 so that would make 94
2694 we're talking about
we're talking about Greg Peppers in Boston?
Greg Peppers who fought-
Hampton Beach?
Yes, Greg Peppers from Hampton Beach who fought in Desert Storm.
26 years old.
20- holy shit.
So he's 26 years old?
He's an old looking little boy.
Does he have mesothelioma? What the fuck is wrong with him?
He just looks like that. I don't know what to tell you guys.
Is it something he does with his hair?
I don't think he does anything with his hair. I don't think he's touched his hair his entire life.
Is it like a Benjamin Button type thing?
But with a horn he looks like Steve Bannon.
Oh, Steve Bannon. Now there's a real gentleman.
Oh, you're a big Steve Bannon fan?
No, I just think he's a real gentleman.
You just think he's a good guy?
No, just a gentleman.
So he's not a good guy, but he's a gentleman.
He has manners. I understand that. He does just know how to wear a suit.
He knows what he's doing, but only in a gentleman, in a manner, in an etiquette fashion.
So can you tell us a little bit about what was it like having Greg in the home growing up?
Well, it was taxing.
Absolutely, it was very taxing. He was always doing his experiments. I remember there was this one thing he did where he actually created this
just gigantic green cloud that
Seemed to all the green cloud. Okay. Okay. You guys have heard of the green cloud. Oh, he's told us. He's told us. Yeah
Yeah, he's never stopped talking about it. Oh, yeah
My mental faculties never returned to what they were before the day that he created that green cloud
So did you did you sound like this before the green cloud? No, I used to say where are you from?
I'm from Hampton Beach. I was born in the same hospital as Greg
Really? Because you sound like you're from whatever house Hank Hill grew up in.
Yeah.
Yeah, that was the Green Cloud. I was actually watching King of the Hill when the cloud hit me and it kind of melded
our brains together. My brain into a cartoon's brain, in a way.
Gotcha, okay. So that's why you have
what I would describe as medically Hank Hill characteristics.
Hank Syndrome. It's a documented kind of condition.
So I was the first and second case.
Oh, it happened again?
They cured it?
They cured it and it happened again?
It happened again and it kind of layered on top of the first time.
So the first Hank Syndrome compounded with the second.
The first one made me sound like Hank Hill and the second one made me look like a cartoon
now.
I don't have my video on because I'm two dimensional.
Because you'd need a piece of paper.
I'd need a piece of paper.
So you need a piece of paper behind you to be visible or else you're sort of in a flat
world plane?
You're kind of like Flat Stanley.
That's true.
Is what I'm getting.
No.
You're nothing like Flat Stanley.
No, because Flat Stanley has photos of him.
Flat Stanley is a book and cartoons are different from books, yes.
That's correct.
I feel like we're getting a little off topic.
We told you to talk about Greg.
Yeah, we talked about Greg and Greg's comedy career.
Now, did he do, so you hear stories about Jim Carrey,
you hear stories about Andy Dick growing up
in their house as children, and they would do,
they would do just crazy, crazy things.
Did Greg, what did Greg do as a child?
What was Greg's thing?
- Oh, well, his main comedic styling, I suppose,
was flatulence in a--
- Oh, yeah, oh, that makes sense.
That is definitely consistent with what we've learned about him.
He would do this thing where he would run into your bedroom, or at least my bedroom, I don't
know about you guys, but he would fart on you and you would actually fall right the
hell over.
But yeah, he would do the fart.
You know, he did this one prank where he would go down to the kitchen in the middle of the
night and he would open up the refrigerator, he would fart into the refrigerator and close
it, trapping the fart.
So when you woke up in the morning to get breakfast, you would open the refrigerator, the fart
would fly out, hit you.
Oh wow.
It would fly out, I've heard of this, it flies out like Slimer from Ghostbusters and it attacks
you.
Yeah, so I have one question for you.
Do you, I don't know exactly how to put this Mr. Peppers.
And again, this is your son, if you feel uncomfortable at any questions that we're asking.
Naturally, naturally.
But do you love Greg?
- Oh God, I would have to say no,
not at all, not even a little bit.
I mean, I really just--
- Thank God.
- The question there--
- Oh my God, wow.
- The only reason--
- I have been walking on eggshells.
- The only reason I hesitated with answering that one,
yeah, I just didn't know whether how,
I felt like I should pause at least a little bit before saying no.
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, it's radio.
You gotta ham it up a little bit.
Yeah, exactly.
Well, Mr. Peppers, it's been a pleasure talking to you.
Yeah, thank you so much.
Thank you so much for calling in.
Absolutely.
I would take any opportunity I could get to slander that awful...
You can call him a monkey.
All right, well, thank you again.
Thank you so much, Mr. Peppers.
Talk to you next time.
Will do, boys.
So that was that was that was mr. Peppers mark peppers mr. Mark peppers
Hey guys, I just finished watching the Lord of the Rings
extended
Fellowship of the ring. What did I miss? Hey?
Okay, it turns out his name was not Colleen peppers. Like we thought what was it? I told you was Colin dude
No, it was actually just mark. Oh
Yeah, yeah, I think it was maybe it was a Gaelic spelling or something. Yeah. Oh, you know those Irish. They're crazy
Yeah, they always fuck it up. What's happening for him? He also claimed that he was radicalized on the side of
Nikola Tesla against Thomas Edison without ever having read the oatmeal
Really? Wow. Yeah, that's impressive. I mean that's the mark of a true scientist
He claimed to have independently come to that point of view without ever having read the oatmeal
Yeah, I heard he knew all about the different color spectrums that a mantis shrimp was able to see
Mm-hmm, and he without even reading a single webcomic in his life
And I heard he could also make snarky jokes about the periodic table without even looking at XKCD
I heard I heard that he knew that George Bush loved oil before Rita ever reading a power-up comic
Yeah, and I heard he knew who spongebob was without watching the show and that's one that really blew my knee actually
He told me that he knew about six
Retards who were secret geniuses without having ever read crack calm
Really yeah, yeah
He independently came up with a list of six and he never, he said he didn't.
I said crack.com and he said I was always more of a Mad Magazine guy.
In addition to live interviews with people close to the situation, we've also acquired
witness testimony from two local comedians.
Thomas O'Shea.
My name's Tom O'Shea, I'm a Boston comedian.
And an unnamed female comedian.
My name is Jessie Rego and I am a former Boston comic.
Their stories help us piece together what it was like to perform alongside Greg in the Boston comedy scene.
So I used to host this women's night called Hilarious.
I host an open mic every Wednesdays, Mouya burgers, fries and shakes, maybe you've heard
of it, I don't know, you know, not a big deal, kind of a big deal, I didn't say it, you said
it, that type of stuff.
It was only supposed to be women comedians, but Greg showed up and watched all of the comedians
with binoculars.
At some point during the mic, he took out a laser pointer and started drawing figure eights
on my chest while I was performing.
In the middle of my set, he just starts pointing a laser pointer directly in my eye and starts
shouting like, "Time's up, time's up."
Like he's fucking Harvey Weinstein shit or whatever.
When I was about to introduce the last comedian of the night, Greg rushed the stage.
he runs on stage in the middle of my set
and he grabs the microphone and starts doing his fucking act
grabbed the microphone, said "school sucks"
and to top it all off, the cherry on the fucking sundae
is that I'm standing there and he's doing his act
and as he's doing it, he rips fucking ass
right in my face, it was so fucking hot, I like fell over
then farted on me and I fell over
I don't know if he shot at himself, like put a little poo-poo in there
and you know, honestly, like part of me was fucking rip shit
because I was there to work out some new killer,
you know, child support bits about my fucking bitch wife.
And I got fucking upstage, but,
you know, if I'm being completely truthful,
Peppa's fucking killed that night.
People were fucking falling out of their chairs, laughing.
Every single fucking person there was dying.
Greg killed that night.
And I didn't.
So we actually have on the line right now.
Hey, I gotta go.
I gotta go to the movies real quick.
I was in the middle of announcing.
All right.
No, I know.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I just I really got to go to the movies.
What do you want movies?
I mean, we're on like, the beach movie.
The beach movie.
I'm going to go to the beach movie.
I'm going to go to the movie.
Alright, bye Pat.
See you man.
I hate Patrick.
So yeah, on the line right now we have Greg Pepper's high school metal shop teacher.
I believe his name was, what was it again?
My name is Daniel Delesbo.
Daniel Delesbo.
How you doing Daniel?
How you doing Mr. Delesbo?
I'm doing pretty good, how are you doing?
Pretty good.
Yeah, so what years of school were you Greg's teacher?
I was Greg's teacher for one month.
He had to take him out of my classroom.
He was very, very disruptive.
On the first day of class, he took a piece of rebar
and he hit a Chinese kid in the head with it.
And it was very bad.
Wow, interesting.
- You said, what kind of class was this again?
- This was a metals class.
- Metal, metals.
So it was a metals class? - Metalurgy.
- Metalurgy class. - Metal shop.
- It was like wood shop, but with metal.
- So you guys, do you make,
what kind of stuff do you make in this class?
- You know, we do a lot of iron casts.
We do our, well, aluminum casts.
- What was your experience with Greg?
What, first day of class,
what was your first impression of Greg?
- I already told you, first day of class,
Greg hit that kid over the head with a piece of rebar.
Yeah, Chinese kid.
Yeah, he hit the only, the school's only Chinese kid.
And what was that child's name?
His name was Michael Kwan.
Second day of class, so I mean, right off the bat,
Greg showed me that he was not mature enough
to be in the class, but you know, I told,
I said, I'm gonna give this kid a second chance.
Second day of class, Greg pulls out
a big piece of sheet metal,
And I see him, he's got one of those big Sharpies,
he's pulling it out, and he's drawing what looks like
the Buster Sword from Final Fantasy VII.
- I know it well.
- Yeah, and so he took a Sharpie, drew a Buster Sword
out of a piece of 24 by 24 sheet metal, cut it out,
and well, I mean, it wasn't sharp enough, thank God,
but he did poke my ass with it,
and it did break skin.
- Oh my God.
- So Greg in your class, he made a big sword
and he poked your ass with it?
- Greg poked my ass with a big sword
and to this day, feels like I got two assholes.
- My God, interesting.
- He went up on me like they did to Gaddafi.
- So he Moammar Gaddafi'd you?
- Yeah, he was watching a lot of Tosh.0 at the time
and he did do the Daniel Tosh viral Gaddafi prank.
- Yeah.
Just a terrible, terrible child.
I did tell him his mom should have aborted him
and I did get in a lot of trouble for that,
but just the worst student I've ever had.
- The teacher said his mom should have had an abortion?
- Mm-hmm, he would storm into the classroom
like his name was El Nino while he was hanging out
drinking in the back of his El Camino.
That's what he did.
- And this is when he was a kid?
- This is when he was 14.
- Interesting.
- He was a skid.
No one in the class knew his name until day two.
- Till day two?
- Uh-huh.
- We got, we're getting reports.
Hold on, I'm getting a report in my earpiece right now
that he actually crashed his own house party
because nobody came.
- Oh my God.
- Is that true?
Is that a true, does that sound like him?
- I'm one of the teachers at the school, I can't confirm,
but that sounds like him.
That sounds like some nerd shit he would do.
- Yeah.
- And look, I love all my students.
- Just the one student I've never been able to connect with
was Greg Peppers.
- Did you ever, did you punish him?
- I believe I did.
- Was this at the Wayside School?
- This was at the Wayside School, yes.
- And corporal punishment is allowed at Wayside School?
- It was allowed, I did punish him by welding the zipper
on his pants shut so he couldn't go pee in the bathroom.
- Well, yeah, I suppose he could still go pee.
- Oh, he could pee in his pants, that's what he could do.
- So what was the last straw?
What you said, he was in your class for a month.
- You know, first month of class,
everything's going fine and we had the hangups
the first two days.
The first two days were a mess, I'll say that.
I'll say that, the first two days were a mess.
- And it was fine after that?
- Fine after that until day--
- Smooth sailing.
- Day 29.
Day 29.
- What month was this?
- This was February.
- February.
- February, okay.
And you know, day 29, Greg,
I finally see what he's been working on.
And it is an aluminum cast sculpture
of him fucking my wife.
Wow.
Mm-hmm.
I don't know where he found a photo of my wife.
And that's a large, was it life-size?
It was life-size and I did respect it.
However, you do not use my tools
to fuck my wife in metal.
I mean, do you ever think that maybe he didn't,
Maybe it wasn't from a photo that he got the reference?
No.
Oh, okay. Did you ever think
that maybe Greg became all too familiar
with your wife's body and maybe he didn't even need a cast?
I mean, it wouldn't surprise me at this point in my life.
It wouldn't surprise,
are you and your wife still together?
Yeah, I don't know where she is.
You're together but you don't know where she is?
Nope.
Okay.
Legally, we're together.
Yeah, but she's been gone for how long now?
Uhhhh...
Three hours.
She's been gone...
Oh, okay.
She's been gone for three hours.
Yeah.
And you don't...
And you're not sure that she'll ever come back?
No.
What was the last thing she said before she left?
I'm going to the store.
Oh, okay.
It has been three hours.
How far away is the store?
About 20 minutes.
okay i think you have reason to believe that she might be gone for i mean you
know
well
uh...
she's back
i don't think i don't know happy for him and those of those one
as close you must last year why if did the another and i was here could you
call it a real quick and ask if she ever are the came in time it with great
answers and i really don't know
now when she gets back from the store she needs
she needs to glide down for at least
three hours. Can you wake her? Why? Does she have some sort of medical condition?
Let's just talk about Greg. When is the last time you saw Greg?
Day before graduation and he handed me an envelope
I said "Fuck you" and I've never said that to a student before
but I looked him in the eyes I put my finger in his chest and I
poked harder than I've ever poked and I said "Fuck you Greg Peppers"
and I took the envelope out of his hand and I left it in my desk drawer and I
I haven't opened it since.
You wanna pull that out for us?
Alright, I'm gonna open it right now.
Oh!
Jesus.
What is it?
It's a picture of a horse's ass.
Fuck.
And he's fucking the horse's ass.
Greg is?
Greg is having sex with the horse's ass?
Greg gave you a picture of him fucking a horse's ass?
Jesus.
It's my wife's mare!
So you, okay, so you have a horse.
- There's a photo of Greg Peppers fucking my wife's mare.
- Wow.
- Do you still have this horse?
- Yeah, it's in the garage.
- What are you gonna do with it?
- It's in the garage?
- Uh-huh.
- Why?
- It's in the garage.
- Is it okay in there?
- Yeah, I live in a condo.
I can't, I don't have the proper stable.
- We don't, so one last question.
Ed, do you, has, I don't really know how to put this
without kind of leading you to the answer that I want.
Has Greg ever made you fall over?
- Oh boy.
Okay, so I think there's something I didn't wanna talk about
but I mean, it did happen,
so I feel I should, feel as though I should talk about it.
- Please do, yeah.
- He took the welding torch
and he held it up to his hind end
and he let out a fart so, so big.
Knocked me over and that's why I don't have eyebrows.
- All right, thank you, Mr. DeLesbo.
- Thank you, Mr. DeLesbo.
- Thank you so much for your time.
Hey guys, I just got back from the beach movie.
Oh man, how was it?
Was that a 17 minute movie?
So how'd the call with the gym teacher or whatever go?
I think Greg fucked his wife.
And his wife's horse.
And his horse lives in a garage?
That's crazy.
That's a triple whammy if you ask me.
Fucked his wife, fucked his wife's horse, and the horse lives in a garage.
Yeah where's the wife live?
The garage.
The garage?
The wife lives in the stable.
- Whoa, yeah, that's how it should work.
My wife's in the stable, my horse is in the garage.
- The garage, and I'm in the living room,
and I got a 50 inch curved TV,
and I'm watching Family Guy.
- I'm in the living room, I'm watching Wheel of Fortune,
and I'm yelling the answers out to myself.
- And I'm grilling in the living room.
- I brought my George Foreman into the living room
just so I could feel.
- And I'm fishing in the damn bathtub.
- Just so I could touch some hot meat.
- I got a grill chimney full of hot charcoals,
and i'm throwing it on my wife's rug and i'm coughing and the room is filling with smoke
and i'm passing out.
okay so this is actually really exciting we sent a letter by snail mail to uh...
walter brother peppers, greg pepper's brother who i believe has been living off the
grid for quite a while and nobody's really been able to get in contact with
him but we got him to respond to this letter and we got a... he actually
used his personal tape recorder and sent us a tape of like a statement. yeah i heard
I heard that Walter Brother Peppers is living in the charred remains of Gigi Island's home
in Littleton, New Hampshire.
That's also what I heard and that's where I sent the letter to contact him.
Yeah, it was mostly just a guess and then we got something back.
I mean, am I crazy or is that like the wettest envelope you've ever touched?
It was yellow and it was wet.
It smells like a marker.
But it wasn't like, it was too viscous to be piss.
Yeah, no, it's some substance.
I don't know.
Might have been polenta.
Alright, well let's pop this bad boy in and see what Brother Peppers has to say.
I remember the first time I saw my brother, Greg Peppers.
I was a baby, as was he.
I looked at him, he was breakdancing.
I said, "Damn, this white boy crazy as hell."
And I'll never forget that one time when that one crazy white boy killed a Chinese dude with a brick.
Yeah, I remember the day like it was yesterday. We were walking through the town looking for a bite.
For all my other folks not familiar with the term, by that I mean we were looking for a restaurant
at which we could obtain a meal.
Now Greg Peppers ain't eat his meals like a regular motherfucker, no.
He'd go,
and he'd eat the whole goddamn meal
with a loaded pistol.
He'd pull the pistol out,
he'd sprinkle some,
you know, some ground beef, things of that nature,
on the pistol,
and then he'd suck the tip of the pistol like a penis.
And that's just the type of motherfucker he was.
But anyway,
we were at this restaurant.
This Chinese restaurant,
to be specific.
Not related to the
story at hand,
it just happened to be a Chinese restaurant.
And this motherfucker Greg
happened to be
eating a meal
In his standard fashion, he was sucking the noodles off a pistol like it was a grown man's
penis.
And this dude came up to him, who happened to be Chinese.
Now did he work there?
That's not something you can assume from the given story.
There's a lot of ways to look at it.
He said he said to Greg and I am quoting him here. I'm not using any sort of accent
He said to Greg peppers. He said
And that motherfucking Greg, you know, he wasn't gonna take no disrespect like that
You know Greg came through with that pistol and I'm not talking about the one he sucked off like a penis for all his meals
Nah, he came through with that shoddy too and he pulled it out and in the stock of it. What did he have?
but a brick
signed by none other than Mark Wahlberg
He pulled that motherfucker out and he just started bashing and bashing and he fucking he kept bashing and bashing
BASHING AND BASHING AND THERE WAS FUCKING BUD EVERYWHERE YOU CAN SEE IT ALL OVER THE FUCKING RESTAURANT
AND EVERYBODY SCREAMING EVERYBODY SCREAMING OH NO NO YOU GOTTA STOP HIM YOU GOTTA STOP HIM YOU CAN'T LET IT HAPPEN
YOU CAN'T LET IT HAPPEN
And I let it happen. That's my brother. I'm not gonna stop him. But anyway, so he finished his meal, right?
And I'm looking I'm waiting for the police to come right now. I'm saying red peppers
What are we gonna do?
And then he farted on me and I fell over.
Okay I don't know what the fuck that was about.
Yeah that um.
I'm almost certain that was not, that guy had no relation to Greg.
Yeah I think that.
I think he read the letter and then just kind of.
Kind of made something up.
Yeah.
Fuck that I feel really stupid for playing that on the show. That was kind of me too. I'm not sure I want to associate with
Geez, yeah, I'm bummed that we're recording this whole thing live. Yeah. Yeah
So we can't make any edits. Yeah, there's no way
Yeah, it's like Jimmy. Um, yeah, you know, I'm actually I think I'm gonna send an anonymous tip to the police about that guy's cabin
I just what are you even gonna say? I just say there's a I don't know. I'm gonna send them that say
- Hey, a guy was extremely weird.
- Tell them that that's Gigi Allen's old house.
They'll get over there with the friggin' hazmat team.
- Yeah, they'll go Waco on Gigi Allen's old house.
- They'll go scrub that shit, all the poop off the walls.
- Yeah, I'm gonna have the ATF go Waco on Gigi Allen's widow.
- They're gonna send a damn ATAT.
- Yeah.
- They're gonna send the--
- They're gonna send Judge Dredd and Robocop
joined at the hip baby.
- They're gonna send-- - Siamese robots.
- They're gonna send a tank man
from the Tiananmen Square massacre
because he's the only thing stronger than a tank.
- Yeah, he-- - Have you guys ever
been to his apartment?
- He has this apartment in East Boston.
- Or had.
- He had this apartment. - Yeah, had.
- Yeah, yeah, it was underneath a Mexican grocery store
And I go in one day because he was buying weed for me
'cause he's very easy to rip off.
And I asked if I could use his bathroom
and I went into the bathroom and I lifted the toilet seat
and it was a full koi pond
in the toilet bowl.
- And did you go? - Really?
Yeah, what happened?
- Yeah, I went in, yeah.
Where else am I supposed to go?
I mean you could have got you want me to go in the sink. There was another toy pond in the sink and the bathtub I
Can't had he had that many. How can he afford? I mean and then when I walked out I said hey I was like hey
From what I remember he worked at Subway. I don't know how he could afford that many koi fish. I'm sure they just swam up
Yeah, well, that's possible
Yeah, and then I sold him a gram for
$260 oh that was the best. I mean the best thing I ever did was I sold
one Adderall pill to him for $300.
- Yeah, yeah.
I remember he came up to me at a mic and he was like,
"I'm about to fucking crush tonight."
And I was like, "Why?"
And he was like, "Have you seen Limitless?"
And I said, "No."
And he was like, "Okay, that makes this
"really hard to explain then."
And then he walked away and he just ate shit on stage.
- Yeah, I sold him, I picked grass off the ground
and he was standing right next to me, he saw me do it
and he bought it off me for $500.
- Damn. - Wow.
- Told him it was a joint, I didn't even put it in anything,
it was literally just blades of grass
in the palm of my hand.
He tried to smoke it. - I talked to one
of his childhood friends and he said that he,
when they would walk around their neighborhood,
he was the kid who would always eat the berries
that nobody knew what they were
that were growing on bushes and stuff.
- I mean, that's a scientist behavior.
You know, you have to investigate and stuff.
- You're right, I guess he is, he's testing the hypothesis,
are, will these berries kill me?
I did one time, I sold him an ounce of nutmeg
rolled in a post-it note.
What did you say it was?
Oh, I told him straight up,
it's just nutmeg in a post-it note.
(laughing)
How much did he pay for it?
He paid 250 bucks.
So now on the line we have, I believe,
Greg's old coworker from Subway, where he used to work.
Wait, wait, before we interview this guy,
I gotta pop out, I just, I'm gonna go see a movie.
Oh, what movie?
Okay, man, what movie?
Where he's dancing.
I'm gonna go see, "Hateful Eight,"
but just the first part.
Just the first half?
Yeah, just the first part before the intermission.
I think that's like--
But it does have the, we're gonna watch the first part
and then have the intermission and then leave.
- Okay. - Yeah.
- Oh, okay. - That sounds good to me.
- All right, bye you guys.
- Have fun, man. - All right, yeah.
See you in a bit.
Yeah, so we have Danny from Subway.
- Hey! - Oh, hey, Danny.
- This is the Subway at,
which Subway did you work at with Greg?
- We worked at the Subway on Tremont Street.
Come give us a visit.
- Okay, so when did Greg Pepper start working
at Subway with you, Danny?
Probably about a year and a half ago.
He said that he worked at Subway for 20 years.
Yeah, he told me he'd been working at Subway for 50 years.
Oh no, no, no.
He worked there for six months tops.
Really?
Yeah, see I was his assistant manager
and we had this total bitch of a manager, Carly.
She was a real bitch about when we would bring home
the ingredients, she would get real mad.
And she just got fed up with him.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, she always had it out for Greg because he could never remember what BMT stood for.
Really?
Yeah, he-
What does- what does BMT stand for?
Bacon...
Um...
Meat...
Okay.
And turkey.
Yeah.
That sounds delicious.
But he would tell-
Oh, that sounds very good.
He would sometimes just tell people it was what you call the guys in the ambulance.
Oh, okay.
Didn't people wouldn't order it after he told them that?
Well he would say it was named after them because they were the real heroes of the world.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Okay.
Uh huh.
How was it working with him?
Honestly he was like the perfect guy for me to work with because he loved having a good
time.
Yeah.
Yeah, like sometimes we would put all the ham on our face,
uh, like that one episode of, uh, The Office.
Uh-huh.
With Dwight.
And we would do that.
I remember that one.
Yeah, and we would do that.
I remember that episode with Dwight.
Yeah, and we would do that Dwight face to each other.
That's pretty cool.
Sounds pretty fun.
We thought it was pretty funny.
So, Greg, uh, how did Greg interact with, uh, how was he with customers?
He was incredible with customers.
He was like the king.
Really?
Yeah, he was like the king of movie trivia.
Yeah?
Yeah, the customers would try to order, you know, like Italian herbs and cheese with tuna
and he would be like, "Did you know that one of the midgets from Wizard of Oz killed themselves
on set?"
Wow.
And I would be in the back trying to toast the bread and I would get so distracted by
his facts that I couldn't even toast it anymore.
You couldn't toast it?
No, I'd get so distracted.
Like I was saying, he was a great employee in my opinion.
Obviously Carly disagreed.
But he always- Who's Carly?
Carly was our manager.
Go further into Carly.
Carly was your manager, but specifically what about Carly was so bad?
She was mostly just like a stupid bitch.
The only cool thing is she had some really cool tattoos.
She had on her back, she had sophisticated ignorance written in cursive on her back,
which I thought was pretty cool.
- When did you see her back?
- When I had sex with her doggie style in the ass.
- Oh, cool.
Good for you, man. - Congrats, man.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- We were together for a little bit.
It's not a humongous deal,
but we had sex a humongous amount of times.
- Did you ever put your dick in a bread roll
and give it to her as a sub?
- That was basically all we did.
- Oh, okay. - Yeah.
And I started calling her my girlfriend from that,
but she said that I was just the meat
between the buns on her sandwiches.
- That sucks, man, I'm sorry.
- Yeah, it was one of the most heartbreaking things ever,
and that's why I appreciated Greg so much,
because he was there for me in that trying time.
- Is there any reason why Greg stopped working at the subway?
- Yeah, apparently he gave away over $25,000 in BLTs
to uh... to uh... boston police department
yet but when he got fired he was really torn up and uh... he can't he said hey
come over man like we got a
like i'm i can't be alone right now and maybe i'll do something insane
and i was like him and for sure so i brought like my fifteen favorite dvds i
have burned on my favorite clips of dennis miller
and i came over his house and i've pop those things in the p_s_ three that we
only use for dvds
and we watched those things and we howled at the moon.
- You howled at the moon?
- Yeah, 'cause we was laughing so hard.
- You and Greg are big Dennis Miller fans.
I think Greg was heavily--
- Dennis Miller is the king!
- I think Greg was heavily influenced
by Dennis Miller and his comedy.
- Yeah, did you ever see Greg do comedy?
- Did you ever do mics with Greg?
- I mean, I knew he was a funny guy,
but I honestly never knew he did comedy 'til right now.
- Really? - Oh.
Although I guess that makes sense,
'cause he did try to start an open mic
in the subway that we worked at.
- Really?
- Yeah, he tried--
- Was it just comedy, or was it comedy and music?
- It was comedy, music.
He said that it was comedy, music,
and wet t-shirt contests.
- And how did it go?
Did people come?
- No, not the people he wanted.
It was mostly comedians and musicians.
He called it the Pepperthon.
Yeah.
and what not brought the open what why did you stop doing it
uh... because one time
uh... uh...
somebody got stuck in the bread
that's i'm so sorry
it's ok he died
he died instantly
he died instantly oh man he died instantly his name is terrible
he was a comedian uh...
i believe his name was josh goldstein
That's terrible for him. RIP Josh Goldstein.
He was so small, he was only six inches,
so he fit in half of one of our loafs.
Oh, okay.
When was the last time you saw Greg?
I saw Greg at a Third Eye Blind concert
at the TD Garden about six weeks ago.
Uh-huh, oh, six weeks ago, that recent.
Yeah, and I was on Molly,
and he was on hamburgers and we just,
it just was not a vibe that mixed.
- From your, I mean, not to pull from,
you know, your online, I'm sorry if that's private,
but it says here on a post you made on your Facebook story,
it says here, "Yo, I'm at TD Garden,
"I'm in the bathroom, I'm sucking Greg Pepper's dick.
"This shit's crazy."
Uh, I wish you would step back, hashtag I wish you would step back from that ledge my friend.
And then it says sincerely Danny Delicious.
Yeah, who is Danny, are you Danny Delicious?
Is that like your alter ego?
Is that your gay alter ego?
No I have no idea who, I've never heard of a Danny.
Your name is Danny.
It could have been a different Danny.
There's a million, I think I've looked at the facts and there's a million Dannys.
This was on your account.
Yeah, Danny, I'm looking right here.
There's a picture of you smiling.
Is it possible that I had maybe shared the post?
Because I thought it was so funny to imagine two men having sex.
It is a photo of you and all 1.6 inches of Greg's penis in your mouth.
four inches I mean one point I mean whatever it's you know whatever it looks
like I guess um what's that oh there's a guy there's a guy over here who needs me
for something I'm sure there is a guy who needs you for something pal no yeah
no he no is that I'm sorry no I'm sorry there's actually a girl there's two
girls there's a hunt there's no two girls who are here and they and they are
are asking they want to have sex with me so I kind of got to go to do that.
Oh okay.
Alright.
Go have fun.
Go have fun Danny Delicious.
Thanks Danny Delicious.
I can't wait.
Thanks for talking to me about what was his name again?
Thanks for your time man.
Girl Peppers.
Greg Peppers.
It was good talking about.
How's Greg Peppers?
He was your co-worker.
You said he was your best friend.
You sucked his dick dude.
Yeah Greg Peppers.
It was good to talk to guys about him.
Did something happen to your head?
What happened when you were talking to him?
I was talking to him.
Your head what happened what happened between you and great? Why did you?
Nothing happened. No, he didn't pay me in nachos to suck his dick at the third eye blonde concert
That doesn't make any sense. Do you sound crazy sounding you sound I guess you're right man
I guess that's a good boy. Now if you excuse me, I have to go
Suck these two women's pussies off. All right, man
Thank you. I'll see you at subway
That is not my name and what's your last name Danny?
this
DeSantis
Okay, Danny DeSantis
Cuban oh
American is good for me
Actually, I have you know, it's not my name is not Danny delicious. Does that sound like a Cuban last name to you? Yeah
Alright, Cubanos are very delicious to me.
Okay, this has been a joke.
And you two should be ashamed of what you're doing to these people.
I'm sorry, listen, I'm sorry.
We may have pushed you a little too hard.
I was told that you guys were making a Happy Birthday Greg Peppers audio file to send to
him and you wanted to interview me about it.
Is that what Caleb told you?
Yeah, that's what we're doing.
Huh?
happy birthday thing? Caleb told me you guys were gonna put a bunch of a bunch
of clips of his friends saying happy birthday. Well why didn't you say happy
birthday? I was gonna wait till the end. Duh! I thought you maybe you guys wanted
to get to know me a little bit. All right well you can say happy
birthday now. Okay all right will you let me get a couple seconds of clean air so
guys can cut it right? Alright go ahead. Okay. Happy birthday to Greg. Happy birthday to
Greg. Cha cha cha. I'm gonna have to restart now. Just get out of here man. Go. Happy birthday
Greg Peppers!
Pat, can we kick this guy off the call please?
Yeah, you're out.
Can you go to another Third Eye Blind concert sometime?
Oh, thank God he's gone.
Oh, Kalo's back.
Oh my God, dude.
Sometimes I forget how good the first part of that movie is.
And you were seeing that on 70mm at the Quiznos Ample Theater?
Yeah, I saw it in Smell-O-Vision.
Oh!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
a
I don't think he did.
I think he did.
I just have a picture of it on Facebook.
Yeah, I mean, who knows?
Under his stage name, Danny Delicious.
People know how to do a lot of stuff on Photoshop now.
You know, I was a pretty big fan of Greg's.
But that all changed when I booked him on the St. Patrick's Day show.
He's set at the last Milias show?
Where do I even begin with that?
Straight up, I have no idea why Tom booked him.
Greg has a real unique way of doing comedy.
He's absolutely fucking hysterical.
And basically all he does is he farts on you and you fall over.
Some people hate it, some people love it.
I think it's genius.
When I got to the venue, there were like 10 people with signs protesting against Greg being on the show.
I think I remember Patrick Dorn being there, and I might be remembering this wrong, but I'm pretty sure he was wearing a diaper.
Okay, alright, uh, I can explain that. I had a thing going on with my stomach that I-
Okay, I don't care at all. I don't care at all.
No, no, no, we're not-
We're playing the clip.
No, no, the point is you wore a diaper.
I didn't.
Okay, Jesse, continue.
Anyway, so Greg is bombing, and I mean fucking bombing.
Like, worse than I've seen him bomb.
And it was like, he was up on stage, doing his material.
His usual shit.
Some puns, some limericks, some songs, some props.
Classic Peppas.
And it... it wasn't going too great.
I don't think I can ever remember a time when that room was that quiet. Like ever.
And then...
And then Greg decided to pull out his secret weapon.
So he decides he's gonna do the closer early. So he gets up on the stool and he's trying to sit on
it like a baby in a changing station but he can't support his weight and he just keeps falling over
and over and over.
And that's when it happened.
And just like Obama said, if you like your health care, you can keep it.
Oh, what?
That's not fucking funny to you.
That's not funny to you.
I don't I don't know what to do then.
I don't know what to fucking.
All right, you know what?
You know what?
That you know what I can I you guys don't think I'm funny
Don't hear something that'll get you laughing. All right. Let me just get up
And that's the only audio that was recovered from that night
When his set wasn't going his way, Greg Peppers lit one of his patented farts on fire with an Eric Cartman Zippo lighter that had been
illegally modified to produce a larger flame.
Because he had already been farting throughout the night, the basement was so saturated with methane that the flame instantly caused a massive explosion.
Greg's fart-splosion killed two and injured 27.
It completely destroyed Moo-Yah Burgers and Fries, turning a cultural landmark into a vacant lot strewn with debris and limbs.
To put it simply, he farted on the building and it fell over.
Many are calling this event the Boston Marathon Bombing.
Some say this name has already been taken and to pick another one.
But we here at Podcast About Lists believe in calling it like it is.
And that night was a marathon of mayhem.
Greg's body was never recovered from the wreckage.
And the police believe he is still at large.
*sad music*
He went up on me like, uh, like they did to Gaddafi.
He just looks like that, I don't know what to tell you guys.
Yeah, he was like the king of movie trivia.
*gibberish*
One time he did a set where he literally just ripped off old Carlos Mencia material
and everyone was confused because he kept calling himself a cholo?
If you're pissing people off, that means you're probably doing something right.
I think Eminem said that.
So there it is, the story of Greg Peppers.
A whirlwind of laughter, tears, noxious fumes, and childhood neglect.
There were those who adored Greg Peppers and there were those who despised him.
But everyone could agree he made a lasting impact on the faces of both the Boston comedy
scene and the many victims who perished in the basement of that Moya Burger and Fries.
While many came forward with their stories, there are undoubtedly millions of others affected
by his crimes and his farts.
If you have a story to share about Greg Peppers, please reach out to us.
If you have any information regarding the whereabouts of Greg Peppers, please reach out to the police
at their Greg Peppers hotline, 213-458-8170.
Remember, no story truly ever ends, and Greg Peppers is still out there, somewhere, farting
on people and making them fall over.
Maybe one day, you'll find yourself waiting in line in subway, confused about what BMT
stands for.
And maybe you'll get an unmistakable whiff of Greg's scent, a highly potent cocktail
of seafood, baby powder, and the inside of a DVD case.
Maybe he'll be standing right there, behind the register.
And maybe, just maybe, he'll fart on you.
And you'll fall over.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
(upbeat music)