[Music]
Think of the tender things that we were working on
Slow change may pull us apart
When the light gets into your heart, baby
Don't you forget about me
Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't
[Music]
So, well everybody, so before we begin, I want us to all, we're all going to start
rolling for our characters, so everyone who's listening or watching, we're doing
a very special episode. You might be able to tell if you can look at all of them,
but if you're not able to... I don't think that somebody could tell. Yeah. Actually the more I
look at it, it's like this all the time. Pat is the keystone. Pat is the one where if you look at him, he'll figure it out.
Pat is the only one, actually, who makes the most, who makes... You actually, you're kind of crushing it.
I didn't even see that thing in there.
Oh, the bracelet.
Yeah, so we're doing a breakfast club.
I made these.
Very nice.
We got the Home Planet guys here to help us out, to round out the cast.
What up, what up?
That's right.
[LAUGHTER]
So let's start by--
Skip ahead to 14.11 to skip the rolling for stats part and straight into the rolls.
Home Planet guys, the new character sheets arrived.
You guys are used to them.
Oh yeah, the system is so much better than the old one.
The system has been pared down a little bit.
I think you'll enjoy our new system.
So the stats are arm, balance ball, heart, brain, owl, and talking.
Yeah, and there's also heart, big heart, band-aid, bunny, exclamation point, bang, and shield,
and name as well.
Band-aid is going to be your least important, but big heart will maybe be your most.
That's a good point.
Yeah, we very rarely use short rest.
So don't worry that much about band-aid.
Band-aid is basically...
Band-aid is like an advanced kind of thing.
for players like us who really know what we're doing.
- I think we all have a good band-aid score.
- Yeah, I got four numbers.
- So, you'll see asterisks next to each
of those individual stats with the exception
of Caleb, your character, because your character,
there's really all, so those asterisks mean
when you guys roll all your stats and you assign them,
you have to put the highest numbers
into those asterisks that you get.
- Okay.
- You just can't--
- Wait, can you repeat that?
So when you guys roll for your you're gonna roll stats right now. So yes, you're gonna roll three d6s
So three regular die
Add those together and write those on the side
Just so you can keep track of them and then assign them to the big box where your stats are
Okay, you should put your highest numbers
Where there's an asterisk next to them and then you can put the rest wherever
Okay, cuz that's what defines your character your character though
It just has like a little null symbol because I'm talking
Yeah, cuz you're just bad at talking like you can put your stats wherever you want
You just can't put your highest in talking. Okay, because you're not good at talking does talk though. She
What she she does talk I said, you know, I think she's not gonna be her best at talking
Oh, she's not gonna be her best. You think she
The character you just roll 3d
3d 6 and I'm gonna go over the ground rules and member to add them together
- Add them together and write them down on the side
so you remember and then you'll put them
and you'll assign them.
If you have any questions, I'm right here.
- How many times do we roll?
- Six times.
- Oh, so each thing is a different score.
Okay.
- Why are you saying it like that?
- Mm-hmm.
- Each thing is a different score.
Four.
- Nine.
Okay, yeah, write that down on the side.
You keep that to yourself though.
- Nope.
No sweat, no sweat.
You guys listen to that sound, listen to that chorus of die rolling.
It's the worst sound in the world.
It's a great sound, you're so wrong.
True gamers now.
17.
So I just have to put my lowest in talking?
Yeah.
Damn it, I suck.
It's okay.
Okay wait, so owl is wisdom and talking is talking?
Talking's like charisma. Okay. Yeah. Wisdom. Yeah. Okay. How did you know owl is wisdom?
Have you played this before? Kind of the universal sign. I don't think I said owl is wisdom.
I said wisdom. Oh. Yeah. But I understood it immediately. Yeah. I have terrible rolls.
I got a good one. Mine are pretty bad too. Mine are middling. Well this is going to impact
my gameplay. Yes. Heavily. It's going to impact it for sure. That's part of the reason why
there are numbers there. These gloves are so uncomfortable. See, having just watched
the movie I don't think Claire is particularly super wise I think if
anything she's feigning as though she is. Go with just the talking then I
think it's not I don't think it's incorrect. Do what you feel. I was trying to give her another stat that I thought.
Why is talking one of my biggest ones? I think Bender is really good at talking.
He's the top talker in the movie. He's sort of like a rogue.
That always happens. Remember when he like when he like licks her vagina in the movie?
Yeah, we're gonna get there. Don't spoil that for the fans.
Can't do that nowadays. I gotta do that to Joe.
I have a question. What does the brain mean?
Brain is intelligence.
That makes sense.
Sweet. Great question.
So we do this every single time.
I actually know what they all are.
So what is the difference between, is it strength and then like agility?
Yeah, balance ball is like dexterity.
Oh, I thought he was playing soccer.
That's a good-ass point.
Damn, we should call it soccer.
We should call it soccer.
That's faster to say than balance ball.
From now on, it is soccer.
It's soccer.
And then heart is what?
Your health.
Here in Afternoon is soccer.
Oh, wait, which heart?
The beating heart.
Real heart.
Real heart is constitution.
Okay, you're gusto.
So your ability to withstand pain.
Am I fucking things up if I put my second highest one there?
Not at all.
Nothing, it doesn't matter at all.
It's all made up for a game.
Okay, cool.
Everything's made up and the points don't matter.
This is just so if I roll something, I don't have to worry about it.
I don't have to worry about it.
at all it's all made up for a game.
Everything's made up and the points don't matter.
Oh this is just so like if I roll something and it's like oh blah blah blah.
Yeah I know.
Oh and then I add two if it's my good ones.
Mmhmm. Okay.
We add two if it's our good ones?
Yeah that's what all the asterisks are.
So what the hell?
You got the modifier right there.
Got the modifier on the ladder liar.
Whatever my modifier is.
Yes. Okay so two.
So two.
(laughing)
- Yeah, so two.
- So you don't have to add it now,
you can just add it after.
- Zendaya.
- You can add it now if you want to.
- Okay, so-- - What?
- There's something there. - When would I add it
if I don't add it right now?
- Well, because it's your proficiency also.
- This is really good radio.
- You're also writing it to your text.
- There are people watching this,
so I don't know if I have anything.
- Oh, so I don't, yeah.
People are watching and they're gonna be--
- This is-- - Noted, but right now--
- If they made the Breakfast Club--
- It's a lot of crosstalk. - 2023.
- Zendaya!
This is my favorite part of the Breakfast Club movie.
You think Joe would play Zendaya?
So, next--
Zendaya would play Joe.
Once you guys have your numbers associated,
let's do the modifiers for those numbers.
OK.
So--
I already did that.
OK.
So 10 is 0.
Oh, wait, what?
So right-- you see the circle next to the big square?
Yeah.
You're going to add like a plus 1 or 2 or a minus 1 or 2.
Maybe we shouldn't have filmed this part.
Some people like this part.
I can skip through it.
We'll time stamp it.
We can skip it, too.
We get time.
This is going to play in the-- it's just in the same--
If you don't want to see us--
I'm just listening to this.
Yeah, I think this is crazy.
I think some people love this.
This is crazy.
I feel like it should be a separate video.
The microphone feels so good against my lips.
I was thinking of doing this as like a separate video,
and then we all showed up in our costumes.
Yeah.
And like a cut.
But you can just cut, right?
We can take all of our clothes off and do it naked.
We'll just finish it.
We'll finish it out.
Let's finish it out.
So I think this is also a good opportunity
of rebroker the breakfast club and see like you know if it were made today what
would change. Who would get cancelled? We're about to find that out. We're about to do the breakfast club if it were made today.
I have some questions about the setting but we'll get to that. How do we do the
modifier? So the way to add your modifier is look at the number that you have
there in your boxes. 10 is 0. 10 to 11 is 0 to your modifier. You put that in the
circle. 12 to 13 is plus 1, 14 to 15 is plus 2, 16 to 17 plus 3 and so on.
So what would be a 4? So here, let me... 4? You have a 4? 1000. Does anyone have anything lower than an 8?
Yeah, he said a 4. A 4? Okay. So 7 is minus 2. 7 and 6 and 7 is minus 2. If anyone has a 6 or 7, write minus 2 next to it.
If you have an 8 or 9, write -1 next to it.
Okay?
Oh, okay.
And then a 4 is maybe like a +7?
Pat, not yet.
10 or 11 is 0.
12 or 13 is +1.
14 and 15 +2.
We already have those.
Oh, we are?
Everything's filled in?
Yeah.
Now for the 4, that 4 that you have there, that is -4, I believe.
Think about it though.
Ok, so...
I put that under my brain.
I am completely
developmentally disabled.
-16 is a +3.
I'm probably in here
because I did something I didn't know.
Even though I've already added...
My roll was 14, I added 2 with the modifier.
You'll add that after
the fact. So it's +2 for you,
and you'll add...
plus two. And then...
Fourteen and then plus two in the circle. And then you'll add plus two whenever you roll for a save.
The big number doesn't matter at all. It's only the... It's only there to help align it to it.
I hate the big number.
Okay, so then I...
my ten is an eight.
And my eight is a minus one.
Yeah. It'll also be fine.
You have minus three intelligence, right?
Yes. Well, I have a four minus three.
- A four minus three?
- His modifier is minus three, and he has a four.
- How is your modifier minus three?
- 'Cause I got a four.
- Oh, okay, sorry, I thought you had it on top of it.
- No, no, no, no.
- Five is minus three also.
- So you are a weak lady.
- Oh my God, you're a wimp.
- Oh my God, you have like, your sheet is terrible.
- I'm pretty bad, yeah.
- This is why usually people do the roll four D6s,
drop one, but this is more fun
because you get stuff like that, to be honest.
- Mine is pretty bad.
- How about we roll a D20?
I'm kind of good at on this. I got a 17 because then you'll get the ranges will go even crazier.
The chances of being super 1d 20.
Just what do you mean?
You just roll 1d 20 instead of 3d 6.
It's different.
How's it different?
Because there's different math.
It's different.
Think about like the minimum you get on 3 is 3.
We shouldn't explain bell curves today.
Okay, cool.
Well, yeah, but wouldn't it be funnier to get a one for your armor class?
it would be your armor class so that you see that there's shield shield shield on
the shield oh shield shield shield shield is 10 plus your balance ball modifier or
your soccer modifier so the number in the circle it can also be - plus 10 just
didn't put it in there yet Alex. What did you do? Did you roll six times? Yeah, oh, oh no I didn't. I rolled four. You're still holding the dice too. He was staring at me and was counting. And I was like oh ok he's on the right track.
No one, I don't know if anyone's gonna wanna watch this.
What is a 12?
We can put a time stamp.
A 12 is a +1.
That's good, that's 11.
That's nice.
Okay, then what goes in the shield?
11 is +1.
Oh, I thought it was 0.
No, 11 is 0.
11 is 0.
I'm sorry.
You're fine, you're fine.
Alex, your armor class will be a 11.
Your armor class is a 0, is 10 actually, sorry.
actually sorry. No it's 10 plus. Oh it's balance ball I'm sorry thank you. Soccer. So go it's 10
plus soccer. Brother. 10 plus soccer all on the shield. 10 plus soccer all on the shield.
An initiative. Sorry your exclamation point. Thank you. Thank you. Is just soccer ball modifier.
Plus one. Soccer modifier. Wait what's the soccer one? The balance ball. The circle next to soccer.
Oh, oh, so then plus one?
Yeah.
Cool.
Excellent.
I love numbers.
I think that the talking should impact these more.
No, so you just got a bad sheet.
Just put plus one.
Which ones would you like the talking to impact?
I don't know, speed maybe?
No.
No, speed never changes.
Well, except in this one, the athlete over here does have 40.
Because you commented that.
You should have made it...
Let me try that one.
it
glass by screaming. Not with speed. Well maybe it does. That's talking. That's speed of sound.
So. Bro got grills in. Alright cool. We got all your stats assigned. It's bracing. The
other thing we'll need to do is when we get to your attacks and stuff. But I'll deal with
that later. I'd rather not. We could just screw that on the fly. I'd rather keep going.
So I'm going to explain to you how this game works. It's a little bit different from what
we usually do. This. Here yeah. Everyone get your stuff on because this is what we would
want to keep in. Okay. This next part.
Um...
[laughter]
Yeah, so get yourself ready.
Um...
Throughout the Breakfast Club campaign
there are seven phases to your day,
to your detention day.
When you arrive, there's your first
bathroom break, an exercise
break, a lunch,
arts and crafts, your second
bathroom break, and then the final hang
with all your new friends. Every 10 or so minutes in real life, this is me, I'll use this as
a timer, I will be counting down until the phase is over. I'll make a call depending
on how the phase is going, like maybe it'll go a little bit over, maybe you will get bored
and want to just end it, but after each phase ends, the fatigue of detention wears on. I
will roll a d4 and then I will subtract that number from your HP.
So, we can die.
If you guys work together.
Now it is in 2023.
I didn't want to go there but I had to bring it up.
You can die now?
You can die.
What happens is you get a tummy ache and you have to be taken home.
That's not that bad.
And you have to go to detention the following week.
Wait, that's better than having detention.
You get to go home and watch TV.
You have to go to detention twice technically.
But that's in the future, it doesn't matter.
We're only playing one day.
Yeah, for you that's good.
you that's good. Yeah, well I already have that. Yeah, I gotta work it out. You'll get
another detention. How about he just shoots me? How about the principal just fucking shoots
me? I don't think Coach is gonna let that happen. If you guys work together, character,
and break past your stereotypes, and do things that show me your character is growing, you
will get a token. Which is, shit I forgot to get the tokens. But, where are they? I'll
Just any figurines. Just get the bag of figurines.
I'll get them.
Get them.
Okay.
You can spend these tokens either to add to your rolls in the game,
so plus to your rolls,
or subtract from the damage you take at the end of each phase.
Cool.
That's perfect.
Can we get the GI Joe ones instead? They're metal.
I know, but hold on.
The most concrete way to get tokens is to talk about a rumor that is out there
about either yourself or another character and resolve that kind of whole
thing. I don't agree with that because that is bullying. Or about why you ended
up in detention. Yeah, just not sure. That will generally guarantee you a token to
spend. You probably you'll handle it. If I talk about why I got detention? Well if
you just open up. Aren't we supposed to do that anyway? No, but it has to be organic.
I'm closed off. I don't want to talk to you guys. I don't even know you guys.
Yeah, but I brag about detail.
Hold on, here we go.
So if you're...
Yeah, you got your problem, buddy.
Here's the thing.
You're proud of it.
Your HP will likely go to zero during this game.
Like it's very hard to like...
The possibility of...
The probability of like...
You guys not going to zero,
rolling a d4 and you only have 10 HP.
It's pretty low of you guys like...
But if you're still in the game,
you will still be in the game.
So you can get your HP back up to half.
if you admit to one of the rumors that is floating around you
or you tell everyone why you're in detention. So you might want to pocket those
instead of just using them as ways to get tokens.
As in there are other ways to get tokens just by conversing, hanging out, doing other things.
Those are like, let me automatically get a token by having this moment.
So are other people sort of organically discovering other people's rumors
as we go along?
Are there clues to the rumors?
He's got them right now.
When you shuffle all these, you've got all your rumors right here.
And they're being distributed to all of us.
Holy shit.
So we kind of come equipped with some...
Each of you are going to get three of the rumors.
Some tea on other people.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, it's like the Kermit meme.
Can we go around and say everyone's character's name?
Yeah.
Kermit!
Yeah, come on.
Kermits have been on that damn...
Or I guess we can wait.
That will just be at the start, huh?
Never mind.
Kermit's tea.
I basically took command when I shouldn't have.
Your mic is off.
Kermit's tea.
I was going to try to tie my hair.
The only thing is, if you get one of your own...
- Each of you guys take three rumors.
If you get one of your own rumors,
put it back until you don't have your own rumor.
All right?
- I'm gonna throw it away.
- And also, sorry for my handwriting.
Here, put this in the center.
- If you wrote three again. - Everyone take three.
You said everyone take three?
- And the rumors say who they're about.
- Yep, everyone take three.
They say who they're about in my chicken scratch.
If you get one with your own name on it.
- I didn't get any of my own.
- I got all of my own.
[Laughter]
Oh that one's flipped.
So before...
Whoa! Some of these are pretty juicy.
Before we did this, everyone at home, I asked the guys...
Oh I got all of one person.
You got all of one person? That's very good.
That's really funny.
I asked all the guys to send me three rumors about their character, two of which are true,
one of which is false.
So that's part of what's going on here.
So again, these rumors and the reason why you're in detention are things you can use
to make sure you don't, you're not dead forever.
So you might want to save them, but they're also guaranteed tokens, so you might want
to use them.
So it's up to you guys how you want to do that.
Okay.
Next, if you cause too much of a ruckus,
the hall monitors will watch you more closely
in the room, in the hallway, when you go to the bathroom.
They may even start to attack you.
However, sometimes causing a ruckus
is a great way to make friends.
So think about that too.
We're gonna figure it out, you know.
Importantly, you cannot,
you cannot attack Principal Sullivan.
- Shut up. - What?
(laughing)
- You made the one campaign - What do you mean?
where we can't kill him and it would be the funniest thing for us to do immediately?
We just can't? You can't attack him, please!
But we can torment him in other ways. Of course!
Can we emasculate him? Can we emasculate him?
Wait, what did you say about the... You're gonna be so much meaner to him, I already know because I said that.
Sometimes being friends... What's that? Sometimes causing a ruckus.
Sometimes causing a ruckus makes the most friends.
That should be like the tagline for your guys'... for just Pod About Less in general.
And? On the poster, that'd be pretty cute.
you can't escape the school either you have to sit through detention
that's how the game work here let me let me correct this you can do those things
to in care
you can kill Sullivan and then escape the school and then we're I'm just gonna
have to fucking make a bunch of shit and I will do that if I have to do that but
if we want to do it the breakfast club the story where the principal here in
detention, those are the things that have to stay the same.
I'll leave it at that.
That makes sense to me.
That's the only reason why I'll say that.
I really can do it, I should say that, but I will have to just make a bunch of shit up.
Okay, during the exercise phase, a gym teacher will visit you.
There'll be a specific challenge for that. During the arts and craft phase,
an art teacher will visit you. There'll be a challenge for that. There's more tokens you can get
in those instances. During each bathroom break,
you'll be able to retrieve one item from your locker
only if you're able to sneak past the hall monitors. For Bender,
that's drugs to share. Ooh, nice. And if you get those drugs and you use them,
that's 2x tokens for any positive social interaction for everybody
in the party. Give me those drugs, doobage. For the nerd, that's
a, um... Pencil.
I can't tell you because it has to do with your reason for being in detention.
Oh yeah.
For Molly Ringwald's character, that's one hundred dollars
you can use to bribe people.
Yeah, rich money.
That's a baseball bat you can use for fights.
Oh, nice. With the hall monitors.
And for weird girl, it's a real frog.
Yeah. Why does that make so much sense?
OK, we all had the frog girl in high school, remember?
So I dated her.
- Is everybody... - Oh, I fucked her.
- That was the frog.
- We're in a good enough spot right now, right?
- When do we get these items?
- We just own them. - During the bathroom break.
- Oh, got it. - You're in our locker.
- If you want to sneak to your locker.
- Got it. Cool.
- Is my locker next to the bathroom?
(laughter)
- I just want to make sure I'm not talking to you both.
- When we get into the campaign,
you guys can ask me about your abilities.
You have abilities there.
I'll let you know what they do if you ask me about them.
Like, right now, I think,
we can think it's enough preamble.
Let's get started.
So it's a beautiful Saturday morning.
It should be a day that you guys are all hanging out,
watching cartoons and hanging out with your friends,
but you're not.
It's a beautiful Saturday morning in Duluth, Brooklyn.
And instead, you're getting dropped off.
At Sullivan, the Frog High School.
Sorry, Sullivan, the Frog Enterprises High School.
- They named it after him?
The principal?
(laughing)
after the principal. It's the weirdest school ever. It's not normal. Let's wait until you
learn about the children who go there. What? And you're all getting dropped off at the
school. Are you getting dropped off by your parents, by your siblings? Let's go around.
Let's start with you, Alex. Okay. Emilio Estevez. Who's dropping you off at school? I'm getting
dropped off in an unmarked SUV and a man with a suit is pushing a box up to the
front and then I punched through the box.
Okay. It's kind of cool. And then I run into the school, the fastest you've
ever seen anyone run. You sprint 20 feet into the school? Yeah. Like that. "Go get him son!"
your dad says not my dad who is in the car then agent M it's me go get out son
agent M your mom yes no that's I can't get into that okay and then what about
you Molly my driver is actually taking me at least that's how close me and my dad
have been recently it almost feels as though he is a servant in servitude of
of me and my awful mom.
- With a slave dad, yeah.
- Yeah, my dad is just like my mommy's whipping boy,
sort of.
- I know I'm just your mother's whipping boy,
but could you maybe be nice to me?
Just this once.
- Whatever, dad.
- Well, I hope you have a good time in detention.
Oh, if that doesn't make any sense, I'm sorry.
- Whatever.
I'm going in now.
- Okay, here's your lunch.
- Agent M is your dad?
Now he's playing multiple characters.
Oh, okay.
Okay, bye honey. Yeah, bye.
Damn, alright, that's harsh. And what about you?
I'm walking around in the front of the building with a cigarette in my mouth.
No parents. Yeah, no parents.
They are in the car though. Yeah, fuck you!
I'll fuck you, dad!
Fuck you!
Bitch!
I'll fucking kill you!
You'll fucking kill me!
No, stop it!
I bet you will!
Stop it!
How do your mom's trying to stop him from getting out of the car?
I'll fuck you up, bitch!
I'll fuck you up!
And then I just kind of walk in.
Kind of meep in?
Yeah, meep in.
And you?
Uh, I'm...
My family has a car where it's a minivan but it has three seats in the front, so I'm sitting
in between my mom and dad up front and I'm reading a book.
What book?
What?
The Origin of Mathematics.
By Charles Darwin.
It's a good book.
Gregorian.
I thought you would have already have read that book.
Oh, I have.
I'm just reading for pleasure.
Now that's my good boy.
And I climb out over my mom's lap and I go, "Oh wait, other side."
And I crawl back and I crawl across my dad's lap.
That's it, son.
You don't touch your mother.
Come on out of the car.
And I get out of the car and I trip and I fall and I get up.
You trip and you fall and you get up.
Okay.
And you all file into the Sullivan the Frog Enterprises library where Principal Sullivan
is waiting for you.
*laughter*
Principal Sullivan is here to greet you all.
*sigh*
Um, alright.
Well, I'm sorry.
Um, *clears throat*
I'm sorry that you have detention, but you got
detention.
And, um, you guys gotta sit here the whole day
and, um, just think
about what you did, and don't worry,
don't worry about it, it happens. People,
People make mistakes, you know this morning I got up and I went to brush my teeth. I just had orange juice. So, uh, you know
Principal Sullivan you're far too understanding with all of us Cretans here in the detention. You don't need to put on a brave face. It's okay
Thank you. Thank you, Molly
You know, I got a I
Hate you know what Bender?
What I just I don't know why it why you got a you always scowling you make it a scowl face
Stop, what are you, fuc-
Hey, I got a question. Does Froggy Manilow know you raided his wardrobe?
Yeah, that's...
His lily pad?
Does Froggy Manilow know you raided his lily pad?
Alright, hey, uh, my mom got me these, man.
Yeah, is your mom Froggy Manilow?
No, she is not, and that's another week in detention for you.
Pfft, eat my shit.
Damn.
Hey, hey.
What'd you just say?
Eat my shit.
Frogs actually eat flies.
Not shit.
And another week for him!
No, he does not-
He gets detention with me for speaking out of line like I just did.
No, you just are the one getting detention because-
Eat my shit!
I'll happily take detention if that's what you deem necessary.
No, you're good, man.
You gotta not do that to yourself.
I'm sorry.
Don't be so- You've got three weeks in detention now.
Good!
You- I don't wanna do this!
So?
I'm not a disciplinarian by nature!
Who gives a shit?
Freakazoid, stop it!
Shut up!
I have to!
Slut!
Hey!
Hold on, that's gotta be at least three more weeks.
We don't even know that word.
You're a slut, and you're gay.
No, no I'm not.
Okay, look man, I don't know what to do.
You're raped!
You're a nerd.
You're put- Stop it!
And you're the weird girl.
You're put- Stop- You keep naming them- Their names!
I can't-
and you're a little pro, bitch.
This is why Breakfast Club would never happen today.
Because of labels. People have labels now.
I'm trying to write this down.
That's like six months of detention.
I already had six more months of this shit, bitch.
Hey, Principal, at this point,
I think that detention's probably not solving the problems
that we have with this guy, okay?
You should shoot me right now, because I have a bad home life.
What?
Shoot me in the fucking head!
Shoot me with two guns!
I'm not going to do that! You're really scary!
Okay, okay, okay, how about this, how about this, how about this?
I'll call you now.
I want detention forever!
Let's just, let's just-
So what if a good punishment would be not giving me detention?
Oh, hmm.
'Cause I want detention forever.
Don't do it.
So that I can go home right now.
Don't do it, Principal.
Don't do it.
I don't know, he's making sense, so maybe I should-
No, he's on drugs, probably.
Yeah, I'm on drugs and I have him in my locker!
He just admitted it.
You want me to kill him?
Oh, man, you can't- don't tell me you got drugs in your locker.
I got drugs in my locker, we should go investigate it together right now.
ball and kick you out of here.
- You're gonna kick me out?
- Okay, that's not, obviously I'm not enough of an authority figure.
- Hey, put some Sullivan, Sullivan.
- To calm this down.
- Go, frogs!
- That's right, thank you.
Hey, I like it.
- He made the school after himself and made the mascot himself.
- The mascot isn't a mascot.
- The Sullivan the frog frogs.
- He called the Sullivans.
- Thank you, that's really nice.
Look man, okay, you have now five years of detention.
Rich, I already stayed back five years.
(laughing)
Look.
What?
How old are you?
25.
Whoa.
And I really don't--
That's my number.
Yeah, and I stayed back two years
in middle school too, bitch.
So are you 27 or?
No, he did that to--
Oh, okay.
My address is a negative three on here.
I can't really do this math.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I'm gonna come back later.
I'm gonna be right outside that door.
and i i just just just chill just just think about what you do you know and one
more thing hope yet we're going to lose the door in the opener closed
i was going to be propped open
i don't know what you do in this country's
and one of you threaten to kill the other i have to just know what's going
on all the beating up keep it locked down to kill myself
yet no matter how many i i cannot have that on my on my school
you call the police
with the opposite i'm not gonna
what
jack gotta stop using that tone we have two ladies in our present our presence
and what's up
i did that's that may be true but you know
yet that there are new friend of the
the door
the door to the left open
and ask me if i can issue it
and and and one more year will be keeping p_g_-rated
and i'm don't like i'm not i don't know i have a very soft rule on that but i
really would like that to be
a thing so i don't i cannot you just broke your soft rules it had
actually think you get at least three bucks and a p_g_ movie
uh...
actually don't like you very much
and you can check out
well i don't even know i skinner and you're in the old
that's
okay so how about
will those are highly aerodynamic shape
yes it
before it's probably a dis and one more thing before i go
is young gay you're gay
you just said you're gay
you said you're gay
you said i'm gay
you said you guys are both gay
you're gay
i'm gay with the principal
no that was one of my rumors
one more thing
i need you guys to write an essay
by the end each of you about just like what you did
it can also be a drawing if you want
i just need something
You want us to draw an essay?
No, I mean...
They should have called her the stupid girl.
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm walking out.
I'm walking out of here.
I'm going away.
Principal Sullivan, it feels very irresponsible for you to leave after all the stuff he said about...
Look man.
I don't feel safe with him.
I'm going to tell you bye.
I'm going to shoot up the school now.
And the timer has started.
The timer has started.
So, you guys are just getting to know each other,
you're just hanging out.
What's going on?
- I get to work on drawing a Hispanic guy
from South Central LA.
- Yeah, that's what I thought you meant.
- Nike Cortez, big white t-shirt.
- Yeah.
- Doing my stretches.
- You're doing your stretches?
- I'm doing calculations, I guess.
- I look over and I think that you're drawing me.
(laughing)
- Cut it out!
Knock it off, that's not me!
- Oh, I'm putting my pencil up my nose.
to smell it or to...
Just as a... I just like doing stuff like this.
Oh, okay.
It's what nerds do.
I'm kind of surveying the room and I'm seeing how all these kind of freakazoids are like
in these completely like alien outer space planets, like complete, like Jupiter and Mars.
Yeah.
Whereas I'm kind of a normal girl from Earth.
Is this the 80s?
It's the 80s. It's very much the 80s, yes.
I'm looking at both of you.
That's...
You're jacking it?
Jacking off and pointing at them.
Strike one.
What's he doing?
What is that?
Hey, be happy.
It's called jacking off.
Because I'm a freakazoid.
I'm a freak.
That's the first thing you said all day that makes sense.
Freak.
I'm going to go rip up a book.
All right, do you get up and go rip up a book?
OK, you go over.
Can I stop him from ripping a book?
You can definitely try.
I'm going to jump on him like a spider monkey.
So you have an ability called wrestling.
OK.
You can use.
(laughter)
- Here's the thing. - You're so done.
It's over.
- Yeah. - You're done, man.
- Guys are getting knocked out of the game.
- If you want, you can use it as a grappling move,
but you can actually just do grappling,
just straight vanilla grappling,
so just a strength contest.
- Can I roll wisdom, or what would be the--
- Perception, to see him coming?
Well, you will just see him coming either way,
so it'll be like-- - Okay, then I pull out my knife.
- Pull out your knife.
- You have a knife?
- Oh you do, holy.
- I have a knife and brass knuckles.
- So you get up, you go to approach him and--
- I don't do that anymore.
- Okay.
(laughing)
- I'm actually, I pretend I'm going to him,
but then I like turn away at the last second.
- Where do you turn to?
- I go to the yearbook section and I look at all my--
- Why don't you rip it to show me how strong you are?
Then we can have a strength contest.
- I'm not listening to him, I'm lost in the yearbook.
- Lost in the yearbook.
(laughing)
- You're running your fingers over the pages.
- I started my essay and I wrote in big letters,
wrote "Dear Principal" and that's as far as I got.
- Okay, cool.
- And I put dot, dot, dot.
- Nice, I like that.
- I keep looking to the weird girl on the other side
and I keep kind of pointing to the boys around
and going like.
Like these guys are kind of crazy.
- Yeah.
- I think we're talking.
(laughing)
I say, "Hey."
- Hey.
- My name is Molly.
What's your name? Molly.
Are you just repeating everything that I say? No, no.
Are you, are you, do you even go to school here? I've never seen you before.
Hey, there's what I'm talking to you. There's something over here.
I got to look at, you know, when someone talks to you,
you usually have to answer back and you have to like respond to them and be like
a normal person.
actually kinda cool
you like that
yeah i like it more than i like you
why are you being mean to me?
how am i being mean to you?
you wanna have a slut battle with me bitch?
let's get this shit right now!
alright i can hear you guys yelling, please keep it down!
shut up gay frog!
who i'm gay with? you're not gay with me! i'm gay with the principal y'all!
you are not gay with the principal! i'm gay with the principal y'all!
please stop saying that no
because it's it's a whole thing the last time you said that a lot
i had to do a whole thing
and i had to go through an entire... you had to apologize to the newspaper
no i had to
i had to take
i had to sue the newspaper
for saying that because you're crazy
so stop saying i'm gay with you
yeah i'm gay with the principal y'all
i can't do this
uh... i'm actually curious how that would even physically work
you have to stretch your book before you can put it
that's fast
uh...
but right back to the
no it's a little wider than that
i'll make the adjustment
i think that's a good
protractor
it's a perfect
i like that
and this would be the feces
not that's already gone
how do you get it out
the tube
what kind of to put his head is just a piece of water that you put in there
but he's a little bit of a lot of you through it
through a piece of water
to get some tokens
world what the fuck right diagram leading to the issue that i have been drawn a
diagram collaborated on art well nice
i finish my essay
it's a good stuff
well well okay i think it's a good idea it is i think you'll find it to be on
all in order
the
one before i look at it you think i'll find it to be what
on order
all in order, okay
yeah that's my butt
it could be anybody's butt, it's not particularly his
no look there's the freckle
i drew that when you weren't looking
uh...
wait, i take out a polaroid
take a picture of you looking at my butt
i was going straight for the newspaper, idiot
You just try to try to write it this time. Oh, sorry. Yeah, you're amazing. I just get wait
Say that's right. Yes. No, no, no, okay. I'm gonna just go and walk out of here
Okay, I'm I guess I'm crying
As he didn't like my essay. Why are you crying? That's my essay was crap. I got an F essentially
Well, he turned it down and I finished it and I did mathematics on it. So yeah, I'm crying
I'm doing push-ups
He didn't like my butthole
I'm hugging him now
I'll give you one more for that no more of that
They both get tokens for that mm-hmm cuz they're good only cuz they're milk in it
We need to get some tokens you guys need to get some time if you want tokens
Maybe you you know talk like a normal person and you kind of be nice to me, okay?
I had a suggestion earlier that you guys brushed off. What even is a slut battle. It's like
Seriously, I started eating it like
What are you eating?
I'm trying to have a slut battle with you
I'm not eating anything. I know there's no food in the air.
She's eating pussy! No, I'm not. In the air? I've never done that before.
She's eating the air's pussy. Why are you like on this guy's team? Like us girls kind of have to stick together
if we want to get through this detention. He wants to stick us together
in the slut battle, but I'm not gonna do that. You're not doing the slut battle, but you're sticking out your tongue
and you're eating like ice cream in the air.
Do something about it then. Why do you debase yourself like that?
(mumbling)
- Okay, I grab her tongue when she sticks it out.
- Okay.
- What are you doing?
- I say, you need to stop it right now.
You don't know who you're messing with.
- Whoa, she's winning the sweat battle.
(mumbling)
- I can't even understand.
- I start putting my tongue in and out of your hand.
(mumbling)
- I'm grabbing onto it and it's going into your mouth
and I'm still holding onto it.
My grip is so strong.
- I bite her fingers off.
- Roll unarmed attack.
the
yeah you take roll 1d4 one you take one damage damn you change your big heart
down by one down by one and it's over the round is over
whoa so it's about to be a bathroom break bitch and first you're all going
to
a
you're brought out to the halls. This is your chance to either go, you guys go to
the bathroom, you can go steal something from your lockers, it's up to you guys.
I don't want to hang out with these fucking dildos anymore.
Can I go to them? I'm not going to try and run away to my rock locker.
[Laughter]
Before we go to that, what were you about to say?
I was gonna say I take one of the LED light bulbs from the ceiling and I start
eating the electricity.
The electricity? The electricity. That's gotta give them a power.
yeah yeah at least a token at the very it's created a token
i feel that's a token
i think that's like five tokens to be honest
only me with the five tokens but it will say is you do have electric powers
though
haha
you're gonna get plus three damage your tax and they're going to be electricity
for us
the
uh... and i'd eat another one
okay plus
one more plus four and that's a low
okay great so we get we're gonna get another chance to go to our lockers
right this is the only chance alright cuz i don't know what to bring i was in
mind lockers is there any downside to sleeping speaking my locker not you get
caught by the hall monitor so i'm about to review
the review self
you can't you have
there usually around
three or so all monitors between you and your locker
and through your circle
three or so corners you're gonna have to sort of sneak around to get there
each of you guys do...
fuck my ass you have abilities. I'm trying to do that to the principal and to the newspaper
that can help out
so
to varying degrees you have dandruff which helps create a cloud that can kind of
blind people
oh wow
uh...
you have observation. She has black hair that's just all I have. I have observation
what? I have observation. Observation which is sort of like a investigation but on steroids
It allows you to actually understand a situation to the point where you can give people advantage
on rolls, you can see the weakness in an enemy or a hall monitor.
What do you have?
What did I fuck you?
I have charm.
You have charm, yes.
You have charm, so you can charm a hall monitor if you want to.
So it's sort of like charisma, but on steroids, where if they fail a DC, they're trying to
charm a person.
Do the hall monitors have real weapons?
Yeah.
So they have guns and stuff?
They have guns.
Do they have batons?
They have batons and guns.
Do they have an axe on the other end of a sword?
a
Glock head.
Yeah, they have the gun blade from FFA.
Or a taser on a chain.
What?
A taser on a chain.
You are running out of-
They got like the-
Swing it around.
They have the Iron Man.
Okay, okay.
Alright, okay, okay.
I'm not even gonna play along.
What do you want?
Iron Man suit.
I'm not-
You are electricity.
I gave you electric powers for being a-
A word I'm not gonna say.
And my skin-
No, it's not.
I'm not gonna-
My skin is blue from the electricity.
Yo, yes.
That's pretty cool.
Yes.
I go to the girls room-
to
are
a little bit more creative. I pulled a fire alarm. That's creative. I'll give him a token.
No because I took a crazy shit. I don't even get a token for that? I pulled a fire alarm
because I thought the smell of her crazy shit was a fire. That's not, no. The token is for
you, well it is for you guys working together, you do get tokens for that. But it is, it
is
it's important to look for a little water man
the waterman
the
we all know what i think that
the water
what i read about that it's about a hundred
the principal of my trip to a bottle of
uh...
to leave c_u_
as i'm taking my shit i try to hold molly's hand under the under the stall
but
i keep pulling it away but then at a certain point is give up and i kind of
hold it
but so i i
but i put the fire alarm
we'll see how i'm what you guys do that
i'm paying in a stall
yeah you heard that right
Not at the urinal.
Alright, so you want to pull the fire alarm.
Yeah.
Okay.
So the hall monitors are scrambled at that point.
Oh, I didn't need to do that.
You're going to have advantage on sneaking past them, but you're also going to have to,
I mean, you know, consequences are going to happen.
So let's first start with that, see if you can get your drug.
So start rolling a soccer check.
That is an eight.
your plus your soccer it's a nine minus roll you roll again you have a you know
yeah I'd say I'm gonna take an eight you weren't caught by the hall monitor you
are running around you pull the fire alarm you just sprint into one of them
just like I did this on purpose because I want the attention well get back here
No! Wait, yeah. What? Because I want the attention.
Because I want the attention because I don't get paid attention to at home.
Roll talking. Yo, real talk, that's sad. That is a 14. He's like, aww. And you get to run by.
It's one roll of my iron dice. You've got two more. Okay, the two more in a row?
Did you hear what I said before to the other guy?
Yeah, this guy who doesn't see you yet goes, "Nope!"
He's just looking around.
"My dad hit me with a cigar!"
He hit me with a cigar that was the size of his arm and it burned my whole skin off and
I had to grow new skin.
This was five years ago.
Is that your soccer?
I thought I was rolling talking.
You're rolling soccer.
Oh, then that is an 11.
Oh, you're going to try to talk through all of them.
Yeah, I talk through all of them.
So that was a 13.
I
the third one you can try saving him because i overheard him say that your finger in an outlet
and then shoot and shoot you could travel you could tell me where to another outlet right right
he could travel through electricity like mario like right in front i appear in front of the
yeah you're like a jojo character yeah yeah you want to do that whoa whoa that's working together
just roll a d20 tokens are destroying this one yeah
would you get one
you get lost in the electricity forever
i'm in the electricity realm
you get stuck in the wiring of the school
and you take
your fully lawnmower man
and my face shows up on the tv in the hallway
you only take one damage from that
but you take one damage
the big heart becomes six
ok so i'm talking to the third lawnmower
you see like an outlet nearby go
and that's it
you see his face just appear for like a split second
(laughing)
- Out.
- World.
- All right, cool.
So yeah, you see the third eyelid monitor.
He says, "You're not gonna charm me with your dad shit."
- Nope, my friend just died in the outlet.
(laughing)
- Friend.
- He's my friend now.
- We're friends.
- Roll, roll it.
- Two.
Am I seeing you two?
- It's a three.
- Okay.
- Plus one.
- Oh, 'cause of the plus one?
- Uh-huh.
- He goes, "That's not your friend.
That's a jock.
You're a bully.
>> Mm.
>> [LAUGH]
>> You just pulled out my knife.
>> Holy shit.
>> Okay, roll an attack roll.
Roll a d20.
>> Three.
>> Okay. >> Jesus, I never, you just blew.
>> Whiff.
>> God damn it.
>> And then this guy is gonna hit you back with his baton.
>> And he misses.
>> Okay, I'm gonna swing again.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's what we're gonna do here.
>> Okay, 14 plus.
>> That hits.
>> 13.
>> Roll for damage.
It's 1d10, I believe.
>> 1d10.
plus your...
- Three.
- Plus soccer.
- Okay.
- So that's a two.
- Okay, cool.
- You go, "Aah!"
You slice him.
You have a chance to grab it to your locker now.
- Okay, I'm gonna do that.
- Okay, cool.
You do, you get your wee, your drug.
- It is fentanyl.
(laughing)
- What?
- It's a pound of fentanyl in my locker.
- I got a token for trying to help.
- All right!
- Cool.
- Hey man, I heard you called me your friend back there.
you want to snort this shit? Yeah dude! You guys go back
to your room
back to starting the next phase
and we smoke fentanyl with waterman
Waterman is there! Waterman ODs!
Hold on, I don't know how to save him! I just have to operate!
He's cutting open Waterman! It's just like biology class!
and i'm going to get out of here
let me try CPR
please stop
this is his eyeball
um
dissecting water
just pulling out
drinky drink
i believe this is his skin
um
cool
it's time
it's time y'all
no it's not
damage
you'll take four damage all my god token
right
all use one token token i'm also going to use my mind to
okay
okay we should get a token for all you take
I'm really hurt right now. Is anyone?
Ow!
Yeah, we all at the same time go, "Ow!"
Token!
That trip to the bathroom really took a lot out of me.
Um, is there anyone who maybe has a token who could like,
maybe help me out? 'Cause I'm like, kind of low-key on the brink of death right now.
You're acting like a whore.
Hey, what are you gonna do for the token? Suck all the guy's dicks at the same time?
Alright!
Wait, that would be the ultimate act of friendship you see.
I guess that might work.
(laughter)
What say you, nerd?
I've never even considered something like that before, but I guess I didn't care that much.
She did so well!
(laughter)
Alright, this big, dumb me had bust through.
It's the gym teacher, Coach Scoot Marino.
It's my boy.
And he comes in.
I don't wanna see him.
What's up, Emilio?
What's up, Coach?
I'm under my desk.
Alright, that's it.
It's time for dodgeball.
You guys need to get your exercise in detention.
I pretend to be a book.
I pretend to be a dodgeball and they go "Oh wait, no!"
Somebody get that book with dandruff out of here!
Alright, it's gonna be 2v2 for the rest of you.
Coach, I have powers now.
That is amazing, you're gonna crush it.
Alright, who's team? Who's on what team?
I choose him, I want him, I want him, I want him, I want him, I want him.
No, no, no, no.
He's on my team.
He gets to choose the book.
Alright, I want you four to fight this book.
Alright, so it's one side with the book.
How many balls are there?
How many balls? Infinite.
Infinite?
Infinite.
Ok, I win the whistleblows.
I've got an idea.
Is it going to be 2v2 or is it actually you four versus the book?
I mean, it can't be 2v2. There's five of us.
Unless you're a book.
But I want the reward.
I know there's a reward here.
I know that somebody's going to get tokens.
I have 4 HP.
i've been for really at the beginning of the whistle and i grab as many balls as i
can bring them back to my side regardless of what you want
okay so the point of dog was not to get as many balls of possible but we have a
question we have a lot of people we put all the balls together and then alexa
electrocutes them and we make ball man
the i'll tell you all ball manny's
uh... ten feet tall electricity
the i'm afraid i thought i was like a great design connects the atoms to get
I'm like, guys, I don't think I like a ball man.
I'll be on whatever team.
Wait, wait, wait.
Attack the coach!
Yeah, we all start throwing balls at the coach.
Okay, yeah, you do.
Yo.
Roll attack.
All of you roll d20.
I build a trebuchet.
And add, and add...
Nine.
And what?
Eleven.
Add arm.
Twenty.
Yeah, soccer.
Oh, soccer?
You got a crit 20?
I got a 20.
I got a 16.
And you have electric powers.
five would you get uh... i got a nine percent minus three
it's my story okay i got a six uh... because
nobody got a one
and he got a crit and it's also on his own coach
and his electricity
so i don't know what you guys keep throwing it ball man's life
take that dad i mean coach
all that
and you all get a bonus token
yeah
it to tell things ball man
you actually that is a actually the thing you're supposed to do was by really
yes world
look at us uh... you would
figure that out don't even give me the tokens are just a cash and trying to put
you against each other and you guys said
well thanks coach i'll connect with it
world is going to be a first-time ever disobeyed your mind you've ballman right
now
what happens the ballman delhi the ball and we are you guys we are one involving
and
there's there's five minutes left really in this and i have a question is ball
man and water what water is that the bombing exists although they're both
chilling
now waterman's that when i die i became a puddle you've got all the eyes took his
part is body and i got a hard-boiled yeah
that kills me
you should know that or a
yes you're right
that what you'd rather
right to trip
you guys were in this round will
i'm laying it we got well we have a little bit of a lot of all don't cut off
the ball man. Can we have a dance party with ball man? Yeah, easily. Okay, let's go.
Ball man. You guys are not going to believe what's in my locker.
Get it started.
I use my electricity.
My electricity powers goes into the radios and plays.
Whoa. Can I just say guys while we're dancing, if you guys next bathroom break,
if you guys help me get to my locker, we're going to have the best dance party of all time.
And I can't tell you why, but it's going to blow your mind.
All right. Okay. Sullivan's coming into the room.
all right that's ball man's back okay that's enough of this
he goes to turn off the radio stop okay just it's enough ruckus you
already put the coach in the hospital just just just keep it down hey you know
what you're gonna go to the hospital now
bitch hey ball man attack no we don't kill him you can
it'll be a different campaign i'll have to figure some shit out
no don't do it bender
too far bro too far ball man is used for good yeah i thought that we were getting
along finally i thought they were all on the same page
it's kind of like you just always take it to this new level where you like need to
lash out and need to be violent for some reason
wait this is great i like to hear this i have a feeling that
bender actually does evil things like blowing up the nerd's dog
with an M80.
(laughing)
- Well that's-- - And that is just cruel.
- That would be pretty easy to confirm,
we could just ask the nerd.
- Yeah, wait, I don't know--
- Hey nerd, has your dog ever,
has anything cruel or crazy ever happened to your dog?
- No, my dog lives on a farm upstate now.
- Hmm, why don't you do the math on that one, buddy?
And why don't you-- - Okay.
- He loves math. - 300 miles.
- Don't tell him to do that.
- Three and a half hours. - He's gonna be there all day.
- Do you happen to live by the bus stop
where you get off at?
- Yeah.
- And have you ever gone to the bus stop with like an M80
and maybe done some damage to like a dog?
- Leave me alone, I don't even know about this.
- Just answer.
Maybe just say the truth for once in your life.
- I'm just gonna back out of the room.
This seems not about me.
- Wait, do I get points if I admit to it?
- Let's see.
- Why don't you just for once in your life,
just say something that's real.
- Okay, that actually isn't true.
That was just a rumor.
who's making up rumors about you you freak
probably the nerd
i don't know how do you say this about him i've never heard of principal sullivan
for making me say that he's gay in the newspaper or i said that he was gay
stop saying i'm gay
you're gay with me in the news
i think no matter what you two have something that you need to work out i did
not blow up your dog with an m80 i thought an m80 was a computer code
computer and if i if it wasn't a computer code you would actually like
that so
i feel like you would like that it was a science experiment so i think that maybe
we can
get past this you know bender for the first time you're actually making some
sense
and you're actually sounding like you're like a real human being and not some
freakazoid who wants slap battles okay
so
you're putting the work in right now girl maybe if you realize that like
being cool like this is actually kinda cool and you don't have to be like be a
bad guy. I think that's okay because I think that's allowed in the 80s. It's allowed in
the 80s? Thanks for telling me that! My token now. Alright. That's the round. I cash in
my three tokens. Alright, we'll wait to see how much damage you're going to take. I think
I'm going to die. Two. Okay, I cash in all four of mine. I'm going to cash in mine too.
Yeah, I'm also going to cash in mine. You can only cash in the amount that you're subtracted
from you.
You're not going to gain health back.
Ok, I'll cash in two to stop two.
Ok, I guess I'll cash in two to stay at the same health.
Ok, I also cash in two.
Me too.
I'm afraid of the health.
2017.
I'm a let's play.
I can go pee.
Yeah, you can go pee.
It's lunch time!
Exercise is over.
What do you guys have for lunch?
What's going on?
I didn't even bring lunch because my parents wouldn't pack me one and I do not have any
money to even get myself lunch because I'm so fucking poor and my dad abuses me.
Yeah. I ate a bowl of guacamole. I'm eating a paper sandwich. It's just a truck.
Alex, what are you eating? I'm drinking oil.
Wait a second, because I actually heard a, I don't see that he's doing that yet.
and i i turned to to we're going to go
i heard recently and i don't know i'm telling you this
i heard that actually
that milio drinks oil
i heard a rumor that he drinks oil. That can't be true!
I feel like it's not true. And then I look over and we look over and we see it.
Out of a hamster water bottle.
that could be anything that i could be a little bit of a santa but i'm not loyal
and it has a rainbow sheen it does look a lot like a little while ago i noticed
you know that they forgot i know you forgot that there's was the two-fold you
have to follow someone true for some for some reason classically and there isn't
too large
well you would be a fortune model
the yeah i think that has won the year
that's right
you have more than
anymore beer no it's just my lunch do you have any more your lunch
by data uses me you do have your weed
warrior ok yeah now I heard a
and I had a right I that turned to one round you get double double tokens for
that can turn to just in
at home a rumor yeah her if I do fentanyl I get double tokens
everyone will get double toe if you well really whoever does it with you gets
double tokens for that round I do it
by defend not only do it if you want to be ready to defend it all with waterman
and we lost waterman we didn't get any tokens.
Is that what you did?
You used it up, you ruined the whole smoking weed scene.
We still got a little left. We should delete that.
That's what I said. We need the fentanyl. You're supposed to all do it together and that's when we cry.
How did waterman OD then?
He just became a pot of love. We loved him too much.
Yeah, sorry. Sorry everyone who was so excited about Waterman ODing.
Damn it!
Can I turn to Molly and tell her?
Yeah, for sure.
Yo, I heard that, uh, because he's talking about his dad, apparently his dad's brother, his uncle, is Bender from Futurama.
So he's actually half robot.
That's really crazy. Do you think that that maybe impacts his like his brash
behavior and like the way that he acts like towards other people maybe?
Scanning, scanning, scanning.
Should we say something to him?
I'm hearing a rumor about myself.
Hey, hey, I slide my oil across.
There's a half robot. I never would imagine there's a half robot person around us and it was not the guy who's drinking oil and also has electricity powers.
Hey buddy, I know how you feel.
You drink oil and you have electricity powers.
And then we go like...
Why is this happening?
I'm like looking around to see if anyone's staring at me and then I just pick up the oil
and just chug it.
And then he throws the can back to me and I catch it and I eat the can.
The rest of the can.
That's friendship right there.
That's two robots.
Do I get one for confiding in the secret?
No.
No you don't.
Hey buddy, while you're talking to me.
I don't want to talk anymore.
Keep it in the mic, keep it in the mic, before you spend that.
Excuse me, I want to remind you guys that if you spend, if you save your rumor, fuck,
if you save your rumor or your...
I think the principal is drunk.
(laughter)
- Guys, I see the person was drinking in his office.
- If you're rumored, a reason for going to detention
for when you have zero health, you then can come back.
- Oh.
- So if you spend all your rumors,
and you spend your reason for detention,
you can't come back.
So there are other ways, I just wanna make sure that you--
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, can I still, I--
- Do it, do it, do it.
- I've heard some things about you,
and I was just wondering--
(laughter)
You know, you seem like a really great guy right now,
and you're like--
I appreciate that.
You're acting cool and you're really standing up for like the gals in here, which like we
kind of need that right now.
I was raised.
Have you like maybe heard anything about me going around here?
Just like maybe any information about like kind of where I'm, what you heard about me
maybe or like something?
No.
Hey, remember when this bitch turned into a book?
Remember when this bitch turned into a book?
I didn't turn into a book.
I was acting a little bit like a book.
Honestly, my perfect woman would be a book.
I'm gonna be a book.
She can't read.
What?
What did you just say?
This bitch can't even read, she turned into a being a disguised disabled.
Hey bro, some people have learning disabilities.
I don't have a learning disability.
I have a learning disability.
Can you read?
That's why I'm 27.
I do too, I can't get an erection.
In two more years.
In two more years I'm 27?
Whoa.
You should try out for the volleyball team, bro.
Sullivan the frog is asking me if I can't read?
no security
i can read
that's okay and that's fine i never learned how to read i got a book for you
and he's in the bloods
uh...
like that one's not like what my hand over my mouth
and i think that i'd like to
and the electricity like covers
covers your mouth no thank you
and it goes to my braces and it kills me
the uh...
uh...
What do you have for lunch, nerd?
I have a paper sandwich.
A paper sandwich?
That is not going to fill you up, mate.
It's four slices of bread, so it's a lot.
There's no bread in it.
Four slices of bread and then paper in between.
It's a triple-decker paper sandwich.
That sounds good.
A club?
What kind of paper?
A super club?
It has a toothpick in it, yeah.
What kind of paper is it?
Book paper.
Yeah, well, I said it.
Whoa, what's happening?
No, we never use a rumor.
I know. I used it.
You only have one left, motherfucker.
It's easy for me to have all three of mine.
Have you guys heard about the AIDS epidemic that's happening in the 80s right now?
[laughter]
It's kind of scary.
Wait, that's happening in the 80s right now?
Right now? I haven't even heard it.
Wait a minute, I'm gay with the principal!
That's why I brought it up, bro.
These two should be quite worried. I think that I don't have a problem.
Oh, shit.
Yeah. I'm just glad it's not true.
And you got a red microphone too.
And you're wearing red.
What does that have to do with it?
'Cause AIDS is in blood, idiot.
It's in his blood cells, slut.
Do you have a problem with me?
Yeah, I have a problem with you.
Okay, I swing a punch at her.
Oh my god, he's swinging a punch.
Slut that out!
Roll a d20.
I just try to pin her down so she can stop this.
Oh yeah!
15.
15 minus 3, 12.
You got a 1?
Yes.
17.
Okay, yeah.
So you try to pin her down and you...
Oh, but I have minus 1, so 16.
But she still... you still win.
She tries to pin you down, you guys are like, "Oh."
According to my calculations, you will not be able to pin her down at all.
It's already happening.
I pin you back down the other direction.
Okay, I try to not get pinned.
I roll a d20, both of you.
I'm going to pin you back down.
not be able to pin her down at all.
I pin you back down the other direction.
Okay, I try to not get pinned.
One. Oh, you're fucked.
Fourteen. Even if she got a one.
Yeah, you pin her down very easily.
What are you going to do? You going to hit me? I'll probably lick your big boobs.
I start doing the robot. Yeah, we both start doing the robot.
Oh!
They're huge. How'd you get boobs so big? Did you get a boob job? No,
this is just naturally. This is how I came. I don't even know.
I just look at my body in the mirror one day and it looked like this.
How old were you when you got your boobs? I have no idea.
That's a token. That's that's that passed the Bechtel test, bro.
That's a fuzz reel.
And lunch is over.
Yeah, I stopped pinning her down.
I got my--
I took a peek.
Three damage, all of you.
OK, I'm using two tokens.
I'm using two--
Yeah, I'm using three.
Wait, is it better to use my tokens
or should I kind of operate from the death?
I'm going to use my two tokens.
I'm also going to use my--
I used three to take no damage.
I won't use my tokens yet.
No, no, no, no, no.
You misunderstand.
You can only use your rumor or your detention.
You can't use your tokens in death.
Come on, Bender. You're smarter than this, bro.
No, actually I don't understand.
So your tokens are spent to reduce the roll...
Until you die.
...or to boost your roll in game.
And I'll use them, so now I'm at 3 HP.
So if you're not boosting any of your rolls, you're better off just spending them.
Okay.
It's a flaw in the mechanic. I'm testing out this game.
Thank you for playtesting.
HP now from four because I gave you three tokens. Well what?
We took three - you would take zero damage nothing changes if you give him three tokens
You're taking the damage no matter what well no if you give three tokens it reduces it was three damage right?
Yeah, so you take you took no zero you nothing changes, so don't erase anything nothing. I have one token back
Why
So now you take one day. Okay, so now you take three yeah, or no you take one. That's what I meant to do
I'm strategizing
Where my sheets your Charlie's toilet?
What are your sheets? I had?
Paper the effing toilet papers is it those papers you know that's a scrap. Oh, I see them in your backpack easily
I easily saw them
Farts and baths yeah, it sounds like something that you may be good at we're like beats by dad
That's at home.
You take a piece of paper.
Some of you it's going to be my fault.
Is this mine or is this?
I thought the higher quality paper was like depending on our characters.
No it just happens.
Thank you Principal Solomon.
I want to say this because I'm a teenager.
I'm playing a teenager in the 80's.
I get a pencil and a piece of paper
and immediately
and I don't condone this
but this is something that a teenager in the 80's would do.
80s would do. Swastika. Just immediately drew a swastika. That's fine. Feel free to take
markers. Ms. Snooze Pulebo the art teacher comes in. What? Ms. Snooze Pulebo. Joe you
got too many markers I didn't get one. Bitch. Why does this slut get all the markers? She
arrives wearing a foppish frock under a stinky smock and she gestures to each of you. Now
Now I understand that each of you has done something wrong, and art can be wrong too.
Yeah, look at this!
Do you see that?
He drew a swastika.
Does that scare you?
Do it in real life.
It's not scary.
Why are you so afraid to do it?
You're in character.
I'm not good at it.
You have to do it.
All search inside yourselves.
Joe's good at it.
Joe's really good at it.
Yeah, Joe, you draw one.
He draws the best one in the group.
You're the one who doesn't, though.
You're the one who's doing it.
Yeah, but you draw it and I'll hold it up.
It's not true to my character.
I would never do it.
Do it backwards.
it backwards so it's the piece one. I don't even know which way is forward. Boys, boys.
Choose to either paint, do clay sculpture or collage. So you guys, you guys have the
time right now to draw. Draw your art. That's some good radio. I'll help out. I'll make
it worth it. I'll make it worth it. Give a speech. So she's walking around, she's trying
to observe all of your art. She's asking each of you what you're drawing. She goes up to
you first, Bender.
Uh, Bender, what are you drawing?
I'm drawing my dad beating the fuck out of me!
I... well...
Why are you drawing that?
'Cause I get my ass kicked every single day by a piece of shit and he sucks so badly that it makes me think that it's the only thing that I can think of.
[laughter]
Well...
And it makes me hate my life completely.
Well, you don't have to just draw him, you can draw the feeling.
I'm drawing him and he's getting buttfucked.
Well, okay, well what makes you happy, Bender?
My dad getting buttfucked.
Okay, the nerd, Brian, what are you drawing for me today?
I'm drawing a picture of her drawing her picture.
And I'm adding just measurements and statistics and mathematical calculations.
Why do you always think so rigidly?
Why are we so mathematically?
because I'm smart. Touche. And you are Emilio. I drew me and all my new friends together
in the electrical currents. Because I made so many friends here at the Tension and now
I have electric powers. That's so lovely. Which one is you? That's me in the middle.
okay
and then that's
that's bender
and that's a weird girl. You should face it towards the camera. And then that's
uh... molly and her red hair
and that's the nerd that's you. Ah you look great. And these are the...
This is representative of my damn feelings and my soul. Show everyone the camera.
This is what I feel like after my dad beats the crap out of me. It's actually kind of a
cool drawing.
It sucks.
I suck!
No, don't say that.
Oh no!
Oh no, the art is working again.
The art, it's hurting him!
That is cool.
What about you, weird girl?
I drew the big stinky shit that I took earlier in the toilet.
Alright, you gotta toast it for that.
Smells like markers, not like the shit I had.
And finally, Ms. Molly.
I was drawing my eyes like rolled back into my head and I like couldn't really
control my body and I was just drawing out something and you know and I was
moving so fast and like my pen was moving quicker than like you could
possibly humanly imagine and I don't even know what I drew but when I look at
it I gasp and I and I start to breathe heavy
I think she's orgasming.
She just came all over my face.
She just hands free nutted.
I sit under her pants. I push it away from myself.
And the room stinks. What is this?
I grab it and I'm looking at the drawing and I'm going,
"Oh my goodness, this paper is approximately 8.5 by 11 inches in diameter."
Wait. Wait a second. I know this story.
You traded identities with a Girl Scout in the woods, didn't you?
What?
That's a rumor I heard.
How'd you even hear about that?
I heard it from the janitor.
The janitor? Is the janitor here right now?
The janitor is in the game.
So yeah, we'll have him show up I guess now.
Yeah, you see walking by, Eric, the janitor.
Hey kids, what's going on?
Yo, what up, boy?
Eric, tell Molly what you told me about her.
And her... what happened to her body.
Weird girl, I told you that in confidence man.
How do you even find that stuff out about me?
Well you go around drawing this in every fucking art class you take, people are gonna get the idea.
It happens to me.
So it did happen to you.
I go in the garbage man, I see all kinds of stuff.
I know and you see every single time she discards one of these drawings.
It's okay Molly, I switch bodies with a Girl Scout too, but I switch back immediately.
okay
maybe it did happen to me
and maybe it's hard to
kinda you know wrap my head around it but like... bender going ham on his art right now
IT'S MY FATHER!
I can't even see him as a normal person because he beats the shit out of me
you see him as a green and black guy
see him as an army man
he's irish and african
The black Irish, they say.
Alright.
Well, it seems like this really helped some of you come to terms with things.
I'm still shaking.
There, there. I say there, there.
Who were you before?
Admit it, you were a porn star.
Why would you even...
That's why she's so good at slutting out.
That's why she shows her tits all the time.
I'm not good at slutting out.
You made me do that. You pinned me down.
I didn't make you do anything. I pinned you down.
You showed your huge tit.
and then you said rich that's rich cover the girls slept with a class pet
yo dead
that as the weird girl dead ass
mine who
will get a sports so i catch the rebound class that
what kind of that was it
isn't the class but goldfish
she will not
yes it was a goldfish
had even sleep with a goldfish with my fucking pussy what do you think
I don't know, I just was like trying to figure out...
I put... okay, you want the details?
Yeah.
I put his cock in my pussy.
Is that what you want me to say?
Damn!
I put the goldfish's cock inside my pussy.
That's what you want me to say?
I'm turning beet red.
I'm embarrassed even hearing this.
And I like it!
Where is the goldfish right now?
It fucking died!
[Laughter]
What do you think?
You think a goldfish can survive that?
It's like a bee with its stinger it dies. Did you break the chair Alex?
No my jacket got caught.
Oh.
That's how the goldfish died.
Yes. The goldfish died that way.
He died happy though.
I guess at least he had experience pleasure.
Most goldfish go their entire lives
of fucking a human-ish woman.
And I saw this in the bathroom.
Where it happened.
You weren't in the bathroom.
I was hanging out in the girls room.
out in the girls room. Pervert alert, pervert alert, he hangs out in the girls room. Okay,
okay, settle down, settle down. And he does that. What is that pissing shit? Is that why
you always draw the turd in the water? I ate the turd. Nice. This is, okay, to be honest,
this was his final resting place. The turd? In the shit? I took his shit and then I fucked
and then I died and I flushed the man.
You did that during the bathroom break?
When I was protecting you?
No, that was for a different time.
The rumor went around.
Fast work, that rumor.
Did you fuck the fish and then you ate it and then you pooped the fish?
What?
Yes.
Is that what was making Arby's noises in the bathroom?
It was Samuel.
I thought I could smell that.
Samuel the salmon in your shit.
- It's a salmon.
- And did you then run to the bathroom
and put the poop inside the tank of the fish
so it seems like the class pet is still there?
(laughing)
Yes, and then tomorrow when everybody notices,
I'll say, "It's a water snake."
(laughing)
- Oh my God.
- I find water snakes really fascinating.
- It's a male.
- I was really excited.
- The problem is, is you can see the fish bones
through this shit.
- Okay, wait, I have an idea.
- What?
- This fucking weird jock guy who has had a bone--
- He's the weirdest one of all of us.
- He is weird.
(laughing)
- He has electric powers.
- This guy, ever since he used the electric powers
these two times, he's kind of just been like
pulsating with energy.
I've been noticing this pulsating with his energy so much.
And I think we could maybe get him to go make the fish.
- Or we could trap him in a battery.
(laughing)
- It's, oh, our class is over.
Time for a bathroom break.
And first time to take some damage.
- Did we make a breakthrough there?
Did we all get tokens?
- You got a shit ton more tokens, see that?
- Did you guys hit a lot? - I only got one.
- Did we get a breakthrough? - You didn't do enough breakthroughing.
- How much damage? - How much damage?
- Four. - Oh!
- Four?! - Wait, I'm dead.
- Me too. - What do we do?
- Wait, oh wait.
- Can I give you one of my rumors? Is that what it is?
- You can start to admit, yeah, you have to admit to more rumors.
- I'm gonna give my three so I don't die.
- I'm alive. - So I'm at one.
- Wait, I have to admit to rumors, but I, I,
all my rumors have already been talked about.
- You can talk about the rumors you have.
- Oh, okay.
- Those are what you can cash in.
- Okay.
- Wait, I have one, so I have three things.
I need to then do two more rumors on top of that.
- Wait, wait, no, the rumors--
- Sorry, let me explain.
When you hit zero, your rumor gets you back
to automatically half health if you have a rumor to spend
or a pension to spend.
However--
- These are the rumors?
It's not our own?
- Yeah, no, it's not your own, it's not your own, sorry.
It's the rumors that are in your hands.
- Oh, actually, can I take back my tokens
and die instead and use my thing?
- Yeah, absolutely.
is
right now when I may yes wait I have a question about the yeah sure if I if it's
negative for dive one it's not a good for just goes to zero and then okay but can
I just use one token then and live still be either rumored attention the tokens
are only so I'm just gonna hold on my tokens are like to mitigate harm okay and
the rumors and the detention help you just like okay yeah so I'm gonna be some
admitting. Yeah. I'd like to. You guys are walking to the bathroom. Some of you hit
zero so you're feeling so fatigue. I'm kind of like floating over the ground. We were walking to the bathroom. Guys, I had, I want to tell you
something. You're floating with your electricity powers. And I'm like, speak. And I form a microphone. Guys, I know I seem like the
happiest, coolest guy in the school, but things aren't always easy for me.
Actually, this, the reason I'm in detention, you wouldn't even believe if I told you,
but so I shouldn't tell you, but I'll tell you basically what happened was I got an F
in my lunch period and it was lowering my GPA by almost a huge amount.
And my parents, they were going to kill me.
You guys don't know how it is.
Your parents are great.
My parents are so mean.
You talking about idiot my dad piece of shit
My parents are so mean they're always like you have to do your best and stuff like that
so I basically
It's hard for me to admit this and honestly would help me to admit this if I could smoke a little phenanyl first
Yeah
Do you have aluminum foil and a pen?
I have aluminum foil right here
I take out my pen
Can you flatten it out?
No
Woah
We're gonna smoke up in the bathroom together
the
and basically i tried to kill myself
brought to school
dancing robot
like size
and i put
with my ankles and one is one hand and my neck and the other and based on his
dance where it was like
He was gonna snap my spine.
Wait a second.
But...
Hold on.
The dancing robot did not succeed in killing me and instead it created a party in the hallway.
And that is the reason I'm in detention today is for starting a party.
And that very dancing robot, my friends, is in my locker.
Right now.
5 HP.
Did he tell you to bite his shiny metal ass at any point?
No, he is a dancing robot, not a wisecracking robot.
Does he like beer and smoking?
No, he likes dancing.
Okay, then it's not my uncle.
Can I ask you a question, nerd?
Shutting it down.
Yes, affirmative.
Affirmative.
Was this robot Blorbtron 3000?
Yes.
So it's my mom.
Some people have been saying that my mom is Blorbtron 3000.
Oh, has she been missing lately?
Because she's in my locker. Yeah
You're so brave for that you're so
Honestly, I don't feel very brave. I feel like a field mouse. No, you're so brave and I walk over to him
And I gets down
Yeah, I
I shoot my electricity into the AV room and all the cameras come on and start filming.
That's fun. I go up, I unzip the iZods, I unbutton them, I pull them down. I knew it!
You have a heart-shaped pube. What? Who told you about that? The janitor.
Hey guys, this is me, Eric, again. I thought I told you not to tell anybody about that!
I told you that because I thought it was cool!
Weird girl!
It's the second secret I told you that you just...
Why do I keep telling you shit?
Hey Eric, check this out.
Why do we hang out so much?
I just start...
Oh he's smoking jello.
See I'm the coolest character.
I get it man.
I get you kids.
AHHHHH!
I'm back to 5 HP.
- Ron, did you admit you did your rumor, right?
- I said, "Hey, Bozo, give me some of that."
- Oh yeah, I'm also at five.
- Yeah, you're at five.
- Did a rumor.
- Okay, well you maybe think this
Blorb Throne Tron 3000 thing is so crazy,
and I heard about that before too,
but I didn't even want to say anything.
- Thank you for not saying anything.
- Because I'm trying to protect my friends
who seem to have my back.
But while we're doing this,
did you know that Emilio actually has a girlfriend
who goes to a different school?
(gasps)
(laughing)
- I just, I just, I just--
- You can't.
Yeah, I faint. I swoon and I faint.
No!
I'm smacked. There's so much glass and blood all over my fists right now.
He's been using his electric powers and he's been charming the ladies in this room and the principal and the two boys.
And he hasn't even told us that he has a...
I have glass in between all the webs of my neck.
Is it true?
I'm on campus on the ground and I'm doing the thing that dogs do where they run in their sleep.
(laughing)
- Is it true?
Do you have a girlfriend that goes to a different school?
- Are you going steady with another chick?
- No.
(gasps)
- It's a lie.
- Whoa.
- I bolt away.
(gasps)
- Guys, it's not true.
- I dreamed it.
- Thank God, 'cause that's the craziest thing I've ever heard.
- You guys, I'm losing a lot of blood in my veins right now.
- Why did you lie?
- 'Cause I wanted everyone to think
that I've lost my virginity.
- Damn.
- Wait.
- Wait, you're a virgin?
I've had sex like a thousand times.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I had sex with a principal.
- We've all had sex 5,000 times.
- So I had to make it up, man.
I just wanted you to think I was cool.
- Because in my world, the nerd is cool.
- And the jock is lame.
And that's how I perceive the world.
- Is that why it's like an electric world?
- That's what it's like in the electric realm.
Everything's the opposite.
- I guess that makes sense.
- Wait a minute, you have electricity.
I now have Wolverine claws.
(laughing)
- You're like going spotty vision.
- We should kill the principal.
to
i'm like losing three damage i'm going to cash in my tokens
three damage i'm not cashing in any tokens
i'm taking it to the face, three damage to the face
because why the fuck not?
wait is it better, the tokens are points or the HP is points?
which makes us win
also going to get you. This is the last round of tension. You still take damage at the end
of it. I'm going to admit my reason for being here. What's up? The problem is I'm losing
a lot of blood from my fists and I smoked a bunch of fentanyl. Are you all smoking fentanyl
now? Is this it? Yeah. You're all lighting up fentanyl now. You're hanging out in the
library. You guys. Oh wait, you didn't get your dancing robot. We got him. Wait did we
go to the bathroom a second time? Well we just never get snuck to my locker, should we? Let's
get him. It's my mom! Let's do this! Can I say my thing so that I don't die? Before you do your thing,
before you do your thing, don't worry about your damage right now. Okay. Let's do, cause this was
in the bathroom. We're a retcon, go back to you sneaking to go get your room. And maybe they can
help me sneak if they want to have a dance party in the end of detention. Okay, cool. Oh I do the,
I do the light, my electricity to the light so it's dark so the hall monitors can't see. I love
- That's a great idea, you're gonna get a token for that.
Okay, cool.
- There's another hall monitor and I go in front of him
and I purse my lips.
- Use your charm.
- I use my charm and I purse.
- So they're gonna roll against your DC.
- What's that?
- They fail.
- And I use my observe.
- They're charmed by you, what do you want them to do?
- I go like this, ooh, and then I kind of wave my finger
and I'm walking down the hallway.
- Oh boy.
- And I go.
- They just like start walking towards you.
- And I keep doing a walk and I go, ooh,
and then they're doing the same walk behind me.
And I use my observe to notice that and I get a boner.
I take a photo of it and then I show the hall monitor and I say, "Oh, you're trying to fuck
a kid!"
The hall monitors are also kids.
Oh, they are?
Why do they have guns and batons?
Yeah.
I thought they were grown men.
They're cool kids.
That's why I killed them.
You didn't kill them.
Oh, I killed one of them.
Or stabbed one of them.
You stabbed one of them, that's fine.
I thought they were grown men.
Why would, why, you're a child.
Why would stabbing an adult be okay?
Yeah, well you can't go to jail.
Actually, no, I'm a grown man.
I'm a grown man.
Oh, you are grown.
Yeah, that's why I'd stab him.
Oh well.
Roll stealth.
With advantage, you only have to roll once now.
I would say.
Where's my die?
Between your charming and your... what did you do?
I guess we're just going to retcon that.
Can I observe too as well?
You can observe as well.
Alright, so that's balance ball?
Yeah, no, no, balance ball.
I thought I was about to die and I don't know what's happening at all.
You can observe first to try to learn about...
I get plus three actually because of the star, right?
Yes. You should roll sneak balance ball twice, but you can roll your observe once to see if
you can learn something about it to reduce your rolls.
Okay, I'm going to start out with observe.
I can't even with you right now. I farted.
That's 14. You did not fart.
You learned that one of the hall monitors is afraid of dandruff.
I had a fart earlier.
of
odds of this go to hate dandruff
well it happens so i want to present
europe
okay now i see only once now
and with advantage to the lights are off
okay that's six
and in nineteen you got your dancing robot you got my open i open my locker
and immediately disco ball lights are coming up with a lot of her eyes on
there's not a lot of you
and then we uh...
- Wait, I run to my locker and I get what's in my locker too
while the distraction's happening
and I run to the store across the street
and I buy White Claw.
- Okay, cool.
- Okay.
- You got a bunch of White Claw in the AC.
- So we have it.
- And then, all right.
- I get my frog, I guess.
- You get your frog.
- Yeah.
- Well, I have the fentanyl already,
so I think we're all set to have the final part.
- And then I go to my locker too.
- You get your baseball bat.
- I get my baseball bat.
- Okay, you're back in the library now.
- Okay, but I was dying, right?
'Cause I have a new hero.
You don't have time to do your thing.
Okay, I'm losing all the blood, I have Wolverine claws of glass in my fingers 'cause I punched
the mirror after finding out that he...
Had a fake girlfriend.
You should have just waited two minutes.
White as a sheet, and I'm standing there like...
'Cause the fentanyl and the blood loss, and I'm just like...
Yo!
Let me just say one thing real quick.
Okay?
Speak your truth.
I may be the most abused kid at school. Clearly. I may be a bit of a jerk sometimes.
What do you think fentanyl does?
It's the blood loss.
It makes you kind of homo-sensitive.
No, it's the blood loss and I can't, but I'm only alive just based on the pain killer.
Oh, okay, okay, okay, I'm sorry.
So, I'm just gonna come out and say it.
- What?
- I--
- What is it?
- There was a bomb explosion
of boogers and jizz and poop and throw up and pee.
- Wait, I heard a rumor about this.
- In the teacher's lounge.
And yes, it was actually, it's not a rumor
that that was an explosion
it was true and you did it okay i did it
but only because i wanted to eat all the proven that he has said that the in the
bookers because i don't get food at home and it's only thing i know how to eat
you only know you don't know why so you know what you didn't have lunch did you
no
quickly to have a little bit of food let's test this with the other characters
paper
but it's not a fool anybody know that's what he's picking that's the way you
get the radio your frog
here really only had real food you have a lot of only
yeah i can only have some to prove that i'm right more than one of the car
payment of what the police are today's that it looks brown
picture here
here i really want to score completely i'd take your frog a dip it in and give
it to them
i was gonna fuck that
it
i can't eat it
also cameron invented a new type of pencil
the
well
it
that's not true guys
and i think that the pencil it's absurd pencil perfect mathematically perfect
are we dancing or what
that's what i want to run a lot
uh... okay
she's dancing but that rumor was not true i just want to clarify it's
basically impossible to invent a new type of pencil
is that affect pencil and a mechanical pencil it's pretty much a pencil the
sword on it
that's not even a pencil they can shoot no more you know either way i didn't
invent any of those it's a false rumors to don't spread that any i go up to
alex's robot mom and i open up my circuit of the way and then her boobs come out
and she shoots a little
uh... i think
only after that and it brings him back to life
i mean you know
and he's got a full h_p_
you know you still have half but her tits come out and there's oil
okay oiled up
so i'll take that too
i'm sorry i can't stop showing my tits
yo your mom's the queen of the slut battle yeah my mom's pretty cool
pretty cool mom
what? it's just you guys hanging out
it's us cross legs it's us doing the dancing scene right
that's part of it
yeah music's music's playing right now
moves okay i said i'm holding my favorite
uh... glass window for glass door that i'd uh... it's my favorite glass door in
the world
i brought it from home i love it's my prize possession
it's so expensive i spent all of my allowance on it
and i just love it bring it everywhere i go
well it's on last door
wall
and that's my glass door
- Damn!
- You know, looks can be deceiving,
and what you're doing now is actually kind of cool,
and not like a nerd.
- Wow, you're the last guy in school to me now.
- Oh!
- But honestly, you say that now,
but like tomorrow, if I came into school
and I had a glass door, you'd probably kill me.
- The thing is, I've been acting a certain way in school,
like every single day, like when I see you guys,
I act like I'm like, don't even know you and stuff.
- Like a slut.
- But I think it's because I like low-key
don't actually even know who I am myself.
What's gonna happen tomorrow when I wake up and I go to work at Blockbuster?
Am I ever gonna see you kids again?
What?
Honestly, I'm not a kid.
I think we've established this.
This is my last day on earth before I enter the electricity realm for good.
Wait, can I come with you?
I heard nerds are cool in the electricity world.
I heard a rumor.
And then I give the nerd powers.
Oh my god, I get powers.
Kiss the nerd on the lips.
But seriously, will you kids come into the blockbuster I work at?
I will go to blockbuster.
I'm going to be real with you guys, I do not go to this school.
Oh wow.
I just wanted to come here and kind of hang out.
I was stuck on the back of your car for a couple days.
Oh, is that why you're dressed all in white?
I thought there was supposed to be a goth girl here and maybe that's why.
Because I thought it was weird you're dressed all in white, you have white hair.
I tripped her.
I opened the closet, the janitor closet.
the head of the head
dead
she's
all zombie but i a shit what's going on guys let me take a pulse
one three four
uh... you have to wait a minute
okay i think that's a good thing
okay so far zero
nine and eleven twelve
thirteen fourteen all i felt a heartbeat is getting
the
there's no time for jokes and sorry
- The hall monitors start to file in.
You guys are making a lot of a ruckus right now.
- No we're not.
- You're getting started.
- Book.
(laughing)
- Become a book.
- I go into the, I go into the outlet.
(laughing)
- Wait, can I turn into a book too?
- All of you roll a d20 to see if you can turn into a book.
You get higher than a 10, you turn into a book.
- I got a two.
- I got an 18.
- Wait, I don't turn into a book
and i'd wait for all of them to grab it turned to a book
and i grab all of the books
and i act like i was just like a normal person library
well it's only a few of them
we're going to have a look at the only i was a nerd became a book i was so
happy
here
okay i think i did it in a book about it was like okay
good idea
they were the the hallmark is what they were all going
but i i try to use i try to be as charming as possible and act like even
those who didn't turn into a book have turned into parts
there
with the senate
i wrote the three
but a
are not charmed by you their confused
whether it go
he's a book
he died in a meeting i did he's in the closet you'll never find them
it
what do you think you know that we're going to
so you just say what do you mean to you
he's a big dot
i did it and i think you know i think that what do you mean to you that
without the report that we dressed up as a girl
to humiliate 'em
all right and then we killed 'em
i have a better as you guys role initiative with a book
who's had a really a book
i got a fifty
i got a in i got a seven
minus three i got a four i got a nineteen
of this good for me
to have to learn anything again
fourteen
this minus okay i got four
and nineteen and in a
does not have to roll
nineteen go for a year
and the political weapon of who we are just chilling
nineteen you gotta go for the books title is all
uh... i have my nerd
uh...
uh... whose
whose nineteen
what i did
attack
sycam
this is all my life
uh... i think i would be a little bit of a sad flick
s
for you to be a good
uh...
I should. You have electricity powers now. Roll d20. Okay.
I'm writing your name on here like electro like an electro man or something.
Wait no no just roll on the table. Yeah roll on the table. It only counts if it's on the table.
Uh eight. Eight does not hit. So your electricity
shoots out from your fingertips and courses around.
But it creates, oh it creates like a cyclone around it.
It certainly does.
I've got a 14.
You did?
Pat.
Pat?
Alright, you're up man.
Alright, I am going to, so I have a brick of fentanyl.
I'm going to blow it in their face.
That would be, what's it called?
And then can I blow the thing and then go at them with my brass knuckles?
knuckles. Oh yeah, no no no. My brass knuckles with my Wolverine claws. Oh yeah, you'll add
plus two to damage. So you blow at them. I'm gonna go P. They're gonna have lower their
AC. Go. Okay. Well I got a seven. Alright, it's not gonna be that low. But you still
do something cool. They go "Ah, ah!" It gets in their eyes, right? The way they're moving
around, it's still somehow, it's almost like it accidentally worked out where the way they
they were moving around from like getting the fentanyl in their face allowed them to dodge
your attacks. It was just like an unfortunate thing. But they are sort of like blinking,
they're kind of in trouble there.
You're up.
Um, I...
You got the 8 right?
Huh?
Yeah. I'm going to use, I guess my dandruff.
Alright, they're going to have to roll against that.
Okay.
So that makes them blind and lowers their attacks.
So DC 13.
They get disadvantage on attack. They, one of them fucked up. The other one did make
it
to the book though? The sexism is too much. What? Does anything happen to the book when I throw it?
He lands, he turns back into you and you're naked. No, no, no, no, I'm still a book. No,
no, no, no, no. Nice try, but I'm a book to him. How would I know how to turn back?
Wait, I run over to the book and I just try to start reading it. I'm reading what it says inside
the book. The hall monitors are up. They're going after you first, Bender. What the flip did I do to
the
you know i think one and i'm and i'm and i'm not we're going to that you did one
damage from eleven some attend
normal from five zero four
uh... we're going to be a paper towels
we'd read your up electoral
office sidebar
paper towels yeah people also is a
he was a very hard and i don't know if you know that that's fine
we would do
uh... okay so they shot me here what have you got shot
I pull the bullet out.
That's awesome.
Yeah, you got to attack though.
You're your turn to attack.
So then I throw the bullet like a spiral like the perfect spiral
fucking like a football.
Electrolysis.
Yeah, and that's sick and I electrolysis to it supercharges
20 roll D20.
Somebody should do that in a movie to be honest and electric
jock should do that.
Six.
It looks sick, but it just sort of Peters out as it reaches.
It goes like yeah, you might as well be throwing up quarter.
Yeah.
Zoom in.
It's a little Peter face.
It's got a face.
Peter's out.
It's got a little Peter face.
All right.
You're a bender.
How close am I to them?
You're right up on them.
You were swinging at them.
Oh, okay.
Then, yeah, fuck it.
Just going to, just going to, is it, okay.
Which hall monitors is it?
Which ones are they?
Both white.
No, no, no.
I mean, are they though?
Is it the one that I stabbed from earlier?
- No.
- Okay, so it's the two that I charmed.
- You went to the nurse's office.
What?
- Is it the two that I charmed saying that my dad hits me?
- Yes.
- I'm gonna roll for crying.
- Okay.
- Because they already know my sob story.
- Roll talking.
Let's see how this goes.
- Okay, so I'm--
- And before that, what do you say?
- I'm saying, I'm looking at them, they're like--
- Show 'em the scar.
- Guns, oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
I pull up this and I show them right here,
my whole entire arm, this whole thing.
- It's like a Looney Tunes cigar.
- Yeah, yeah.
It's his Acme on it.
(laughing)
- In cigar burns, yeah.
- You see that right there?
Kinda looks like the Acme logo, huh?
(laughing)
Kinda looks like the Acme logo that's on the side
of an Acme baseball bat, huh?
That's what happens when you spill paint in the garage.
- That is an 18.
Wow.
- Wow.
- One of them just starts weeping.
(laughing)
- Is it the blind one or no?
- It's not the blind one.
- Is this, so the blind one is like,
what are you talking about?
- Who's that?
(laughing)
- A, C, M, E.
Now imagine that in braille.
and imagine if it was letters on my arm.
- He's only been blind for like 27 years.
- What's a tattoo?
(laughing)
- I don't think he knows.
- He knows braille immediately.
- He just blinded.
- He knows braille immediately, I don't know.
- Oh right, he's blinded.
- When you lose your sight, you just know braille.
- Three dots, four dots, one dot, six dots.
(laughing)
- One of his hearts weeping, he leaves.
He goes, "I can't do this, man.
"I can't keep hitting these kids.
"I can't keep shooting these kids."
- That was my whole action?
- Yeah, but one of them's gone.
Now, girl.
- Yes, weird girl.
- Weird girl.
I was confused. Sorry. Weird girl. You're up. There's one guy left. He's blind. I'm
I only have one attack so I'm just gonna unarmed strike him. Eleven. That hits. Yay.
- Yay!
- Woo!
- Roll for damage.
- One.
- All right, it takes one day to slash him.
- Bitch!
(laughing)
- All right, Molly.
- I try to campaign the troops to all work with me.
I try to get electric powers.
I try to get dandruff.
I try to get dancing robot.
I think that we've had such a troublesome time right now.
It seems like we're all just trying to figure out
who we are in this situation, and we're not actually,
we're not actually like beings ourselves,
we're being who we think we're supposed to be.
- I've been the most abused kid in school this whole time.
- So true, so true.
- But also you're like 28 and you live with your dad still.
(laughing)
- You're 28 and your dad is beating you.
- All right, oldie 20.
- I think we all need to work together.
- Describe to me what you do, what you do.
- I grab, I grab everyone's, I grab Emilio's hand,
I grab Bender's hand and then I reach out my foot
and put one foot like Twister on the book
and one foot in the lap of the weird girl.
- Just in my mouth.
- In the mouth.
- In your mouth.
- In the mouth and I'm kind of rubbing the foot around.
- She sees the foot and she drops down on all fours.
(laughing)
- And I'm trying to kind of, you know,
- Yeah, blast them.
- Megatron.
- Blast them.
- Voltron.
- You're doing like Paula from Earthbound.
And it's a seven.
(laughing)
- Roll again, you get advantage.
he did some cool
twenty
uh...
you wish you had a setback
of understanding
well
issue to all
i have a lot of the
uh...
this whole
there
it is all monitor
just evaporate
yes
this is the final boss
this is the final boss? ok
and he's gone
*laughter*
and look at this open up the book
uh... can flip all the way
is that's a good hand and i think that's what i'm saying here's what it is
it's a madly
what's on the whole speech that i like that i thought of best thing you've ever
come up with that thank you i'd like to have so excited
now
still in japan
doorway to get to the school run the circle yes i started a all-star you down
book
(laughing)
- Okay.
- Oh.
- So we're gonna go clockwise.
- On the way.
- Okay.
- Verb.
- Uh,
wrestle.
- Wow.
- A day of the week, sorry.
(laughing)
Can I, there'll be other ones.
Okay, I'll do--
- Do a holiday.
- I'll do--
- A holiday.
- Do a holiday.
- Oh, holiday weekend.
(laughing)
- Nice.
- Okay.
- Noun.
- The principal who's gay.
(laughing)
- Nice.
- Okay.
- Adjective.
(laughing)
- Weirdly.
- Okay.
- Adjective.
Literary.
Verb.
Wrestle.
Two.
Wrestle two.
Verb.
Um.
Apply makeup.
Verb.
squirting
uh...
it's important
now
slot
well
that is not like what the nerd with the i'm a majority i grew here that's not
what the book with a little everything better
i learned from you guys we have learned from you
you have a slip out of the economy
of course and it is a lot of the f_ important
okay this next for the alan and now and now and now and now and now
start with you
- Start with me.
Noun.
- High school.
(laughing)
- I'm gonna go,
I'm also gonna go with high school.
- Puerto Rican.
(laughing)
- High school.
- Purple elephant.
(laughing)
- Is Bender on Futurama's?
- I heard a joke in the show that he's Puerto Rican.
- I think he's a robot.
- Yeah, I'm pretty sure he's still a robot.
- He's a robot.
- I think he's steel.
I think he's from Tijuana, because they go back to Mom's Factory and he's in there.
I've only seen a couple of those.
Okay, alright.
Maybe I just made that up.
Thanksgiving.
So you guys all, you guys finished writing your essay.
You're writing it into the book and I'm going, "Oh, it tickles!
Oh, eee!"
(laughter)
- Take your final little damage.
- We're called the fucking Thanksgiving club.
- You only take one damage.
- Nice.
- Easy.
- Yeah.
- I survived.
- Wait, I'm gonna give a token.
- Me too, I'm gonna stay at five, why not?
- Not me, I wanna get down to one,
'cause I think that's almost the most perfect number.
- How do you guys leave the school together?
Do you leave the school together?
- Well, I have to be carried.
- Yeah, I put the book on my head.
I try to balance on top of a book.
(laughing)
- In a tower.
- Yeah, we're all walking down the fake place.
- Everybody gets on my body.
- All your parents' cars.
(laughing)
- They're not getting in the car,
they turned into a fucking tower.
- Found you.
- Forget about me.
- A giant tower of four kids and a book.
- You guys walk out.
Solving comes back into the library.
Oh, I didn't even get to say goodbye.
Hmm, what's this?
It's the essay.
That's nice.
I asked them all to write one, but OK.
Dear book, we accept the fact that we
had to wrestle a whole holiday weekend in the principal who
is gay.
for whatever it was we did weirdly
but we think you're a literary for making us wrestle to an essay of prime makeup
who we think we are
you squirting us
as you want to squirting us
in the simplest crips and bloods
in the most convenient slut
but what we found out is that each one of us is a high school
and a high school
a Puerto Rican, a high school, and a Puerto Rican.
(laughing)
- I'm sorry.
- That's better.
- High school, high school, Puerto Rican, high school.
(laughing)
Does that answer your question?
Sincerely yours, the Thanksgiving Club.
[LAUGHTER]
The Thanksgiving Club.
[HUMMING]
And you guys, all of you, throw your arms up.
Yeah, on the--
Oh, into the electricity realm.
We fly up.
Yeah.
And yeah, that's it.
That was beautiful.
Great movie.
Goodbye, everybody.
OK, then we have employee
injured by soccer ball.
And please tell me this is in FIFA.
An incident occurred when employee
number one was seriously
injured by a soccer ball.
The soccer ball hit employee
number one's head while supervising
kids playing soccer ball.
Employee number one was transported
and confined at the hospital
for treatment of her head
injury and concussion.
Occupation guards and police.
So it was a school cop.
A cop got hit by a soccer ball
and went to the hospital and then called OSHA.
Yeah.
I feel like he was planning that.
He was like, "I could probably get some comps off of that."
It was a girl?
Yeah.
He doesn't think girls can be guards and cops.
Cameron, a lot of yours...
No, I don't know.
Yeah, a lot of yours are girls.
A lot of them are women.
You're trying to hurt girls.
No, I don't think girls die as much as guys.
You don't think girls die as much as guys?
Yeah.
Because they don't have as many jobs.
No, I'm kidding.
Okay, then these are just a bunch of ones that don't have descriptions.
I just put the funny titles in.
"Employee suffers non-work-related chest pain."
So why call OSHA? I don't know. This doesn't fit to me.
Seems like you shouldn't call OSHA for that.
"Employee suffers burns when sprayed by thick, hot beet juice."
Was that a death?
Is that why you didn't include the description?
None of these are deaths.
I mean, the description of this was like,
"An employee got sprayed and burned very bad."
It's not very pleasant.
But thick, hot beet juice.
Yeah, it feels like the titles are funnier than...
Yeah.
So then, here's...
I have a whole series I'm gonna go through lightning round here.
Okay.
Employee is attacked by lion.
Employee's hand is bitten by wolf.
Employee's finger bitten by chimpanzees.
Employee discovers bees at work site.
Employee injured when attacked by river otter.
Employee injures leg when attacked by panda...
When attached by panda bear.
Employee injured by venomous vector.
I had this one. I have venomous vector.
Ah.
Employee injured by venomous vector.
I loved that one.
Employee is bitten by insect during maintenance.
employee performing some apartment maintenance and was bitten by an insect.
He hadn't seen employee injured when elephants
employee injured when door kicked by camel door kicked.
(Sonic the Hedgehog theme)