[Music]
Last time on Trebuchet Vill-
[Laughter]
Sorry.
Last time on Trebuchet Village, Orc Tank.
Our heroes attempted to pitch their wild and wacky idea for an amusement park called Idiotland
Stupidville to some of the richest creatures in Gal Gadot, the largest majority orc city
in the Terrifier Kingdom, built from the bones of long dead Kaiju Manji.
Prior to going out and pitching to the orcs, the gang leveled up to level 3, among the
most important levels in 5th edition.
Dogen spit in the face of his dirt god, but no dirt came out, because he was mad that
Dogen tricked him all these years into chewing dirt to commune with him.
So he did not chew dirt this time, and that's why no dirt came out when he spit.
He has become an oathbreaker, so it means he's renouncing good for an evil paladin.
And he's turning to the evil Oreo God, who is now canon.
Dogen the Oreo God.
As of last week, his name is Dogen also.
Dogen the Oreo God, yeah.
Okay, and I knew that too.
Dogen the Oreo God.
Oreos, God. Oreos.
You should change it to Duncan.
Duncan?
Dogan.
Duncan.
The Oreos, God.
Patrick Yodar decided to learn-
Duncan's a different God. That's the Donuts God.
I said that.
Patrick Yodar decided to lean into the inquisitive archetype.
He was choosing his roguish archetype, so he chose inquisitive.
Perhaps his curiosity and his penchant for mischief and shoplifting
have made him more wary, more observant, and more cautious.
cautious, although there are things he still remains painfully unaware, like the growth
spurts of the verdant.
Evil Steevel got some spells, while the Nards sit at the top of the kingdom, and King Nardwar
has outlawed slavery throughout the kingdom.
The orcs love of slavery defies its decree.
Yeah!
And that's the pitch that the gang made.
Who's doing that?
Wow, there's going to be anybody at the sound design on this D&D campaign.
It's so immersive.
Slaves!
I love slaves!
Slaves are so awesome!
Go slaves!
Slaves!
I want slaves in real life!
Patrick, what are you saying?
Pat, why are you saying that?
Pat, why did you say slaves are cool?
Pat, did you say "I want slaves in real life" really quietly?
No.
Why did you say that, man?
It's weird.
The five orcs in the orc tank are going to be slaves.
Slaves!
Five orcs in the orc tank questioned the adventurpreneurs, challenged their metrics and their vision,
and eventually made several offers.
The one that most intrigued Evil Stevel at least was the offer of two fish from and/or
for the giant walrus that wandered into the orc tank arena of Getsumdum about a year ago
and hasn't moved since.
In Orc Tank, when you accept an offer from one of the orcs, you have to fight them in
in combat. If you win, you can take their offer. If you lose, you die. Also, if you win, you
can take their offer, but you can also field additional offers after that are still on
the table. No one's ever fought, no one's ever taken an offer from the giant walrus
because the walrus never really makes an offer.
Yeah, we were the first ones.
You guys are the first ones. It's a big deal.
It's called being a trailblazer.
Yep, that's right. We're the first ones who had a good enough idea for the walrus to make
an offer.
We're breaking the glass ceiling.
we rolled initiative earlier in the evening so the order here we definitely
we it's not a trick or cheating or anything yep no earlier because people
will think it is we're not fudging the story of the game no each got dirty 20s
no it's not true patches isn't making these up off the top of his head to tell
the story he wants to tell well I'll re-roll right now
I'll re-roll no I got a 19 you are the only you are last in the order the
walrus is second to last okay you want to re-roll I just re-rolled I got 19
I'm happy being last all right Sullivan goes first I'm gonna shine from behind
actually so Sullivan does not go first he does he got a 17 plus 2 and so that's
Well, they're tied then no cuz camp Sullivan has a better initiative initiative bonus than me
We are we can't take we're nice. I have an initiative bonus scene is what I rolled before you do have initiative
I didn't actually roll a 19 just so I rolled a 12 and then what's my initiative bonus?
It's on your character. So your character sheet check it out
It's probably I think your decks is pretty high. Yeah, probably like plus
uh... of my initiative but we're lost three
plus three so i rolled a twelve plus a fifteen yes yet you're still in the same
spot because i'm sure you're in you
uh... don't ever taken at nineteen i didn't roll in nineteen just now i was
joking and nineteen is what i wrote letter so it's all to record this the
first time
i don't know yet i did okay okay so in that case in solvent is blood actually
before
after you because i know
he better be
I didn't know that, I thought you got a 17.
Please don't hurt him.
I actually have plus 6 initiatives, so Sullivan's actually after me.
So the arena is about like, you know, it's about like two football fields by two football
fields.
It's pretty massive, right?
It has a whole crowd of people from the city.
You guys and the walrus, so you see the other four orcs of the orc tank sort of walk towards
the side of the arena and go into like a little private boot box to watch a fight.
The walrus sort of is just kind of like confused about what's happening.
That's good, we got a surprise attack.
Yeah, and you guys are sort of in the middle right now of the arena and you see an announcer
go "Ladies and gentlemen, now the giant walrus versus..."
What do you guys call yourselves?
Uh, Stevel's...
The three best friends.
No, Stievel's Angels.
No, it's not Stievel's Angels, it's uh...
Evil Stievel's Angels.
I'm gonna have you both roll to see if you can persuade me.
Uh, maybe it's uh...
What about the good guys?
How about Stievel's Angels?
Dogen's Devils.
What the fuck?
All of you roll a persuasion check.
yodelers.
We're gonna need some more dice out here.
Get the 20. There it is.
Patrick Yodar?
How'd you do?
17.
Patrick Yodar has a +8 on persuasion I know.
So unless you get a crit.
No.
Patrick Yodar is gonna be able to decide what the name is.
Our name is uh...
Steevels Angels.
It's uh...
Patrick's Angels.
Patrice's Angels.
The worst name I've ever heard.
I'm fine with that, he split the difference.
And Patrice's Angels!
Patrice's or...
See, it doesn't really roll off the tongue.
It's not a very good name.
I think maybe, hold on, we want to change the name.
Maybe if we have a bad name, they'll underestimate us.
It's maybe a good idea.
It might be strategic.
If we get a bad name, hold on, I've got a worse name.
The Poop Guys.
That's a better name.
The Poop Eaters.
That's a way better name.
The shit fuck the homeless guys
homeless guys homeless guys
three three homeless guys three homeless
And three homeless guys
Technically true. Yeah
Where I fucking live you said a bush once
Hardly a home
it's so uh... yeah it's so
initiative starts of the walrus has like a position in the turn order
but he doesn't really know what's going on
so uh... dogan you definitely have a opportunity here for uh... a surprise
round
uh... ok all would have an opportunity basically for a surprise round
uh... again
yeah i'm going to just i'm gonna surprise round i'm going to attack
the walrus with my war hammer which is not a shovel anymore because i don't like
and
lazily just sort of
wobbling back and forth is getting a little wary of you but not really sure
what's happening. Okay well I rolled a seven.
Okay, a seven.
Plus what?
A seven. A seven total? A seven total, yeah.
Okay, you
trip.
He has a low arbor class. Oh no. You just sort of trip and like your spoon goes
flying out. And hits him? And uh... just like five feet in front of you. And it hits him?
does not damage does not hit him he gets your about a dozen feet in front of the
walrus
who is now just kind of just like
he's just kinda like confused and a little startled by you
uh... it's Sullivan's turn
uh...
Sullivan sort of like looks at you guys and says like
should I
should I attack him?
yeah what do you think? Sullivan don't attack him we why would you attack
we want him to invest in our idea
but the rules to go listen go up
get real close to him
okay give him a kiss right on the lips
i don't
come on go ahead
right between the tusks start pushing him by his butt just like pushing him in
uh...
stop puckering up you got some chaps there you want me to kiss him? yeah right on the lips he's about to be your boss
wow uh...
alright so he's gonna have to i guess roll an attack roll i guess to do that
I guess it's an attack roll.
He does anything we say.
Pretty much.
Alright, where are the d20s?
There's one right here.
Oh, thank you.
Okay.
Start emptying out more of the dice bags while I roll.
So we can just...
I'll empty your bag.
Don't say that.
Okay.
So he goes to like, at the very least, embrace the walrus.
And with that, um, uh, you can get all the audio of that.
That's a good sound.
Yeah, and with that, uh, uh, solid zero, like that eight with no bonus on it, he, uh, he
instead sort of like, accidentally like grazes his hand just across the walrus' stomach and,
and uh, uh, the walrus is sort of like, "UGHHH!"
What are you doing, Sullivan?
Walruses hate that!
I'm sorry!
I didn't mean to do that!
We said to kiss him, what are you doing?
I tried.
Oh my god.
I got nervous!
How do you, how do you fail a kiss?
- Have you ever kissed before?
- We're gonna take you out tonight.
- Oh God, he's never kissed before.
- We're going out tonight.
After this is over, we're going out tonight,
we're getting Solomon his first kiss.
- I think technically I'm still, I mean,
I'm not saying this solo--
- Technically they're still married, I think.
(laughing)
So, yeah, but we don't remember.
- Yeah.
- That's why you're too loyal.
- Too loyal to what?
what yeah I don't know I remember something but nothing sorry I was zoomed
out in the moment somebody ever wants to tell me if I if they think I did the
attack role as the option for kissing right I think that makes sense but I
thought it was funny I would love to know okay now it is so far okay
Patrick's turn so far you've done no damage to this walrus that doesn't even
know it's fighting.
So I'm curious.
I'm going to shoot it in the head with a bow and arrow.
Yeah, go for it, brother.
Yeah, this is a...
Let's think of this as an investment.
I guess I don't really...
I really don't understand.
Are you trying to say something cool right now?
Yeah, I was.
Did that work?
I don't know.
You have a plus eight in charisma.
I don't know what's happening.
Say like, "I'm going to invest this arrow in your damn baller's brain."
- I think this arrow's like on a chart of sales.
It's like an arrow that goes up on sales.
- You're about to be in the red.
- What was that animal in that book
that's been going around, Moby Ditch?
- Moby Ditch?
- Yeah, it's one of his fucking dirt books.
- Ditch Whale.
- I think it was a dirt whale, yeah.
- A dirt whale?
It's kind of like a worm?
- What are they saying in that?
Maybe I could--
- What does this have anything to do with--
- I was gonna pull a quote here.
Call me announcer, call me dirt mail.
And he's loading his crossbow I think!
Look I, I, I, I need it.
The whole audience is booing you.
It's the most boring fight of all time.
Ah shit, alright, alright I guess I'm just gonna.
Touch the walrus.
Guess I'm just gonna shoot him with an arrow.
Sixteen.
Check your plus, it's pretty good brother.
Uh, it's your crossbow, I can also check on mine.
my hold on let me just pull that up
um
oh wait
he's talking that whole time didn't even pull up the crossbow
it's plus 5 so it's a 21
oh shit
uh that hits 100%
yeah in his head?
uh if you yeah I would say if you wanted to hit in his head it does
I did say I was gonna hit his head
yeah you did so it's 1d6
oh 1d6
1d6 and then we're gonna add 3 to that
damn ok
so yeah you just like are babbling about random shit
And just like like just casually launched a crossbow on the walrus. He's just
and just like
Like it just screams like bloody murder
He's now kind of aware of what's going on
I would say evil you see you want to lower my voice there evil. I would say it's Europe
You still get you still the surprise round is still going on. Yeah, it's all happening within the same six seconds
I did not realize the the walrus would be so mad at that
I think I'm gonna want to use Chill Touch.
Hell yeah.
Um, to try to take out the crossbow bolt and then stick it back in in the same hole.
Ooh.
I will allow that.
You should try that shit.
Okay.
So...
I don't, I, I, that sounds fucking cool.
What do I roll here?
Um, you would roll...
Attack roll.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Alright.
A one.
Ooh, crit one.
Oh my god.
- Oh my God.
(laughter)
- The, uh, you take out the crossbow bolt
and you pat his head with a chill touch.
(laughter)
Whoops.
- That was really, actually really kind of you, Steevel.
- My non-dominant chill touch hand.
- Level three changed you.
- I don't have a lot of control over it.
- You're a nicer guy now.
- So, yeah, maybe I became a little bit sweet.
Maybe I've been evil this whole time.
Level three changed me.
- Sweetie Steevel.
That's a rough, yeah.
- The walrus. - Evil Sweevil.
- Evil Sweevil. - Evil Sweevil.
- Sweetest Beevil. - Sweetest Beevil.
- Sweetest Beevil. - I don't know,
we'll come up with a new name later, it doesn't matter.
- This arena has made us, it's very flustered I think.
- Yeah, something about this really.
I got a lump in my damn throat.
- Yeah, I think, Ken, our stage fright.
- It's the stage fright. - Oh my God.
- Butterflies in my tummy.
- Will you guys stop talking?
- Oh, that guy's part of the audience.
- Come on, guys, like, head's exploding with anger, he's not seeing blood.
- I forgot about my stage fright.
- So the walrus is now up,
who he is, I'm gonna give him a chance to attack in this case.
He's going fucking nuts. He's going to go after Sullivan, 'cause Sullivan's right in
front of him.
And I think, is that how it's arranged on that? Yep, it's just Sullivan.
So let's see how that goes. Wow, he got a crit one.
So he tries to body flop on Sullivan and instead he falls backwards.
He just like goes "RUAAAGH" like he hasn't fought in so long.
He just rolls backwards like "RUAAAGH" he's like on his back.
He's all upset.
He's like so upset about it.
I can't wait.
I like, can I real quick just like walk up to like the middle of this like kind of fight
that we're trying to have.
Yeah.
Just look at everybody be like "What are we doing guys?"
Yes.
I mean we've just been-
As a reaction, you're doing a speech.
Just barely, just whiffing punches point blank.
Just looking at- just fucking slipping on banana peels and shit.
Hey, I hit my target. I don't know about you guys.
How about this? Not you, but how about this?
What if we just call it a day?
We just restart. We just go-
Walrus, you still want two fish, right?
Alright, listen here buddy. I'll give you two fish if that's what it's gonna take.
Roll... God, I don't know. Persuasion on the walrus? He doesn't know what fish are.
He doesn't know what fish are?
He kind of knew.
He said the word fish.
Oh yeah, I did do that, huh?
Wannick?
(laughter)
You know what? Never mind.
With that "wannick" the walrus just like...
Like you're like wandering up to the walrus.
He's like on his back, like whining.
He just fucking farts in your face.
(laughing)
Not even on purpose.
- This is getting worse by the second.
- He just like farts.
- Yeah, I'm starting to taste that.
That is disgusting.
That is one of the grossest things.
- Oh God, I was gonna say.
- It tastes like two fish.
- You know, we're outside too,
and the fact that I can taste it is just awful.
- It's like he farted in a sedan.
God damn.
With the windows up.
Yeah, you know it tastes a lot like pickled onions. Can you taste that?
The giant walrus has the ability to hold his breath. That's like a known ability.
He holds his breath.
For 30 minutes.
What?
Yeah, I'm running in a circle and like a green cloud of fart is following me in a circle.
I think the cloud's forming a fist.
Alright, I'm going to say that the walrus, which typically has a multi-attack, is not
able to with that one.
So I'm going to say we're going to go back to the top of the order.
Dogen, you're up.
Okay, alright, this time I'm going to make this count.
You're still, yeah, you're definitely still, like, you're close enough that you can try
to hit him, I would say.
I'm going to, you know what, I'm going to cast Inflict Wounds.
Alright.
I'm going for it.
Tell me about Inflict Wounds, brother.
Well, basically, you know how like when you take an Oreo and you twist it apart?
Yes, yeah, I'm familiar.
So it's like that, but I can just take a, just, you know, just like the cookie part of an Oreo,
I just have one of those in my pocket and I put it on their skin and if I twist it,
it can pull out, like it can like peel them apart.
You can pop their heart.
You're in a temple of doom, this poor walrus.
It's the only thing that's gonna work, okay?
Okay, I believe you.
Yeah, roll a melee spell attack.
*laughter*
That's crazy!
Oh my god.
How did it do that?
We can't even count that.
It was as no number was up.
Non-NA.
Okay, that is a 13.
That absolutely hits.
Okay, that's...
That's 3d10 necrotic damage.
Yeah, okay.
So, get wicked wild with it, brother.
Let's find you a d10, yeah.
You can just roll one three times.
No, you gotta roll three at once.
You gotta roll all three at once? Yes sir.
That is...
24.
God damn.
Can you describe, like I'm gonna give you free reign
to describe what you do with that kind of damage.
Yeah, well I do the Oreo thing
and it just like takes out like a cylinder
of like blubber
of like
and it just, it looks
and I pull it out and I take another Oreo
cookie and I put it on the other side
It's like a 100x stuff Oreo filled with walrus blubber.
- Yeah. - Do you eat it?
- Hell no, that's disgusting.
- Why not? - Oh my God.
- I only eat Oreos with cream.
- You feel the dark presence of the Oreo God
like times wobbly. - And these times
blubber is clean.
- I put it, I put it, here's the, I put it in my bag.
I'm starting an Oreo collection.
- Okay. - That's my character's
new twisted thing is he collects the flesh
of everybody in Oreos.
- I'm gonna add that to add to your inventory.
- I turned it into a-- - It is one of the
weirdest things I think I've seen.
Well, I can't help it, I'm evil now.
Yeah, this is like a new turn for this guy.
Blubber Oreo.
I don't know, I think I'm not used to it.
I think maybe--
You'll get used to it.
Yeah, as time goes on, maybe I'll become used to it.
The thing is, it's still the same old me.
I just do weird stuff now.
Yeah, no, that is not the same old,
you just made Oreo out of walrus fat.
I would have done that before.
While the walrus--
While the walrus was still alive, too.
I'm just more confident now.
Yeah, the walrus, he's screaming in pain.
I mean you've beheaded a guy but we've all done things but
Yeah they should say one more thing for me. That walrus is still alive.
Yeah well I didn't kill it.
Oh I guess okay I mean I'm not gonna kill it. Yeah rather I killed it. Now that I'm thinking about it
you didn't kill it Knight. It's fine. I'll just heal it later too. Well
I guess it's my turn in the game. Go Sullivan.
Go Sullivan. Eat your birthday.
Sullivan is going to do. We're gonna party like it's Sullivan's birthday.
I wish it was Sullivan's birthday. Drink Bacardi like it's Sullivan's birthday.
Sullivan is gonna do a uh... instead of trying to kiss the guy, he's gonna do
um... fairy fire.
So um... this walrus has to uh... Instead of trying to kiss the guy, he's gonna do fairy fire.
Alright.
You know, you're gonna be thankful if it goes well, I'll tell you that much.
So the walrus has to try to
avoid the fairy fire if it's coming towards it.
and he does console vans
uh... spell spell d_c_ is not very good
so solvent russic s very fire on them
and the walrus is just able almost like sees the lake blue sparkling energy
that's gonna like wrap around and create a guys all advantage and sort of like
uh... that's it away with a flipper
and i think it's a man in the crowd you suck up
that's what i say when i see guys i'm about to thank solvent about you really
thankful that i have a nice dot is anyone in the crowd ur it gets close to
like a child and then dissipates right before it reaches it and Sullivan's now
gonna do gonna gonna look to Patrick Yodar and he's gonna say Patrick Yodar
you are you will go far in this fight tonight it rhymed yeah and he said that
because he gives you a bit of bardic inspiration so it was beautiful I
I actually, uh, actually really, can you write that down for me?
Uh, yeah, uh...
I have a little bit of parchment in my back pocket if you could...
Okay, yeah.
While I'm attacking, can you just write that down?
Yeah, absolutely.
And then I'll put it in my back pocket and I'll just...
Yep.
Do you know how to write?
Oh, yeah, I'm one of the few who are literate in Trebuchet Village, so...
You know how to write?
Yeah.
Is there another way I should say that?
Are you lying to me? I think you might be lying to me.
I'm not lying.
Can you read? I can read, yes.
I can't read every language, but Common for sure.
Can you do complex calculations?
Yeah, that was what I was going to ask next.
Well, that sort of depends.
How complex?
I did want a general score.
Yeah, he's lying.
What number am I thinking of?
Yeah, answer that.
While this is going on, I'm like...
Six?
Absentmindedly just like...
No.
Oh, that's the number I'm thinking of.
Zero.
Oh.
My favorite number.
Well...
All right, so I launch you while while that's happening. I'm so consider shooting. Yeah, yeah, so roll d20 you also have us now
You have a cat one bardic inspiration. You could use as well. Okay. Do I have to use it right now?
No, you can use it whenever you want. It's a d6 to any ability check or attack roll. Okay, or that you do
All right. I think I'm just gonna go plain here. Yeah, go for a plane plane shot
You can use it after the roll, but before I declare the result, okay
17 again. Yeah, we lost five that's for sure. Yeah, we're damage. So that's a d6 again
Three plus three so there's six damage to this walrus it walrus is not looking too too hot right now
You guys are just chipping away at it
So it's just like
bitch now it's a walrus his turn so he's gonna get up and he is gonna try to
belly flop again this time on Dogen because Dogen took out a chunk of his
flesh so see how he does that's a natural 20 oh man so that's gonna be a
crit so let's get the give me some d8s at least one is fine no okay so I'm
I'm gonna roll this a few times.
- Uh oh.
- Okay, that's not so bad, it's a one.
- Oh, okay.
It's another one.
- Oh baby.
- All right, you're getting--
- Oh dude.
- A five, okay, and another one.
- Oh my god, dude.
- That could have been very bad.
Instead, you take 14 damage from that.
- 14?
- That could have been--
- What are you talking about that could have been,
That's pretty bad.
That could have been, I mean it could have been anywhere between...
Alright, I'm at 11.
You got this, bitches.
I believe in you.
38.
Mmhmm.
And, uh, kinda closer to what we got this time.
Alright, so, uh, now he's gonna go after you again, since the body flop went so well.
What?
He's gonna go after you again with his tusks.
Um, so he's gonna roll a d20, let's see how he does.
Is he trying to bite me?
He's gonna try to like just like fucking gore you.
His mouth is going towards me?
His uh yeah yeah.
I hold out the oreo that I made out of gum.
Oh you gonna make him eat his own damn food.
He's gonna do it himself.
Dude it's it's up to him.
All right.
You gonna make him eat a snack man out of himself?
It's his own choice.
You gotta figure out how that resolves.
You gotta.
Wow it worked.
It worked it worked in the universe we live in now.
We got a crit one.
He yeah wow amazing.
So he goes to get you, and he sees his flesh, and you watch his eyes well up with tears.
I think he thinks it's his son.
Yeah, his son is a little Oreo.
If you had Walrus POV right now, you would see it becomes like a baby Walrus.
It goes "mrm, mrm".
And he just stops short of attacking you.
It just rears back and just like is thinking more than a walrus has ever thought before.
And now it's Evil Stevel's turn.
Okay.
You said he's not looking so good?
No.
Alright, I'm not going to waste one of my awesome super spells on him.
That's what I call them.
I'm going to use...
Yes sir.
I'm going to use Ray of Sickness.
Fuck yeah, dog.
Problem?
That's so funny you had that in your...
Ray of Sickness.
Describe to me Ray of Sickness.
Ray of Sickness is I mean...
I don't know.
I've never used it before.
Hell yeah. I guess we'll see. I'm guessing it's gonna be
like a green beam of vomit.
It literally says a Ray of Sickening Greenish
Energy lashes out.
Yeah, so I'm pretty smart. So it'll come out of
my hands like kamihamiha
and it will hit him.
And I guess he gets like sick in a couple days?
Uh, yeah.
I mean he basically on a failed save he'll get poisoned so it's a it's an attack
Plus it does damage right? Yes. Oh, yeah, it does damage. So roll roll a d20 to see if it lands and then I'll see if I can save
Shit balls
There we go - fuck
You shoot this ray of sickness out
And it just sort of like dissipates as it's reaching towards him
and he's still like staring like sort of like he's hearing like a
Like a Mazzy star song in his head as he's like zoning out
Can't believe that he like saw his own flesh before him. I think he didn't notice I went
able to do another turn
Nice try pretty funny, but it's Dogen's turn okay
I okay now it's time to get really evil
the crowd hears that and goes like nuts when they hear so I hold the Oreo over
the spot that it came from and I'm trying to hit it in with the shovel to put it back into its place
like hammering in a nail
this is awful
and I'm and I'm gonna do this attack on every enemy from now on
Wait, plus what though?
Seven.
That hits.
A seven hits?
Oh, you got a seven.
I think you said plus seven.
No.
No, no, no.
A seven.
So you go, "Can you tell me what happens if this fucks up?
Because it's pretty funny."
I hit my thumb with the shovel and it puffs up really big like a cartoon.
And I go, "Ouch!"
Yeah, yeah.
You go, "Yeah!"
Yeah, exactly.
I start hopping around in a circle.
Yeah, the walrus is still in a daze.
Sullivan, it's Sullivan's turn.
And after his, the terrible showing of his fairy fire,
he's instead going to take out his knife, his dagger,
and try to just stab the walrus.
As it worked for him last time,
the last time he stabbed, he stabbed the brave lion,
so he's going to try it again.
D, 20.
There's two right there.
there you kidding me there's one right there oh no wait nevermind it's not d20
here stupid oh my next time next time we'll just have the dice there's one
right there for and okay that is six or nine that's a six and that hits that's
whoa this guy's AC is cuz plus three that hits and so solvent is gonna need a d4
so it's a triangle the pyramid the triangle fucking all right and let's see
Yeah he does.
He has a four?
Nice, Sullivan!
So Sullivan runs up to this thing,
after you try to like, knock the flesh and hit your thumb,
it's like you pull back, and Sullivan rushes in,
and then just like goes like,
"AHHHHH!"
Just starts stabbing him in the stomach,
uh... normal
like finally snaps out of its days after seeing its own flesh after all these
failed attempts at attacking it
and uh... assault asserts damien sammy and stamming it
the walrus starting a really fucking pissed off
uh... you're up
uh... patrick
so i see the whole that cameron left
you really need the orio
and uh...
i just i look at the crowd
like they bruise
and i point my arrow
at the whole
I'm just like you know like windmill swinging my arm like huge balls huge
balls huge balls that's right I'm gonna hit that I'm gonna get my arrow in his
hole
yeah right they're all chanting your name huge balls 18 that fucking hits
oh god I can I just do one lick of damage and then I hope you can
What? D6 for damage?
Yes. Okay. And we get a...
Preview. Roll again.
There's two. So bad at rolling it onto the table. You just shoot at him and yeah it goes in the hole and just like
you almost can feel, see the arrow like nestle in there like it's a fucked up thing and the crowd is going nuts
and the walrus is like "No, no, no!"
I think it's just like so upset about it. I just, all I do is I look at it
put the arrow like into my back and just
flip it off
that's gonna do psychic damage oh yeah how much do i do i roll for psychic damage
no
not quite uh... how bad is the walrus looking
he's looking pretty bad a couple more hits i think he's gonna die uh... yeah he's
definitely looking bad
he looks like shit
walrus ass i say that to the crowd
this walrus looks like shit right now yeah this walrus looks like shit
which you big ass buck teeth. Yeah look at this stupid ass walrus. Yeah he looks so awful.
He looks like shit. Can we roll for psychic damage? Yeah guy he looks like shit. He looks
terrible. If we bully him. If we bully him. I don't care about bullying him I just want
the crowd to cheer for us. I'm just saying for the long game. Yeah kill his ass. I still
have stage fright though. Fuck that walrus. The walrus is. Get it out. What what what what
hours no don't don't do that to him it's the hardest feeling. It's a humongous stadium right now.
Just picture everybody in the crowd in their underwear. I mean I know half of
them are already in their underwear they're orcs but I mean picture the half
that is not in their underwear specifically in their underwear. All right
all right I think I got it okay. Man you are the most beautiful woman I have ever
a scene you have humongous breasts imagine it's all guys
actually you know what never mind I think I think the response that was good
The crowd is loving this we're gonna make a t-shirt of this phrase later.
Hey! Get him out of this hotel!
Woo!
Like it's just, it's silly.
That's our new pitch.
I got this for you.
T-shirts here! Get your t-shirts! Get me out of this hotel t-shirts!
So anytime you finish a joke just say, "Get him out of this hotel."
I got it.
Alright, so the cowboy hat's gonna add to that.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Uh, it is, uh, the walrus's turn.
[laughter]
So he's gonna try to belly flop on--
You're gonna be called to get him out of this Hotel Jones.
He's gonna wander over to, to, uh, uh, he's not really close enough to get to Patrick, I just realized.
So he's gonna try again against, uh, uh, this time against Sullivan.
Let's see how he does.
Okay, so that hits our poor Sullivan, our poor sweet Sullivan.
Let's see how he does. Alright.
Uh, yep.
-Oof. -Oh ho ho.
Alright. Uh, that's one.
-Oh boy. -Oh no.
Alright, two. So, Sullivan takes a...
Uh, oh god.
Sullivan takes 16 points of damage.
He is down to 2 HP.
This walrus just body-fights.
I was like, "Ahh! Ahh!"
Solvin's like trying to run away wherever he goes, the shadow's following him.
And eventually he just like...
gets crushed.
And the only thing that saves him is that he goes directly into the hole...
[laughter]
...that Dogen made.
And now the walrus is gonna try to gore Solvin.
Is he stuck in the hole?
What?
Well, he's stuck in the hole, how can he gore?
He's gonna go back out.
His legs are sticking out of the hole.
Yeah, his legs are wiggling out of the hole like a Winnie the Pooh thing.
He's like, "Ahh! Ahh!"
So if the walrus attacks the hole, he's gonna attack himself with his big tusks?
I would say potentially.
That's pretty bad. Does that hit Sullivan though? Because he has a...
So the walrus could be inflicting damage upon himself right now.
Right, or Sullivan could be like biting the walrus from the inside.
It does hit Sullivan, unfortunately.
So...
This is... I mean, I'm just gonna...
There's literally no possibility...
Maybe when Sullivan falls...
Sullivan might be dead, so I should roll for that actually.
When Sullivan dies, maybe he voids his bowels and it gives the walrus sepsis.
Let's see...
What if Sullivan dies?
Is he just gonna straight up die?
He might.
Like, not like unconscious, like die?
Let's see, 'cause that was...
That can't happen.
Oh my god.
2 plus... what was that second roll?
It was a... yeah.
I don't know.
I don't remember.
It was actually a negative one.
Okay, he almost died, but he didn't die.
He is knocked out, though.
Uh, yeah, if you get negative your full HP, I consider that death.
That's how I do it.
Oh my god.
So he almost died. He was about two hit points away from dying.
That's really scary to me.
Uh, yeah.
I'm gonna fuck this guy up.
Solvin is knocked the fuck out.
Uh, that was the walrus's turn.
Uh, still in the hole, just...
Yeah, the walrus just like, somehow like, fucking like, gored him a little bit with his tusk from the hole.
I mean, Solvin just like, stopped moving.
You just see these like, frog legs dangling from the hole inside his body.
Um, but yeah now it is your turn Evil Stevel.
Okay. Um.
*clears throat*
Let me get my book of spells out.
I will use...
Ah, my book of spells is loading.
*laughter*
Uh.
Is, uh,
It's gonna, for me it's gonna be, uh...
Yeah! Get him out of the hotel!
Get me out of this damn hotel!
See, I told you it's gonna be amazing.
It worked, alright. I got full confidence now. I'm gonna use level 2, uh, Inflict Wounds.
Woooo! Yes, dude, do it.
Three. Dude, I, what the fuck, there's something wrong with me today.
today yeah dude this is this is gotten like well and one five three is that plus
five yeah damn I'm gonna just tell you now his
AC is nine I know did I deduce to that yeah you did all right well you almost
inflict yeah you see like the outline of a wound appears on him like a dotted
line where it would have been some question marks pop up you say you say
like get me out of this hotel everyone's like yeah like they're a little confused
on what you just did and like what that has to do with the catchphrase the
walrus is is is though like reeling it is it is furious
Dogen you're up okay he's not looking too good I'm going inflict I'm gonna
cast inflict wounds. Get the fuck out. I am. And I'm going to... Can you do that? I can
do that. And this time my inflict wounds, because it's different every time, is that
I reach into my bag and I pull out a glass of milk and I'm pouring evil milk into the
hole because milk and Oreos is like a... Oh yeah, no I'm... An Oreos thing. I'm smiling
evilly at this. That's a crit. Sorry. Sorry Caleb. I just don't get what I did wrong.
- Okay, wait, no, I pour milk onto the spot
where you aimed and it only crits
because you almost got one already.
- Mm-hmm.
- So it's basically like I couldn't have done it without you.
- You loosened the jar.
- Yeah, I helped on that one, by the way,
and get me out of the hotel right now.
- Get him out of the damn hotel.
Get this guy out of this damn hotel.
- Fuck hotels!
- I'm in the corner, like, there's like a,
what's it, the mill?
What's the thing that makes shirts?
- What?
that makes sure like a woman yeah I guess in these times I'm the preacher is like a
Chinese baby yeah well so I just have like a loom I have a loom and I've been
making shirts that say I'm not confident enough to correct him yeah I have a loom
and I'm making sure you say get me out of this damn hotel turning I'm turning
it Caleb like yeah that's right keep it going this is orc tank that's gonna be
second pitch. Just that sure. I mean you guys saw how funny this was. So I think you do
with was it 3d10? It's like some crazy shit. Yeah. Yeah I mean so you do 6d10. Okay.
6d10. Alright that starts with 10. 13. Oh my god. 23. Oh. 27. Okay. Okay. No let me keep going.
to
kill this thing or just knock it out with inflict wounds, which is why I think this rule by
5e is crazy, but I like it.
Yeah, I'm knocking it out. I'm knocking it out by the milk goes into the hole, the milk
drips into the same disgusting hole, and the milk goes into the walrus's bloodstream, and
it becomes unconscious.
Yeah, it's just like it as you do that
Just like it that walrus that can't say anything but sometimes fish just say lactose
it's just like collapses on the ground and the audience goes fucking nuts and
these
Goblin medics run out and they like prep the walrus and like revive it and it just sort of like wakes up days
It is like starts to charge you guys. I've been like one of them like when they got ones holds a fish up
I mean
Like feeds it a fish and it's like sort of calmed down a little bit
And you see the other orcs come out you see the announcer come out and the answer goes the winners are
The poop eaters it was that three homeless did three homeless guys. I didn't remember sorry three homeless guys three
homeless guy
let me out of this hotel
yeah, cause you're homeless you can't
so, it's not allowed here
you're a vagrant
so you guys can go with the walrus
with your
extremely confusing offer
or you can talk to the other orcs
see what's out there
I grab them, I grab them
is it like a magical microphone?
say it's a magical microphone
say there's a magical camera too
TV camera go on good and I say we're going to Burger King that was just you
know what hey it was just good enough that's all we're happening now so what
it does is it you take the camera is just constantly drawing an image every
image yeah 20 24 images a second it's just drawing on a giant like projector
uh... reporting is said
uh... of the honestly
what's that
it's like i have a king of bird and you guys are the burger king from the burger
kingdom dot entire audience goes are are
will be
maybe a fucking go out for once maybe don't stay in the stadium
that's what i have a lot of what i thought i had a hotel
it's not a big it's not a funny anymore. You owe me 600 dollars. You owe me 600 gold coins.
This guy is like a little kobold, he's like scurrying away. He's like scary. I can see you.
Cameras, get this guy. Follow him out of the stadium if he tries to run away.
He owes me 600 gold coins for saying his catchphrase. Yeah, follow him out of the stadium from a really low angle.
Yeah.
Get up in there. So do you guys, are you guys gonna... He's wearing nothing but a kilt.
You can clip through it. Get under the kilt.
Are you guys gonna go for the walrus
or do you guys wanna do other offers?
I think honestly,
I think we should feel more offers.
Here's my idea.
We feel more offers, we now sweeten the deal
with the let me out of this hotel t-shirt line.
What do you think?
Yeah, we can sell it at the--
Well, we sell it at the park.
Yeah, we can sell it at the park.
Okay, all right, and okay.
We could have a ride maybe called Escape the Hotel.
Yeah, it's the haunted hotel.
Escape from Hotel.
Escape from Hotel, that's a good name.
And it's haunted.
And they could have little cardboard cutouts of me.
Like I could be the like,
you must be this tall to enter a ride.
- It's a good one, and then maybe--
- And I could be like one of me that says,
we're going to Burger King, baby.
- Yeah, that, and then I think maybe like,
you know like the ride starts out,
so you get into the hotel.
- Yeah, and you're in a car.
- You're in a car, you get into the hotel,
and maybe I'm one of the people that says,
enjoy your stay, if you dare.
- That could be good, that could be really good, yeah.
Can I be like the old-timey prospector before you drop off the log flume?
Well yeah, well I mean, you see Sullivan is trying to write all of this damn thing.
Are you getting that? Can you write?
I'm trying, I'm trying to keep up with all of it.
I still don't know if Sullivan can write.
I think this is a good idea because the fish thing didn't really make any sense money-wise.
I think we should field at least one other offer. I'd be open to two.
Yeah, I think one offer is good.
is good. I say I want to talk to Mr. Awful. I think that's our guy. I want
I want there to be I want on in this escape the hotel ride I want there to be
one one room where you can buy and sell drugs on the ride. Yeah that's a good
idea I think maybe I think maybe Ola the the the what did that orc lady I kept
yelling it. Yeah that was her name her name was Ola. It was Ola? It was Ola. H-O-L-A?
It was OLA. I was trying to avoid that sort of thing, but yeah. I mean I was trying to avoid that sort of thing, but yeah.
What sort of thing, Sullivan? A Hispanic name? You don't like saying them?
The DM's brain breaks.
You got a problem with Latina baddies?
No, none at all.
What do you think, Steve?
So, so Patrick thinks we, we, we fight Ola. I'm saying Mr. Awful, you're a tiebreaker here.
Or you could make it even harder.
There's also Venni Vidi Vici.
I don't want to make it harder.
Or I guess you could also fight Gelatinous Cuban, but he has never...
But I am pretty interested in Gelatinous Cuban.
[Laughter]
Yeah, yeah.
But I don't want to make things harder for us, so hey.
I think Gelatinous Cuban is now seven and a half feet from you guys.
- You guys, listen, here's my thing.
First of all, he's right there.
Right, second of all, it might be fun to jump in him.
- You know what, you know what?
You know what all you gotta do
is throw a little bit of sand at him.
- Really?
- Yeah, try it, try it right now.
Try, pick up some sand off the ground and throw it at him.
- Okay.
It just goes into him.
- Oh, I just, he got bigger.
He got a little bit bigger.
- Yeah, didn't it look cool though?
- It did look cool.
- It is an extremely easy fight
if you fight gelatinous Cuban
with no clear offer for what you would get out of that.
I, I, I'm going to attack him right now.
I think if we could sweeten the deal, if we take out two of them.
We could sweeten... What? What would the deal be? What are you talking about?
I mean, there's one of them. First of all, there's one of them.
I feel like we would be doing them a favor if we just killed... I think we'll sweeten the deal.
We take out Jalat and Escubin. We've already taken out the Walrus.
Two of them.
Three won't want to fight us.
You know?
Maybe you'll be-
But we have to fight them.
We have to fight them.
What's the problem?
Well, yeah, but you know, maybe she has a chance, you know, if we go with Ola or whoever.
Oh, it is a girl.
Okay, alright, then the girl.
I want to kill a woman.
So we don't want to-
You'll kill her or you won't?
I want to-
Alright, so-
I only will kill women.
So here's the question.
Alright.
Do we fight gelatinous Cuban-
I don't think we do.
Show that we can fuck up gelatinous Cuban so bad and the whole time we look at Ola and
this will happen to you. Did you see how I mean all we have to do hey Ola you see
what we just did to that walrus we're gonna do that to you that's it that see
yeah but if we knew it twice I mean you know maybe the first time she thinks
like oh it could be a flip. I pick up Patrick Yodar and I throw him into gelatinous cube.
Alright I'm with him I think we go with Ola. Alright. Ola or so Ola over
Kevin? Sure, yeah. Okay. So. Ola. Now. No, I'm just saying hello. I... pause. Como, como
estas? So with Ola, if you guys want to go for Ola, she's like kind of the only
like legitimate like business person in the platonic ideal of business that
people espouse right? Mini Vidi Vici is more of a BC guy. Kevin Ritterfin and Mr.
Awful are criminals. Ola is the first orc to have done magic in like a hundred
years and has built a legitimate business. If you go with her she will
offer substantial capital but you will also want probably around 40% control.
Is that a good or bad?
I think it's good.
Whose phone is that?
That's not my phone.
I don't know.
Yeah, they just keep, they do it every 15 minutes.
Oh, they're going to do that every 15 minutes?
Yeah, yeah, because they keep pushing it.
They can only give you a three hour flash flood warning.
That's so cute.
For every 15 minutes, they think that it will continue to be a flash flood.
You guys might be stuck here.
Yeah.
For the folks at home, we're recording this inside our house.
During the day, we're recording this.
We're recording this.
were recording this inside during the worst hurricane in the world which
apparently I had no idea was happening I didn't even yeah I didn't have an
umbrella I had to wear I mean I brought number one Caleb shirts right now yeah
it's really great I did I did do some shit to my pants just to you just sit in
your hands what that's not a beer that's right yeah the claw yeah you know what
that's good for you guys that's a good point that is not a good idea
no it is how still tell not to do that all you can do a lot of finding a fun
way to inform the audience as to what's happening
i love that he's doing that secretly and this is serious and comfortable yeah i
did that i know we're at the party you change your pants it's sparkling water
so it is a man balls around fire you know it's a good
it
but what
You just ruined your mic in some way.
I shut it off. I was pretending to be like,
"Oh, you know what's the coolest feeling in the world?
Putting your balls in sparkling water."
What? What are you talking about?
Why did you turn your mic off?
I turned it off because I didn't want the audience to know.
It'll make sense when the audience...
No, it won't. None of this is going to make sense.
This is going to be the part where they tune back in
because they're like, "What the fuck are they talking about?"
I tuned them back in.
I guess I'll have to get credit there.
So I think my failure at doing a bit brought the people back.
So you guys want to fight Ola?
I guess if we have to.
I'm going to kill that.
You're the one who wanted to.
I don't want to fight.
You're the person who suggested it.
I don't want to fight again.
But you were saying we should do two more fights.
You were saying we should fight two more people.
Well if we fight, you know, a fight against gelatinous cube.
We are going to take a long rest no matter what.
I need to. A fight against gelatinous cube would be nothing.
You need to go home. I don't. I'm the strategizer. You need to go to bed. No I don't. Yes. Okay.
All right we're gonna take a long rest. Yes. You guys are all gonna take a long rest. I'm
long resting. Yes. You guys go back into the uh uh you guys want to go back to your to your hotel
Because you are staying in a hotel.
Get him out of this damn hotel!
Now I can't go into the hotel and ruin my new image.
Yeah, I think you're walking into the hotel and like a magical paparazzi like takes like a magic photo of you.
Oh, oh, yeah, I'm actually moonwalking out of the hotel right now.
Get me out of this damn hotel.
He's going in to go out.
He's gotta be in to go out.
to go out. Give me that fucking camera. Give me that camera. I'm like walking up to the
camera. I'm like, yeah, he's going into the hotel. All of a sudden I'm the most famous
person in this world. I'm like, I'm like the two week celebrity. It's like I can't go anywhere
from now on. So the hotel you guys are staying in is is on on Thorax's dime. Hold on, hold
Hold on, real quick.
So the paparazzi gets you.
They get you going into a hotel.
So I have to, as your scooter brawn figure, I have to pull you into a stairwell and I
use my disguise kit on him.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, go for it.
Oh shit, let me make sure I know if that's a particular role with that.
I never fucking do kits in games so I always have to look it up.
Hold on.
second see I only have to describe me I only have to use the disguise kit of you
going in yeah which is the right part yeah but when you leave when you leave
you you got to announce that loud and clear just just an ability check and
your proficiency bonus with you do if you have proficiency in it you can add your
proficiency bonus so yeah there's the d20 and then so I'm sorry sorry sorry sorry
yes okay so 1d 20 mm-hmm yes cuz it's just what does this I mean it's gonna
the disguise kit will work regardless right I mean let's take it like a one
you're rolling something like that it'll be I got a I got a natural 20 oh my god
what do you want to look like I can go crazy just the just the just 30 38 G
boobs I did not say yes to this 38g boobs and that's it
war 38g is all boob right now 38g boobs and a blonde wig yeah pick me up carry
me to the front desk the paparazzi is like who is this girl's also famous I'd like
to check in my name is lovely Lindsay is gonna be free and my room will be free
I mean you got her into this hotel. So yeah, you were already staying in that hotel room
You just have to swipe it away or yeah, you can also you can flip if we all
My notification sound is turned off. Oh
still do the um my little switch on no turn your volume down because i got the
same get it down to oh wow i did i got the same thing and it didn't go off
really mine is just turned the volume yelled at me yet
me neither hmm interesting your time will come
i got the warning so yeah you go to the hotel so the the hotel you're in
is is is uh blinky's warm place uh there's a uh a one-eyed uh uh uh
a one-eyed uh one horned goblin named blinky flying
who runs a hotel. He masters in unseen servant spells and animate objects.
So he has all these like invisible servants running around
and all these like objects that are like doing stuff.
What kind of objects?
Like a wardrobe that organizes itself. Like a desk that is able to like hold stuff.
I know he be fucking the objects!
I say that really loud when we walk in.
And you know he be fucking the objects.
And you know the objects get fucked.
lovely that's exactly right.
And I'm also a singer.
She's the only female singer in the land with a full beard.
I don't recognize Evel Stevel and I'm like oh my god.
Hello young one.
Would you like to autograph?
Let's not do this in the hallway. There's paparazzi.
There's invisible hands all the way up here.
Let's wait until we get into the hotel room.
until we get into the hotel room. Oh yeah. So this is the... Lindsay Lovely's been seen
with Dogen the Oreo.
Yeah. They have a, they have a OMZ. It's just a orc version of TMZ. Just gonna be like, "Oh, did you
guys see this about drinking blood out of a big mug? Harvey Goblin. So it's a
two and a half star inn so the only... Ah shit. Yeah his dream... That's pretty good.
Blinky's dream is... You don't know anything about hotels. I think that must be pretty good.
- It used to be the first three star hotel in Gal Gadot.
- Well, here's a tip.
Maybe--
- Yes, please tell me, my name is Blinky.
- Here's a tip.
Don't require tips.
- Here's an idea.
- That's a good idea.
- I have a good idea.
What if you had superstar, pop star,
Lindsay Lovely performing in your lobby?
I think that might be--
- Yeah, I think that is as her manager and as--
Maybe and maybe she could have a sexual male backup dancer perform behind her
Yeah, I manage both Lindsay Lovely and the sexual male backup dancers
Temporally, I just need to know when this is happening. Are you Lindsay Lovely right now?
Is this when you first checked in before orc tank?
No, I we checked in before orc tank and then we came back and I and he because I'm famous now
He had to throw me in the Lindsay Lovely
outfit yeah which then people because I have such huge boobs just assume I'm
famous mm-hmm and so now I'm telling them that I'm a pop star my name is
Lindsay Lovely and I'm wearing tap dancing shoes now and he yeah I have I
have guys guys guys kit I would have to keep re-rolling I mean I got a crit got
Once we resolve this I have a plan I need to talk to you guys about.
I just want to, before we go any further, I just want to let everybody know I have a magical Bluetooth earpiece.
Yeah.
So, in 30, so yeah, it takes 10 minutes, no, just the time it takes.
Because it's not like the sky, it's like a spell, it's not like the sky itself.
Yeah, it's just permanent.
The sky itself is an hour length.
It's permanent so you can take it off.
- Guys, check it out.
- Yeah, it's just a physical thing, so it just lasts.
- Okay. - Lindsay, baby.
- Yes, doll.
- Tell me, how would you like to come with us
and pitch a brand new idea to Ork Tank tomorrow?
We could maybe pitch a new album for you or a music video.
- Where did the other dwarf go that you were with?
- Oh, oh. - Where did he go?
- He went to the bathroom.
- Well, he doesn't like hotels.
- Yeah, he had to go to the bathroom, though.
- Yeah, so he's gone. - Oh, get him out of this hotel!
- Let me out of this hotel is his catchphrase.
Yeah, his name is E. Westin.
Because he doesn't like the bathrooms at hotels, so he had to go to a bathroom in the street.
Of course, Miss Lovely.
You don't speak for him, he's not here, and he can't address it.
I'm his manager. You're not.
He hates going to the bathroom, you know why? Because he hates wiping.
Yeah, and he makes terrible smells.
None of this is true.
He's actually a pretty normal guy when you get to know him.
How do you know that?
How do I? Uh, well, you know.
I mean, famous people, we brush shoulders with each other.
That's kind of a... That makes sense.
Yeah, you brush shoulders.
don't brush his ass. I'd brush his ass. He hates wiping. It'd be good to brush someone's ass.
I hate wiping. We could clean in his ass. Yeah with a what kind of like a steel
brush. I'm done with you. You are fired. I'm not fired. I'm your manager. You can't fire me.
I could be your new manager. You don't fire your manager. You know how to cast disguise spells? Maybe. He doesn't know how to do that.
- All right, you're rehired.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Listen, point is, I think that both of us
would benefit greatly from me doing a set in your lobby.
You could pay me some coins.
- One song.
- One song, one opportunity, one shot in this lobby.
- And you know, we could go do it right now.
- I can't think of anything better.
That's an amazing idea.
- We'll just do the one song.
- Three stars, here I come.
- And what is it, like, what is it?
- How long is the song, four seconds?
- Well, how long, yeah.
(laughter)
- How long does the disguise get last?
- Until you take it off.
- Definitely.
- Okay, cool.
- I mean, until people start to pick up on the fact
that these are fake boobs.
Like, my boobs are not fake.
(laughter)
Are you kidding me?
- Yeah, they're size 38G.
- These are natural.
- They look like airships.
- Dwarf with bolt-ons.
(laughter)
POV.
but uh... yet it was so will do will do one song
and one dance one song with it with a very sexual backup dance so sexual in
the lobby
uh...
what it would it will it was a song called the song is called let me into
this love
you're gonna bring a performer and i don't think that they're gonna perform
lindsey lovelies
let me into this love
in your lobby
and uh...
That is gonna...
That is gonna get people to come to the hotel.
We have a wizard who's gonna do a laser light show during it.
You see a YME, he's like, "What? What do you want me to do?"
"Hey, hold on, just give us..."
You go wait inside.
Anything from the magic fridge...
Why does he have tits now?
Shut up. Anything from the magic fridge, you can drink it.
Excuse me?
Uh...
Anything from the magic fridge...
I know it's you, what the fuck?
Anything from the magic fridge, you can go drink it right now.
shit okay.
He just sort of walks away.
I walk him.
But don't touch the grog.
Actually everything but the grog you can, the grog is for me.
Okay fine.
Yeah so you guys want to prep for this evening of song and dance?
No prep.
I'm off the dome.
Like shwe in the morning.
I've got a dance choreography planned out in my head.
I have a...
It's very simple and very in your face.
I have a I have a keytar made of bones.
I'm the manager but I'm also the keytar player.
Thorax is on the bass.
Yeah.
So it's it's it's a couple hours go by.
Sullivan is security. He stands in front of the stage.
He's not.
Well who's the drummer?
There's no sunglasses so he just has two eye patches.
I don't think this is a good idea.
You know what this is not your show you don't have to worry
Okay, and yeah, there's a couple hours go by
The power is
Liquor and I'm flashing blinky's warm place is packed it is
10 p.m. On in the evening is prime time for like a late-night show oh
Oh man, the lights are literally flashing at Caleb Farman right now.
Oh, that guy just lost power.
Yeah.
I think we're next.
Oh, that would be so cool.
Yeah.
Okay, we have to get, we have to do the show.
Okay, so describe to me the show, then we'll do some rolls.
Purple lights.
Okay, the audience is here.
Everywhere, yep.
They're purple lights everywhere.
Purple lights flashing.
Get me out of this hotel t-shirt.
Lights that are flashing between, not knowing that you're him, but it's all coming together.
The lights are purple and yellow and they're strobing.
They're strobing between purple and yellow.
Yeah, you see Wimey weaving his hands together, casting dazzling light spells.
It makes your head hurt within like two seconds.
Yeah.
Thorax is starting the bass line to sort of get things started.
We're doing the sound check right now and I'm like,
"I just can't, uh, I mean, my, uh, yeah, I think you gotta turn the keyboard up."
Turn the keyboard up.
You gotta do the keyboard and the bass at the same level.
Alright, okay, alright. With the same level.
Same level. I mean, I have 15 pedals down here.
Okay, alright, alright, okay.
I mean, there's a lot of stuff that goes into this, I think.
He's EQing the audio, raising it up with magic.
You see Thorax sort of like, looks at you like,
"I don't know why the bass and the keyboard need to be the same level."
They gotta be the same level.
I literally start the song.
Yeah, you start the song.
Look, you gotta pedal.
The whole crowd is waiting.
Get a backbone of this band.
Yeah, sure, but it's just literally all we have is a keyboard and a bass.
You see Prince Jumanji in the audience go, "Yay, you guys rock! Woo!"
Are you guys the three homeless guys still or what?
No, we're Lindsay Lovely and her three homeless guys.
Lindsay Lovely and her beautiful boy band.
Lindsay Lovely and the Beautiful Boys.
Okay!
Alright!
Alright, you go back up to the room. You're not allowed down here.
I know! I just wanted to see!
They don't draw X's on your hands down here.
Before we start performing, I need to have a huddle with my band members.
[Laughter]
Yeah, everybody-
The audience is like-
Okay.
It's a normal, I know you've never seen a concert before, this is a normal occurrence at every concert.
We can do this backstage also.
Nope, we have to do it on stage.
Alright, huddle up, huddle up.
Actually, you know what, turn all the microphones off right now.
You see why me like, "Ugh, okay."
Alright, come here, come here, come here.
Okay, um, guys I forgot I had Stay Friday, I'm really scared.
Lindsey, I'm telling you.
Yeah?
You gotta go out there tonight, you're gonna fucking rock it.
rock it. Guys we have never played a song before and we don't know what we're doing.
You got to just let the music guide you. Yeah and the dance. And you
gotta watch his hypersexual dance. Also I have these boobs and they're making me
uncomfortable. They're not making you uncomfortable. They hurt my back. Yeah
it's gonna hurt your back. Is this what. That's the price of fame. Don't you. My
dance includes a back massage. It's part of the dance. You mean it? I mean it. We have
Everything covered all you have to do is go out there and sing. Do you see this codpiece?
Yeah, he's got a codpiece like it's gonna push into your back a lot back and forth in different spots like a massage
It's a what's this why me or fuck fuck you is gonna use the
Those are both right though, yes, go on. I thought your name was fuck you. I thought we changed it for you
anyway anyway he's gonna turn that into a massaging codpiece it vibrates with magic
okay okay all right all right I'm not ready I'm ready to say okay all right
okay let's go and then I and then the thorax thorax nods and he like looks you
guys realizing there's no drums it's smart okay wait for the tap dancing is
the drums I'm tap dancing with my tap shoes it sounds like a fucking like it's
It's like a Keith Moon drum solo.
Let me in to this love.
Your love should let me in so that we can both win in this love.
I'm Lindsey, my name is Lindsey.
Oh yeah, and I'm singing.
Let me into your love.
Let me out of this hotel.
Well...
Alright, roll performance check.
Everyone roll performance check.
Everything falls silent when you say let me out of this hotel.
I gotta crit 20.
For a natural 20.
Let's get this.
I got a 1!
No!
I got a 17.
No! No!
That means I say let me out of this hotel.
I get a fucking 1 dude.
This is so fucked up.
This is the most fucked up night of D&D ever.
Okay.
Holy shit.
Alright, let's resolve this.
You say let me out of this hotel.
We all got pretty good rolls but him.
I know.
With the crit 1,
you say let me out of this hotel,
"Your tits fall off."
*laughter*
I grab them immediately.
But, with the Natural 20,
everyone's like, "Who's this manager?"
*laughter*
I'm only playing Jump by Van Halen.
That's it, dude.
It is like, like,
Fucking pastorious
You're fucking you're carrying this by yourself man. You are your own beast
The tits fall off they roll to the side you don't I?
Dive onto the dive on to them
solvent
Here's the commotion turns around and bangs it to the stage falls over
The audience is is now what's your name? What's your name? I?
I'm a I'm Patrick Yodar.
Wow! Yo, is that Trunchbull's nephew?
Wow! They're going crazy.
Yeah, that's me. Yeah.
Yeah. Trunchbull's nephew, famous guitarist.
Uh, uh.
Hey, check this out.
Lindsey Love?
What was your name?
My name was, it was Lindsey Love, but uh.
Wait, hold on, hold on. I got an idea.
Actually, I'm.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the stage, Evil Stevel!
Roll persuasion, roll persuasion.
15.
Wait, wait, 15 plus 8.
23.
Everyone is mightily confused, but they'll roll with it.
Lindsay Love is dead!
It was me the whole time, it was Evil Stevel the whole time.
It's the hotel guy?!
Yep.
Oh, shit!
It's like a Tony Clifton situation.
Tony Clifton situation.
Now say it with him, everybody.
Let me out of this hotel!
And I guess we'll end it there.
[LAUGHTER]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
And nothing gets me down
You got it tough!