[Music]
Last time on Trebuchet Village,
our heroes took on the mighty stone serpent that grew from the earth.
Dogen communed with Dogen, the dirt god, who was always chewing on dirt,
and told him that stone is like hard dirt,
which Dogen took to mean he should not fight this creature.
Patrick Jodar tried to converse with the beast, but failed to charm him with words,
so he opted for an arrow straight to its skull.
Finally, evil Steevel used his cold hand to sing the beast "Silly,"
and Sullivan's fairy fire allowed Dogen to score an accidental whammy on the thing's noggin.
That last blow shook the fiend so that our valiant crew were able to barter a ride on its back in exchange for not killing it.
Realizing they didn't know where to go to get out of the forest, they opted to ride the beast to Grandma's house.
The Grandma... This Grandma was a Kubler Elf, one of the native woodland elves in the Whippet Woods.
After nearly filming a porn, she informed the gang that their best bet out of the woods would be to find...
That was awesome.
...the Mud Men due north.
Through there, they'd be on their way back to Trebuchet Village to return the young Prince Jumanji, who's still in their company.
Before leaving, however, Grandma Kubler issued a stern warning to her adventurers.
"Avoid at all costs the kitsune and their trickster spirit, the jester, who haunts these woods."
Not before robbing this woman blind, the gang hiked north until they came across a creek,
a cross which sat a destroyed campsite that featured a massive iron cage with the bars
bent outward, presumably whatever was inside it having escaped.
After snooping around, Evil Steevel discovered a discarded flyer for a performance by the
Vegas Brothers featuring their giant beast, but presumably the one that got out of the
cage and proceeded to, from what could be gathered at the scene, sever someone's hand.
Following the trail that the beast left, our heroes journeyed for several hours before
growing weary and anxious, as time seemed to stand still at dusk.
Two fairies, or fey-like creatures at least, began to harass and taunt our heroes, beseeching
them to see the jester.
Our heroes brushed their warnings aside, with Evil Stevel even doing the moonwalk, and,
seemingly satisfied, the mysterious fairies vanished, and with them so went dusk.
As night suddenly crashed upon the party all at once, our heroes readied themselves for
a well-deserved rest.
Dogen watched a frog while it slept or tried to sleep, and Patrick Yodar ignored the cries
of someone in pain, which was immediately followed by cryptic words hissed from deep
in the woods.
"Not a bad night."
The next morning, everyone got up and continued walking along the trail, and in doing so,
They managed to stumble upon the Mud Men's home.
They welcomed our heroes, told them their tale of woe, of being turned into Mud Men
by the Jester, his horde Kitsune, and the terrible beasts that marched through their humble town.
If they find and slay this beast, the Mud Men will show the party how to leave the Whippet
Woods.
The quest has begun.
Will they find their way out of the Whippet Woods?
Who is the Jester?
The kitsune and those fairies, the Vegas brothers and their beast.
Many unanswered questions and so many more to answer still.
And only one way to answer them.
To begin the show.
Mudman I just want to say right off the bat I meant for you to have sex and then I would
give you this mud baby I was trying to create.
I didn't try to say, I didn't create a baby for you to have sex with.
That's not what I.
That's what I heard.
That's not what it was.
I had actually completely forgotten that you said that ten seconds ago.
I don't know if you need to bring that up.
Why are you trying to re-litigate this right now?
The listeners in the woods would hear it.
And I just want to...
The what?
The audience.
[laughter]
They would probably not let me live that down, the listeners in the woods.
I would hope that they would try to understand that you're just playing a character, right?
'cause all the stuff, people would think I'm pathetic.
(laughing)
- Nobody would ever think that.
- Okay, so.
- Yeah, that is not something people would,
you're a fantastic man, Sullivan.
- Okay.
- Thank you for letting me work at your whatever the--
- It was a general store.
- I think that's what it was.
- Okay.
- I really just have not been paying attention
to my job at all.
- Yeah.
- I--
- I gathered, but I appreciate it.
It's just a fun poor person thing I do.
And uh...
Like a hobby.
Like a hobby, yes, yeah exactly.
Like pretending to be a poor person is a hobby for me.
Yeah.
Well, for me it's, I like to collect uh, I like to collect stamps, but you know.
You like to collect stands?
No, stamps.
Like things you put on a pedestal, you collect?
A stand?
Clamps?
What are you saying?
What the hell is a stamp?
Oh, well, I guess I couldn't think of a pathetic hobby in the medieval setting, so I opted
for one.
You say it's sand?
You beach babe motherfucker.
Yeah, it's sand.
Wait, you like sand?
Yeah.
We should totally hang out and talk about how similar sand is to dirt.
I would love for you to write that down and just give me all your thoughts, just in the
written word, through parchment maybe.
Well, how is he going to send it to you?
though do you get it
yeah i mean i could put it in an envelope but from there
right here we're just a go from there that you had a little sort of central
and how do you know if only there was a year old website
yeah
that so uh... you guys are you know in the mud men village uh...
you're sort of given a quick i guess sort of a quest where the men would help
you find the way out if you
find this beast and slay it as sort of a revenge
for the mud men whose homes and mud folk were trampled upon.
Obviously, you know, the trail went through the mud men's place.
You could see sort of the debris and the things there.
And it continues on after that, but you could see that it's a little bit fainter now,
just because of how, you know, that works, right?
now it's sort of like you can see a bit of a mud trail though so you can make a
survival check I would say to continue to like track it since now it's sort of
changing trajectory he's got the highest survival I have plus two I got zero I
think you might actually Patrick really oh I don't have to roll that d20 and
we'll see what's going we're we're in person by the way folks listen to that
die roll 14 plus 14 14 plus 4 is a Wow great okay that's a very good roll so
yeah you why why so good is it cuz you're a scion of an adventure like like did you
learn anything from from your uncle like why are you you you so I want to actually
start to try to interrogate this what's going on I I learned how to my time
pretend cosplaying is a poor person has taught me a lot of valuable skills right
such as how to how to survive without a butler. Poor people love using a compass
it's like their favorite thing it's like TV to them. We is it am I supposed to say
that in character? I don't even know. They like using a compass. It's sort of a net worth where you don't need a
compass anymore where you start making a certain amount of money and then you're
like this is dumb yeah exactly you're a rich adventurer I mean yeah you walk any
any direction they build a town around you yeah that's pretty mindset yes
trying me I mean that's what they did for a village was built so you get one
patch it's all in there it's already in there I already wrote it down in the
place that counts my head so yeah you guys yeah so Patrick you know is very
Very good at tracking beasts.
So he starts to track the...
He starts to follow along the mud path.
You guys see that it goes through the creek, but you still see the imprints beyond the
creek.
As you move a bit further now south, back towards the woods where you were, because
you guys went north to see the mud men.
And as you're starting to get to the woods, it starts to get a little bit thicker in the
woods.
You know, it starts to get about...
It's about to be midday, I would say.
And I want, Patrick Yodar, roll a perception check.
- God, that's crisp.
- It was a nine.
- Nine, okay.
So you, as you sort of like walk a little bit further,
you sniff the air for a second.
(sniffing)
- Oh God, I got a globule of pollen in there.
I saw a bug go in your nose.
- Yeah, I think that might be a bug or a globular pollen.
- I think that was a hummingbird.
That was, what the hell was that?
- Hold on.
(laughing)
Yeah, it just came out my mouth.
- Yeah.
- So the hummingbird just like,
plops on the ground just dead.
- Like, it looks like it went through it.
- I picked it back up and I put it in my mouth.
Start chewing on it like it's a sunflower seed.
- I like you.
- Yeah, I'm kind of a gross person.
like your style. And with that insane sniff I guess, you sort of get the sense that there's
somebody nearby, but you're not sure where they are, and you know that now it's not just
sort of one of the critters that have been lingering. You've been walking for a few hours
and you feel like someone's been tracking you guys.
Knock it off.
You hear no response.
Yeah, if we just keep saying that for a little bit, maybe somebody will...
Hey, stop following us!
We know you're there...
...Dragon.
If it's a dragon, that's pretty smart.
That would be important if it was a dragon.
That's not a bad idea.
It was you, Sullivan!
No, no, no!
Yeah, you've been following us this whole time!
You've been following us since the...
Right behind us, every step of the way!
No, no, I ha-
Hey, wait, uh...
Does anybody know where the Prince is?
And you guys noticed that the prince is not with you.
Oh, I noticed that like a while ago.
(laughter)
You didn't say anything?
Yeah, I wouldn't have said anything either.
I thought he was playing.
Yeah, you guys sort of like try to retrace your steps.
What do you guys want to do about that?
Moonwalk backwards.
(laughter)
Through my, the way that I left a trail was exactly,
there's two lines, 'cause I moonwalked the entire way.
Yeah.
Okay.
I do Freddy got fingered backwards man. I turn my armor around. I can't think of anything funny
Okay, yeah, so you guys sort of start to retrace your steps, and it becomes pretty clear that
Wherever the kid went it's hard to tell
Just walking backwards if like if he like got abducted or if he got distracted or something
So have you roll an investigation check to get a little bit of a better sense of this
I got a four mm-hmm I got a 12 17 okay with that for you just notice the dirt
and smother what's on your mind it's kind of your characters the perfect role
there's some mud touching some dirt
Evil Steve-o and Patrick Yodar, you both hear a faint "Help! Help!" and you guys can sprint
into a little bit further into the woods and you see a hole in the ground and you see about
like 20 feet down the kid.
You say "Help!
I don't know what happened!"
"Knock it off!"
"What you doing in that hole?"
"Get back up here right now!"
"Get out of that hole!"
"Or you're grounded!"
"You get back up here right now!"
"I'mma count to five!"
I'm gonna count to one. Wait, can you guys help me out of here?
One. One. Two. Are you gonna keep counting?
Three. What are you gonna do if you get to five?
You know what? I'm coming down there. I jump in the hole.
Okay. As you do, roll a...
Oh, God. Roll...
a acrobatics check. I can fly, right?
No. Fuck. Roll acrobatics.
One. Oh, God. So you...
probably gonna be so the whole the holes diameter is not that like you're a dwarf
you're not that tall but you seem bigger than 20 feet yeah you jump and you sort
of like just misjudge your weight and you just scrape your head like on the
side of the hole the entire because you're falling to the ground like and
you will take a nice back I'm gonna go ahead and get a pen okay oh yeah I have
pencils for you I'm sorry but yeah you take a five damage from just this
tremendously bad oh hold on let me get pencils don't worry I'll come save you
just with like no teeth I'm like I thought I told you I'm coming down here
whoa so many pencils yeah there you go you moonlight is a substitute teacher
not just moonlight oh yeah so yeah and now you see you see Kit the Jumanji
Prince Jumanji's like are you gonna are you gonna punish me are you okay
fuck no I'm not okay in my in my thieves tools do I have a like a rope you I
think yeah you should all I think I do have to have rope and actually now you
have inventory printed so yeah I think you I think I wrote I have carpenters
tools yeah I have 50 feet of room yeah you all should probably have about 50
feet of rope you live and you learn I got an idea I open up my I open up my
pouch of forever dirt and I start just spraying dirt into the hole and I just
climb up on the dirt and it will fill up the hole and you will take you to the
top it's actually not a bad and I drown me in this dirt bro just no you climb on
to climb on top of the dirt.
- So yeah, that's not under, it's the other way.
- See, we're gonna, okay.
- Don't you have a rope?
- Are you stuck in moonwalking?
- A little bit.
- Going down instead of up?
- Okay, stop moonwalking, you're making the hole deeper.
- You gotta pay me to stop moonwalking.
- Here's one piece of gold.
- Swag.
- Okay, yeah.
- Yeah, you just drop a gold coin in there.
- Okay.
- It's a chocolate coin, don't tell him.
- I would say you guys--
- That's for two gold coins.
(laughing)
- You and the prince sort of keep scrambling,
continuously on top of the dirt as it keeps coming down from
Dogen's pouch.
And Patrick Yoda, roll a dexterity saving throw.
Oh, no.
Is it which one?
T20.
I got a nat 20.
Holy crap.
Okay.
So Dogen is pouring dirt into this hole.
You guys are sort of scrambling on top of it, Prince Jumanji
and Evil Steevel.
And you and Sullivan are just sort of watching the affair.
and it's great
used to have this is
are through our three friends just working in a sense it's always so nice
c_t_n_'s image amazing it's one of the best
one of the best things i think uh...
you can you can witness especially as it is a grown man
you know to see a
you know see people get together like this in the just work together is a kind
of thing i really tried to foster at the general store i mean yet you know you
never really did that not not straight up with you guys didn't really listen to
me so there was no I guess camaraderie not to put the blame on you I know what you
guys be quiet over there it's completely your fault but I just want to listen to
the dirt Patrick Yodar while you're like talking to Sullivan you see like like
you see an arrow shoot towards you did you guys see that and you like you in
In the middle of the sentence, you're like, while saying like, "and it's completely your
fault," you just like grab this arrow out of the air and continue talking.
Yeah, got it.
That's probably the only one.
Probably no more arrows on the way.
I gotta look into this deeper.
Yeah.
What do you want to do?
So the, it's being filled with forever dirt?
Jumping in the hole would be pretty funny.
I don't have a shield, do I? No. How full is the hole at this point?
You're not going to address the arrow that came at you and you caught?
No, I'm going to, but I just want to know. This is how I'm going to do it.
Okay, I'm sorry. No, I should have guessed it. I would say like, it's probably about like,
how, I wonder how fast, how fast does Foreverder come out, Cam?
Yeah, you could just, I don't think there's any...
A million miles an hour.
So somewhere between a million and one, not one mile an hour, that's maybe even too fast.
Yeah, I don't, it doesn't.
Yeah, no, no, I know.
So I have no clue.
So let's say like maybe it comes out like, like I'm thinking of like a...
I think it was like a 30 foot line was like the maximum, it was like 30 square feet or
something.
Yeah, so it's like I imagine...
It was a 25 foot hole?
Yeah, it was a 20 foot hole.
So I imagine that like it would fill up in like maybe like 45 seconds of like dirt coming
Okay, so it's not full enough. Let's say but it's like a slow but it like continuously comes out right? Okay. So yeah
well, what I was gonna do was jump in the hole get my bow and arrow ready and then whenever the
Mm-hmm gets me up. I would fire just
It's like it's definitely like 15 feet like up at this point. Not 15, maybe like 10 feet
I was yeah, but then like 45 seconds. That's too slow. So I guess
I'm gonna get I'm gonna crouch down behind Sullivan
Okay
uh... what
what's up
yet there was a couple there's an arrow
and get that you remember this from earlier here i was really sc worried
about that so there's a another one coming right now you have been in this
and uh... uh... solomon's got the role of the exterior of the third now
but see how he does it that
well great did
probably not
you know
uh... solvent just takes a hero right in his shoulder are
See, I told you to look out for that.
And he takes three damage.
"Ahh, what the hell?
Who's doing that?"
"Hey, can you knock it off, please?
I really don't want a problem right now.
My friend is stuck in a hole."
"Okay."
"I'm trying to...
Ahh!"
He just pulls it out.
"Yeah, this thing, and you did this thing, too."
And you guys are now sort of out of the hole at this point, and you now, Patrick Yoder,
I would say, can sort of get the sense of where the arrows are coming from.
It's coming from one of the treetops.
Okay.
Well then behind Sullivan I have my bow and arrow ready.
I'm just waiting for the next arrow to come.
I'm looking at the tree tops.
I'm just waiting for the next arrow.
I would say roll a perception check.
15.
Okay.
You can see pretty clearly who it is.
some sort of human male shooting at you from the treetops.
- Okay.
- And he sort of sees you seeing him,
and he goes, "Crap!"
And he just sort of like ducks down
and jumps out of the tree.
And roll for initiative, guys.
- Oh, fuck. - What?
- Oh, fuck.
Two, five.
- There's no initiative modifier on here, right?
- Yeah. - There is?
- Yeah, you just have zero.
- Okay, I got five.
wait to so that would be two plus three I also got five but I'm not actually yeah
then I also got five holy shit you all get five yeah I would just make no
sense now oh actually who is the highest X I should say probably him zero I have
one five dexterity okay so you're gonna go first okay he's so broken yeah you
got really good role is a pretty funny and then you're gonna go Dogen Patrick
dogen just wait till your character gets cancer then steve all that's gonna
happen you know Stievel and then Sullivan got the lowest but going first
is this fellow who has he has a sort of mid-length grayish brownish hair
count dooku and and he has sort of he has like a old-timey spectacles on and
And he looks sort of like a dweeby kind of hunter type.
And he knocks another arrow and aims it at you,
Patrick Jodar.
And that is gonna hit, I'm gonna say.
And he will attack you.
So he knocks another arrow and you're sort of just like
chatting him up and he deals five damage to you.
- Oh no.
- Yeah.
And he goes, "Ha ha, gotcha!"
That is completely uncalled for.
I mean to say that right now.
He's got an arrow sticking out of your gun.
That is, I mean, look what you've done.
It's all in a day's work for a goofus Tiedrich.
Listen, yeah, you are a real goofus, I will say that.
That is, I'm in a lot of pain.
Look, if you just hand over the kid, we can stop this fight right now.
Why are you-
Okay.
I hand over Sullivan.
what are you pushing forward no not stupid little kid I need the kid the
Nard boy why well this means head he's worthwhile I don't want head from him
no hey this guy wants head from a kid that's not true we're gonna call the
cops if you stay all the Bobby's what are the constable I don't yes wait I
don't I don't want no yes I just want his scalp why are you winking I'm not
Wait, stop winking.
Sir, your fingers are crossed.
It's a tick, okay?
It's a tick.
Your fingers are crossed on your arrow.
You're ticking me off with my arrow.
You're not a child, nonsense, you're doing.
I have two ticks, they're winking and finger crossing, okay?
You're fingering his dick?
No.
Did you say you gonna fuck him?
No, please.
No, I didn't.
You better not.
I'm gonna say that right now, you better not.
You've seen my prowess.
Just, just, just, just.
You wanna show a kid you're-
You said you wanna grow your ass.
No, no.
I'm not gonna grow my ass.
now you better not. You've seen my prowess just just just just. You want to show a kid.
You said you want to grow your ass. You nasty. That is that is absolutely disgusting and I'm
looking down right now I have a an arrow in my belly and uh you know I can see right now I can
see a little bit of my my my gut and uh you're grossing me out more than that. I'm I I I I I I
I'm sorry, just please, just, just, just, just, just, just give me the kid and we won't have to, I won't have to keep shooting you.
If you leave us alone and go away and never come back and don't come back ever again, we'll consider it.
Wait a minute, no, that's not how it works. If you want to marry that kid, you gotta marry me first.
I don't, why does everyone, no.
Okay, uh, it's your turn Patrick Yodar, uh, by the way.
Okay, all right. Uh, how close am I to him now?
Uh, so he's still about-
Wait, I have a disguise kit?
Dress up like that kid.
He's about-
At your own peril.
He's about 40 feet out, I would say.
Oh, not 40, I should say. Yeah, 40 feet out.
I just dressed up like a cop.
I don't think he'd know what that is.
No, that's true. All right, never mind.
Um, then 40 feet out, um, all right, so I guess I'm on the ground in pain.
I already have my bow and arrow ready, right?
So I have that out, I'm just gonna...
Yeah, I'm gonna knock him.
Okay, yeah, go for it.
Add the...
Eleven.
Add the, uh...
Where's the attack for this?
Oh.
Oh, there's my...
It should be on your...
Oh, if it's not here, I can tell you, just based on your dex...
Uh-huh.
...and your proficiency.
So it'll be plus five.
Okay.
So what is that?
That's sixteen.
Sixteen?
Yeah, that that hits okay roll for damage. Yeah, rofrit is oh there it is down there, okay?
Seven
That's wrong. Oh wait. Which one do I roll it you're gonna roll for the D6 the d6 okay?
Three nice okay, so three plus three so you do six damage to him
So you're chatting him up, and then you shoot him and you get him right back in the gut. He's like no same wound
Doesn't feel too good does it? No, it doesn't. Yeah, it actually feels pretty terrible. No, I have been shot by arrows before
I'm a master hunter. I'll have yeah. Well, I haven't this is actually a very unpleasant experience. What?
Really? I'm never been hit by him. I've always dodged him or caught him. Oh, I mean when you caught I was pretty impressed
I have to yeah, you better be I'm a fucking I'm the son of a famous explorer. You're the son now
I the nephew. Okay, I
There's something there's a gas leak
So it is now your turn
Dogen cool
You said he's he's
40 feet away. Mm-hmm. Okay. How much can I move 30 feet? All right. Um,
Mm-hmm. I do have javelins. I think yes you do. Uh, they're not listed on here. So I don't know how javelins work, but I
I'm being a Mars bar dude. You're at work. I don't know. Do you know how javelins work off the top of your head?
Oh, you can throw them. I don't remember exactly at least hold your mic away from your face when you do it
You know let me get um
So yeah a javelin is it's just a range weapon. Yeah, you're in range, okay
I throw a javelin okay. I kiss the javelin before I throw it for plus one
No
All right, just roll the plus two
Plus a half plus plus one
Plus one minus one uh-huh times two times three times four
Divided by six deal okay fine, so that's times six cool five by six
18 plus whatever plus like 40 right so um
No, I mean that hits roll so roll for damage. It's gonna be a
piercing d6
Plus your, um, dex.
Four damage.
Ooh, mommy!
So you, um, yeah, you throw the javelin and, uh...
Can I aim, can I aim for it?
I want to hit, I want to do like, I want to split, I mean, I know this is a bit tough,
but yeah.
You split the arrow in half with the javelin.
Maybe it's not good enough of a roll for it.
No it is, a hundred, but no, it's fun, that's for sure.
Um, yeah, so you, yeah, yeah, you throw the arrow and you see him like, he's like, "Ugh!"
to pull it out and then you just the jabler just goes right in between it's
his weak spot you see it's glowing red
who sent you no well well no no one the brave lions of course they they the brave
lions Christ not them yes so you guys would know who they are insofar as so as
As you know, people like Evil Stevel or other non-evil races are very fun.
I love D&D.
Are called Scaredy Cats because they're not Terrifyer born.
So there's like a resistance group that is called the Brave Lions that even though King
Nardwuar is trying to do all this reform of like, "We'll try to treat our former slaves
better. There's still these brave lions who will accept the scalp of like a
nard for money. And so he's like this, this, this goofus Tiedrich fellow is some
sort of bounty hunter perhaps, who's working either on behalf of them, either
because he knows it's the prince or he doesn't know it's a prince, but there is
a precedent for this kind of behavior. Once he said brave lions, it would click
for you guys. Okay. Yeah, these guys suck. Yeah, we, me and Patrick Yodar hate
everybody who's not Terrifier-born. Hey guys, that... what? Nothing. Yeah.
Continue about your story. I only like people who are Terrifier-born coded
personally so no that's that's that I mean he doesn't say much else I guess he
says like the brave lion sent me probably says now so yeah he says a little bit
more it's about a mama yeah ask him can I ask you a couple questions he's just
looks like bleeding. Okay, when's your birthday one second?
Let's see if we can find Mr. T.
George's birthday March. Sixteenth Yeah, that's my brother's birthday. Is it
really it's right before Saint Patrick's Day? Why do we have his entire
Rockaway, New Jersey. Why do we know all this?
Rockaway, New Jersey, baby.
His father is Warren Lloyd Teedridge.
And this is Goofus.
Yes, this is Goofus, sorry.
Anyway, so, uh, uh, whoa.
And so yeah, it's now your turn, by the way, Evil Steve-o.
I'm gonna use my ghost hand, which I believe is called Chill Touch.
Yeah, it is.
Okay.
But for you it's called Ghost Hand.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
understanding.
Well, any time.
So what should I roll?
Yes, so...
Roll attack, right?
Yeah, chill touch should be a...
Is it on there as a spell attack?
Or let me see...
It's also here as well.
Or is it a DC?
Yes, it's a spell attack, sorry, it's plus four, so roll.
See what you do.
That hits!
It's a 15!
Yeah, that hits.
So yeah, roll for damage on that one.
That's a d8.
Yeah, baby, it's d8 necrotic damage.
No, that has an 11 on it, probably not.
is this is her nice five hell yeah so yeah you what do you do with this hand
how do you fuck so there's an arrow with a spear stuck through it yeah I just
kind of like just like grab the spear just start kind of moving it back with
my ghost and they pick him up all right so I pick him up and yeah I kind of just
twirl them around. This is the worst day for my stomach. I bet that hurts. Oh god! I bet that one spot hurts so bad right now.
Oh it's all I could think about. Yeah. It's hurting me too. Probably not as much as that.
You're getting spun but. I would do anything for you to shoot another spot on my body. No. Oh no.
I think we're gonna stick to this little area. Okay and now it is Sullivan's turn. And Sullivan
is going to take out his crossbow and do his best.
- Oh, he has a crossbow?
- Yes, he does. - Yeah, when did Sullivan
get a crossbow?
- He's a bard, it's one of his weapons.
- I thought he had a lute. - So he's a fart?
- Oh, he has a lute also.
- Oh, okay. - But his weapon is a crossbow.
- Can they be combined?
- You know what? - Yeah, dude,
he uses the string of the lute to shoot the,
well, that would explain why he got a five
and missed so badly, maybe.
(laughing)
- He took out his lute by accident,
he had the crossbow.
So he tries to, he panics, takes out, yeah, in this scenario,
it is very much, oh, it's my turn.
And so he panics, realizing it's his turn to fight.
Takes out a lute by accident, goes, ah, like,
like gets nervous, grabs an arrow,
just tries to do it in the lute.
He's like, boom, like the string breaks.
(laughing)
And he's just like, he's like, I'm so sorry.
- Sullivan, what the hell was that?
- This never happens. - Yeah, don't be sorry,
that's the most beautiful song I've ever heard.
I place the opening chords of
so I usually sound much much worse, so that's I guess good
and he just misses and we're back at the top of the order is Mr.
teacher's turn and he is going to actually
sort of like freak out a little bit and throw a some sort of like he's got
sort of like concrete like ball and he like cracks it open on the ground and it
shoots up smoke and you don't know where he is now you can sort of get the sense
of him dashing away but you're not sure where and it's now your turn what would I
use to like seek him like perception I would say yeah I think you could take
a round to do perception then that's sort of like what you're doing so if
that's what you're doing I mean it helps everybody else after because you can
and
again with disadvantage. And that's plus four, I think, yes, for you. So, or no, it's plus
six. And what did I have as, god damn. Did it hit? Yeah, it did. What did I get? You
got a fourteen, that hit. Oh shit. So yeah, roll for damage. Roll that d6. Wow. Well that'll
count that's a four here oh yeah keep that then yeah four plus it's gonna be
plus I think another four for you right yes my god is it decks what is it what's
your decks is it three my decks is I think it's plus three yeah yeah yeah
okay so so so pretty good so so it's seven yeah so you just like you the
smoke bomb kind of goes up and you you were sort of just like what like you're
kind of like peering in like how do you get the sense of like where he is like
how did you figure or did you just like I like I turned to them like they're like
standing like here mm-hmm I'm like hunched over with the my the arrow in my
gut yeah I'm just gonna see where this goes you are you here think oh how did
he how you see he comes out of the smoke he's really fucked up and the arrow
splits the chaplain down the middle you see it burrowed a hole in it and you see
like blood like squirting out of the like end of the javelin hole.
It's like, "Ow! Ow!" That's my bad I just kind of let it go. You ruined my
javelin. Hey you know what I will make you a new one out of this stick. Thank you
so much. And he's really bad off so he sort of says, "Okay, okay I'm sorry,
I'm sorry. I'll leave the prince alone. I didn't know, I didn't know, I
I didn't know he'd have you guys with him.
Hey, now get over here and take this arrow out of my belly.
Okay, okay.
And he crawls over, and the initiative's over.
He's given up.
Take that arrow out and put it in the end of that javelin.
When he gets in range of me, I hit the javelin like I'm hammering in a peg with my shovel.
I guess I'll roll for damage.
Dude, we gotta talk to this guy.
We need info.
Okay, wait.
I wait.
Okay.
I'm gonna do it yeah I got flinched roll intimidation I guess with advantage what
a bitch oh fuck yeah 24 yeah he see him like like you like do they like fuck
like yo what's up and like he just like you you yeah I mean like as always with
my characters do you like smell a little poo and like like oh god and he goes to
Patrick Jodar and he like instinctually is like like try it like strut does like
a full aiding to suck the arrow and like pulls it out yes master didn't have to
do all that honestly it was kind of nice I know now do that to yourself he's like
I can't there's a big javelin in the way Lord knows I'll do it you're so stupid
Yeah, no wonder they call them goofus.
What do you... what do you guys want?
What do you want from me?
Twenty dollars.
Wait, hold on.
Okay, hold on.
Thirty dollars.
There we go. That sounds a lot better.
Sounds a little better, right?
Yeah, you could probably buy like some...
probably get each of us like three or four cups of meat or something like that.
I only have twenty-eight gold pieces.
Ah, crap. Well, you know, give us that anyway.
You have a piece of gum?
No.
Gum would be great right now.
Gum would be really nice.
I haven't been able to brush my teeth.
We're in the forest.
Three days not brushing, how many days has it been?
- It's been about one day for you guys.
- Yeah, well, three days for me not brushing my teeth.
(laughing)
- Can I have your weapons?
- Yeah, let's just take 'em out of his stomach.
- Okay, yeah, here's mine.
He gives you a long sword and he throws down a short bow.
- Yeah, I don't want them,
I just don't want him to have them.
- Yeah, yeah, he throws that down.
- Hey, you know what, while we're here,
give me your shoes, I actually--
- Your tunic.
- No, my Jordans, please.
yeah I want those. My ye olde Jordans.
He's like okay okay and he like takes off his shoes and hands them to you.
We want all your stuff but we're going to let you live because I have a feeling that
you are going to you're destined to do great things and your your descendants
are probably going to be some very important people. I hope so I mean I
haven't seen her since I but what do you want? I can give you all my stuff.
Have you seen...
28 pieces of gold, your shoes, your weapons...
What was the other things we wanted from him?
A beast?
Have you seen a beast?
Yeah, a beast.
Do you have a beast?
Do you...
Wait, are you the beast?
Did we slay the beast?
That would be pretty easy, right?
I mean, look at this guy.
We could probably bring back his corpse to the mud people and say we got him.
Yeah, you could kill me and just make me look like a beast.
That's it.
Wait, no, hold on.
I got confused.
I haven't seen I haven't seen any beasts. What about a beast's footprints or have you smelled a beast?
I I great questions. I know great questions. Don't you have seen any signs of a beast?
Well, I have you seen a prince. Did you we were looking for one earlier?
Yeah, I was he fell in my trap. So you knew he was a prince
Yes, I did cuz he's gone. I think did you know he's
remember what he did you know he's a beast no yeah well yeah he's a nard like
all of terror fireborn they're all beasts all of you are there is I kick
him in the shin oh god yeah he was hiding behind like a bush or something
he was blended in okay okay okay I saw I saw a beast okay why didn't you tell us
you saw what it took me kicking you in the shin what else do you know yeah come
Come on, what the?
- The kitsune's took the beast.
- Ah, crap, these fucking guys.
- I can't, I can't, I don't wanna deal with them.
I don't wanna deal with them, they're crazy.
- Well, you're gonna have to do it.
- You're becoming a permanent member of our party.
- No, that's three NPCs.
That's way too much.
- We need at least six.
- No.
(laughing)
- That way, if one of us dies,
it can be one nobody cares about.
- Please, please, okay, okay.
Look, I'll take you to the white woman of the woods.
Okay, how about that?
She'll be able to help you.
- I don't know.
I think she's still mad at me.
- You know her?
- I won't get into it.
- All right, take us in.
- Yeah, we'll do it as long as you're naked.
- Okay.
- And he gets naked.
- That's disgusting.
I didn't think you would do it. Put those back on.
Okay, okay. Put this acorn in your butt.
It's almost impossible for him to put his shirt back on.
The acorn's in his butt.
Never mind. Pine cone.
Ugh, it's worse.
I usually only do acorns.
And he puts the pine cone in.
I'm happy. What about you guys?
Can you take the pine cone out actually, Em?
Yeah. Alright. He doesn't die.
He takes some damage from the pine cone in his ass.
Swear fealty to dirt for the rest of your life.
I-I-I-I swear feels he's a dirt fag.
Say you're a little girl.
I'm a little girl.
What the hell? Why'd you say that crap?
You told me this saying.
You're crazy.
You know, there's a- there's a thing.
You don't really have to do what people tell you all the time.
You guys almost killed me!
Do you want- do you want me to not do what you tell me to do?
I'll do that.
Be- be your own little girl.
Do- just right now do something spontaneous.
Do something you want to do.
It doesn't matter what we think.
he just vomits blood you wanted to do that no no um you we that was disgusting
stick it to us oh stick what it stand up for yourself
uh you guys stink i can't hey don't you two pine cones
so he's just like being brutalized and abused he's there
If you happen to look over at Sullivan, you see like a dark smile crawl across his face
watching someone else suffer the abuse.
Hey Sullivan, you want to get in on this?
No, no, I'm just fine watching.
You're weird.
Yep.
And you guys go into this sort of walk through the woods and some of the weirder parts of it start to
look a little bit less like the Whippet Woods as you've seen it, less of that
sort of a like a constant subconscious cackling that you hear and the weird critters that like
float around and do their weird dark crystal things. It starts to look more like a regular
verdant-ass wood and you come-
Verdant?
Verdant, oh yeah. Very green.
Oh, you're verdant, yeah. And it comes across like a little bit of a clearing,
you see a pond and you see Tidritch, he's been like just limping all the way there, goofus.
Do I heal my stomach wound?
No.
Okay.
So I'm also launched over one.
Yeah, you're also just like sort of in pain.
How much health are you missing?
I'm missing five HP.
What are you at?
Four.
I'll heal two HP on you.
Lay on hands?
Yeah, I'll spend two of my lay on hands.
Nice.
Just because I don't want you to die in like one hit.
And you come across this pond and you see Tidrich and he says, "Go beseech her and she will
talk to you."
I hit the javelin in like a peg.
Okay.
And he dies.
Didn't think that was going to happen.
Yeah, I mean he had one HP at that point so.
Also I want to say my lay on hands is that I rubbed dirt into the wounds.
And it hurts really, really bad, but it works.
As he's dying, he says, "Good thing I impregnated someone earlier."
And just dies on the spot.
So yeah, do you guys beseech the white woman of the woods?
I instantly beseech her.
I might not start with beseeching.
I might say, like, maybe holla first.
First, I try to holla.
You sort of see a couple of bubbles show up in the pond.
You try hollering.
Okay, I move on to saying what's up.
I'm testing the water.
Okay, yeah, yeah.
Literally, right, yeah.
I have my hands in my pockets and I'm just looking at the pond.
I'm like, "Ah, crap.
This brings back memories."
Yeah?
Yeah, this is...
Wait, you said you have a history with her, right?
Yeah.
You could probably get her attention.
Yeah, I could.
I could.
- You try hollering. - Hey, yo!
- Well, I just, it's a--
- Patrick Yodar's up here.
- Ah, come on, man, what you--
- Yeah, you see, now you see
a top of someone's head peering out of the pond
and slowly rising up,
and these beautiful blonde dreads
that cascade down this white woman's body,
perfectly covering all of her privates,
but very much highlighting her navel for some reason.
- I was about to say, is the belly button open and clear?
- It is open and clear for entry, sir.
- Swag.
- And you see her in her fullness,
and she's like hovering over the water,
and she like looks over you all,
and she sees Patrick Yodar, and she's like,
Patrick?
- Hey, yeah, I don't know if you remember me.
I'm Trunchbull's kid.
- I remember you.
Yeah, I'm real sorry about what I did on the fourth of--
I'm still trying to get the stains out.
Fourth of Juudars.
That's right.
Excuse me?
Juudars.
Juudars is one of our months.
What is Juudars?
Juudars.
J-O-O-D-A-R-S-E.
(laughing)
Juars.
No, it means July.
(laughter)
- We have July, just say July,
why you making up all this weird shit?
- I was trying to make it sound like Skyrim.
(laughter)
- Are you trying to impress her?
You still like her.
- I was in a human form at the time,
I didn't expect to get so drunk,
but I laid with a very charming verdanne.
- Yeah, my uncle and I was in the room.
(laughter)
Where'd the stains come from?
I was listening to... she had this...
The tears?
There was a bard in the room playing a song, it was amazing, you guys should have heard it.
Oh my god.
It was a good song.
I mean, I wasn't gonna leave the room.
We, your uncle and I both asked you desperately to leave.
And I did when the song was over.
Yeah, you did, and then you spilled, you spilled juicy juice all over...
That's what I called it at the time.
*laughter*
This is actually, uh, blood wine.
*sigh*
You've all come to the woods.
This is wonderful news.
You're outsiders.
There's much-
My uncle was insider.
*laughter*
She can't help but smirk.
That's pretty good.
Um...
This once wasn't the Whippet Woods, you know.
Yeah, I knew that.
Okay, good. Well...
I know tons of crap.
Yeah, it used to be just the woods.
[laughter]
Well, I mean, it was still called the Whippet Woods, but it wasn't...
Yeah, that's what I meant.
Yeah, there wasn't just so much laughter.
It wasn't so much... things weren't possessed by this. There was no jester.
The jester was relegated as a smaller spirit. I was the dominant spirit of these woods.
But after the terrifier won the great war, I became a mere lake spirit, a pond spirit.
And I've tried to expand my influence, but to no avail.
And meanwhile, my Kubler elves are enslaved by the kitsune's.
Which is something that I know the king now frowns upon.
now i guess his dad
uh... this is the prince then units that
it's not a one say anything
hi yeah well this is too many m_p_c_'s so i'm kind of disorder carted around in
and make sure i talk every once in a while but can you hold this for me
that's what i'm here for
and she's holding all of them
do this is close to the head
She says, uh, she says, um, you're not going to be able to...
You guys want that beast, right?
- How did you know?
- I'm a spirit of the woods.
I know all the, all kinds of--
- Yeah, she can hear through like trees and shit.
- Oh yes, that's right.
- What color's my penis?
- Did you hear what we said to grandma?
- Well, I've lost a lot of power,
so I can't hear that far.
What did you say to Grandma Kuba?
- She's mostly high and bi.
- Okay, good.
- We like her to be...
(laughing)
Some crap in between, but not all that much crap.
Okay, that's...
Yep.
I didn't try to fuck...
What?
I have no issue...
Let's just stop it right there.
Yeah!
Let's stop.
I'ma look the other way now.
So...
If...
The only issue is that I can't help you...
I can help you find your way out of the woods as well, but I need to have my power restored from the jester.
So this is another thing we gotta do on top of finding the beast and then we gotta get rid of the jester.
I'll give you your powers back.
And then I just kinda put my hands up and go like
*mimics sword noises*
That should probably do it.
She's like, "Thanks!"
No problem.
She's become evil.
She says, "You see, the yoni egg of Baskin, it's been..."
It's been...
stolen...
by...
Conneria.
A dark warlock...
who serves the jester in these woods.
If you bring me the Yoni Egg of Baskin, I can restore my power...
and help you...
fight off the Kitsunes, free the beast...
slay the beast, even.
Yeah, it could probably do that. I mean, we got nothing else going on, right?
Yeah, I mean, that sounds...
delightful!
You like that, then?
I'm smiling!
I have a crush on her.
Okay, well...
This is the first female character I've put in the game in a while.
You haven't harassed, so...
Good job on all of you.
I want to poop on you.
Is that better?
Yeah, that's what I was looking for, thanks.
Now, I will show you where Conneria is inside of your minds, and you all sort of just instinctually
know some sort of like waypoint exists above your provision.
You're able to figure out where Conneria is.
I remember that.
Yeah.
Beware, though, the jester will try to stop you if you try to go after this warlock.
And he has many tricks up his sleeves, Conneria.
Like what?
Like a...
- Can we get some examples?
- Well, he has a familiar that can take on the shape
of any form.
The shape of any form, huh?
Is that what came out?
Doesn't really make sense.
(laughing)
Take on many shapes, it's a changeling.
- He can take on the form of a shape.
- So he can be like a triangle.
- Maybe like a rhombus.
- If he's a square, I'll lose my mind.
(laughing)
I hate squares.
- I really fucked it up.
The familiar that he has is a changeling.
It's a very rare familiar for a warlock.
- I have one of those.
Wait, so how do we know that you're not the changeling?
Um...
Thing.
Well, she remembered that thing about my uncle.
That's true, changelings wouldn't necessarily remember the thing about the uncle.
Well, what if they do and you're telling us that because you're changeling?
Yeah, what if I made that all up?
Boys, what shape does she look like she is right now?
[Laughter]
She's in a big circle of water.
I'll say it, hourglass.
[Laughter]
You gotta pass.
Well...
"Well, thank you. I hope the changeling doesn't become a woman in that case."
"Me too, man."
"It sounds like you'll..."
"I'm gonna have trouble as it."
[laughter]
And she says, "Go now, return the yoni egg to me,
and you will be able to slay the beast.
And stop the kitsune's."
"Can I actually just use your bathroom real quick while I'm here?"
"Yeah, me too, actually."
"I think the bathroom is just the pee-a-peeing in the pot."
Yeah, no, I just pee here.
Just sort of do it here.
- Oh.
All right, everybody else is doing it.
- Get your mouth out of the water, Stiebel.
- It tastes sweet.
- That's, honestly, I have a very poor diet.
- You might wanna get checked for diabetes.
'Cause this is sweet as hell.
- You know, I don't know if it's like being a spirit thing,
but you know, I'm a little,
I feel sluggish a lot of the time.
- Yeah, that makes sense.
You nap a lot.
- I, yeah, and I'm not depressed or anything.
- Yeah, I'm worried I got diabetes.
(laughing)
- Like diabetes, well, have you drank your own pee?
- Hey, look, I don't wanna talk about this.
- Okay, well, you were very open about it
when it was me and your uncle, so.
- Yeah, well, I had Juicy Juice in there.
(laughing)
- I hate Juicy Juice.
So yeah, you guys wanna go find the warlock or you guys wanna do this other...
You can also go right to the Kitsune settlement too.
I think finding the warlock...
I wanna find the warlock.
Will we get a special item?
Yeah, you will get an item.
I wanna put that item in me.
Yeah, okay.
I head straight to the warlock.
Okay.
I hope my friends follow.
You guys walk a bit further into the woods now.
You gotta know where the waypoint is.
And now it's sort of approaching dusk again.
back to that time when the fairies were around. And I do have to roll something. Okay.
And he's rolling for how much fun we're going to have.
Was it a 10?
It was a 10.
A 100?
Yeah. And so you guys walk over.
It sucks when I can see the dice.
It's a bummer.
Why don't you just roll one in your mind?
Hold on. I'll look away this time.
No, I mean, no, I'm just going to keep that number. It's not, it doesn't, I'll explain
one day. So you walk a bit further through the woods and what's all of your... actually
I have your sheets with me, I just realized.
One thousand.
Yep, it looks like I have ten trillion.
I actually have your sheets with me.
He knows, dude. He knows we're lying.
I'm not lying.
hmm so hmm all right yeah
Patrick Jodar, roll a dexterity saving throw.
Oh, fuck you.
Mm-hmm.
I got, uh, 15.
Okay.
Patrick Jodar, you, um, see, you're walking through the woods, you're leading the pack,
'cause you're sort of now, you're the survival guy, you're the tracker.
Uh-huh.
And, um, you see in the corner--
So would you say I'm the leader?
- No, I mean, I'm not here to--
- You're the tracker, I'm the hacker, he's the attacker.
- Okay.
- Mm.
- Ah.
(laughing)
I'm so--
- I don't remember asking.
- Yeah, and you start to see some weird, like,
stirring in some of the bark,
and then you see, like, a hand come out,
and it looks like an ape's hand,
and it goes to slap you in the face,
and you just dodge right away.
And you're (imitates ape)
And like, you hear it vanish into the tree.
Like, into the tree.
Like, phased into it.
- Knock it off.
- Yeah, if there's a dragon out there.
(laughing)
- It's not a dragon.
Some kind of a...
- Chop the tree down.
- Some kind of a beast.
- And you see, Evil Steevel,
you feel now all of a sudden,
something go, "Ahh!"
and just like jump on the back of your head
and start slapping you in the face.
- Knock that off, I said it once, I won't say it again.
- And you take four damage
as this thing is slapping you in the face.
- I'm at two health, bro.
- And fucking scraping at your face.
- Okay, I'm gonna swing my sword at it.
- He's scraping at the same wounds
that I got from falling down the hall.
- Oh yeah.
- Damn this monkey tree.
- Yeah, and so you see that there are these,
you see two monkeys that are just sort of like
diving inside of trees
and diving out another one almost like they're teleporting between these trees
uh... and you once we're sort of
was it off his back now
always on my face on a case on the hit the one that's on him
okay uh... roll-and-roll
away a
mhm you know i'm a special abilities
monkey be gone
uh...
abilities i have
I have Thieves' Cant.
So that's like a language.
Well, monkeys kinda...
Maybe they speak it.
Yeah.
Limited telepathy.
Use Thieves' Cant and say you have a banana.
I'm gonna do that.
So you use Thieves' Cant...
No, I'm gonna use my telepathy, my limited telepathy.
What is limited telepathy?
I can telepathically communicate simple ideas and concepts with any creature within my reach.
I can use my telepathy to communicate with any creature within my reach.
You
As long as it understands at least one language.
Okay. These monkeys don't really understand any language.
What's all that "ooh-ooh-ahh" about their partner?
I guess they understand ape-speak?
That's a language.
I'll allow it because it's funny.
What's your match?
I know common, giant, gnomish, goblin, orc, and thieves' cant.
You know a lot of languages.
whatever i'll deal with that later um okay
i'll allow it try to talk to this monkey okay so the way that i'm talking to the monkey
telepathically is i'm just showing him pictures that say i'm showing him like sign cut it out
like he's like big neon like yeah neon sign fingers that are doing the joey gladstone cut
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, and the monkey goes "How rude!"
[Laughter]
I think this monkey speaks English. I knew it understood a language.
And keeps slapping Evil Stevel in the face. Roll for initiative.
Bro, I got 2 HP, dude. I'm about to fucking die by--
I can heal you. I can heal you 3.
I'm about to get death by monkey'd right now.
I got 8.
13.
12.
Okay
Dogen you're first
Okay, um, we're all pretty close to each other. What kind of action is lay on hands
It's just as an action. What does that mean? So an action in in in combat?
It's like like an attack an attack is an attack action. So that's an action. That's like one action
Moving is a move action. There's really only like your action and then your move action
Yeah, I'm in a bonus action and reaction
But um so that would take up like what you would do instead of attacking you would do lay on hands. Yeah, um I
Guess you can certainly try to pull the monkey off his face to or do whatever you want to do with that
What did you get on an initiative I got an eight
Twelve okay, so you're probably going next right yeah, so I'm gonna heal you and then you can try to get the monkey off your face
So I'll use lay on hands and heal him for three. Oh, yeah
That feels good all right cool. Yeah, I'm rubbing dirt on his face
Like clawing at me. Yeah, the monkey's like
We like confused by the dirt
So I get three HP right yeah, okay, so I'm now at five I
Love helping my friends you were so kind
You're up. My turn?
Mm-hmm.
Um, I'm going to use...
I hate to go back to this every time,
but it's such a cool ability.
I'm gonna use Chill Touch to rip the monkey off of my damn face.
Yeah, it's very useful. Go for it.
So what it's gonna be, though, is it's gonna be an attack roll with it,
and then you're gonna do a strength check.
Fourteen.
Plus, I think, four, right?
Plus... what do I add? Just the hit?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Uh, yeah, so eighteen.
Nice, yeah, that definitely hits.
So now we'll roll a, um, strength check.
with the hand so it'll just be yeah just add your strength because I'm gonna
assume that the chill my strength to a basically treating chill touch like it's
amazing which is probably not what I should do but I don't care yeah it's
great so another 18 see how the monkey does whoo okay the monkey also got 18
but the monkey is also less strength than you I think what's your strength
Zero.
Oh, maybe not.
Let me see what monkey...
How do you have zero strength?
You're as strong as monkey.
Oh, I have zero strength too.
Or plus zero.
Let me see what monkey5e...
Let's see what they say.
I forgot to write that down.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
It was minus three.
Yeah, monkeys are not that strong.
Yes!
So, you take this chill hand.
You do...
Roll for damage for the chill hand too.
I'm basically making chill hand very good, but I don't care.
I think it's cool.
Four.
Yeah.
So you grab this monkey with this chill hand, and you roll for damage.
And you get a kill.
I think it's cool.
- Four.
- Yeah, so you grab this monkey with this chill hand,
and it's like, "Bah!"
And you just rip it off your face,
and what do you do, you throw the guy?
- I throw it underhand like a softball right at Sullivan.
- Yeah. (laughs)
- Just wind it up.
- Yeah, just the windmill.
- Whatch!
Sullivan is gonna roll a dexterity saving throw.
- He'll probably dodge it, it'll be easy for him.
- He will not dodge it.
- Fuck!
- And the monkey just lands on his face,
like, "Ahh!" and Sullivan's like, "Ahh!" and it's just like this, this Sullivan like tumbles
on his ass and this monkey's on his face like yelping in pain and like contorting
itself. And it is now, it is now the monkey's turn and the monkey is going to hop off
of Sullivan and scurry and go back inside of the tree and hop out of another part
of the tree about like 40 feet down further in the woods and then hop back
in that tree and dive again, like using both of its move actions. It seems to be running
away from you guys. So you can obviously pursue or you can let the monkey go.
I'm going to hop into the tree. It's not my turn, is it?
It is your turn now. Okay, I'm going to try and hop into the tree.
You hit your head on the tree. God damn it.
We should burn down the whole forest.
So it's like 40 feet away now.
It's like 60 feet away.
Also we know the direction we're going to the warlock right?
Is the monkey going towards the warlock or in a different direction?
It's going in the, it doesn't seem like it's going directly towards the warlock.
It seems to be just going away, like running from you guys.
And is it like, does it, is it fast enough that we could reasonably catch up?
Like would be.
could
not to worry about this money i think i think we might go to the only hired a
monkey
race yeah i bet it's part of the i've been a case or did jester
uh... all she it just recently what shape is the monkeys yet triangle
first squares or something like that some rudimentary shape
the rombo
sir rombo room
so it's that
so it's the change i think you might be a changeling
I think this might be the changeling.
Yeah.
And I turn to everyone and I say, "Yeah, I think that might be the changeling."
And yeah, well, it's, it's, it's, if you don't want to do anything, it'll just be gone from
your side.
I flip at the bird.
Yeah.
Fuck you, monkey.
Hold on, let me do a strength check.
Can I throw a javelin after it?
Yeah, you certainly could.
Okay, I'm gonna do that.
Do it.
plus dexterity right?
14.
Can I flip, can I, if I flip at the bird will that, do I have to roll?
No.
Can I roll?
Yes.
For psychic damage?
I mean, I'll allow it if you get a 20.
Okay.
What happened?
My knee.
He re-injured his knee playing Dungeons and Dragons.
Not a 20.
Not enough bud.
injured his brain.
He's smart.
Yeah, you hit the monkey...
Wait, what did you get again?
A 14.
Oh, no, the monkey sort of like, "Wah!" and just like zoomed right into like a tree and
kept running away.
Yeah, so he got away.
I'm fine with that.
Yeah, let's keep going.
Yeah.
Okay.
I ain't worried about you, monkey.
Yeah, be more careful of trees.
But that better be the last monkey we see on this trip.
Say that much.
Yeah, so you guys travel a little bit more.
I'm starting to approach evening if you guys want to,
want to like take a rest,
'cause you guys got beat up pretty bad.
- Yeah, I'm definitely taking a rest.
- You guys want to take a long rest?
- Yeah.
- All right, so you guys start to make yourselves
a little campsite, make a little fire,
sit down, chat about your day,
you know, typical long rest stuff
as the evening approaches, the stars in the evening.
- Are they beautiful?
They're alright. They're pretty good.
Yes.
Um, Planet E-Bomb has some nice stars that they can look at, some interesting constellations that Cam and I have to finish figuring out what the lore is for that.
List them all right now.
No.
Uh, and, uh, you also see sort of a, you see a, a, a, somebody approaching your camp. Uh, your little encampment.
Oh, hey Sullivan, I didn't realize you were so far behind.
He's like, "You guys started sprinting! I don't know where you went! I was so scared!"
"We need to get you a scooter."
"But who's that behind you all the way towards the camp?"
"Here, take this, Sullivan. It's called a s'more."
"Thank you. I'm allergic to good-tasting food. I gotta..."
[laughter]
"Then do not put that in your mouth, Sullivan."
You will die instantly. That's the most amazing food there is.
Don't eat that s'more, Sullivan, if you want to live.
I slam it out of his hand.
Goddamn, why didn't you tell us sooner?
I'm sorry.
I've been feeding you so much stuff.
Eat this nasty crap.
I've just been pretending to eat it.
I didn't know how to say no.
You've been wasting our food?
I'm not.
Not the rations. That shit sucks.
All right, good point. Actually, you know, I'm sick of rations. I'm honestly glad we
found this s'more stuff right next to where we set the campfire, right next to
where we set up our campfire. Almost like a trap when you think about it. Maybe that's why that guy is all pissed off.
You see a guy coming, he doesn't seem pissed off, and he looks like sort of like a
dashing sort of a bard type and he sort of looks to you all he's like sort of
shows up he says oh I didn't know there'd be other people out here we did
not touch your s'more stuff no no it's all still there don't check no it's
those were not my s'mores though I do appreciate you saying then we were lying
to you probably gonna do that a lot in this interaction coming in a friendly
way how are y'all doing today wait good tell me something only you would know I
need to make sure that you are who you say you are well I haven't said who I am
by the way which is very suspect I'm sorry my name is Martin I'm a bard I I
I was looking to find the lady of the woods, the white woman of the woods.
I wanted to beseech her with a song, but I seem to have gotten a bit lost.
Hold on.
I remember you.
God damn it.
You guys, this is the bard.
He was in the room with my uncle and the white lady from the lake.
Oh, that Verdane who was- Yeah, Trunchbull.
Trunchbull Yodar.
Can you play that song for us?
I could do my best actually.
He pulls out a lute and he says, "If you all don't mind, I'll happily sit down."
No, you guys are going to want to hear this.
Yeah, me and Steve are going to plug our ears, but you can go ahead.
I can't stand the crap.
Okay, all right.
I put marshmallows in my ears.
Yeah, I put chocolate in my ears.
And he starts to play this song and he says, "Once upon a time there was four guys."
And a child.
I do not like where this song is going.
Every person we meet seems to have...
Just because I got chocolate in my ears doesn't mean I can't read lips.
I know this is going south quick.
You guys, you gotta let the sun play out.
I'll take these out, hold on.
And there was once a beautiful white woman.
And a handsome dashing verdan.
He's probably talking about my uncle, not me, but if he's talking about me, I will accept the complice.
You're willing to see how long this song is?
Mm-hmm.
It's 25 minutes long.
Whoops.
Okay, what's your HP?
Oh no, 11.
What's your HP?
Max, or?
No.
6.
Well, we didn't long rest yet, or we did?
We didn't.
Okay.
As he's singing this insane song,
Evil Steve-o, your eyes start to grow heavy.
You start to get real sleepy.
And you start to slowly drift off to sleep.
Patrick G. Odar, you as well, slowly drift off to sleep.
- And you know this song is not a man, it's a girl, man.
And he's one of them.
- And Evil Steevel, not Evil Steevel, sorry, Dogen,
you start to nod off.
And you, you're at 11 HP, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay, six, five, seven, eight, five,
just adding everything up.
- I think you're asleep, Patches.
And you start to almost fall asleep,
but you manage to stay up.
And you see Sullivan sleeping next to you as well.
- I did have marshmallows in my ears.
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, you didn't take yours out, did you?
- No, I didn't.
- You don't sleep at all.
- That's right.
- You see your friends start to fall asleep,
and you see the--
- I was so stupid.
I can't take them out.
They're really stuck in there.
I tried to.
see the handsome sort of bard look to you and sees that you're not sleeping.
Can I pretend to sleep? Is it too late for that?
Go for it. Roll a performance check.
You are so smart.
Oh, nat 20.
Fuck yes. Okay, you perfectly pretend to fall asleep.
It's so perfect that me and Pat both start clapping in our sleep.
Yeah.
Yeah, you slow your breathing down. You almost like literally slow your heart rate.
Can my HP go up while I'm sleeping?
Prince Jumanji was asleep as it is. He was a kid. He was tuckered out.
And the only one who seems awake now, who seems awake, is Sullivan.
And Sullivan sees you all sleeping. He's like, "Ugh!"
And you see the, he looks towards Martin, the bard, and the bard looks towards Sullivan,
and he runs to attack him. And he takes out, his hand turns into a giant claw,
and he goes out to attack Sullivan. And so he's like finishing the song, he's like going like,
He like goes to attack Sullivan. What do you want to do save him? Yeah, I mean, I'm obviously gonna save him
I'm obviously gonna the bars. I let it hit you with a big fat. You can't attack another bard
Bards code. Yeah, can I like surprise attack him with my shovel? Like can I just like just yeah
You can't up and just I would say just clothesline him. You can definitely do a
Reaction here because he thinks you're asleep
With I'd say with advantage you can do this. Okay. Yeah, I'm gonna just try and clothesline him with my my big shovel
17 okay that hits roll for damage
Okay, 10 damage, okay
So it makes a really really loud clang that sounds like an alarm clock
So yeah, you you're like pretending to fall asleep, and you you kind of are able to get the sense of where he's coming from
And you see as he's attacking. He doesn't look like a handsome bard anymore. He starts to look like
some sort of like
featureless creature
Who comes at Sullivan with a claw? A creatureless creature? That's easy! A meetureless we- what?
And as you're trying to figure out what I just said
You swing the shovel around your shovel ballax and things like like going to attack Sullivan and you just like
Like like yeah, right the imprint of his face. Yeah
Yeah
and he's like
You fuck and like like he like what was that that was that was schoolyard language. What did I just hear?
You're asleep. I thought I woke up and this weird featureless humanoid then then
Starts a sprint away, and he says connery. I will hear about this and like javelin
You throw that one roll roll for an attack
16 that hits roll
6d 6 plus your decks
- oh
You you p. I use fury of the small to add one damage. Oh
I have a goblin ability where I can add one damage if somebody's bigger than me I
Fucking forgot about that. Yes. I can only do it once per short rest though. Mm-hmm
It's a good use of it. Very good use of it
So you see you see your jowl goes through this thing and you see go
And you see like poof
Away, and you feel its presence is gone
It's like that was probably nothing
You too start to stir now that was a sleep spell right now I
Thought I woke up earlier, but I think I was dreaming that I woke up
May you talk in your sleep man. It's weird. Yeah, I interrupted my shit
I have night terrors after seeing some of the things of my uncle did yeah to the white woman. Thank you Dogen
Oh, yes, that was terrifying
Oh boy.
Say my hero.
My hero.
Say it in a girl voice.
That's right.
I didn't mean that to be a burn.
No, you got it right.
Damn it.
I just don't really know how to...
My hero.
What are you making that girl voice for?
Yeah, that was good.
That could have ended very badly.
Dude, I was probably going to die.
I had 5 HP.
God, you're so smart.
I am so beautiful.
beautiful so yeah you guys can also we have no idea what happened yeah I'm also
already asleep when you guys wake up yeah all right back to bed for me I just
figure I'll tell you about it in the morning yeah I'm gay I would say because
we made him stand watch last time we probably go nobody watching this time
yeah yeah okay what's the worst that could happen yeah that guy's gone right
nobody nobody watching from now on for the rest of the game he put away don't
listen to that okay don't plan anything for that I would never um he rolled
something so he did he rolled how proud he is of me yes and I'm I'm one proud
that's a lot yeah proudness that's true yeah so you guys uh yeah you know you
guys sleep without a vent I mean you guys sort of were able to handle the
the
towards the where the the warlock is supposedly and you come up the the wood
start to look muddier and dirtier and grosser this is truly where a warlocks
hovel would be and as you it's truly where a warlocks and as you get
approach a little bit closer to him. It's, you hear that laughter that you heard
that you always sort of kind of hear in the Whippet Woods. It's a little bit
like stronger now in terms of its sound but it's still just sort of like
hovering in your subconscious. And you see a stubby, sweaty-looking, clean-shaven
dwarf communing with some sort of clownish figure. So with the jangly
little balls on the top of his silly little hat. He's floating above and he's
talking to Connoria. Who is that? Can they see us? They can't see you. I crouch
down and I sneak attack. Chill, chill. He hasn't even made the setting yet.
When you're done, I'm going to sneak attack. Yeah, eavesdrop first.
Yeah. And you can try listening to roll perception check, see if you can listen in.
Who has highest perception? All of us? Okay. Go for it.
I got a 19. I got a 15. Oh yeah. I got a 3. All right.
The marshmallows are still in your head. Yeah and I'm also just staring straight down at the
ground too. I'm not even trying to read lips. Yeah and you hear the Jester like sort of
saying something. Something you guys can kind of hear pretty pretty well. He's
like saying something about like somebody it's in the woods. Outsiders.
You hear Connery like, "Oh, come on, meow."
You sort of get the sense that they're talking about you guys, probably.
And then, Patrick Giotto, you're sort of like crouching over, looking in, and the jester's
like talking, and then the jester stops moving and turns and makes complete eye contact with
you.
I already have my bow and arrow ready.
And then the jester appears five feet in front of you.
Ooh, that's scary.
I flip him up.
Wait, pause. We didn't want a horror game.
We didn't want to clear you on doing something scary.
Can he be like 10 feet?
But he's backwards.
He's not looking at us.
That's really scary.
What do you want me to do?
You're right, you're right. I should have told you before this.
What if he is...
What if he dies and...
What if he is a friendly guy?
What if he's friendly?
He's friendly to villains.
And...
evil Steve oh it's a just evil and we're villains - no I can't allow that I can
make his villains I can make him seven feet away what if the jester what if
he's one inch tall what if he's the gesture well he's a spirit so he can be
any size you want okay so so at first so that it's not like a jump scare he's
raised to what it shrinks to one inch tall okay and then comes and then
shrinks back up like kind of slowly so it's not too scary when he switched on
one inch tall and then he teleports to seven feet away so it looks like he's
the same distance away because yeah expect is that scary though that's my
carrier you know what that's scarier than what you had no no I might not be I'm
just trying to understand and 19 how do they see me oh he's a spirit fuck um and
he's really tiny and he's 10 feet away oh and a relief good thing he wasn't five
feet away or I would have said my penny I would have gotten so scared he slowly
grows bigger and he's the right amount of scary for me and he says to you all you
ignored my cries in the woods my cries of pain he's like giggling to himself as
he's saying this I thought that was laughing yeah I feel like that's not on
us really yeah I didn't hear anything I don't know what you're talking about he's
He's got marshmallows in his ears.
Yeah.
You shoot away my ambassador fairies.
You've made me very upset twice now.
Well is there any way we can make this up to you?
I mean...
How do we know you're not the changeling?
The way I see it, you have three options.
Three!
I choose three!
That's the bad one.
I made my decision, I'm okay with it.
Can we hear the rest of the options?
Give me those marshmallows. I put them in my ear so I don't hear them.
Option 1, you can serve me in my woods.
Nah, that one is not happening.
I'll provide for you.
Shut up.
Okay.
Option 2, you turn back now.
If you can't find a way out, why don't you just force the mudmen to tell you?
You all seem strong, you could probably...
I don't know why you're laughing, it's not funny.
Yeah, what?
Are you laughing at me?
'Cause I'm small?
You could probably...
Have you gotten to option three yet?
[laughter]
Option three is no option at all.
Then why did you say...
That's two options, then.
Yeah, what the f...
You press on doing whatever it is you're doing.
Okay, so it is an option.
And there will be consequences if you do.
Well, there'll be consequences if we don't.
Can't you see that we're just three friendly guys?
Hey, I've got a joke for you.
Knock, knock.
Hey, wait, you're a comedian, right?
Tell us something funny.
I can't help it. Who's there?
Chicken butt.
Joe?
Chicken butt Joe who?
Chicken butt Joe mama.
[Giggles]
See, he liked that. He liked that.
That was pretty good.
Yeah. I've got a million jokes about orcs, too.
You've chosen to continue
Why did the uh
Actually what's the uh hold on
Why'd the orc cross the street?
Should it be orcs or
Maybe it's somebody who's not terrif-
Are you terrifier born? Can I just ask you that real quick?
I'm a spirit of the woods
Alright I guess I'll like
Orc jokes I don't know
Why do the uh
Why are orc ships uh
Why do they have glass bottoms?
I don't know why
bottoms why so they can see the old orc
Navy he orcs are so stupid
yeah I could say I'm part work I can
invert invert and I don't I guess it's
kind of an orc or something right that
and he says he looks you all and he says
you've made your choice and he vanishes
what no we did it we I told you some
good jokes three and you see him like like he is spirit sort of like zooms
away you love that joke and he's still that one's a thinker it takes you a
minute to really get it and you see Connery a turn around and and sees you
all and you see that his eyes are sort of shifting colors and he holds up what
looks like some sort of egg and he says to you all in the jester's voice and now
the fun will really begin.
You'll roll for initiative.
We should roll now.
I'm rolling Pat.
War 20 is like a table ten.
[music]