[Music]
Last time on Trebuchet Village, end of Zeebom's World,
our heroes, down to two, met a valuable third in Chuggie, the Changeling, the Singing Submarine.
I was dictating this.
Then I stopped.
the confines of potential pervert and certain murderer Flint Lateralis, Chuggie was happy
to accompany Dogen and Evil on their quest to "vibe" the Quadro Mudmarks. Or perhaps,
'tis more accurate to say they were glad to accompany Chuggie, because after all, he is a
rare changeling who took the magical herb Percocet and forever became a real working submarine,
at least when he's not shapeshifting, with a periscope made of congealed hair,
Pixar-style eyes for front windows, and he shits out his exhaust and he is gross inside.
The now undersea adventure began with an ill-fated encounter with some rubbers,
who weren't interested in living up to their namesake as workers at the sex factory,
which I was reminded was honestly pretty dope, and they get to have tons of sex with babes.
An honor.
It was less about the thing, it's not about having sex with babes necessarily,
it's more about reproduction.
the factory monitor
it's
citizens
like six in a story i actually i don't really what's wrong with what's right
just with sex proceeding a sex factory is fucking dole
well i don't know that there's a problem i was saying i was wrong this was me
this is a mea culpa it was a generational gap i think we'll talk about
that yes that's got generated by the on views on reproductive rights yeah yeah
patches is twenty thirty years older than that
is true is yes
he's in his mid-fifties
so he's just not
all the way up to a yes i doesn't
doesn't know what's what's right now
so chuggies we talked away those robbers
and they continued on their journey
then you guys uh... chose to ignore reused asset from a prior game
which had a different thing going on yeah i know i fucking believe that
with the fleet but he can't say what it was actually are for you i could say
what it was yes it was it was a
magical tried yes if you pulled it out
was also stock underneath some volcanic rocks he would have taken some damage
those magical trident would've begun a little encounter with a merfolk
adventure who was looking for it was in a beast was not a beast
so we got
fought by not doing
no i mean it was still a risk to do it big star man
well yes and then then you had to deal with them
What's the name of that thing?
So I've been going through some names in my head.
Right now I've settled on the winged predatorium.
The winged predatorium.
It's kind of like planetarium, but it's a predator.
Predatorium.
Predatorium maybe I guess.
We have winged predatorium.
Nigel.
How about chicken little?
Chicken little is pretty...
Chicken big.
Chicken big, yeah.
Chicken big, that's pretty...
Poultry.
Mine is cool.
you're a loser I guess but I like yours a lot. Chicken Big.
And it has a chicken's face. That's better. That's a retcon. That would be good if it
was called Chicken Big it should have a chicken's face. Okay finish the intro.
A beast that preys on sailors who navigate by the stars. Luckily our heroes
were in a submarine and knew to dash quickly under the sea using loud noises
to sartle the beast until Chuggy could dash away.
(burps)
- Whoa.
- Holy fuck, I'm sorry.
- That's a possession right there.
- It has been three days of uneventful travel since,
as Chuggy hugs the knife's coast,
entering the seas by the dirtlands.
So, you guys have been going down the coast
towards Beriberi, if you recall the map.
Now only a week away from Port Loseberry,
our adventure may at last find some solid ground
uh...
uh... anyway so yeah what it was the last three days of the on a mental travel so
and ninety nine bottles of beer on the wall
ninety nine bottles of beer
you were going to ask what he was singing?
I was going to ask what you guys were up to during that time
I had my head stuck in his flesh just to close my ears
the
you
you know yes I'm not underwater
do I see you do you ever go could you go up above and go I'll
I'll go up. You find like a small island or something? Yeah. You have to chart it.
An isla.
He has to be a hut. I still have to be inside this fucking guy? No no no no.
It's a spell. It's a spell.
It's a spell. He can cast a spell. There could be a hut.
Well I'm a pretty big like how many feet what did I say I was like 30 feet.
You're huge. Yeah. In your submarine form. Yeah.
So that hut would have to be pretty big huh? Well unless you transform unless you
shape-shift back into like a humanoid form. To use the hut I have to
a
It doesn't have to be maybe we could put out and then have football games that we can bet on as a source of gold
that's
Insane it's not a bad idea, but no you'd have to you could pick a humanoid character
It doesn't have to be one of your I think I'm just gonna because if I put my blowhole above the water
That'll be fine. Yeah, you could just live that way. Yeah, you could make the hut for I'm gonna do that for right now
Okay, and so that he's gonna put a hut on top of his body
No, no on top not on top of the island or on top of your body. Where did you where what is happening?
I'm just trying to figure out how you sleep because you probably have to sleep at some point
I just there's a submarine sleep and go big guy. Yeah, well cuz I said he's a guy
No, he's not. He's I have an autopilot mechanism. You have no no pilot. Yeah, it's like he's like a shark
He's got us keep moving that I sleep slowly goes that I like. Yeah problem solved
So he just you just like your eyes just like roll back. Yeah, just like
as you're like sort of me me me
snoring underwater me me me me me me me me
interesting command on physics
I love to snore
they don't have a very good command on physics
that's a good point
ok yeah I was trying to figure out what have you guys been
so you guys have been traveling along
I'm playing cards with a tapeworm
with a tapeworm?
I'm ranking how good tasting every part of Chuggy's body is
What's the ranking right now?
His butt is number one.
Oh, that tickles!
Awesome.
We're going to begin some underwater encounters.
Thank you.
Who said that?
Which one of you guys said that?
Who the heck said that?
Oh man, we're having a little...
Oh, this is not the right side of dice.
Bruh.
What you looking for?
You seem so lackadaisical today.
Your heart's not in this.
My heart is totally...
You need to drink the rest of Diet Coke right now.
I will drink it.
I will, alright.
You already led to one of the worst burps I've ever heard, but I wanna hear the second one.
I wanna hear what's the next level, yeah.
Yeah.
Wish I should've gotten Diet Coke before.
No, I got a Yerba before this.
You had a Yerba before this?
Yeah.
You're a fucking psycho.
Yeah, that's crazy.
I had some water.
Oh my god.
It hurts to drink Diet Coke.
Why are you saying that in a Jamaican accent?
I can't drink all these right now, man.
Diet Coke in your throat, Billy!
Okay, that's a fun one. All right, cool. It's a fun one it is
So
Come on tell us it's Spongebob. Fuck you man. It's wait. Can we really?
Right, we'll let him finish it could be squidward
Did you guys hear that yes a dog
so
yeah, you guys are swimming along and
You see, I guess Chuggie really, you would catch your eye, or one of your two huge eyes,
where you would see a sort of a faint glow below you.
Not below the, you know, like the pressure sea level,
but this sort of like, just faint, like reddish glow, kind of like flashing in and out.
And you would see that it's coming from some kind of like scaly looking man.
He's blue and green and he's like bald and
He has been trying to
He's like waving around a staff and it's shaped like a clarinet
It's very funny because this guy I didn't realize it till after pretty much looks like
Gotcha you got then just make him Squidward man. No half-stepping
God say
Say
Wocky slurky slush say that walkies walkies large
Bleeding spongebob
Are you getting business cards?
No must be must be really old episode remember that it is the old episodes are the good ones
Yeah, sure first three now dude the last season was go to yeah, that's right
Patrick star show that oh my god, that's it. It's next level. It's like better call Saul. You wouldn't think yeah
They did it but it's even better
All right. What is this guy doing? So good work. Yes
Squidward, what's his original name? His original name was Kwanzaa spell Q u a and
They both got a Q in them, but they do they could be squanza
I think it's a word and uh squanza black squid word he uh he as you're going by
He goes halt you
whale
I'm not a whale. I'm a submarine
What what's a submarine? It's a thing I made up
well
Okay, I
Need your help with what I?
am trying to summon a crackin a cracker a
Crackin you're summoning a cracker a crackin
If you're summoning a cracker you could just go to Applebee's, honey
What what's Applebee's
It's something I made up
Well, you're just full of surprises. I'm full of people right now
He looks and he sees in the two window. I'm doing I'm like pushing my face against the side of his body. So you see
Like a imprint of our face. Yeah, I'm doing the same thing. Yeah
Then I'll eat you too if you don't do it
He's gonna think he ate all your gold. I don't have much give me it all
He starts waving his staff faster and faster. I was kidding
Okay, roll
persuasion
14 no so I I did that you have plus 10
You keep talking what so that's a 20 you've plus 10. Yeah, I mean
So what I did wrong is you get both your proficiency
So anything that I have a plus the parents actually attend not everything
Certain stats you get another bonus
Unimportant. Yeah, do I get anything like that character sheet?
What do you have that no because part of being a bard is having like insanely good
You have mad skills bro
Skills to pay the bills. She so that is a 20. Yeah, so shizzle so he says
You're gonna have to do that math every time that that happens. No, I'm gonna pull up the
Math sounds difficult. I wouldn't want to have to do plus six multiple times
I'm pulling up the sheet. It's not plus six. It's plus ten. Oh shit. That's even harder.
That's so difficult!
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm wrong.
It's more. It's higher numbers.
You actually have plus seven, but still seventeen.
Oh, he did fuck the math up!
You have performance ten and deception ten.
Because that's like your two skills you have expertise on.
But you have plus seven on persuasion. I don't know why I didn't add proficiency bonus on that. I should have.
But anyway, so characters fucking four feet tall bro. You're a dwarf
So he says um, where does it say you're okay?
well
If you're not gonna eat me then and you're not gonna help me then why don't you just move along?
Though I will say if you help me summon this cracker
There's more gold than you can even imagine. Okay, I'm gonna do and power. Oh
I remember when I was just can you shut up? Okay
What are you gonna do with it?
I said I'll do it!
Okay, okay. Then come. Come swim here.
Any uh, uh...
If you want me to come, you're gonna have to buy me dinner first.
What?
I don't know!
I'm teetering on gay boys!
Yeah, we're calling that teetering.
Um, yeah, so yeah, you swim over towards him and offer.
Yeah, you offer. Do you have...
I have little fins.
I was just trying to...
You do?
No, I have full arms.
Wait, hang on.
I have full...
Like, Michael Phelps arms.
Michael Phelps arms.
Yeah.
That just, you do the breaststroke?
Yeah, and legs.
Wow.
What?
You're not a submarine then.
I thought you had a propeller.
Can we just use your...
You have a fleshy propeller.
But I have full arms.
But...
But they pop out maybe?
My hands look like this.
You have rock and roll hands.
You've got rock and roll hands.
It's like, yeah, so imagine my middle finger.
ring and my middle finger are gone on the hand. So you have three fingers. I will say that
they are like anchor arms because you can't do combat with them. Anchor arms? Squidward
tentacles? Spongebob? Alright, you've never seen Spongebob, I'm convinced. Spongebob?
You've never seen him? You actually are an old man. What's that called, Spongebob? He's
He's one of them Pokeymans!
Yeah, he's got a friend, he's under... the water?
Who's that character from Spongebob, that blue one, Kwanzaa?
Kwanzaa here?
Kwanzaa!
That blackfella, Squidward!
He's got the shaved head!
That's the only guys I see do that.
Squidward is black-coated, and we're here for it.
So, yeah, you swim down, you offer one of your weird arms, he takes it, and Squanza starts
waving his staff around.
He says, "Oh, great Kraken, come to me!
Come and bless our lives with your presence!
Be the Kaiju Manji that we've always need!"
I didn't finish writing this, and then he waves it around.
It is like a spell, it is powerful, and you can tell.
what comes out of the spell and it's powerful and you can tell it comes out
of the ether is not a kraken but it is a it is a huge shark that just rams right
into squanza he's gonna take some damage why did we wait we knew he's summoning a
crack but he said we get a bunch of gold but we didn't have anything to anything
I say I'm the thing yeah there's all Patrick no fuck told us it's a fun one
I'm in front for you too I'm having some amount of fun
there we go actually okay that is for now
dead what's is not dead can he come into the submarine yeah I mean he got hit by
by the shark and he says, "Help me! Help me!"
And so we're gonna roll initiative now for you.
I mean, you guys can roll initiative too,
if you want to determine just general turn order.
- I don't want to fight a shark.
- Yeah, I'm inside.
- I think I'd like to hide in his huge body.
- I'm gonna have you guys roll initiative
just 'cause you're around.
- Okay, we can man the controls inside.
- The dot on the bottom is a nine, right?
- What?
- Dot on the bottom is a nine.
- Yeah. - Okay, so I got a 10.
- Well, it's on the bottom of whatever the number is.
- Okay.
- So if the dot is on the bottom of a six, it's a six.
- I got a six.
I sound like Squidward. I got he does it slower. He goes like
Sponge Bob sponge Bob sponge Bob and Patrick
He's the heart he's difficult Squidward is a hard voice that's facts. Yeah, I got a six patches all right
Sixty oh I forgot to add my initial off day. I got a 17. Oh, I got a fucking
I don't fucking even know because my sheets are all shit. You just need the top one really
Oh, I don't miss with this one. I don't have that. I'll make it. I don't have that one. I don't
What every other sheet in there is it it should be on the top of your front page?
He doesn't have it
it
no this one's i will have all your
it's a little
doing this transition to analogue
uh...
of the world my racial traits on it
it's like you to go to a sub-zero i have a plus one parts all that to say that
instead of six hundred-fucking seven
uh... but don't you're gonna go first
okay you also don't need a huge favor
if i ask what these are
that's like spells and shit here and they're all right yes i can help you
with that and so many spells that you have actually a more still you're way
more still a little bit
so you also is right now we're in this form you can't
do combat
but i'm gonna have to have to throw everyone up
you can follow up stated here
of clinton's room at all
also more and clean it's like high school all over again what happened
poltergeist will have to figure out what happened figure out how i got first i
think we should figure out the way mechanics of you guys trying to steer
him so here is your now we've been i'm not i'm not a very serious i want to
actively not fight this show yet now that i've heard what he's doing on my
turn i got first i'm gonna clue myself to the floor i'm not interested in him
surviving i probably have something
i can't talk at time myself to him or something
since i saw myself to i don't know his you feel a little weiner are you type
something like usual
weiner inside
tires of the middle of the fun my role of my inventory i guess i'm not going to
because i'm going to be a time like cosmos and i literally really really
tired you have wrote that it will have a weight on it and that you feel a if i
move around you do have a real good now how to tie yourself not a fucking
scientist okay i'd be making my head
you can tie yourself to
my like a control
definitely don't tie yourself to my uvula
i'm tying myself where
anywhere that's sticking out
ok
that is tieable
do you have a handle in your body?
i don't care about which
i do have a handle but it's an eject handle
and it ejects every person inside of me
it doesn't, i'm gonna be tying myself to it
i won't be ejected, that's the whole thing
patches, i'm just gonna simplify this for you
i'm just gonna dig my fingernails
into his body
not your turn
and i'm just gonna hold on for dear life
and just so you know, that's gonna be my turn
Okay, then I tie myself to the steering wheel.
Okay, so you can do that as your first action, technically.
And now it's the shark's turn.
The shark is just gonna keep trying to eat Squanza.
Hey, great D&D fantasy character patches. A shark.
Nice creature.
The point is he was trying to summon a Kraken, and he fucked up and just got a shark.
What's up?
We can bolt if it's going after Squanza.
We should shoot a bolt at him.
That's a very fine idea, so miss.
Do I have a cannon on me?
No.
And yeah, the shark tries to chomp at Squanza, and Squanza's able to sort of like, get out
of the way.
"Ahh!
Ahh!"
You know, the Squidward yells.
He's like, "I'm gonna leave."
He does like that.
Okay.
Your turn, Chuggy.
I'm going straight up.
I'm gonna do a free-willy jump.
Okay.
Over what?
Just out of the way.
I'm gonna look, there's an island close by, right?
Yeah.
So you can beat yourself on that.
There isn't necessarily, I mean, you can just go.
You can just use your turn to just...
I just wanna do like a giant jump and I wanna beach myself on shore.
Can you save the free willy stuff for when there's somebody.
Alright fine, I'm just gonna go to shore.
Can't the fucking jump over?
Yeah, I mean if you just, just, you know, swim away you can just get away from this.
Okay, I'm gonna do that.
I'm just gonna swim away.
Yeah, you just go, you just hear.
Do I roll?
No, you don't have to roll, it's just movement.
I'm gonna just see if Squanzo lives.
Squanzo's gonna do one of his spell attacks.
Why do we care if Squanzo, he's out of sight out of mind.
so i'm not squandering a folks was a good fuck off he's not it's not squirted
occur
yet he's barely also all this i'll go ahead and tell you right now just to
seven die
this film still matches so far you have a shark
as your fantasy creature and i'm fucking clear ripoff of squid
already get fucking sued
so we'll find out squandra uh... you know screams after you
i'll catch you for that
for what's what i want to talk to me do it
it has been a
uh...
you might not get you for this all i will resolve that if he tries to get us
for its fucking crazy he fucking some of the shark is crazy he was trying to
some of the crack and i said a crazy guy
you should be a
you know
living there
and there are a few reply are you flying up
I'm going to the island you're going up to up to the top top top of the top of the place top of the water
Holy shit, I'm just trying to get to shore a little horrible day. I'm just going to short. Okay. Yeah
Oh, yeah, you get up you go to shore you kind of rest on an island
Yeah, what I do is just like a band in the little island you guys can coconut hunt investigate
I'm gonna change into a I want to make sure it's actually abandoned and we're not gonna go to sleep and something strange
to
at my thing.
And what form are you in?
I got a 7.
You could just be a detective you saw once.
I think I'm going to introduce G'day.
What's up?
Well, weren't you already acting pretty G'day if you ask me?
No, this is one of my forms.
Oh, okay.
This is G'day.
I am G'day Contole.
It's my name.
are you are so you you are you became him and we're stuck in your work and some
of the other you know you're not a lot of the island i was tied up
they want to know how you know you're he's out i think so he just died
who's the biggest part of it so it is a little bit about the public's public
consult that has a role in the character
you know
who's good day control what what kind what races as i have i would like to
meet you to do you are you given us a warning you're about to change or
military one way we're investigating and we can't let it is a process and i'm a
a
I'm assuming G'day, Kuntal is a scaredy cat race just because that is the accent of the
scaredy cats.
And I have a crocodile codpiece.
It's a codpiece.
That's a penis holder.
So you're 5'2"?
5'2".
So you're like an elf I guess?
Yeah, it's a guy I saw one time.
And you're not sure what race he is?
I
you
I mean with the 15, I'll say like, at least from what Chuggy is able to suss out, I mean
this is just a island, like one of those, just one of those islands.
Well just like a random landmass that kind of like billowed up and doesn't really have
anything going on.
But we're not gonna get, as far as we know, we're not gonna get like coconut crabified
or like head shrunken or something.
But is there any kind of tropical wildlife, like maybe like a, like a, like a, like a
star fruit?
Or is there like a starburst tree?
Oh my god, we almost said the same thing.
Yeah.
We almost had a jinx.
What were you gonna say?
Starfruit.
I said a starburst tree.
There are-- there is fruit in here.
I asked about coconuts basically the second we--
Sorry.
Yes, there are-- there are coconuts.
Are you rubbing my leg right now?
I'm sorry.
I'm just-- sorry.
Why are you being so weird today?
Why are you guys making me weird?
Gently rubbing my back.
He's being weird and old today.
Yeah, there's like-- there's like coconuts in here.
[LAUGHTER]
killed as a closer to you
yeah i don't know if not weird old man
uh... so we're going to put a
i'm a put a coconut my pouch
my stomach
as their new everyone going to raise them
written a coconut
i put one coconut my stomach that's a very normal that's like a kangaroo
what do you want
all my god it's candy sand i'm getting the same
uh... yeah you start eating the sand it uh... it can be candy sand it cannot be
the
golden
brody's are hearing
you know in the dirt
okay i'm swallowing the sand as fast as i can so it's not a man of the more
as i'm water
yes i'm important to tell you
Give me some advice.
I'm a water guy now, I don't do that kind of thing.
What if he taught you like a new street joke, knock knock?
You should, if somebody betrays you, you never want to talk to them again.
And that's something I guess that maybe some people don't understand.
I think I've betrayed you probably 30 times.
I got a street joke for ya.
What?
What's your name again?
G'day cunt hole.
No, it's hole.
Oh.
Cunt hole.
Good day, Cuntle.
Cuntle.
Cuntle?
What's your joke?
Good day, Cuntle.
So a blind elf.
A blind bozma
walks into fish market
says, "Hello ladies."
[laughter]
"Good morning."
Because he's like, he thinks fish are women.
He thinks it's their vaginas.
He thinks the scent, the smell, the look, the way it looks.
Is G'day Contal like the kind of bard, is he like a comedian bard?
Is he like a Ricky DeVito?
He's uh, a drunk.
He's just a drunk guy.
He's addicted to Fosters.
Fosters are cool.
Fosters are home for imaginary friends.
He loves that show.
He's patched like a kangaroo.
I guess he's, he could be a kangaroo guy.
Yeah, okay.
He's a kangaroo guy.
I guess I saw a kangaroo.
In gun city?
Or in gun, in tributary village?
He made a fucking shark earlier.
Yeah, you're right.
You can get a kangaroo.
That's true.
It's actually, it's a dangeroo.
There's no way there could be a kangaroo.
Okay, it's a dangeroo.
It's a dangeroo and its feet have Nike shocks on them.
That's what makes them dangerous?
That's sick.
That's actually really cool.
I want somebody, I want to see a picture of one of these.
See this guy's not even DM, he comes up with that.
He's got a shark.
Alright, I'm trying to write this down though.
Danger room, danger room.
the
mostly dressed like crocodile dundee except for these new features that were added
but he has no pants just an alligator or crocodile
cod piece
and a pouch so he's like a hermaphrodite
i mean he's a changeling and he also has
mental problems
he has a mental problem
due to
his mental health
he's dressed like crocodile dundee but he has a pouch
is a pouch he's part danger route or is basically part danger
he's part danger route you are a key to remember from an island
it
well i'll be talking about australia's so cool for once you have you know and then
you just started just talking to my i'd fuckin i was trying to think of a
really good as the rest of the injury that's all we need to be dangerously
injured rockwell dundee
make sure that they have a nice shocks
got it done
and that's on last week and he still have the sunglasses yes but they're like part
of his head? They're part of my face. Yeah. I think that's cool. But it's kind of like
a clay face thing where I can make anything because I'm a changeling. Yeah. But it's all
flesh. Okay. You're like a... That's what I was trying to say. You're just an abomination.
Yeah. Okay, cool. Everything that I look like is an abomination except for one. Okay, cool.
So except for one of my forms. So we'll now, yeah, so what do you guys, you guys want to
like chill here? You got coconuts. Did you get a coconut? You got a coconut, you got a
and
he said
i'd look at the guys and say
watches
and i just start
trying to push the uh...
push that
coconut out of my pouch like it's a
okay yeah it's like a
was that you know you know for the you probably know what the hell are you going on about
a video where the lady shoots the golf balls out of her butt
what it looks like in my pouch with a coconut. Trying to do that with a coconut in a kangaroo
in a dangeroo pouch? Yeah.
Holy fuck I think I might just stick around.
Check it out boys!
Wow! Oh my god!
Holy this is way, you're way better than chuggy the
engine
Thanks!
Wait does- That actually hurts his feelings a little bit. Oh so it's different, it's-
I never, listen I don't know where you came from all I know is I fucking hate Chuggie
man.
I'm so glad he's gone.
Never gonna see him again.
I just step one foot in the water.
Hey bros!
He's just like, hey bros!
He's just like, you're trying to be cool now.
You just explode!
Oh, oh Chuggie.
Hey Chuggie.
jagi
and i go back on the display
turned into a couple of the out of the puddle like you see like bones
like blood forming
doesn't look good when i tell you're talking it doesn't determine your to it
looks like
like imagine like the the same viscosity is like the terminator thing but like
it's also like
creating bones
blood and stuff
and every time that i try to change into it it's like
like it's the memory of the memory of it
so every time i try to change into it i get more fucked up
nothing you mean, you just... it's like a game of telephone with my forms
that was one of the most insane descriptions i've ever heard of anything
i'm trying to think of it on the spot
look, it's not all gonna be winners
i think it's, no i think that's cool
so yeah, do you guys wanna like
chill on this side again, it's like a non-descript island
you can chill here or you can keep going
do you have a changeling that might be some kind of
like beach chair or a floaty
and drink my coconut
uh...
what
i mean
alright check this out
and i pull off my leg and turn it into a floating chair
oh my fucking god your inspector gadget
holy shit
he's allowing it
i'm already sitting in it so there's no way we can go back or else
I take my other one off and I turn it into that big Margaritaville chair.
You can only turn your limbs into Margaritaville shit.
Okay.
That is- I'm sitting on the other leg.
And I turn my arm into a Margaritamaker.
See, you gave him the leeway by saying your limbs. He was only at the legs.
No, it's fine.
And then you were like, "No, go wild on the arms."
Because we were talking about a Jimmy Buffet character, so like, we found a way to like, still have that.
Is this Margaritamaker, is this thing endless? And also, be real with me, is that your blood I'm drinking?
Yes.
Fuck.
I'll have ten of those.
Alright!
I'm drinking a bunch of them too.
We're drinking all of his blood.
It's becoming very sickly.
I'm eating coconuts to try and keep up.
I'm just like...
I'm having a great time, guys!
I'm having one of the best times in my life!
No blood in your body, no limbs either.
in
I mean, I look like Kirby, so I'm not.
Do you have any, like, shrimp?
Oh, what would really hit the spot right now is some coconut shrimp.
I turn my penis into a net.
I put all my body parts...
I put all my body parts back on.
That is your final limb you could use.
Okay. Well, no, I'm putting all the limbs back on.
What about your toes? I feel like those would be good.
So they're already stuffed full of margaritas right now.
But I really want shrimp.
I'm turning my penis into a big net and I'm trying to just catch
Oh, okay, I was gonna eat his fuck out of your penis. Yeah, same
Yeah roll survival oh my god, I finally get to roll survival
Yeah, well my survival is like the worst
Yeah, well my work sets ever yeah, you get like
like
Oh my god.
Are they at least already popcorned?
Are they pre-popcorned?
No.
I pull up a fucking...
They are de-veined though.
It's a cardboard box.
A freezer drink.
Half of it's gone.
Half of it's gone and they're so wet.
There's a note on it that's wet that says "sorry."
Yeah.
They're expired and...
Alright, I'll eat them anyway.
I'm chowing down.
Yeah, that's great.
I mean, I would say you should save them because they can restore hit points.
more on my right now i think i'll out there how much was it a little bit of
a reason i have a look into white hold on
take my head off and i turn it to the barbie
the head of the land ahead head no the head of the drama line alright
what did you write on his head with a bit funny i could have had another voice
for a talking grill
we use let him do robin williams shit just fucking like do a bunch of your
voice in the senate this session
just stomping on his bowl just okay just for this island is that is i was for this
this
this is the s this is the the d_n_a_'s dead all five million legal five minutes
of out of game time twenty four hours and
all right you think of it what do you think i'd turn it into a grill
to grill
the barbie
and i started a shit all on the grill and cooking the shit all
always on that i'm i'm running as fast as i can't running almost two miles per
hour i think i'll just fly around as well
I start flying, I fly through the sky and I start erecting giant, it's like a lucid dream,
I start bringing up giant skyscrapers.
Maybe that's how we justify this.
But then we create this, I see, I, I, you create skyscrapers and I'm on the ground and I'm
molding sand into little people and I'm creating a civilization that lives in the city.
We have a civilization that's going, "Hi, we love you!"
And they're developing technology but then the technology becomes too strong and it starts
destroying them, pulling them apart, right?
Climate change comes, a giant wave wipes out the city.
Oh my god.
Right, and from the ashes, one worm.
The worm builds a spaceship and he escapes the climate change island.
And he goes all the way out.
And he builds a space station up in the air.
With a hundred other worms up there.
Yeah, he reproduces with them and they create beautiful - and then the worms, they look
down and they see the ruins of this civilization and they want to explore it.
But they're a warlike people and they are very aggressive.
So they're coming down in these jet fighters and they're just making sure there's nobody
alive left in the civilization. They're going "Mreeeow" and they're dropping bombs.
Atom bombs.
They're pretty rad.
Mushroom clouds.
Where's your grill?
Oh, I turned back into myself and I turned my finger into a bottle of soda.
Sorry, keep going.
And then the mushroom clouds and then...
I'm just standing and watching all this drinking a soda.
What kind of animal eats mushrooms?
Snail.
A pig.
A snail.
of a planet. It sees the mushroom cloud and thinks it's a mushroom and comes over and
tries to eat it. And then it becomes irradiated. And then it starts to attack the earth that
we us four actually in real life live on. And it starts to destroy us. And it kills
Patches, his entire family, his mom, his dad, his brothers, his sisters, every single person
in your family is completely wiped out. And it kills a lot of people all over the world.
but
and it's called it's called um... the life of uh...
the life of a penguin and he plays a penguin sergeant
he plays a sergeant in the penguin army
wait one more thing
and the beach is made of candy
man i'm about sick and tired of this beach and i'd like to get back to our
adventure
Alright, I'm gonna turn back into the big blue bitch
These bloods blue on the inside
Oxygen
All right turn back to Chuggie
Some sort of lucid dream happens that I guess tells you tells me how you guys really feel about me
And you know you know your whole family and how we feel about Ukraine. Yeah, that's true, which is we don't play
All right, Slava
Slat
Slava my slat in the Ukraine my slimes over and we don't fucking play when it comes to Ukraine. No, let that be known
Guys keep going along. So now it's been that was like one day now. It's been another day
So we're closing in on time now until you guys are finally gonna reach berry berry
and you see in front of you a faded find a
side of the road know a giant octopus and
And what it's doing is it's taking-
Can it be called a croctopus and it's part crocodile?
Yeah, yeah.
Or what about like a croctopig and it's part crocodile and part pig and octopus?
No, I think just a croctopus.
Alright, well it's two out of three ain't bad.
Okay, what about-
I don't like to take this, we're not on the island.
No, I think the croctopus is fun.
The croctopus-
Oh my god, it has like crocodile tails for arms.
No, no, no.
That's sick.
is
time
We
a
I'm
I think I'd like to play this game.
the
I'm
all
Wait, wait, wait, I use challenging instincts.
Oh, what does that do?
You gain proficiency with the two of the following skills of your choice, deception, insight,
intimidation, and persuasion.
So I'm going to use that on both insight and intimidation.
Or persuasion?
I have a question too.
Yeah, you might want to do persuasion.
Okay, I'll do persuasion and insight.
You get one on all of them, by the way?
You gain proficiency with two of the following skills.
Okay, cool.
So we'll add...
Yeah, because you don't have proficiency.
You already have proficiency on insight is the only thing.
Does it add...
Deception and persuasion.
You have expertise on those.
No, you already have...
That's just like a boost.
Oh, is that a...
Okay.
Oh, so I already...
I can't...
No, yeah, yeah, yeah, no.
I can't activate it.
Got it.
What you can do...
I mean, you have...
What you do have, you have the ability fast friends.
So when you need to make sure something gets done, you can't rely on vague promises, sworn
oaths, or binding contracts of employment.
You cast a spell, choose one humanoid...
We're gonna ignore that.
Within range that you can see and hear you, and that can understand you, the creature
must succeed in a wisdom saving throw or become charmed by you for the duration.
I'm gonna use that.
While the creature is charming this way, it undertakes to perform any services or activities
you ask of it in a friendly manner to the best of its ability.
I will do that.
So what are you gonna ask of it though?
I'll think about it.
Can I ask a question about the mechanics of the game?
Can I ask a question about the mechanics of what this...
So is it, there are shells that are getting shuffled up and we're trying to point to which
thing is...
Yes.
is
so
the
doesn't work then this is our backup.
Ok.
So in this case, this is instantaneous and it is standard action, no it's one casting
time so in what level is it?
It's level one spell right?
How many spell slots do you have?
I have four I think.
I think you do too.
So I think you can probably cast.
I mean I also don't have to use it until we don't, until we get a bad insight roll.
Ok cool.
Let me see how many spells you have.
It's just our bad, we have that in our back pocket.
the
You can also do blindness and deafness if you want to get into a fight.
I'd do it on myself again.
Okay, don't do that.
Blind and deaf.
You'll lose the spell slot.
No, go ahead.
Alright, so roll insight.
I need a D8.
Oh, I need a D8?
No, I need a D8.
You got a 9 and a 3, right?
Yeah, 3.
And then roll again because you get advantage because you guys are working together as friends.
Oh, damn, that sucks.
A 7.
seven. Let me roll my d8. Here, I'll roll it for you. No, no, no, no, no. So you, you roll
an eight instantly. All right, cool. And what'd you get a 12? Yeah. Okay. It is not, you know
for sure it is not in tentacles. So there's one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight
You know for sure it's not in tentacle.
8, 7, 4, and 1.
Do we want to cast my spell here?
Yeah.
Okay, I'm going to surreptitiously cast detect poison.
Okay, cool.
So roll...
Why detect poison?
Because we're trying to find a baby octopus which is poisonous.
Which does have poison.
Octopi.
We had a whole discussion about it.
It is a croc-topus.
That's true.
Holy shit, man.
So yeah, okay, you can detect it underneath three.
Okay.
I tapped three times on the inside of his body.
Three!
Okay, and the octopus lifts it up and like claps two of its tentacles for you and slide
and reaches with one of its arms behind itself, the croctopus I should say, and slides out
15 gold.
Yo
Add 15 gold to your inventory
His inventory yeah, I'm the one who's the one who found the damn boy. He's giving it to him
We're splitting it up after okay
Okay, so now
Wait did I use become fast friends? No you did not yeah, I'm gonna do that right now
Well the only thing with that is listen buddy the only thing would become fast friends
you should know is it's about asking it to perform a specific task and
the task that performs if it's like so what if I just say like
but get baller a normal and just give me all the good stuff
well I do love that idea you saying that
but I'm it's important to support the thing is that
I'm the activity result is much more make sure to the country at the
conflicts the creatures normal activities and desires a creature can
make another wisdom saving their training in the effect
said the only thing you'd be risking okay but if it just ends the effect
it might be aware that that happened I'm
I don't know, I actually don't know if it becomes a ware.
Well he's a carny.
Yeah, when the spell ends the creature knows it was...
The creature will know it was a rare.
You should save it until we don't have any more detect poison left and then try to use
it on the last one.
I would wait.
Alright, so now roll another insight check as it whiffs everything around.
We're gonna get all five of these fucking prizes.
Let's go.
Ooh, that is a 19.
20, 21, 23, 24, 25.
You know it's...
25.
Okay, you know it's in either 5 or 6.
Okay, now just do whichever is higher
Which is Patrick's I cast the spell or no
If we if we get this one wrong do we not get to keep going I think it's in five
We don't get to keep going if we get it wrong. Okay, then we just cast a spell every time so we can get at least
Yeah, yeah, all right
Cool, that's fine. I'll just sleep on him
Over the next day. Well, but it's already narrowed down to two. I feel like yeah, I mean, okay
Well, is it worth the risk live, but I know he's gonna change it. Okay. We'll say okay that I won't cast this spell
I mean, I'm funny as long as both slots. Sure
You know, so I'm getting talked out of it here. I do know what it is. But all right, you know, you got spell
Okay, it is six
Wow, I
Mean this would be the time to try to do one that's fast friends and see if you can get I just thought there's no way
Yeah, give you the prize instead and keep going
What do you mean give me the prize?
If you do fast friends you can ask him, "Well why don't you actually just give it to me?"
Did we not get it?
I thought he already got a prize.
I said it was six.
Oh, I thought he said five.
No, he changed his mind before you.
Oh he did?
He said five and six and five and six a bunch of different times.
Yeah, that's why I was confused.
He said six.
Because I said, "Because it's six."
No, I swear to God.
Okay, you listened to my advice of saying that it was the higher one.
Okay, good.
Alright, good.
In that case, then you get roll, one of you roll 2d4.
roll 2d4 you've got it oh oh my god two three and four three four
potions whoa oh that's very good oh my roll so awesome okay cool you guys like
you playing yep no I'm just gonna cast it every time from now on okay well but
Wasn't that kind of a good moment for the listener cast
Like that
So I have it I have in cities
Yeah, just go ahead and roll and if we don't know which one is for certain I'll cast it
Okay, I'll burn all my spell slots cuz I'll just take a long rest
15 okay
Sorry
No, you said 15. Yeah, okay, you know it's not in one two three four and five I cast it
Yeah, okay. I cast that I can't take that poison. I cast it
It is in seven. I
Did not realize I was not thinking that the octopus was we have poison. This is great that you guys gonna get a lot of cool
Shit. Yeah, he claps. He's like very impressed
He didn't clap the time that Caleb rolled
Can we can we get a clap for him? Maybe it's a little one. Thank you. We've got a little octopus clap
Boy you guys get amulet of the drunkard. Oh
Old ale stained wood. Oh my god while wearing it
You regain 44 plus 4 hit points when you drink a pint of beer ale mead or wine
Doesn't make you act like lit once the amulet has restored hip. Don't use it when you get lit
Once the amulet has restored hit points it can do so again until the next dawn
I mean, this is basically health potions are really hard to come by if you're wearing this amulet you basically have like
One free very powerful health potion a day. That's sick if you for me that would be very affordable
We need to be writing this crap down. I have it written down and I will split it up at the end
Yeah, you split up at the end. Call the amulet of fucking being drunk if
Not cool, okay
Next roll you guys are gonna get everything that's right. That's right. Okay. There's only one item I mean on here I
Want every I want every good thing. That's right. Yeah everything you got we're cleaning out the kiss 11 today. That's not good
11 that's just like okay
I'm casting it don't even roll. You just can't this octopus is don't even roll. I'm casting it
Yes it all right, so you're down to I have one spot left. That's perfect
You know it's up, but we didn't use one for one of them. You know you know it's a little
You know it's in one. Yeah, so yeah, you get it
I tap once one and what you get the octopus octopus you can see he's fond of this item
It's a deck of illusions
Fuck dude. This is gonna make everything
I always wanted this this box contains a set of parchment cards a full deck has 34 cards
The deck found as treasures usually missing 1d 20 minus 1 cards, which I'll have to do that for next time
But the magic of the deck functions only if cards are drawn at random
So the one he made this magic. No. No, I didn't make this one. I don't make this wish I did
This is from D&D from the Wizards of the Coast
But what it does is essentially is it's like a bunch of cards and when you draw a card out
It'll just make an illusion of a creature and so then oh, so it's like you yeah
Yeah, basically and then like a mirror so it could be a massive beast
and then we'll scare the shit out of everybody or can distract people and
Once you use it, it's it's the card is gone. Okay, you basically have this deck of like you can have like 52
34 but it's a lot of different creatures basically your well
Sounds cool. It's not as cool as the fucking amulet. It gets you fucking slizzard doesn't get you slizzard. It's not but hey
That's one. Oh wait. Let's see what the next one is. Let's see what the final one is
Let's see what this final one is and listen. You still have the tech poison. I still have one left a chiller
Nice chiller episode folks
It's 11 again
Yeah, I cast the right poison spell slots
Okay, so this one's the one I made
Okay, it's cold and the octopus probably like a shoe or
Tentacle is trembling. Is this a shark? This is a computer. Yeah
and he takes out what looks like a
If like the octopus is like kind of scared of this item
It's called the blutter the what?
the blutter
No, it's an ancient terrible gun
After an attack connects, a player can declare that they're using a blood bullet.
Rather than dealing damage immediately, a blood bullet lodges into a living target and begins to deal the damage as necrotic damage over time.
The player rolls 68 and then divides the amount taken each round and round it up.
That amount is then granted as temporary hit points to whoever shot the weapon for a max of one half the user's total damage.
Holy crap, we have like a communal chest you can have a max of three blood bullets can be deployed at one time
And only one blood bullet can be lodged in one target until all the damage is done
So it's like you can't like stack mm-hmm, but you can like have it on three different people
Yeah, drain their HP each turn and add it to your own temporary
Letter it's called the blutter. Okay, who has the most HP? I think I have 28. I have 39 -
-43 okay, I feel like whoever has the highest HP should whoever is the lowest HP should get either the blood bullet or the drunk
Amulet right
Over the three things we got we got the drunk amulet the blood bullets and then water deck of deck of illusions
so
Who I mean also who wants what I guess I want this lizard amulet
Because I like getting fucked up. Okay. Yes, sir
Okay, and the bladder and a big cannon on me and amulet of the drunkard
I have a coconut smiley face. I have an amulet of the drunkard smiley face. Mm-hmm
You can turn the blutter into a okay, I guess I just haven't held potions
I guess I just get the deck of illusions and everyone else gets what they want. That's fine. Actually, I want to say any illusions
That's fine. Wait, I was yeah
I was being that with that one friend who like tries to make their home get the first and then you and then you
Start you then you try to cash it in immediately. I want to do I want to take illusions
No too late, it's too late
With my creative mind in that deck of illusions I would make some of the greatest beasts
No, it's not it's just a set. It's random, bro
It's random. I don't make up the beasts as I go. Oh, but no you think he'd give you that type of power and shit
that's true about a
Luggage named Oh lug. No, I had a slap the shit out of you for saying that Oh lug. No
know
Alright.
Wait, who got what?
Pat, did you take the deck of illusions?
I don't care either way.
You were telling me that I should take the blutter because my health points are low.
I mean that makes sense to me.
Yeah, I guess I'll do that then.
Because you get temporary HP.
Like a blizzard.
I also will say your dex is a more important stat for you and the blutter is going to deal
damage based on dexterity.
Turn it down for what?
I'll take the deck of illusions. I'm enjoying my amulet. Alright, cool. I'll give you the
chart for that next time we play. And if you're going to use it, I mean, now, let me know.
Okay, I'll use it right now. Alright, so, um. I'm just joking, dude. Use it to make
another octopus. I'm just playing. No, I'm playing. We could watch them mate. We could
watch them mate or we get the octopus to do this game to the octopus. It's literally an
Why does he have a baby octopus? Is that his son?
And why is he using his son?
His only begotten son?
Do you want to ask him?
Yeah, that's fucking irresponsible as shit.
What if I used a blaster on the fucking... where the shell where his son is?
An octopus just sort of shrugs.
And what if I got so angry at you that I decided to smash the shells?
And destroy your only begotten son?
An octopus freaks out about you destroying the shells and like sort of like...
You are just, I don't want, I'm glad that we lied and stole all your stuff.
And used secret magic that we didn't tell you.
Because my eyes widen.
Or at least I wish that we had done that.
We didn't do that. We played a normal affair.
But I wish that we had just rocked you.
Look at this, his eyes narrow.
There we go. Get those eyes back down.
[Laughter]
Because you are an irresponsible father and a bad human.
The octopus is sort of like, "And you smell fishy!"
Yep, and if I walked into a bar, he told me a joke earlier.
If I walked into a bar and you were there, I'd say there's women in this bar.
No, you screwed it up.
No, I think I didn't.
You screwed the joke up.
The octopus pulls out a joke almanac to try to recall what this could be.
It's all written in octopus.
I don't know how to read this.
It's all just black ink on the whole page.
I just see my mother.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I got it.
Thanks.
Yeah, alright.
That's the octopus in there.
That's the octopus in there. The octopus sort of like swims away. You see him takes his son with him
The sun sort of waves that you guys. We should kill him and harvest him for his ink
We could sell it at a high price. Chuggie something is you have something wrong. I have a lot wrong
What is wrong with you I just I just told him how to. I'm completely a criminal in other forms. Your name is evil Stevel
But I've become good-vil stuv-vil as of recently with my huge heart
And as I saw that son and it reminded me of my son that I've completely abandoned and forgot about until right now
Oh shit. You have a son. Yeah, and I'm what's your son's name name's fucking Doug
Fucking Doug Doug Stievel no
No, just Doug Doug and Doug fucking Doug. Yeah, and I Jenny was the light of my life
And I forgot about him until right now
Isn't that sad? What does his mommy look like?
He never knew his mommy
You
He never knew her at all. What about you? I don't he'd never even met her one time
What about you did you meet his mommy? I think I did a couple times
But I didn't remember her that well because she just wasn't that's kind of just not much to me
She didn't mean all that much. That was a different man. She didn't look like a whale
I was I used to wearing lipstick. I used to be a hoe in trebuchet village. I was a hoe
You're a hoe and I had a son and I forgot his name was Doug Doug
Son of Steve Doug son of Steve son of Steve. Oh, okay. I'm trying this down. Okay, that's a huge part of your character
Yeah, and I completely forgot that
And now I'm addicted to drinking
My drinking amulet and I'm gonna go back. I'm addicted to Percocet and he's got a pill problem
It's an herb and he I've seen him comes from the earth. We all have
Vices he put I seen him put floor in his mouth
On the floor I didn't do he put that in I kicks that I don't do that anymore
He did it at the bit. We got to that sand. It's different
But it directly when you found it's different than dirt you put your floor or the what I consider the floor
water in your mouth I've done that too water with my floor but now dirt is my
floor I think this might be the most emotionally poignant moment that we've
ever had in the entire year. I'm about to dry. One of us died a day ago and this is more emotional than that.
Look at that. Look at the sky.
Yeah.
I'm drifting. I'm drifting away.
Congratulations.
That was just lovely.
Alright.
I'm being hideous.
This love that I'm feeling
I wanna know, wanna know, wanna know now
I've got to know, got to know, got to know now
[Music]