We're on.
I just made a stinky fart.
So last time on Trebuchet Village, Tales from the Seabomb, End of the E-Bomb's World, you
guys finally made it to Hot Babe Island, where you were welcomed by Juniper, the right-hand
babe to the Queen Bee, the head babe of Hot Babe Island.
You met the Queen Bee and she told you some interesting things about yourselves by consulting
a relic from, once again, another realm.
In this case, the Realm of All-Knowing.
Which is how Hot Babe Island has stayed so safe and protected for so long.
Told you, Evil Steeble, that you don't belong here.
But that it's more complicated than just not belonging somewhere.
'Cause I'm a steve.
I'm a steeble.
What the hell am I doing here?
I'm not going to join in guys.
You're singing about my character and I'm not going to join in.
So you think your character is not a steeple?
Did I say that?
I didn't say that.
Yeah, you essentially said that.
That song was not accurate.
You're wasting our time.
He thinks the song is accurate.
Patrick is trying to explain the intro of the thing.
Okay, let's hear it.
And I'm not a teacher's pet either.
And Patrick Yodar, you were told, you were asked if you wanted to still be an adventurer.
You gave a hardy affirmative and you were told that danger is following you.
So I should have said no?
No.
I think you gave a farty effeminate.
What?
That's what it gave.
I like that.
And Dogen, you were told that the dirt cod still plagues you and that...
Yeah, like anybody have experience with an X?
No.
potentially traveling to the dirt lands could help you alleviate that if that wasn't an
interest.
Y'all ex-girlfriend ever plague you?
Nope.
Plagues my inbox.
Facts.
My email inbox.
See how's that?
Is that a better fax this time from yesterday?
Yeah, that was a little better.
There's still some work that can be done, right?
Yeah, still sounds sort of like a...
You sound unsure.
That's the problem.
Well, I'm not sure if it's a fact or not, I guess, is the issue.
Oh, God.
So anyway, then you guys went from there to try to do sex trafficking and sell your were
dolphins as sort of sex slaves for Hot Babe Island.
Tried to get a permit and it didn't really work exactly as planned when Stevel shoved
cotton inside of a woman's mouth.
I don't remember that.
I do.
And then, but then she sort of said like,
all right, fine, just go play,
because Patrick, as we've learned,
is from this island, or at the very least,
was spent some time here as a youth.
- I was conceived here.
- Yes, and he has some memory of his time spent here,
and he is looking for his mama.
- Yeah.
- Who's actually my aunt.
- It's a little confusing.
- Yeah, we haven't revealed anything yet about it.
- It's not revealed yet.
- The genealogy is imperfect, but it is there.
- It's my aunt who might be my mom.
Or it's my mom who might be my aunt.
That's right.
Sort of a quantum uncle.
My uncle could be my daddy.
Right.
Yeah, if that were revealed.
It sounds like you grew up in damn Tennessee.
That's right.
Yeah, because you're only a Tennessee.
Because I was ten when I saw it.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
So you guys said you already got your were-dolphin start building the thing.
heard a bugle call go and now it's at the pillow fight tournament's about to begin
so obviously you guys can go join the pillow fight tournament.
Am I at my coloring station? What? You had a coloring station? Oh yeah as a kid.
The Queen said that she still had his coloring station. She said I still have my
coloring station and I said that I wasn't gonna look at the pillow fight
because it was all my aunts. So I think I'm at my coloring station.
pill if it's not sexual yeah it's violent yeah it's like MMA we also want your
aunts were fighting I also want to say you want a good macaroni painting so how
about you just you just can't see it you're gonna have to describe it you're
gonna have to wait until after you're so shit at D&D you could bring your coloring
station maybe to or bring coloring materials to or you want to go to your
station I want to go to my station yeah it makes sense all right so you do one
Yeah, I'm you two anymore for me you guys want to go to the pillow fight
Fuck yeah, dude. Okay cool, so I guess we'll we'll do a little split see here
So we'll start with you guys going to the pillow fight, then we'll go to Patrick going to the coloring station
Okay, alluring station
He's dancing
So yeah, you guys you guys head over to the pillow fight and what the hell are you doing? I'm at my coloring station
He's pulling up some sort of website. Oh, you're gonna actually make something okay all right. Yeah, all right
You have one coloring for kids on swag poop calm
You have to save it go look like you guys calm slash coloring - for - kids
I don't what you're the one with it on your phone. That's I was pointing to you
coloring - for - kids - game
Okay, okay
you say you're an ass s okay okay so yeah you guys follow one of the streams that
sort of strewn about the hot babe island and you ride on one of them one of the
rafts there and you end up at the pillow fight it's another pool where the pillow
fight is and it's an arena it looks similarly sort of in this like lovingly
crafted arboreal sort of tree plant sort of style like everything else here but
it is still like an arena sized arena yeah and just a detail I want to throw in
because I think I got buried in the intro the sky above the arena right now
it's completely black because we built a factory oh yeah there's so much I know
you were trying to like distract us and make us forget that we did that I didn't
say but it kind of looks for building it all of a sudden it looks a little like
like you know when a movie takes place in like night 1890s London or something
yeah, just like black or it's like it's like yeah, like in like it's like
stranger things or something it's an evil dimension with cobblestone yeah,
just it looks like blood-borne kind of yeah exactly yeah, it's horror, it's
horrid looks really it's raining green and white yeah, oh, what is it we can
get back to the act. Yeah, I just needed to paint a picture of that. I need to
- We gotta make sure that we didn't lose our factory.
- Yeah, so your-- - 'Cause it got built.
- Your factory did get-- - It's pretty hard
to play on the phone.
But-- - The coloring game's
hard to play on the phone.
- Yeah.
- Actually, it's perfect and normal to play on the phone.
- And you all should go play it.
- Yeah, you should all play it.
- We need to turn on ads on those games.
- They are turned on.
- And so you guys end up at the arena.
You see that Juniper is leading the yellow team.
There's three teams, red team, yellow team, and blue team.
Missy leads the red team and Mary Kate Ashley leads the yellow team.
You guys didn't meet Missy.
She's the head of the armed forces of Hot Babe Island.
Oh wow.
They have forces?
Just in case.
So yeah, you guys see Juniper comes up to you guys and she says, "You guys are welcome
to watch or join in the games if you'd like to."
Okay, but my pillow is very small.
My pillow is my hand.
[laughter]
I usually sleep on my hand.
Mine is very small and it's attached to me.
Well, we'll give you guys pillows.
So you don't have to worry about that.
Nope, I only will use my own pillow.
I don't like, I'm allergic to cotton.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, we'll use latex pillows.
Well, then you guys probably shouldn't play the games
because there are cotton pillows.
But I'm only allergic to cotton
when it touches me, when I'm holding it.
I mean, when I'm holding it.
That's funny, 'cause I would've assumed
that Hot Babe Island is all babes and women,
and maybe it might be a little PC,
and maybe accept people who are different
and need to use a latex pillow,
but I see now that it's actually--
- Well, if you wanna use a latex pillow, that's fine,
it's just there aren't also cotton pillows around.
- It's over my hand, my latex pillow.
I stretched it over my hand.
Okay, I lied about everything.
- Okay.
- I think I'm realizing I'm a liar.
- Yeah, I've--
lying a lot yeah that's okay okay I'll just play in the games okay here well
she gives you which team you want to be on red team yellow team blue team I want
to be on that same team yes do you want to help me fill up my pillow with spit
I'm filling mine with cameras.
Mirrors.
Yeah, pinhole cameras.
Oh, wait.
You know, that doesn't make any sense.
What?
Tell me.
I just remembered, obviously we don't have cameras, but I do have a funny ability, a
funny spell.
Yeah, once you're in the games, there's no spellcasting.
interesting. Well, it's an it's just an item, but before the
game's okay, well, what can I cast a spell right before the
game? You definitely can okay good because let me let me look
at my while you guys while you guys are strategizing this way.
I do I want to go to Pat and Patrick and where you are so
you guys strategize this. I'm at my coloring station. You're
at your coloring station. Your coloring station is inside of
the palace. You guys you had a little palace room and while
you're in there you hear a knock on your door while you're
coloring hello hello I can't hear anything I'm coloring Pat Patrick hello
and you someone walks in and it is a older Verdan who is a woman look at this
I don't know why you even came.
And you would recognize her as your mother.
Hi, Mom.
Patrick.
Literally no different than when he had the phone in front of his eyes.
Patrick, I'm trying to find you. There we go.
Oh, honey.
That sounds amazing.
Right? Thank you. I'm just trying to do a girl, Alda.
That's pretty good.
Right? Yeah.
That is pretty good.
Alice Alda. Alice Alda. That's my name. Try to make it a little bit more like this.
Make it a little more like this. It sounds like my voice is cracking.
[Laughter]
What's the deal with you returning to Hot Pape Island?
Um...
Oh crap, I don't even remember.
I think I heard the name of the island and
completely forgot that this is where I was conceived.
hmm yes and that you told me that yes many years ago every single detail and
then you left with your uncle yeah on adventures is there gonna be a reveal
right now? maybe oh I feel like you decided that's up to you and not me you
did decide that so you're the drill. well mom I guess this is the reveal. you know everything and nothing so it's
really i guess this is the reveal
that he's actually my dad
my eyes go i'm in a completely different place don't hear any of this my eyes go
wide
and i'll it's like i've been struck by lightning i feel the reveal in my body
yes
he was your father
wow
but he wanted
that's what's great about dean you get to do these amazing character moments
It's a role play and just really dig into...
What I like about it is like Patrick just so fully just embodies a character like you
really like are thinking like him too.
You know and reacting like him naturally.
He wanted to seem like your uncle so he felt...
Well I already know I have a gem in my chest that tells me everything.
They felt more like he could get away with going on adventures and not being a father.
Yeah that makes complete sense.
Yeah.
But then he brought him with him?
Well, he brought him with him because he had, you know, complicated... why are you...
Why are you in my coloring station?
I am the janitor.
Oh, I guess, I mean, if you wanted to ask that question you could.
It's really... I could tell you, I think he had complicated feelings probably.
He's like, "Oh, I love my son, but I also want to go on adventures.
I'll say I'm his uncle and keep him around, but at arm's length and, you know..."
And so he could not be a good dad.
Hmm arms length is how it is a bad dad is a good uncle that's correct
True, that's a good point. Yes. That's a fine line
If we did if we got anything out of the last two years of doing this bad dad
We got a good uncle two sides of the same coin. Mm-hmm
And so we'll we'll zoom out from this reveal so you can finish your drawing
Okay, I got the drawing because the reveal has made me
This is right before the game starts. We're both prepping.
I reach into my pocket and I fumble around and I feel that I have my peephole ring.
Oh, fuck yes. I forgot again.
And then I ask, "Who am I talking to?"
Juniper.
Is there a girls' locker room?
All the locker rooms.
All of them?
Is there one that's got like the best girls in it?
Well, I think it's my team.
What team is that?
- The yellow team.
- And where do they live?
- Oh, it's right over there.
- Okay.
- And she points to sort of--
- And is it like a fully nude locker room?
- Yeah, we don't care.
- Okay.
- Are you joining the yellow team?
- I gotta go do some reconnaissance first to decide.
- Yeah, sure.
- Or actually, nevermind.
I'm gonna put my people ring on the pillow, right?
- If you put, you could put on your eye
and just see through everyone's clothes.
What? Like an x-ray goggle? Yeah, that makes complete sense. I don't know how you don't get that.
You don't, you know, it only goes through like one surface. It goes through a layer.
Like a peephole. Then uh, what, then it's put it on a woman. Alright, I put it on
Juniper's stomach. You see sort of like... A baby? You see a, you see a stomach and
she's like oh oh is everything okay it's poop in here. I take it off. I don't
know what to do with my corn ring. I will find a use for this one day. All right,
so this is less of a free love kind of place about a pillow fights about to
start right yeah. I'll join whatever it what team did you join. Whatever team you
join okay, we'll join red team okay, red team and I cast I'm going to cast a few
spells right right beforehand. So first I'm going to cast I'm going to cast
Thaumaturgy on myself. I'm going to use the option you alter the appearance of
your eyes for one minute. My eyes are going to be completely red.
I'm going to pick up my pillow and I cast Searing Smite to set my pillow on fire.
I
Mean I do you're gonna do something I guess the but urging again to alter the appearance of the flames and make them really huge
Look like I have wings made out of fire
And I would also like to cast okay blindness and deafness on on
on
okay. I think is that
I'm going to cast I'm going to cast command where you can give a one word
command. I'm going to give you a command attack to myself.
Pray for myself. I don't think it's a command.
I don't think a man works like that.
I think you could just--
Become evil.
I think you could just convince yourself
that that's what you're doing.
Sin, that's good, sin is good.
Sin, sin.
So you're completely blind and deaf,
you have bright red eyes,
and your pillow's on fire.
Yeah, and it looks like the flames
are going all over my body too.
Yeah, yeah, so blinded, I mean,
you're not gonna, I guess you're not gonna
try to resist it, right?
No, yeah.
He embraces his new life.
Yeah, I mean, I guess like,
you're just not resisting blindness and
deafness it just happens to you. So
everything's black around you and there
are no sounds you just feel a tremendous
amount of heat. So you're drawing.
You're coloring. He's been eating something nasty.
There's a paper jam in the printer. Did you just draw that?
No. That's from swagpoop.com/coloring-book
You heard it here first folks
you can print out your coloring page.
print out your photo when you're done. Pretty cool. That's huge. Yeah. Okay, so
you're now some sort of demon. Not some sort of. I'm a demon. Okay, and what are
you doing besides casting blindness and deafness? You're just gonna hang out next
year? I'm gonna hop on his back. Okay, can you fly? I don't think so. Right, just
checking you can carry yes. Let me think if you can yeah. I mean you can carry
him that's about that's actually fine because you're a dwarf. It's just kind of
carrying another person yeah, because you're also like a little goblin. So
you're just like this like a little little or you know it never. I also will
cast. I get him on my I put him on my shoulders. Okay, so that he's like we're
tall. I'm going to use my final spell slot too, and I'm going to cast bless on
myself to give myself bonuses. Hold on, let me see if I can do anything for you here.
You're just blinded. Okay, you see Missy, who is the head of the red team, and she, again,
like I said, she's like the head of the military. I'm the head of the red team now. And she
sort of looks at you approvingly and is like, "That's what I like to see!" Like, she's like,
like, like. I'd like to create water in her brain. In her brain? Yeah. This is not going
This is not going to end well for you guys at a certain point.
But I am...
How's she going to even know?
Just wat... it's going to... it's like the easiest way to...
Okay, fine.
Also, I think you also need to be... is it where... doesn't it need to be somewhere you need to see...
you can see?
That would make sense.
No.
What if you create water...
Yeah, in her mouth.
In an open container. It has to be in an open container.
Okay, as she's talking, I create water in her mouth.
I didn't even think about that when we did the destroy water thing.
I just let you destroy it within a tube.
You create it in her mouth.
Yeah, okay, and not as an attack. It's not like I'm not trying to hurt her and
just a little bit of water. I just wanted to it will kind of wanted to just
interrupt her her like whatever speech she's about to give to the she was just
approving and thought it was cool what he was doing. Well, she's just as water
in her mouth. She needs to understand who the real leader is and it's the guy
with the red eyes. I'm blind and deaf. I assume the game has started. I'm a
swing. Yeah, she looks around who did that. She's like wondering who put water
Yeah, who put water who has a creator destroy water as a spell I
Don't know roll deception
Why would she why would I be suspected
Cuz you could just cuz you said it if you said nothing it would have been a lot easier
You're such a bitch yeah, I know
Well
You're a bitch.
You're just a bitch.
Wow, you guys got really mean.
No, I was--
That's a four.
Bitch.
She sort of looks at you and says, "That's a warning."
Got it?
I create water.
I go, "What do you mean?"
I create water in my own mouth.
I go, "See?
Why would I do that to myself?"
So you're just like using up all your spell slots to do this?
Yeah, of course.
That rocks.
Okay, cool.
She sort of shakes her head.
you're just starting to swing so you just roll I think it started yeah yeah it is
starting so nearly pillow fight begin all these hot babes are running out I
don't hear that at all yeah you don't hear that and the pillow fight starts to
begin I walk out with my hand in my pockets I'm just like kicking little
rocks around I'm like oh you know you're back in the palace you're a big reveal
you're walking out of the palace you can walk by your mom the big reveal Wow
Wait, wait, Patrick. Patrick, wait, wait. Before you go.
Okay.
Don't you want to catch up? How have you been? What have you been doing?
I ate a big stone that tells me everything.
You ate a big stone that tells you everything?
Yep.
Oh, well, anything else you've been up to?
I, uh...
I don't know, something about a dimension or something. Like, somebody doesn't belong here, uh...
There's a dirt god.
Yeah, there's a dirt god, Dogen. He's been around.
He's been around?
Yeah! Is he here?
Well, no. I mean, he's been around...
Okay.
...the multiverse.
He just died- Oh, great. It's a fucking multiverse thing now.
Not a mul- You know, I said the wrong word.
Oh, jeez.
I said the wrong word.
Is this some everything-everywhere-all-at-once type shit?
No, I wouldn't do that...
...sort of thing.
You hate Asian Americans?
No.
Okay.
Don't- I didn't hesitate, either.
Look, I just wanted to see how you were doing now that you're here.
It's good to see you're still doing your art. I always loved your coloring and your macaroni art you used to make.
Yeah.
Do you remember the one you made where it was you, you were climbing a mountain and you claimed it, you called it Mount Patridge?
I thought that was so sweet.
That actually happened.
You claimed a mountain?
I claimed a mountain.
Wow.
Yeah.
I can tell you anything.
Yeah?
[laughter]
Look, I also wanted to talk to you about something. So, I don't know if your
father was ever... I don't know if he was always perfectly honest with you besides
about not being your uncle. Yeah. You see... We're cut away from that. You guys...
Okay, I also... I used up all my spell slots but I have one ability left that I'm
going to use which is my channel divinity which I can and I'm shaking my head
channel divinity dreadful aspect and every creature you can see me within 30
feet has to make a saving throw or be terrified of me. I'll roll I guess one for
I guess I'll roll one for each team because otherwise it's like 100 women.
dude within thirty feet thirty foot like radius. Oh my God, it's so funny.
Okay,
you're team. It's not where you see. I think it's thirteen, but it's not fair.
If it's if they all pass it, you have to make individual once for every woman.
There's like a hundred people yeah, so just average it out
for every. What are you talking about? Average it out. I just need some people
to be scared of me. There will be don't worry, okay,
okay with okay I'll say in total about two-thirds of the women here are
terrified of you.
How are the other women not terrified? I feel like I might get advantage or something.
Yeah, the fact that he's got red eyes on fire, he's completely deaf and blind.
Yeah, I'll give you advantage. Yeah, they're all terrified.
Including his own teammates.
For one minute.
Oh yeah, and for you too I guess.
Oh you're not an enemy, is it enemies or?
Each creature of your choice.
So if you don't choose him, you're not afraid of me.
Okay I choose you.
Roll a d20.
I just accept it.
I'm gonna be terrified.
I'm like so scared that I made him deaf and blind too.
Yeah so you're just this terrifying
beast on the, and you're just swinging.
Roll attack rolls. Wait, can I use... hold on, wait.
I'll tell you what you're seeing while he's... Wait, I do want to do one more thing.
Do one more thing. Can I use chill touch real quick?
Um... we're gonna enter
some kind of initiative probably soon just to... Alright, never mind. No, no, no, not for...
even just for combat. I just wanted to make sure I'm like... I just wanted to use two...
at this point... of my ghostly hands to like pull his mouth
like way wide so he's just like got his... everyone just sees his teeth.
Okay, let's have everyone roll in this you to roll initiative. Okay, me roll initiative. Yeah, I'll roll initiative for the three
teams of girls
Okay, what is that Jesus I got 11 I got an 8
Would you get you got 11? Mm-hmm, and I got an 8
Okay, I got an 8. I got an 8 Charlie Brown reference
No, I got a rock. It's not a reference to that. I got an eight. Okay, and you're going first actually Caleb
They all ruled really badly. Oh my god. I'm so awesome
No, they are bad. Um, I
Would like to what is word of radiance do I was I had that open right here - what does it do?
Yeah, that just does a lot of damage to people it does
It's everyone it's a five-foot radius around
damage to them.
Oh, okay.
I mean, yeah, you should, you should, what I will say is that like with this already is
a problem.
You should try to be wary about doing damage.
About hurting people?
Yeah.
Besides, outside of the flaming pillow.
Can I?
Cause you will just, yeah, you'll just be booted off the island, probably.
What is, okay, can I use ray?
That's obviously up to you guys.
What if I use ray of enfeeblement?
I mean that, right, so it's a debuff.
So it is a little different, but you are, at this point you will be like, there is, I will
say now that it's begun, like any spells you want to cast you would have to do like surreptitiously,
you know, because it's supposed to be a no spell.
All right, well then you know what I'll do?
I'll point, to make him even scarier, I'll point at him and like get everyone's attention
and be like everybody run for your lives. He's a crazy deaf maniac with red
abilities and a flames pillow roll persuasion because that's not even not
true at this point. It's completely true. He's a crazy deaf mania and not and
everybody's true.
I'm going to win this pillow for your
18 persuasion. Oh, wow. Yeah, I mean they were if they weren't already like
Focused on him because of all the ways that he is. How do you win the pillow fight by the way?
What are the rules here?
Do you I mean like if everybody leaves the arena?
Well, the original rule was gonna be like it's like three hits and you're out and so it's like you can deflect pillows
Nobody's getting close to him. Yeah. No, I mean this is a completely
This is why I didn't create the like create any
It's hard rules because I was like they're probably going to do some fucking so we win
by being the only people who aren't disqualified because everybody else ran out of yeah, absolutely
you can all right, so on their turn so you did that on your turn that was your action
9 that was the red team so on their turn I mean because they're terrified of you and
which actually can I can I see what was it just says there it doesn't say what they have
to do I assume they run their friends for one minute they have to move usually 30 feet
away from you. Yeah, that's what it is.
So they're all going to try to move away from you,
whichever direction that is.
So, that's not always outside the arena.
But for a lot of them it is. How big is the arena?
What? It's like a
football field. How big is that?
Like a hundred yards.
It's more like a hundred feet around.
It's more like a hundred feet around than a football field.
That's too big. It's not that big
of an arena. Okay. It's like a hundred
feet circumference or something. Okay.
A hundred feet circumference? No, not me.
Okay, okay, okay, that's fine with me.
Perfect. You said it, you said it, you said it.
That's tiny.
Let's do the math. What's the radius?
If the radius is 30 feet or less, we win.
I have to Google it.
Google it. 300 circumference.
I can't do that math in my head.
300 feet.
Sikinemephorus.
What?
- I'll let you, I don't look sometimes.
- Yup, okay.
All right.
- Circle calculator.
- All right, circumference 300.
Put it in, calculate.
- Right, it's 47.
- 47 feet.
- All right.
- So they use both their movement though,
which they all have,
if they all use both their movement, so.
- It's just slightly too big to instantly win.
- That's okay.
- So they will use their movement though to,
So I will say that like 50% of them are out.
- Oh wait, it's also, yeah,
because they move 30 feet away
and then they just can attempt another.
No, it says they attempt another saving throw.
So if they don't save, they just keep moving.
- Okay, so they move 30 feet.
So you've got like about, this is for the red team.
You got about like half of them out pretty much.
- That's our team though.
- That's right.
- Yes.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- I can't control this.
- All right, they still have disadvantage on this.
I'll say because you are actually.
- We just made you just a monster.
you just genuinely terrifying.
for like 5 minutes.
wow, yeah they failed.
so this is the red team losing.
except for you.
oh yeah, i'm also, i'm out.
i run.
because i'm also terrified.
oh wait, i got a roll of saving throw.
this assumes that he's directly in the middle of the field.
yeah, i'm also assuming that
they're afraid and they're not going to
try another action too.
like they can run and they can still be afraid
like do an attack or something or but they're not going to their constitution
saving their wisdom wisdom. Sorry. Yeah, like they're not really prepared for
this kind of moment. It's kind of creativity. Six. You are you go by
goodbye. All right, Alicia. Okay, it's my it's my turn now. Um, yeah, I was
just like swinging wildly around. Okay, you don't really hit anybody. Yeah,
that's what I was. They're all. Yeah, you're just swinging. I'm doing the
that Texas Chainsaw Dance, swinging the pillow in the air. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, no thing you don't hit anybody. Yeah, now we're going to do the this is
the yellow team. Oh, my God, please. Okay,
my God, please yep, they're gone and now the blue team.
Yeah, they're gone.
So you see, I'm still blind.
I just know he won swinging around. See the Queen bee who's been like
watching this for like Red Team wins
swinging a flaming pillow alone.
Just everybody just sits on the
all happened in the space of like six seconds. Yeah, like I walked out. I
just said a bunch of magic words and then suddenly just turned into a
monster and just everybody runs away. It's over. It's so I'm still a
for like what I think of another minute well let's just let him Tucker himself
out he'll fall asleep you've seen him do this before yeah pretty much yeah all
the time yeah he'll just he'll just calm down yeah I think probably him he got
another minute in him what's harm huh does he mean us any harm he doesn't even
know where he is he's completely blind and deaf oh poor thing just flailing
around in the middle the arena I walk out in the middle of the arena yeah so we're
- We're coming back to you now.
- We'll see this, oh no wait, no, there's something.
- Yeah, we're coming back to you.
And your mom says-- - Oh, they get hit.
(laughing)
- There's still time.
- Your mom says to you, "Let's do it again."
- Yeah, wait, you have to walk out and get hit
'cause I have a bunch of weapon buffs on.
(laughing)
- Your mom says, "Patrich, I, oh, Patrich, wait."
- I gotta do the-- - Yeah, what's going on?
- Yeah, I gotta do the voice first,
and then I gotta do an eye, yeah, that's how I get into it.
"Patrick, um, here's the thing.
Your father and...
Sticky...
Fingers..."
And then...
"Was Sticky Fingers my uncle?"
Then, uh, you watch eyes roll in the back of her head...
and she dies.
"Holy crap."
And so you're right now alone in the palace... "Holy... What just happened?
What the hell, my mom is dead?
Another incredible character.
Sorry I put this on you today.
Ah, geez.
Ah, Jesus.
What are you gonna do? What's going on?
You said, "Oh my God, my mom is dead,"
then you picked up your pencil to draw one line on your...
Ah, crap.
There's so much going on right now,
I don't even know what then even know which way to go about this.
About I can I investigate the body. Yeah, absolutely.
Real investigation.
It's a good first instinct. I crap. Let me check her out.
Best to give you a dead body.
You might look at her eyes rolled in the back of her head.
She might have seen something back there.
There might have been a brain.
She was trying to look at seven might have been something so scary.
With the 7, you're not able to like, what you're able to suss out is that there's like, there
was no like, there's no entrance exit wound.
There's no like...
Can I roll perception to like, check the room out?
Yeah, you can definitely do, you can do investigation again for the room this time.
What'd you get?
25, but it was under perception.
We'll just add whatever your investigation is instead.
Okay.
So what is that plus?
And then what was the original roll?
Well I rolled a 20
and then my perception is this. You rolled a natural 20? Yeah. So it doesn't matter, don't worry about it.
So you got a natural 20.
Uh... there's nothing in the room
that indicates it had anything to do. Great, what a fucking waste of a roll. So, um...
yeah, you can't, there's just like, you can tell very clearly, you've been in these,
you've been in situations where
you're a thief,
you're rogue, you've been in situations where people have been like, you know,
assassinated. She must have been poisoned.
There's no evidence of that.
Earlier.
Wait a minute.
I start hitting my, the gem in my chest.
My belly.
I'm trying to think.
Yeah.
I'm trying to remember.
I'm trying to see all past, present, and future.
You can just see your own past through this.
Okay.
So while you're hitting this and thinking about your mom, you do have flashes of memories
of her being here, of your father who was Trump's.
Can I go back to the minute that she died?
Can you go back?
Can you remember that exact moment?
Yes.
That's interesting. I like that. I do like a Batman Arkham Asylum. Yeah, I'm thinking
of I think what we can do with that is I think it's a good idea. I think Roll,
I guess this is really arcane. It's kind of your ability to understand the magic that's inside of
your tummy. That's an 18. Okay, so you're able to recall the moment when she died, which it's very
painful to see it, obviously. I'm remembering that and I go, holy crap. And Roll,
perception as you're in this sort of like memory state that you're in?
Another 25.
Okay.
Wow.
What's going on?
As her eyes are rolling in the back of your her head you see very faintly on her around
her like sort of clavicle a rune glow.
She also swallowed a gem.
She like has a necklace on?
No like it's like a like a rune glow from underneath her skin.
Oh, what rune is it? What does it look like?
The rune, I don't know, you would probably know this as a rune that is looking for like a kill word.
You would know this.
Murder.
Well, like it's a...
Assassinate.
No, so it's like, what I mean is that like it's a rune that activates when you say,
like within certain contexts when certain things are said.
Oh, okay.
What did you say?
No, she probably tried to say something about...
about. She said sticky fingers and then died. Your father and sticky fingers. Oh shit. Somebody.
The reveal. The reveal. The reveal was a murder. Okay. There's a reveal here. And so what would
Patrick Yodar say if he realized all this right then? Damn it. Perfect. God damn it.
Damn it to hell. This sucks. So we'll go back to the, I don't know if you're going to try
run to your friends at this point or if you're gonna like talk to the people.
Yeah, come run out into the arena and tell us.
Like a maniac.
You're not gonna stay power-dodged.
Should I invest?
Well, I know that it's a rune now, so that's like everything else is.
Yeah, I mean you could talk to someone.
So yeah, I run down to the arena as fast as I can.
That's where most of the folks are.
I mean, there's definitely guards here.
You can like let them know that this happened.
But like you can also...
Hey, I tap one of them on the shoulder.
Hi, Patrick.
My auntie, who was my mommy, there's a rune for a kill word and it was on her neck and
I said, "God damn it."
She died.
She's dead?
Yeah.
Where is she?
She's in that room.
Oh my God.
Thank you.
Can you inform the Queen?
Yeah.
yeah I was like I was gonna say like no she just died she's not the queen okay
so she she calls over one of the other guards and it says tells him to go get
like a paramedic and like the the and then like female guards and then never
thought I'd see the day world come to this so you now you've been like I you
Maybe there's long enough left if Patridge Yodar wants to run up and tap me on the shoulder to tell me any news.
In one minute. He's not going to be here in a minute.
I jump off the stairs very, from a very high.
I need to hit one person.
Okay.
Steevel, that's on you.
What do you mean that's on me? I'm terrified still.
Well, that's what I mean. You can enable him to hit one person.
Does the Queen maybe walk up to me and try to hand me a trophy?
We're in an initiative right now. So it's a minute left. So you have basically
Like nine more tries to not be afraid and then try to get someone to hit him him for him to hit
All right, cuz you I'm gonna try you are well, I mean you can try to get somebody to hit you
Yeah, just start running straight. I
Will people just move aside? Oh, I'll roll a wisdom save and see if I'm still terrified
hmm
16. Okay. You're not yeah, not terrified anymore. Oh, come on
I'm gonna see what's going on with it. Just walk directly towards him
Listen dog it just stop just be you it's over you won you won. Okay. Yeah, and also
So while you can't hear him and as you've been raging and it's been like a lot of fun
You also hear hasn't been fun
Program my brain to sin you also hear a
Coughing sound I hear it how oh in your mind whoa and you hear a woman's voice
Ooh-la-la and you hear you hear her say
I
Know a dirt man when I see one
Instinctively, I don't like that. I instantly swing my weapon. Yeah, evil standing right in front of me. I'm standing directly in front
I'm gonna roll an attack roll here, and I get to add a d4 okay
I rolled a 14, but I get to add a d4 from bless think your AC is not is not even oh yeah
I think you might have higher AC when I remember my AC is 15
plus two, so it's a sixteen. Yeah, it hits you. Roll for damage. Okay, I have
to roll for damage and then I also have to add some stuff to that. Okay, that's
six damage plus hold on. I have to see how much damage
searing smite. That's
this is fun. I forgot to have the game log. I'm at seventeen HP right now. I
think I'm going to kill you. Oh. It deals an extra 1d6 damage and causes you to ignite
in flames. Don't worry guys, I'm going to calm him down. Wait, wait, wait, what level did
you cast searing smite at? Just one. Cast it at the maximum level. I couldn't, I didn't
have enough slots I don't think. I'm on stevel right now, sorry. It's plus 5, I don't remember
remember what number I said before plus
five
what I said I don't want I was looking at
your
oh yeah. No, you only have first level
here. We go right because you're
pounding okay is six it's eleven damage
and he catches on fire. Okay, yeah, so
it's really see what I have six HP. What
is catching on fire do at the start of
each of its turns until the spell ends
you must make a constitution saving
throw. If you fail you take another one
six damage. Yeah. So, yeah, you just got hit in the face. You hear the whole crowd go,
"Gasp!" And then like you're getting up and saying, "Don't worry." Yeah, yeah. "Don't
worry." "I'm still, I'm on fire." Yeah. "Nobody just, he's completely harmless."
All right, roll, roll. It's, I mean, we're back to the top of the order. So you roll again a,
a, a, a, roll a constitution saving throw. Constitution saving throw? Yeah. Three.
five. You take another one, do six damage. And you have six health, so if he gets max.
Let's see here. Rolling. It's a four. It landed on six and then tipped over.
Oh, the fire gets like one fire length higher on my body. You start to see where it used to
just be orange and red. There's a yellow layer in there too now. Patrick, you're showing up as
as we're looping around the order.
- I look at everything that's happening and say,
what the hell?
- Yeah, and then roll one more save.
- This is basically 2020 in a nutshell.
- This is the only time that create or destroy water
will actually be useful.
- I forget that I'm so focused on calming everybody down,
I completely forget I have it.
I got a 17.
- Okay, you passed.
- All right, cool.
- Okay, the fire goes away.
See what I mean, folks?
I mean, he's completely on.
- I'm just like, how can I swing again?
I'm right in front of you, looking away from you towards the crowd.
He's completely, he's entirely harmless.
This attack doesn't have fire, but it's a dirty 20 plus 4.
Yeah, he's dead.
So yeah, he's like, "Don't worry, he's good, but I'm dead."
Like just knocked out from a pillow.
Yeah.
And Patrick shows up.
11 damage.
Yeah.
And then it shows up and what do you say?
You say, "Goddamn, this is 2020."
This is 2020 in a nutshell.
Damn this bullcrap.
My blindness and deafness ends and I'm like, "Oh my God, who killed Stiebel?
There's going to be hell to pay when I find out who did this."
Are you still have fire eyes and stuff?
I still have the fire eyes, but that's it.
As you say this-
Everything else ended.
You also cough up a bit of sand into your hand.
Uh oh.
And Queen Bee goes to you, Patrick, and says, "Patrick, I'm so glad you can join."
I had to tell you something, but I've--no, I remember.
My mom is dead.
Oh?
And so we'll take--
And it was a rune killing.
And so yeah.
it was a rune and it said glyphberg on it
now what?
evil stevel is going to end up in the infirmary slash hot springs
whoa
you two, all part of my plan
what prize do i get also?
i won the pillow fight
uh...
yeah you get to uh...
get like a chicken, i don't know, there was no prize, it was just fun
It was just fun. I did all that and there was no prize?
No, it was just a fun tournament.
It's Hot Babe Island, they have everything they want and need.
Ahhhh.
I'm sorry.
[Heavy breathing]
Oh, he's getting my head.
You two are back at the palace as the Queen Bee is examining your mom's body.
And uh...
Doesn't that look like crap?
[Laughter]
It looked like total bullcrap. Yeah, I agree. Yeah. It was a power word. Yeah, the word was
Glyfberg. Glyfberg? Ruin Glyfberg. What could that have meant? I'm so sorry that this has
befallen you in your visit here. Yeah, I mean, she has no reason to distrust you. I'm so
sorry that this has happened while you were here. Things like this never happen on Hot
Bay by than usually. Yeah I bet they don't. They don't? Yeah I bet they don't.
What's up? I'm just agreeing with you. I don't know what you're... No it just seems
like you're insinuating that they happen here. Nah. I'm just I'm just sorry I'm
pissed off cuz my mom just died in front of me. Of course your mom just passed of course.
look I don't know what we can do for you we can give her a proper burial but
something we set her on fire um would that be what she would have wanted I
think that's a ritual right you set her on fire in the ocean oh yeah I heard
about that that's what you're doing what do we put her in the hot spring and she
comes back to life I don't think that's on top of my body what about we bring
her back to life. Like Frankenstein. Please. Well, I don't think there's really any way
to bring her back alive. She's passed. We live in a fantasy world where there's literally
necromancy. Well, if you want to dabble in necromancy, you're welcome to. Get me alive
right now. I don't, but you just said there's no way. Make me alive right now, guys. Is
there a necromancer on the island? Not on our island. Like a female necromancer? Well,
the only person on the island. Who wears like a skull bra. I'd like for some of these females
Romance my neck. Oh, I'm playing. Oh, the only person on the island who would know about this would be Albert
Albert the witch
Albert she lives in a cove. There's a woman named Albert it happens. All right
Okay, you could go see her. I I
Don't advise going for neck. What about like a rune expert?
Well again Albert would be the one who has any real knowledge of this.
So we have to go see Albert, huh?
Well if you want to know more about this particular instance, I suppose, but...
*sigh*
What do you guys want to do?
Let's go to Albert.
You certainly don't have to. She might not be able to help you at all.
Then why did you say that?
I mean that's an option.
I'm sorry for snapping, I'm just pissed off because I'm looking at my mom's dead body.
No, I understand. I was being pretty immature earlier and I'm trying to reel it back now.
I also just quit drinking Diet Coke.
coke oh that's tough you see all the girls in the hey I'm nodding Steve oh so
you're in the hot springs you start to come to and you see to plan beautiful
nurse baby I just got it I come to and then I have two cums yes when I see
these bitches yeah and there are taking care of you in the hot springs what does
that fucking mean it means they're spell it out for me just don't men's work
tending to which wound I'll be tended to the wound in my hair that's right I'm
attending to her wound that's a nice thing to call that yeah attending to her
incision slot oh my god to the like third-degree burn let me see that grievous
bodily harm baby. I think that I am fully convinced whether it's because I just I'm
so delirious from whatever they've been giving me or because I've never really
had real sex I'm completely convinced that I'm fucking these women. Like them
touching my skin is like intimate contact and I'm just like looking
directly at them but I can't smile or really move my eyes at all because
the burns hurt so bad. Glad to see you come to Steve.
If any woman would be so lucky to see that
she said she goes to get you some more like some herb. She's putting in a like
a more pestle and putting in a fucking thing and like rubbing it ointment on
your on your body and she's like we hope that you wait on my body. Oh,
Oh, yeah, that's where you're hurt or oh my God, dude. I want to be glue in her
gloober show with my gloop, so she's rubbing ointment on my body. So what's
happening besides
she says trampoline. She just ask you questions. Where were you from?
Oh, you can't speak right now. I
- We'll get you up and out of here soon.
- That's what your doctor said.
- Get over here, don't crawl in the bed with me.
- Oh, that's funny.
You're, oh you, she's like just laughing.
- What's funny?
Bitch, I will fucking kill you.
(laughing)
I will fucking kill you.
- He's going under a lot of stress.
- Suck my dick or you'll die.
(laughing)
- It's like Michael Scott.
- Um, here, wait, hold on.
I would like to cast ray of sickness on this woman.
So that would require you to be able to like, there are like...
I'm creating, wait, never mind, I'm creating water in her pants.
Whoa.
Genius.
Next level.
Yeah.
It does...
Next fucking level.
It does require some, so it's not just, it also requires somatic.
So you do, I usually don't, what I usually do is say, don't worry about material components
because that's very frustrating. But somatic means you do have to like sort of
move your hands a little bit. If you can try to move your like finger. I try,
okay, I try to roll a... My spells are broken also. But just constitution really to see
if you can get through the pain of moving your burned flesh around. Okay.
Is his penis burnt too?
A little bit.
[Groaning]
I'm like having to
answer that question.
Nothing is working on my app today.
Just roll a d20 and just add your con.
Add your head is what?
What?
Did you say add your cunt?
18.
Got an 18.
You can move your finger a little bit.
Create just a little bit of water.
Yeah, I mean she's like oh, oh, yeah, it's embarrassing. Yeah
That's like I got cheap peed
It's not me. You see peed. Okay fun is people made her do it. Yeah, I made her
So embarrassing
It's me you see you walk in and she like sort of like recoils from you Fred first cuz she remembers you being a demon
And then she's like sort of embarrassed that she like sort of walks away and like I bite her hair
My kind of near my face I reach over take a big bite
I'm shaking your head around and then I come and I fall asleep.
I
Trick her into thinking she peed you come in she recoils backs up into my mouth
Out come in my pants and falls
Oh, you see it looks like he's not feeling so well you need to take better care of you just threw up from the front
different. We're going to just fast forward to you guys in the palace, I
guess, or in the yeah, let's do that yeah yeah and you're you're you're
healed more or less yeah. So bits of hair in your mouth yeah like a long
this is coming out of my mouth. Love your beard. Thank you. I got
highlights. You got some new colors in there yeah mostly some blonde pieces
real straight hair. I see some green there yeah some green and white globs.
I don't think I see the... no I don't think. No, it's clearly it's right there.
Yeah, I mean, it's at the bottom. Listen, obviously you two have never been in the
hospital, but it's basically the craziest sex party in the world. So, yeah. Oh, that's
a sex glob? Yeah, it could be. And it's green. Probably a girl's sex glob though,
and not my own. Nope. I love making sex globs with girls. Oh my god.
exchanging sex clubs with each other. Check this out. I give him a piece of the hair for my teeth.
It's so, you guys are like standing in front of the queen and just like having this
talk and then she says, so you have a cough.
Covid has come to Tribute Village.
That's the big reveal.
Holy crap, that's what the rune said.
Oh my god, they weren't runes, they were Chinese characters!
[Laughter]
She says, um,
"I don't know what the meaning of the rune is just yet, but
I suggest you either go see Albert the Witch,
or you continue the sail on your way and try to seek out
What was the last thing your mother said?
Glyphon... Glyphon?
No, the rune said "Glyfberg".
But you said it was a power word though, right?
She said "stick"... wait, I'm not saying it.
Well, if you don't have the rune on you, there shouldn't be any issue.
How did she know she had the rune? It's better safe than sorry, right?
Yeah, I think you should say it.
Yeah, why don't you just say it.
I don't know it. Could you write it down?
Okay, so it was...
Use your coloring pad.
She said y-o-u-r-f-a-t-h-e-r-a-n-d-s-t-i-c-k-y-f-i-n-g-e-r-s.
He dies. He drops dead.
No, no, no, he doesn't.
Your father and...
Sticky Fingers.
You have to have the rune on you.
Why do you guys think anyone just...
You guys said Sticky Fingers a lot in the last campaign.
You guys think just people...
Well, we don't know. The thing is we don't know...
I assume that the mom didn't know she had a rune on her or else she wouldn't have said it.
Oh yeah, you guys were, you all have a rune on you, then you're saying.
Okay, I get it.
Yeah, well you have no idea, we have no idea.
Why would we know if we had one?
Whoever put it on would not tell us.
Alright, we need to test-
If somebody says something and then dies, I wouldn't say that thing.
Alright guys, we need to test to see if we have the rune so everybody needs to say it.
Okay.
One.
Stinky fingers.
You say stinky-
Stimpy dinger.
What?
Did I say- no, we all checked, we don't have the rune.
Simple thinker.
Sticky binger.
St-
- Dippid lingers. - Sticky winger.
- Sipping liquor. - I think we're probably better off not--
- Prickly pringer. - Risking this.
- Risking... - Pricky ringer.
I'm a risky ringer, okay?
- So I do stuff like that. - Chrissy Teagern.
Yeah, you prissy queener.
- So she had said your father-- - You're a bitchy wiener.
Before she hadn't said...
- Yeah. - Sticky fingers.
Well...
Does that mean that Sticky Fingers put a rune on my mom?
I don't know what it means. I will say that I remember Sticky Fingers. He was a
part of your father's crew before he was the famous Sticky Fingers.
Yeah. I don't think he was part of this this
group. There were there was like 60 tricksters.
Or 50 tricksters.
(laughing)
- Am I missing this?
What am I missing here?
- Or 60 fifters.
(laughing)
- But there was, but he has 60 fingers, right?
- Yeah, yeah, it was, his name was,
he was in a group of 60 trickters.
- I don't feel like I gave you guys a word game this time,
but you still found one, I feel like.
- That's all we do.
- I'm gonna pick up a lollipop and say,
should I lick these fingers?
- Yeah, there he is.
a lily pipper yeah they were called the 60 tricksters and they all ate chicky
tinders what was and it was a co-ed group they were mixing genders what was
trudge bowls crews name wasn't it the did we ever decide that no sticky fingers
was part of like the Brave Lions. It was the 60 tricksters who had
chicky tenders. This could be what it's called. The 60 tricksters was
with 60 fingers doing their tricksters. They ate chicky tenders and they were mixing
genders on the boat named... El Capitan. El Captain Royale. Bryan Singers.
they can't do that the boat was called the SS Brian so the boat was the boat was
you guys did call the boat um with stinky swingers the Caribbean Royale or
the Royal Caribbean is the boat that he had all the El Capitan yeah and the
Stinky Fingers was just a part of a thieving guild he wasn't like a line
with the Brave Lions. He was a scaredy cat insofar as he was a gnome, but he wasn't like
a lion with the Brave Lions. He was just a member of the Thieves Guild, or like the leader
of the Thieves Guild by the time you guys were in Trebuchet Village. Since Trebuchet Village
has undergone a bunch of stuff, you guys knew that Sticky Fingers got more recognition from
the king, was promoted to some undisclosed position. And that's all you really know about.
Like, you guys probably haven't kept up with him since then. It's only been six months,
too since that happened. So that's about what you know about him. But he was part of the
60... let's get it down.
60 tricksters.
60 tricksters eating chicky tinders.
With their 50 fingers.
And they're mixing genders.
60 tricksters.
120 fingers.
60 tricksters eating chicky...
Tinders.
And they're mixing genders.
And they're...
Yeah, of course.
And they're mixing genders.
And I like...
With their 120 fingers.
Queen, I like your prickly stinger.
With their 120...
Thank you.
With their 120 fingers.
I think it might make a nifty dinner.
And then I bite it.
Ew, who's...
Wait, so who's been ripping stinkers?
Do they only have two fingers each or is it...
- No, every single one of them has 50 fingers.
- Who's been ripping sneakers, that's the big ass singer.
- Big ass?
- Big ass.
- Biggest singer.
- Biggest, bigly singer.
- Bigly singer.
The big league singer.
- The singing singer.
- Yeah.
- Yep.
- So we basically did our thing.
- The S-T-E-C-T-A-T-M-G-W-T-1-20-F.
(laughing)
Of course.
[laughter]
That's some kind of acronym?
Yeah, it means the 60 tricksters eating chicky tenders and they're mixing genders with their 120 fingers.
[laughter]
Okay.
They were your father's adventuring party, yes, and well, I don't know why sticky fingers, if he had done that,
but I don't know why that would be a power word unless someone's either after sticky fingers or he did that. I don't know.
Well that's that's why we got to go see Albert.
She could potentially help.
Yeah I guess we gotta go do that.
Yeah let's do that.
She lives in a cove.
Do you mean a cave?
No.
I wouldn't go if it's a cave but if it's a cove I'll go.
Yeah it's a cove.
Are you sure you don't mean a cave? What's a cove?
It's like a cave.
I think it's called a cave.
It's a cave with an o.
Are you talking about love like I love you?
I cove you.
I cove it you're wife.
Cove it?
Cove it.
My god, it really is happening. Oh god. We sail to Wuhan
We get it there
He's done
Tell the wrong one.
Uh...
Fuck yeah.
[Music]