[Music]
Last time on Trebuchet Village.
The gang left the town of Idiot Village to find the village idiot that lives in a cave who could save the town from its own rampant stupidity.
They ran into a merchant on the way, Larry the Planeswalker,
who liked getting roasted to the point where he wanted people to touch his penis,
which was off-putting.
His bodyguard, a pleasure man, approached Evil Stievel,
but Evil denied his involvement in what happened at Mount Honestoodle, confusing the pleasure man.
When they reached the cave, they met the wizard Why Me, aka the village idiot, a towerless wizard who whines about how
everything that happens to him is someone else's fault.
Why me, oh why me?
As they listen to Why Me's woes, and Why Me reveals to Dogen that the Dirt God doesn't
even need dirt to commune with him, the wizard told our heroes of the threat of an orc brigade
that collects taxes on the plains, and how idiot Volage will not be able to pay it.
The boys convinced Why Me to return to the town and declare himself the mayor, save it
by escorting the villagers to his cave and maybe make something of himself instead of
deflecting.
Our heroes escorted the townsfolk to the cave, only a quarter of whom vanished from being
too stupid to walk over the short journey.
Once they arrived at the cave, knowing that they were unable to pay, Thorax and his orc
group arrived to either make the village citizens into slaves or make them into food, whatever
worked.
However, Thorax took a liking to our three heroes, because of their beef with the brave
lions.
the resistance group who wishes to liberate all the terrifier kingdom from the grips of
king nardwuar and all the terrifier born.
patritch, dogan, and evil pitched a solution to the problem.
make a theme park called idiot land stupidville which would be the first amusement park in
the land and make the denizens of idiot village work there as walk around characters because
they will just think it's their life anyway.
Dude, I'm like so smart.
I did not remember that that was the plan.
That's a really good plan.
It's a good plan.
Yeah, that's like smart.
If I had tried to think of a plan for the amusement park right now, I would not have
come up with one as good as us three weeks ago.
It was all me, dude.
The walk around characters.
Thorax was enthralled with the idea, and our heroes set out on a journey to the city of
Gal Gadot, the orc capital of the Terrifier Kingdom, and the cruellest place in the land,
all with the intent of pitching this idea to investors in the city.
With Thorax and their group, however, the passage was remarkably easy, but what comes
next will be much harder.
So you're all standing in the barracks of the arena, where you see nervous young entrepreneurs
just like yourselves milling about and pacing around practicing their pitches
on dummies and trying out different weapons on those same dummies the arena
is called the get some dome and it is the largest combat / business arena in all
the land. Like much of Gal Gadot, it is made of the skeletal remains of Kaiju who
came before. The bone of this beast was so tough, Cameron's
sorry-facing, that not much could be done to change its shape, even with the most
powerful magics. And so you are more or less in a pelvis with some stone
interspersed to make it a bit more arena-like. - Godzilla. - Thorax and
fuck you who's now why me is now called
fuck you who's you guys sort of told me
should call him so yeah I remember that
yeah yeah yeah are having a tense
conversation about ROI and different BC's
are catering as well the concerns about
the current supply chain of the fabrics
and vendors who won't return with the
signed SOW because as always everything
gets stuck in legal right so you three
though you're the pitchman you're the
idea guys okay you stand to make a tidy
Not ideas guys, but idea guys.
I said idea guys.
You guys stand to make a tidy profit from this if all goes well.
A consistent revenue stream.
And with one of the Ork 5 by your side in this Ork tank.
They're going to open some doors for you guys.
Okay?
So, before we get into it, we're going to do a level up.
And then we're gonna do five minutes of real-time discussion about your pitch
Okay, okay, so first though. We're gonna level up. Okay. Keep the tension keep the tension up
So you guys are leveling up your level three very exciting for some classes less exciting for other classes nothing for me
Yes clerics clerics get a lot of their exciting stuff early on yeah, you can definitely go go to the bathroom
You can jerk off you everyone
So but it's true. Oh, yeah, we're all we're doing this in person
This is presumably if all goes according to plan and nobody dies here in this wonderful city
We'll be trying to do this in person for the foreseeable future. It's a better time
Yeah, so I've decided to move
So um but you two paladins and thieves
Rogues rather you guys have level three is pretty big for you guys. You're kind of oh, yeah classes here. It's pretty big
Patrick you are picking your your roguish archetype mm-hmm, so you have a number of things to choose from inquisitive
You pick inquisitive, so that's interesting because we were talking about this leading up to this
You were saying you're gonna pick just the vanilla sort of thief
uh... i've got what's right through inquisitive and it is me
reader
here for deceit which is a when you choose is our good site
you develop a talent for picking out lies and i'm sick of being betrayed in my
life
okay
uh... that's a good move then
and uh... i for detail
uh... starting at level three you can use a bonus action to make a wisdom check to
spot a hidden creature objects to make an intelligence check
to uncover or decipher clues
which is probably gonna
be pretty good for the foreseeable future. Insightful fighting
uh...
Ooh, this one's cool. I do know this one. Go, go, go. You gain the ability to decipher
an opponent's tactics and develop a counter to them.
As a bonus action you can make a wisdom check against a creature
you can see that isn't incapacitated, contested by the target's charisma check
which I mean my charisma is like the highest stat. It's gonna be your wisdom
in their charisma.
Oh, okay.
But it's still very good.
Keep going.
Okay.
Yeah, it's very good though.
If you succeed you can use your sneak attack against that
target if you don't have advantage on the attack roll, but
not if you have disadvantage on it.
This benefit lasts for a minute or until you successfully
use this feature against a different target.
Yeah, it's basically like you can you have the potential
of like getting additional sneak attack options.
So yeah, I mean if I were if I were trying to optimize your
build I'd say next level pick something that can boost your
wisdom because a sneak attack is rogues best friend their big DPS because of
that I'm interested in I want to do a little a little a little like a
character thing I don't know like because like different like classes have
like oh you pick this archetype and this journey for this character is such that
like when they pick a Bard college for example or they pick a discipline and
um that's in New York domain I want to know what was what was the I don't know
what the rogue is I don't know what the flavor around that is but what makes you
Patrick Jodar gravitate towards this more you said betrayal is that sort of
the that was the impetus for it? That was my real life. What's Patrick Jodar?
that's just a real-life thing but um you think this fits into his character? Do I have to say this in character?
uh you don't have to I would say like yes okay all right yes is this we have
What is it?
- Yeah, my uncle Trunchbull,
he was good at telling when people were lying.
So I just wanna do that.
- Amazing.
- Told me to say it in character, I don't know.
I just think it's probably easier,
'cause I mean, it could probably help,
I mean, in the Shark Tank segment,
I can tell when somebody's lying.
- Right. - Yes.
- I can detect a lie. - That's a huge part
of Shark Tank.
(laughter)
- They lie constantly.
- I hate when they say,
when they say, "Okay, I'm making you an offer
"$75,000 for 20%," and I find out that all along
they were only gonna give me $75 for 100%.
- Yeah.
- Or they just say, "I don't have any money."
- And if only I had been inquisitive,
then I would have been able to tell.
- I think this is great.
I think this is like Patrick Jodar,
but it's a little bit more on the crafty side,
'cause you're a big shoplifter.
- Yeah.
- But in this case, you're sort of a,
what if the shoplifter thought a little bit bigger picture?
I like this. What if you can make people shoplift for you?
What if you stole the whole shop?
Yeah, right. Right from under them. I like this.
Um, that's good.
So do I just hit next?
Yeah, yeah. Just fill in the rest of the stuff. I'll help you with that.
As necessary.
Are you freaking out?
Hit next again?
Let me see.
Yeah, I couldn't figure it out either.
Oh my god, great catch, Pat. It only spilled it on my bag, which is good.
Guys, if I have one Capri Sun, I'm sloshed.
Let me tell you.
Okay.
Let me see.
Yeah, how hard did the...
Arizona makes a new hard seltzer.
Yeah, they're pretty good, dude.
You should try it.
Not bad.
Oh, yeah.
Shit, brother, you gotta pick...
Yeah, it just tastes like the mucho mango.
Jesus Christ.
Wait, bro, you gotta pick another...
Damn it, I gotta look at your character sheet more often.
You get to pick another skill proficiency.
Oh, what?
Yeah, you should pick another skill proficiency.
Oh, I'm gonna pick...
I'm gonna pick...
Yeah, you should do that. What do I do? Pick whatever you want man. Pick whatever is good for your character. Skill?
So, oh then fuck it wisdom. Oh, I can't do that. Yeah, wisdom's a stats
You can pick stuff that like would make so perception is like a classic like so what about it says
Okay, so I have I can choose acrobatics animal handing arcana athletics
History insight intimidation. Oh, I'm doing intimidation. Oh
That's cool, and your charisma, and you're kind of like a freaky guy who like says kill stuff sometimes
Yeah, be a fun way to actually work in sure yeah
so
Panning panning over to my my right yeah, Dogen dirt gobbler. We get to pick another
Yeah, I got you level three level three for you is
You get to pick your um your oath
Paladins hat make it. Oh yeah. Oh yeah, I've got yeah
I reach into my pocket and I pull out a handful of dirt and I put it into my mouth and I say
Hello, I'm communing with dog in the dirt God
What's up, I knew I fucking knew it this isn't dirt this is crushed up Oreos
Shit, I thought I never had to put dirt in my mouth the whole fucking time
Yeah, you were making me fucking eat dirt for no fucking reason
I like dirt, but I don't like fucking eating it. It makes me sick
It was just kind of throw up like every fucking night. Okay, my shit. It's like soft and hard at the same time
It's like wet sand
It's like moon sand like moon's in
I just found out that we live in a medieval world. There's no such thing as urinals. So people just piss in the dirt
Yeah, well, you know it was okay. I'm sorry
I'm sorry. I'll admit I make my you know disciples eat dirt cuz it's kind of funny
You know what? I don't even want to hear it. No Dogen from now on. I'm Dogen the Oreos
He's just yeah gone. I'm an oathbreaker. I broke my palate and oath so now I turned evil
Are you doing the sweet goblin or dogan the Oreo Oreos?
So we'll also need pitch Oreos
Because yeah, there are now a thing called Oreos. I'll figure that out later
Well, I invented them you did. Oh, that's the part of the
So Oreo
Oreos.
Fuck my ass.
Hey Cameron, tell me about Oreos.
Cam, I don't know what you know about the Oathbreaker.
I can obviously chime in there.
Yeah, well what I saw that I'm very excited about is that I gained the ability to control
undead.
That is correct.
You guys are going to have a lot of synergy.
Really?
Yeah, so I can control it.
You have that as well in the death domain, so there's sort of a lot of overlap of just
darkness between you two.
You have more magical abilities over that, okay?
Ha ha.
Okay.
Yeah, I also, I basically just start turn, I also, I get Hellish Rebuke and Inflict Wounds
and Dreadful Aspect.
Yes.
Hellish Rebuke's really cool.
Basically if somebody hits you, you can, as a reaction, do I think 2d10 fire damage to
them?
I mean, you know, you have the roll and stuff, but it's pretty cool.
It's basically you become a really petty, dark person.
pretty badass and usually it's to pursue some dark ambition according to the
flavor text your dark ambition is basically is I guess sweets Oreos in
particular. If you see candy you can't. Yeah I can't control myself. Yeah the coolest part is that
you're a fang. Your 20th level is called like the dread Lord is like what you
know if you like don't multi-class you go all the way to 20th level for
Oathbreaker you become a dread Lord. That's sick. Which is tight. I'm gonna do
that. Yeah, it's a pretty big deal. Dogen is now gone, at least for the moment. Yeah, and
then you, Evil Stevel, I think you probably just got a few more spells right now. You
get more stuff later on, like you kind of have more of an eventful level 4 like everybody
else does, but you're kind of on the steady path where you're just getting more shit for
for your butt. - I get it, man.
You don't have to, I get it, I suck.
- I know, that's not what I'm saying.
- This is like in middle school
when all the girls get taller than you.
- Well, it is like that,
but that's neither here nor there.
- That never happened to me.
- Oh, shut up.
- Shut up, dude. - Shut up, tall guy.
- You, you get it, you're tall like a girl.
(laughing)
Cool, so, okay, cool, that was exciting.
I love when my friends level up.
Let's get back to the notes.
Here and out.
(laughing)
Sorry.
You guys are a little, yeah.
You guys are so much more powerful than me now.
You're all level three, so you're all--
You're just at a different stage in life.
I look at you guys, I'm like,
hey, you guys still like playing, right?
You still wanna play?
Yeah, I'm actually playing math right now.
Yeah, we're more interested in business.
You know, we're about to go on Orc Tank, so.
Not really a lot of time for playing.
That's all right, yeah.
- Yeah.
- You have it like you're playing to get money.
- Okay, yeah, I mean, I didn't, you know,
I don't really like playing anymore either, so that's fine.
I'm like, I don't like playing pretend anymore,
so like we're all at the same level now.
- Yeah, it's not pretend.
- Okay, yeah, no, I'm getting it, all right.
- Yeah, it's real, it's for real.
- Hey, Patrick, do you wanna go to the cinema later?
- Yeah, I'd love to go to the cinema.
After that, we can go to a bistro.
- Oh my God, that would be divine.
Hey, do you guys want, after all that shit,
do you wanna go to like the arcade or something?
Maybe play perhaps the casino.
Yeah the casino or the barcade.
I'll go to the arcade with you, Evil, if you want to go to the arcade.
Yeah, you can hang out with Sullivan here.
Sullivan, seriously? He's like 8 years old.
You can hang out with him. He likes the arcade.
Yeah, he's level 3.
I am a level 3 bard.
If that means nothing. I get to pick my bard college, actually.
Alright, I'm actually... Oh, you're going to college?
College is crazy.
goes there. Sorry, my friend Walker goes there. And I'm gonna pick the college of...
Wow, I didn't... I forgot all the Bard class stuff's really cool, but I guess...
Well, there's one that I want to do as a player, but there's one that Sullivan
must pick which is the College of Glamour. Are you becoming a beautician?
I've been carrying this pamphlet around with me it's a this is a DeVry
University. Yeah Sullivan's becoming a nail tech.
beautiful it doesn't it doesn't work out uh you know it's gonna do I'm gonna
choose yeah and if you if you flunk out of being a nail tech you can always be a
nurse so don't worry so yeah the college of colors is is very cool it's just the
name is perfect for Sullivan that's it's a very what does it do it's based in
like fey magic so it's all about like guys and like yeah you guys can't see
what's going on over here I'm getting ribbed but uh yeah it's based in fey
magic the ability to like cast a certain like disguise spells that will if I
remember exactly I want to make sure I'm getting this right right yeah and
thralling performance once before it rest you could use one creature that
watched and listens you perform for one minute. Each target makes a wisdom saving
throw and is charmed if it fails for one hour. So basically you can do some little
silly dance and then people will be charmed for one hour if they fail.
Didn't he already have that ability? Uh, no. Oh wait, was that Gun City? Yeah, no it was somebody else.
It was Colin. Colin the pig had that. Colin the pig had that. Yeah he started, he has echoes of
Colin. Yeah, the only good character anyone's ever played in this show.
guys, guys, Colin. Um, but yeah, whatever. I mean, you don't need
to worry too much about Sullivan. That's my job. So I
definitely will not. You guys so yeah, you're in the arena, like
in the sort of barracks kind of like area you see like other
entrepreneurs like practicing, like I said, practicing their
pitches, like also fighting for some reason, it seems like I'm
going to give you guys. So I mean, here's the thing, before I
even give you guys a five minutes real time, which I'm
I'm going to have a timer and everything for it.
If you guys want to chat with, you know,
a Thorax or WhyMe about like ideas and stuff,
you can do that.
- I would like to talk to the other entrepreneurs
about their ideas.
- Yeah, for sure.
You can go talk to them.
- Yeah, like who's around?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, sure.
- Can we each go to a different person?
- What?
- Can we each go to a different person
and then come back?
- Yeah, sure.
- Guys, Patches, don't listen to this.
We're going to steal their ideas.
- Oh yeah, we absolutely are.
- Okay.
- Cool.
- That's what I was going to do.
- All right, sure.
whoever you want to go to you see a a giant bone snake that's wearing a little
tie you have a couple of goblin brothers I'm gonna go to the goblins okay and
then you see a humanoid who looks bright and shiny and I go to the bright shiny
guy and Patrick has to go to the bone snake I was gonna go to the bone snake
anyway all right well you wanna wonder how do you want to play this out gang
Okay, okay, I'm gonna go talk to that bone snake. Okay. See you later. All right first. I'll talk to these goblin brother
Okay, cool, but first
I'm a talk to this guy who I think is me cuz I see my reflection in his skin. Yeah
Okay
Hello, beautiful. Okay, cool. So you go over you see this a bright and shiny looking human guy
He turns to you and he's like hi there
My name's if never mind
I'm Garth C. Enterprise, oh well.
Well at least I got that reference in there.
He goes back to doing whatever it is he's doing.
You guys want to talk to the bone snake?
You want to talk to the-
Can you go back and talk to Garth C. Enterprise?
Fuck no man.
We'll go over and talk to him later.
Yeah okay cool.
Do you want to hang out with him?
I'm talking to the bone snake now.
Hey.
Hey guys.
Can you keep it down over there? I'm talking to the bones
Go ahead talk to the bone snake
Sorry about that, okay
Hey guys, I wanted to talk to you about your idea see your goblin brothers right here
So and I'm a goblin too, so I wanted to talk to you about your idea. We can just do it overlapping
Okay, okay
Oh hi! Hi, I'm- I'm Tit. I'm for Tat.
We're the Goblin Brothers!
Wait, hold on. He sounds-
What does he sound like? What did I fuck up?
He sounds too much like a-
Fuck, I lost my voice.
He sounds too much like a guy in our party.
What? Oh, the kid! Right?
Not that one. The other one.
I'm for- Oh shit.
hold on hold on come on I'll do a nerd thing hi I'm for tap or tip for tat
what's up and we're here nice to meet you you're another goblin what do you
bring to the table are you inventing well I we're inventing a certain type of
of area that it's under patent pending so I can't reveal too many details.
I understand I mean you're about to go in front of the whole city but I totally
get it man no worries. It's well I mean if I told you you'd steal it so what's
your idea? Okay that's interesting. What? You think I'm gonna tell you you're not
gonna tell me your idea? Okay what if we both write it down? Okay let's both say
at the same time. Okay. One, two, three, a sponge that can dance. Fuck! I just immediately leave.
Don't say anything else. I just wink and walk away. I told you not to say anything! Hey
why don't we just... So meanwhile, yeah, you're... This bone stake meanwhile has just been slowly
coiling itself around you this is a this is not what I wanted to happen
you here to pitch a thing are you here if I'm gonna shake his head very slowly
you're not you're not here to pitch anything you're just a you're just here
if our idea is bad huh? Patrick what are you- there's a wild bone snake what are you doing
so close to that thing? Get that thing- we gotta get that uh sag to try to trap him or something.
What are you doing man? You see- yeah she bats her eyelashes. Yeah she is. Yeah. Talking about a
shre- talking about a donkey dragon situation over here. What are you doing after this?
boats it goes oh whatever are you doing talk okay all you can say is whatever
actually I have to go right now but uh you are seriously bombing with that hot
snake shut your mouth and leave yeah I gotta go yeah crap I walk up I push
Petra's out of the way oh hello bone snake Howard how have you
been on this lovely evening only his eyes for Patrick oh look at me baby you said
I was blown it you do it you do if you want to do a person like a charisma like
just do a rocker is my check my persuasion persuasion if I can't seduce a
snake brother brother brother brother I got you oh shit physical last nice all
Alright, which...
He's...
That's a 19.
OOOOP!
Okay, plus your charisma, which is...
Let me see, hold on.
I'm trying to do a drum roll, but I can only really tap with one hand.
Yeah, I...
Just hit the mic as hard as you can.
Charisma? Zero.
Zero? Really? You have a zero charisma?
Get the fuck out of here.
Plus your wisdom class. Um...
19 is still fantastic. Yeah, that's a good roll.
She sort of like shimmies a little bit back and forth, you hear her bones rattling a little bit.
And she writes down a few slashes on the ground that might be her number.
Ah, alright I'll call you on...
Wait, ain't no phones here, this is a fake number!
She's like, "Uhhhh, Uhhhh."
Thank you, thank you Janice.
Alright, I'm out.
I leave.
yeah so you got the sponge you can damn a dancing sponge some class and a bone
system classic off the dome shit for me even talk to Garth C enterprise it's
gonna like what am I gonna learn I wanted to fuck a snake what what we
should have done is incorporated both of their ideas don't worry we don't worry
we the dancing the dancing sponge the dancing sponge is a backup idea if they
don't go for the amusement park. We can be like, we can say...
I'm saying the dancing sponge will be the mascot in the amusement park.
I mean, a dancing... I was about to say, a dancing sponge could be a mascot.
No, the mascot... the mascot is clearly...
The dancing sponge should be the mascot. It's the best idea that we have.
What do you mean the mas... we got all these stupid people. They own mascots.
They're walk-around characters.
Wait, hold on. I think there's a... there's a timer in my brain that might start going down if we talk about this.
What are you talking about?
Shut up. I'm trying to...
Do you have a bomb in your head?
(laughter)
That is terrifying.
We gotta diffuse it.
So yeah, uh,
Somebody give me your sword.
Thorax and, uh, uh, fuck you walk over to you guys and they go, "Sir, how do you guys
all feel?
Do you feel ready to do this?"
Yeah, I'm pretty ready.
Yeah, in fact, we don't even need the five minutes.
(laughter)
The what now?
This character doesn't know about it.
There, alright, listen, there's a bomb in our friend's head.
Oh, not again.
- Again, the fucking frog. - We're gonna go off in five minutes.
Point is, I think we feel pretty good about it.
I think all of us probably feel good because it's just gonna, I mean,
like it's a private thing, it's just gonna be us and these five investors, you know.
I feel pretty strong about that.
- It is, we are, uh, Thorax, uh, Thoraxier.
[laughter]
Uh, we are gonna be in an arena.
You guys know that, right? - Yeah, but it's gonna be empty.
- It's gonna be no one else's arena, right? - No one else, no one, yeah.
- I mean, we all get stage fright, you know, like, you know how it is.
[laughter]
horrible stage. My teeth are gonna chatter if there's any. I kind of pee
myself sometimes. The entire way here you guys kept bragging about your stage
presence. What is what is happening? Well part of it's like a thing where we turn
the stage right into a stage presence. It's kind of like a subversive like
like. So the presence is that you're pissing yourself. If I'm on the stage I'm present.
Talk to them, Thorax.
Look guys, we can do this, okay?
We have built-in imbeciles who can work the park, okay?
We have a solid labor force right out the gate, okay?
It's a no-brainer, it's a layup.
Relax, loosen up, okay?
- No-brainer can be one of the names of the restaurants.
- Amen.
(laughing)
Shit, that's really good.
- That's a really good point, yeah.
Okay, that's what I'm talking about man. That's that's off the dome - brother. Okay, you just show up in there
I wrote that down a mile ago
If only someone would offer us five minutes of time to discuss it
You're after you have to you have to date. I want okay. We're gonna take it
Okay, okay, you can obviously just roll it in there. It's fine. Okay ready
Says give me the three of you in character and solve it. Yes, ready wait
What what is the do are they gonna call us in in five minutes?
Is that the pressing time does a stage hand come over and say five minutes till you walk out?
Yeah, I think that's sort of the fiction here, right? I basically was I wasn't I'm sorry
I should have actually yeah, that would have been a bit bit of better more immersive do it do it now
You can cut it out. Okay, okay, okay
Come with the stagehand character
How the third time sir?
Whoa five minutes you guys gonna go out bitch. Okay. Where is your neck? I?
Lost it in a bet, okay
Campbell brother, please just you're eating into our time and you're doing our partying so oh
Bitch don't get me hurt
How about this minutes and 45 seconds?
- Okay, bye.
- Fuck you, man.
- Okay, all right, all right, let's go.
We're gonna ask for 100 trillion gold coins
for 1% of the business.
- Because you gotta set the bar high.
- Exactly, because if we ask for a small amount,
they're gonna think it's a worthless business.
- I just think we gotta try to provide
some sort of proof of concept or of sales or something.
Maybe some sort of like pitch maneuver.
- We just lie.
- Maybe we draw a picture.
Maybe we walk, maybe we send in the idiots first.
Maybe we-- - I'm the only one here
who owns the business. - Will you be quiet?
Maybe we send in the idiots first,
and then the orcs are like, "What the hell?
"What, these guys are doing a horrible job pitching."
Then we come out and say, "Wasn't that so funny?
"Imagine if they were walking around selling you hot dogs."
- That is an amazing idea.
- Okay, I'm not opposed to that.
- Also, they're dressed like the Rockettes.
(laughing)
- What are the Rockettes?
The women that dress up like different types of rocks?
- Yes. (laughing)
In this world, yeah, that's what they is.
Okay, and then...
A gal could show a staple!
We could just take turns just throwing out statistics for them about our sales and our margins and you know, it doesn't...
Ah, pretty much 100% and stuff like that.
Yeah, pretty much, that part does not matter. At all.
No, I think, the thing is, if we say 1% for 100 trillion, I think we'll be in a good spot because even if they say, "Okay, we want 2% for 50 trillion," we say...
That's at least 100!
And in their brain, they're like, "Well, we got 'em.
"We got 'em on the road."
- I got an idea.
Okay, so it's gonna be 100% sales.
Maybe we should divvy that up into two 50,
50% and another 50% of,
guys, I'm freaking the fuck out.
I have no idea.
- Okay, listen, and here's the thing, right?
They say no to 1%.
We say, "Okay, how about $100 trillion
"for 100% of the business?"
Then, then we don't have to run the business
and we can just leave.
No, but we don't own any of it so we're not getting any profit from it.
But we just got a hundred trillion gold coins you stupid frog!
Let's go into the business, it's not gonna go to me and you.
Okay, what if we say-
Wait, what?
Yeah!
What do you mean?
We- we- it's our idea.
Okay, 99%, 100 trillion.
We start with 100 trillion for 1%, then we go to 100 trillion for 99% if there's no
bucks.
Okay, yeah, that's actually pretty good.
That's a lot of money in that case.
That's not a bad idea.
We can cash that out and just vibe.
we can make Sullivan go in a spinning teacup on stage.
- Why do you want me to do that?
- I think we figured it out.
- Okay.
- Your honor, I'd like to cede the rest of our time
to Sullivan doing an opera song.
- Between now and the end?
(laughing)
All right.
- Hold on.
- We could just hang out for the rest of the time.
- Let me actually look a bit old standard, I used to say.
- I believe you have two minutes and 20 seconds left
to blow me away.
You know, we're about to be our shark tank. I want you to pretend you're on American Idol.
*singing*
Yeah, I don't really know if there's anything else to talk about.
Are we gonna have a pitch idea? So we're gonna have the idiots walk out, okay?
You're gonna put me in a teacup, I think?
Or whatever, we could put you on a rollercoaster.
Yeah, do we have a picture of a rollercoaster?
Wait, why me? Get over here.
Can you use your magic to conjure any kind of amusement park ride?
Yeah, of course.
Okay, well do that. Do a really crazy one to put Sullivan in it.
Okay, how about...
What about a teacup that spins in a circle?
Well, I like that but what about a teacup that goes fucking nuts and jumps in the air and what did I just say? Yeah
Okay, that's pretty good, all right, so I'm back to the opera I think we figured out the rest of the idea
Hold on. Hold on. Okay, you sure?
to teacups
We could and then we could have praised. No, I'm G come out. No, we can't show him. No, no, we can't show him
The one teacup bounces Sullivan from one teacup to the other and he just keeps going back and forth and it's spinning very fast
Okay. Yeah
Two idiots come out and be like check this out, but they'll be stupid about it and then that'll be funny
They'll do like a they'll do like a punch and Judy thing. Wait, yeah
Okay, but I have to play the idiot. So what is a punch?
I thought we have idiots with us you do you do you do you good?
Punching Judy was a new use of its puppets that chase each other around and hit each other
Three it was a fast five
Wait what this is you oh my god, that's the that's the orcs that or tank theme song
have to produce this episode and put that song in there. Okay, so yeah you guys are
ready to go. You have your insane idea, no proof of sort of revenue or sales or
whatever. What are you talking about? We have a million, but also they don't have to know that.
We just say 100% sales. Yeah, we just say a bunch of numbers. Alright. I'm sorry, you're right. The trick is keep
them on the offensive. They have to ask the questions, we just answer them. No
follow up nothing true so just yeses and no all right all right I think we got
walk out into the arena don't say anything yes walk out to the arena it is
a massive arena you're in the biggest city one of the biggest cities in the
terror fire kingdom Gal Gadot city of Gal Gadot massive city you're surrounded by
some of the scariest looking fucking monsters and motherfuckers ever and they
all want to fucking eat you guys alive you have five investors in front of you
Okay, Ola the Orc. She's one of the foremost businesswomen in the
Terrifier Kingdom. Ola the Orc was the first to learn magic, first first Orc to
learn magic in a hundred years. With her superior intellect and
moderate attention span. She used her magical abilities to make other Orcs
think she had their nose, starting a thriving business where people would buy
their back their nose from her. With revenue skyrocketing she expanded her
business by teaching other orcs to cast simple everlasting, in quotes,
everlasting flame spells. These orcs would then heat homes for a small fee.
They'd say they'd show up to fix their everlasting flames sometime between 8
a.m. and 5 p.m. and then they'd either show up at 730 a.m. or 6 p.m. and then
they'd leave five minutes if you weren't there for them. Eventually more orcs
learned magic and started their own businesses but Ola was the first one in
and Ola's Magic Service, which is the sort of the umbrella company, is the
foremost operation in the whole kingdom. It's like the like like Amazon or
fucking whatever sort of company. If you're looking for someone who knows how
to expand and has ties to many industries around the kingdom, Ola's your girl.
She will likely look for higher stake, grow the business in a sure but steady
rate, and will be a terrific guide and partner for you, but slow and steady
doesn't always win the race, and she could be a bit controlling at times.
I'm writing all of this down on Sullivan's back.
Yeah, he's like, "Ahh! Ahh! Ow! Ow!"
Next, you have Venni Vitivici, the Mind Drinker.
Venni Vitivici, or Venni, is a mind drinker, a vampire that sucks the thoughts and, more importantly, the secrets out of people.
As such, he's made his money in the intelligence community by selling the secrets he siphoned.
He began his career as a boy, learning who had a crush on whom and selling that information to interested parties.
This became a lucrative business as well among adults in the vampire community who sought
Venny's wisdom and insights even when he was just a child.
As he grew older, his powers were sought by many across the land.
They would trek to Venny's castle north of Gal Gadot and offer him riches, lands, titles,
as well as secrets of their own for the secrets he held.
With his Berbalang, Winifred, Berbalangs are these sort of like disgusting little winged
freaks, I'll show you guys a picture, who takes to the skies and
acts as a spy, so he gathers additional secrets as well as verifying the secrets
he's gotten. He's become basically one of the most entrusted and
successful venture capitalists. If you want someone who has insider knowledge
will just sort of be a capital injection but then kind of be very hands-off, which
positives or negatives, you know, open many doors for you, won't open many doors for
you, but without, you know, that kind of partnership part would need to be
earned. Third, Kevin Rudderkin, aka Mr. Awful. Kevin Rudderkin the Rudderkin is a
disgusting piece of shit, smelly freak, who inherited his wealth from his demon
lord father, Zeltaros, and has turned that into a burgeoning drug-running business.
He runs it with the subtlety of a sledgehammer, but no one wishes to anger his father, so he gets away with quite a lot of nonsense.
He's the biggest loser of his family, but became wildly successful thanks to the second mouth that sits in place of his left hand.
[laughter]
Lucky.
I think this is our guy.
[laughter]
It possesses a sinister intelligence that employs to actually run the illicit business that Kevin has.
On occasion, Kevin will go unconscious and his second mouth will handle any of the business concerns that actually need to be handled,
while Kevin just sort of is a bit of a blowhard.
The mouth calls itself Mr. Awful.
Some say the mouth came from a spell Kevin's father placed on him.
Some say it's a curse placed on him by a witch who he got too handsy with.
Either way, you will have to impress both of them to get their buy-in.
And most importantly never ever address Kevin's mouth while Kevin is still conscious
He will freak the fuck out
Here's the thing he's it's illicit right so what's good about this is very hands-off you guys want to fucking do shit
Yeah, he's got one hand. Yeah, he's gonna one hand. You know your hands are off
Basically you'll be able to get what you need you'll be able to sort of show up and say what you want to happen when you
want to happen
He'll take a pretty big cut of whatever you guys make
But you know again. It's a lot easier when it's just mob run, and you just have to sort of turn the other way
Don't look at it
mob run amusement park
But
He's gonna call you in for a favor, and if you refuse they will hunt you down like dogs
Mm-hmm, so that's sort of the trade-off. They're a lot easier to run it you get something very steady
You don't just have to look the other way when all kinds of weird shit is going on your amusement park and then
Occasional favorite you'll have to sort of call in
Next last two gelatinous Cuban
Jelatinous Cuban is a richest entity in the whole kingdom. No one knows how he makes his money
It just has a lot of it. He's never invested in anything on the show
usually just makes gurgling noises and tries to engulf the contestants by
slowly and extremely obviously sliding towards them no one has ever heard him
speak he's been married for 17 years to Cara Del Veen final final shark not
shark orc is a walrus that wandered into the arena a few years ago and sat on top
of one of the former orcs he will try to eat the gelatinous cube and yell
occasionally and that's it so he doesn't really they don't know how to move him
he's really huge so he's just kind of hanging out there so I take it back
that's our guy nobody knows how much money the the walrus has you just know he's
like 17 feet tall I don't care how much money he has I want him involved smells
like fish and makes that sound so yeah you guys walk out and you see these five
entrepreneurs five and a half I guess four and a half five and a half I added
one and they entreat you you hear Ola say so what do you have to offer us investor
says what well first of all we're not good it's the it's the idiots that are
out there not us if we remember our plan oh man is just in the shit I really just
fight you said it all backstage yeah all right so these idiots coming out which
Do you want to bring in like go out there? I'm gonna go up to all of them
I'm gonna say every last one of them are all going on stage
150 guys
Morons rush the stage
Yeah, you see everyone all the orcs in their seats like just certainly fucking like back away and then
*Screaming*
And now the orcs think that the idiots are the investors.
And then us three, yeah, we set the bar really low
with the idiots coming out first. You watch the orcs and they're all watching this and they're taking
notes. And then us three walk out through the crowd. There's no information about
the product. We're parting the idiots like the Red Sea. Yeah. And we walk up
and I go, "Hmm. Impressed yet?"
(laughter)
Little walrus goes, "Aaah!"
And you see, uh, Veni, Vidi, uh, not Veni, Vidi.
You see, uh, Kevin.
Kevin the Ritterfin.
Before I go any further, I do want to show you guys what these people look like.
Okay.
'Cause I, it's very fun. Hold on, let me, uh, let me pull it up.
Uh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Oh, which reminds me, there's one other thing I have to tell you guys.
Before I even show you these, just you guys, so for everybody at home as well.
The way Orc Tank works, they're all very close to me right now in real life.
The way Orc Tank works is once somebody makes an offer,
you have to defeat them in combat.
What?
If you want to accept the offer.
Okay.
And refuse any offers.
Once you defeat them in combat,
you can also have an option to field other offers.
You can take a long rest.
You can take up to two long rests.
This can be a multi-day process.
Okay.
Alright.
So I wanted to let you guys know.
So not only do you get to do the pitch, once you get that,
once they make you an offer and you guys accept it,
or you consider it a good offer,
it's fight time.
Alright.
Okay, but let me show you guys what you guys look like.
Gelatinous cube.
This is what Mark,
I mean, gelatinous cuban looks like.
He just looks like a gelatinous cube.
What do we do?
Alright, walrus.
He looks basically how you'd expect him to look.
Yeah.
Sort of like a giant walrus.
Mm-hmm.
Um, oop, bleh.
Uh, our friend Ola.
Oh, okay.
The orc woman.
Oh my god.
Damn.
She's okay?
Yeah, she's pretty fine.
And then, uh, let's do our friends the mind drinker, Venni Vidi Vici.
Here he is. He's kind of spooky looking. Oh, wait, alright.
Okay.
Oh, he's scary.
He's a little scary looking, and then this is what a Berbalang looks like.
What's a, what's a Berbalang?
What the hell a Berbalang?
You're about to see it once this shit fucking loads. It's gonna be nutty as hell.
Um, refresh it. Interesting.
Refresh it. I will, I will. I'm doing it. I believe you. Hurry up.
Hold on. But I do want to show you also what, um, most important person to show you guys though, honestly,
is what a Berbalang looks like. Ooh, a Berbalang. They're pretty cool.
He's like a creepy guy with a beard and wings. Yes. For everyone.
The most important thing to show you guys though is, is, uh, Kevin.
Kevin I think is the best designed of the creatures here. Kevin looks basically like
a sort of Cronenbergian flesh monster with a disgusting mouth on his hand.
He's a Rutterkin which is a kind of fiend. They're very prideful and they
wander the abyss. Oh creepy. So that's Kevin. He got teeth where his wiener
should be that's right sir all right cool just like me so oh yeah there he is okay
you guys walk up to these guys you guys part the seas yeah are you impressed the
walrus screams and sort of swats at gelatinous Cuban who once he gelatinous
Cuban sees you guys walk up it starts to slowly inches away towards you but you
will just do you just have to sort of move aside a little bit he won't reach
you you see Ola and she goes that was extremely confusing what what is the
business is it here's the deal where it's screaming what what oh it actually
actually worked no way you were expecting that I wasn't I wasn't
expecting that um what's your idea you just said it again you dumbass you see
now you got a body got a double invest you see Kevin I'm hungry tell me your
idea I'm gonna eat you hello burger if you wanted hey wait hold on do I actually
Hey Orcs! Hold on, hold on, hold on.
We're so...
Didn't I check your inventory?
We're so happy to be here and pitch our idea for...
Idiot...
Stupid Idiotville...
Land...
What was it again? Tell me again.
Extra special. Idiotland Stupidville.
Idiotland Stupidville.
A brand new amusement park staffed entirely by...
These guys. Weren't they funny?
funny I mean real quick let's give a round of applause for all our ideas here
in the audience I mean did they not do an amazing job see the idiots and start
just floating towards the sky now come back here basically we're looking for
100 trillion dollars for one percent of this beautiful business you see many
anybody of each goes, "I do say that is quite a steep offer."
Well, you'll have to explain a bit more about your business.
That's pretty shocking.
So basically, all right.
No, we don't.
What's the number one problem with owning a theme park?
What's the number one problem?
Just you explain it to me.
Well, this would be the first amusement park in the land.
So as people for--
Well, don't you wanna be on the ground floor of that?
It's the first amusement park in the land?
Alright, alright, and tell me, why has nobody ever built an amusement park before?
Yseola says, "Well, we just didn't even know that we were allowed to have fun until a few years ago."
Investor says, "What? Oh, you keep getting me! I like this one!"
[laughter]
Here's the reason. You gotta pay the employees.
Yeah, that does suck. I don't like that one bit.
Here's a little idea that maybe you never thought of that I have thought of.
(laughing)
- What if they were slaves?
- Yeah, if you eliminate--
- You're an all-nighman tree.
- You eliminate paying of the employees,
we are talking incredible margins.
We're talking in the 100s, 200s, 300s.
- And here-- - Different percentiles.
- Let me ask you, you might be thinking--
- There's so many percentages, your head's gonna explode.
- Sales, 1,000.
- You might be thinking, "Well, slaves,
"well, that's an interesting number."
- Overhead costs, one million.
Those are good, right?
- No, no.
- You might be thinking-- - Those are not good.
Those are not good.
Overhead cost is zero
Zero until he explains it
What you might be thinking yourself? Well slaves that's interesting, but then also what's what's the biggest issue with slaves?
Well from my experience they got it eating shit. Well, listen, here's the actual issue
the two damn smart
So what if I told you we have a hundred and fifty of the stupidest damn slaves you ever seen
And we're gonna make them fucking spin cotton candy
Press big red. What about King Nardwaur's regulations around slavery? How are you planning on getting around that?
I don't listen. There's no newspapers here so I can tell you this King Nardwaur died
He's been he's dead I mean roll deception can they ease with disadvantage why?
24 hour news network we just got to get him to say yes, right?
Let me see what my deception is hold on
Charisma so probably not ideal
No, like here's our plan just know that guy's not real. Yeah
There's a that's gotta be pretty
Okay, you got roll that shit one more time
All right 13. All right
Okay, okay you see have anybody beat you say, um
He's dead. I
Heard there was trouble in the kingdom, but I died of he died of laughter
When you saw these slaves
And what are and the guests to the park will not die
We tuned down how funny they are
What do you mean by turned it down we used an allen wrench on the on the hole in their back
And we tuned it down
Show me the hole in one of their backs. Okay. Okay. Just close your eyes for one second
Roll slide A and roll slide A and see how you do it biting a hole out of one of their bags.
(Laughter)
(Slide sound)
Roll again, roll again, unless it's good.
What is it? It's my roll.
Alright, cause I'm a nice guy.
(Slide sound)
Alright, six. (Laughter)
You just very, very clearly
took a bite out of a human's back.
I had to check to make sure it was still there.
He took off the lid.
He took the lid off of it.
Ok, roll deception.
Roll deception.
You fucking god damn it.
I'm gonna make you roll each of these, bro.
Wait, let me roll deception.
Ok.
Ten.
Alright, you can roll deception.
Wait, yeah, you should roll it.
Yeah, I already said it.
You can roll again with advantage.
Let evil roll again with advantage if he's helping out.
Ok.
Four.
Ok, ten is what you got.
Ok.
All right, you see that you see Ola sitting there and she's like
Look, oh, this is investor says what?
Not not this time
All this is fine, but
But what what what's your what's your return on this?
What have you guys seen as far as interest in this at least if you don't have concrete sales, what are we talking about here?
Yeah, we're not here to sell concrete. I'm telling you
Let me tell you see if any video each you go. I don't want to hear anything about sales
I want to know what the vision is. Okay, I can invest in a vision not in sales
I only concrete number let me money capital. Let me go I can I think I believe I can help with that. Yeah
helping them picture this a
giant cup
Spinning around really fast and
The guy and the and when you get out of it, you see a really funny guy with a funny haircut
Hey wait guys, I think I have an idea
my picture this
Giant hold on. I got make a second picture of my head now. This isn't so much for you
This isn't so much for you picture this just ought to all the investors a giant cup
filled with fish
You see, okay
Do any of you have any interest in that idea?
(laughter)
- So, give me five seconds,
'cause I wanna look up what Walrus's intelligence is.
In D&D.
- Do you have stats for how much money he has?
- He has no money, I'm telling you.
(laughter)
He's a huge walrus that wandered into the arena.
I want to see if it's at least high enough maybe to like perceive any of this to some
extent.
I just want to know.
I'm getting a 2 on intelligence.
That is probably not high enough.
But I'm gonna bump it up.
I'm just going to keep in mind that officially he has a 2 on intelligence.
Keep in mind, a dolphin I think has 6.
So that's what we're working with.
Okay.
Roll persuasion with that.
You guys, if you want to give him advantage, you can.
I'm going to give him advantage.
Well, you know, it's going to be limited how many times you can do that in my brain.
Okay, go for it.
I don't need advantage.
Okay, I won't give him an advantage.
20 with my advantage.
Okay, dirty 20?
Dirty 20.
Roll again.
No, I didn't give him an advantage. I told him I cancelled it.
Dirty 20, okay.
The walrus is like...
[Growling]
[Laughter]
He's sort of wiggling back and forth.
And seaweed.
[Growling]
Boy, I'm detecting a lot of excitement about this business from one certain investor.
I think any other investors who are thinking about making an offer might really need to go in soon.
I think maybe everybody would like to invest in this.
Okay, you don't want to get left in the dust by a fucking walrus
He's like a little perturbed by that but then gets distracted by the gelatinous cube and he tries to eat it
Cuban is now by the way like halfway to you guys
So he can pivot anytime you want
Pick up some sand off the ground
Get in your chair right now.
I'm sick of you.
Sort of jiggles a little bit and like sort of like wanders a bit to the left and right
and like doesn't remember where you guys are.
You see all I go now.
What are your what are your supply chains for this?
How are you supplying all this?
And OK, there's no overhead because they're slaves.
That's fantastic.
How investors says what?
God damn it.
What are your marketing efforts?
Damn it.
supply chain
we got a hundred fifty guys right here
they care about how it is to them for you
you can have some of the runners
i think you said on others what you're talking about let me speak
who has a we got a hundred fifty guys who are going to work there
that's what that's the one part of the supply the other person plaza have a
wizard you can make amusement park right here
we can build this thing and like it is a very rare
you see a lot of fun fuck you going
They're like waving his robe down, "Hey, how's it going?"
"Hey, how about this? Make the Yankee Cannonball right now."
"Shit, alright, fuck it."
And then he makes it.
See?
I mean, look at that. Isn't that the most beautiful,
the greatest amusement park ride of all time?
And that only cost 100 million gold coins to do.
Yeah, so basically, we'll have him.
I know magic!
Ola Magic Services.
So then why are you asking stupid questions?
Because I want to see what your stupid answers are.
I wanna see what your stupid answers are, okay?
You're getting fresh with me now.
- Hey, who you calling stupid?
- Nobody in particular.
- Investor says what?
- You see, if any of you go, look, I've seen enough, okay?
I think this is--
- Wait, check this out.
And I take my finger and I do like the, like--
- Separating his finger?
- Yeah, separating the--
- I don't know where your thumb is going,
but that's besides the point.
- No, that's my finger.
- Investor says I'm out.
Investor says I'm out.
I'm not going to say I'm out.
Okay, just-- Oh, shit.
(laughing)
It finally worked.
I'm going to make you a counter offer
for your offer you've put out.
Okay.
Okay?
I like the idea.
I think an amusement park in the location you suggested
would be huge for people.
I think there's a lot of opportunity here.
I'm offering you all, okay, 100,000 gold pieces
at 20% but, but,
- Thousand or trillion?
- A hundred, a hundred thousand trillion.
- There's no way I'm doing a trillion goat pieces.
- Well, you can't change the money amount.
- Yes.
(laughing)
- That is true.
- That's the rule.
That's the rules only if there were,
if there was another version of this show
that wasn't in a game,
that would be a rule, that's a rule on that version.
- I think in the version of that show,
it's totally fine to do that.
Now he sounds like fuck you. Okay, hold on.
Okay.
Let me find a new voice for him. How about this? This is a good voice. Okay.
Do Peter Griffin.
Eh, so where... What about a... How do you do Peter Griffin again? Hold on.
Eh...
Lowish, lowish. Okay, how about this?
Lowish, how about this? A hundred thousand... Is that short of it?
That's good enough. That's good enough.
A hundred thousand gold pieces.
At twenty percent.
This is Peter Griffin.
Now you're doing Stewie.
*laughter*
But...
You're also going to get two secrets from me.
Two valuable secrets. I am a dealer in secrets.
What, you want me to be your damn boyfriend? You're gonna buy my business.
Look...
I'm open for boyfriends, but that's not the point.
Two secrets.
You can't change a secret about them.
*laughter*
Yeah, that's like the only rule.
Three secrets.
Four secrets.
Five secrets.
Three secrets.
One secret.
(laughing)
Three secrets, three secrets.
No, we already said deal, one secret's good.
Okay, three secrets.
Okay.
Is it one or is it three?
It's one plus two.
Okay, so we'll write you down for five secrets
and 100 trillion gold coins for 0.5%.
Which is not what I said, no.
No.
100,000 gold coins, 20% stake, 3% advisory board.
I'm on the advisory board here.
- But listen, you have to do all the work.
- Absolutely not, that's not how I do things.
- Come on, man.
If you want someone to do all the work,
you gotta ask me, Kevin.
I got mob guys that do basically fucking everything for you.
- Wait, I think we, wait guys, I think,
anybody got a rock?
- You see Kevin go limp for a second.
- Oh, nevermind, I don't need it anymore.
You see the mouth go up and goes, "Hey, yeah, so, uh, um, uh, hi, I'm Mr. Awful. I'm Kevin's,
uh, I'm the guy who actually does everything for Kevin. He's a little slow. Um, uh, we will do
most of the work for you, not all of the work." Sounds good. "Uh, we're just gonna need a favor
from you guys if you go through with it and we are-" What is the favor? "Uh, it's to be determined.
We will also be running-" We have to know the favor. "You have to know the favor." Can the secret
be the favorite what the favor is now we don't need i don't care i'm not
associated with this whole uh you know illegal enterprise i have no
interest in that secrets thing look okay loser says what just tell me
what what is your money
oh my god oh my god i believe did you guys see that i didn't hear what you
what
Listen, just tell me the offer that you have for us.
Yeah, who is your offer?
Alright, you want to know my offer? I don't know what I can...
I don't know what Kevin's going to agree to, but I can say $200,000, okay?
At 25%, so that's already a better sort of situation for you.
But, again, you're going to have to do a favor for us,
for us and we are gonna run drugs through your amusement park.
- That's fine with me.
- I'd rather you did that than not.
- I love drugs.
- All right.
Okay, cool.
So that's--
- How about this?
We throw in a song from Sullivan.
- You're gonna give me more stuff?
(all talking at once)
Okay, we'll knock down--
- You're gonna give me more stuff.
Can the frog sing?
- It's gonna sing for you and it's gonna be beautiful.
I already sang once, kinda sincerely, which is annoying.
I don't know.
It's gonna be Freedom, not Freedom 90, by George Michael.
Or actually Wham!, not George Michael.
Well, that's sung by George Michael.
I don't know that song though!
Listen, can we double it to 400,000 if we throw in a dancing sponge?
You hear, you're, "God damn it!"
From way back there.
What do you mean a dancing sponge?
like a mascot for the amusements park.
Like a sponge that dances.
It's a different invention. Actually, why don't we have our spokesperson come up and explain the idea really briefly.
And just explain the idea and say nothing else in any way.
And actually it's his final wish to do this because he's going to die.
Because he's going to die. And he's definitely going to die if he says anything else.
Do you want to run back and grab Ted?
He can hear me.
okay tip wall up you see for tat like oh my god I can't believe you did this
again tit and you see tit wander up it's like I'm gonna kill you man do I get a
cut of this at least uh yeah totally yeah yes I know sarcasm I was stuck now a lot
that's just how I talk yet go I've seen that sketch - from get it all do that do
Do your thing. Talk about the sponge that dances.
Say the sponge thing or...
Okay, so, imagine this.
Okay? You have sponges.
These are a new thing for us here in Gal Gadot.
Before this we weren't very clean.
Now, sponges are great because they clean things and we like that now.
But you know what? They're kind of fucking boring.
What if all these sponges came enchanted with a dancing spell?
So right before you started cleaning and you're like, "Aww, I don't want to clean. Cleaning sucks."
They do a little dance. Is that what you want me to pitch?
Yeah right here's your cut. Off stage. Go. Go. Go.
I got pissed.
Okay roll an attack roll.
Kill him?
I'm not sure he deserves to die.
Miss.
Oh my god! What the hell?
We will be doing more performances like that.
We will be putting on shows like that.
Yeah it's gonna lighten up the show.
Yeah he's gonna swallow a sword.
I will not be doing that.
Offstage go.
Okay, he walks offstage. And you see a Ola go, "What was...?"
That's our second idea.
So what was that? What was that exactly?
It's our other idea.
What did you just say?
I will make you an offer as well. Because of how the DM
structured this 300,000 gold pieces I get 40% okay plus I get 5% on the
advisory board and you're gonna be a part of the Ola magic services family so
you get a lot of benefits from that you will have to give up relinquish
additional control at least in terms of which vendors you use you're gonna have
to start with internal companies first,
and then before you move into external ones, okay?
For any of your needs.
So I don't know what existing relationships you have now,
but you'll have to sort of renegotiate those.
- I don't care about this at all.
- Yeah, does that mean we're just gonna make like less money?
- Let's just go with Mr. Awful.
- Well, but listen, all right,
we have heard your three offers, okay?
Gelatinous Cube seems a little...
- He is touching Patrick Giodar right now.
- I'm not sure we're interested,
Before we officially deliberate, I would like to hear...
AHHHHH!
Now that's what I'm talking about.
FISH!
What?
Brilliant.
Oh my god, I've never heard him say anything.
Listen, alright.
You must really love this idea.
So listen, how about two fish?
AHHHH!
Oh!
The piece of his head is like gonna explode.
Guys, I think...
Hold on, hold on.
What about a red fish?
You see Thorax in the back like, "Stop!"
Like, "Guys, let's not do this!"
Guys, I think...
I think we...
I mean, what's entrepreneurship about?
It's about going with your gut.
That's right.
What's my gut telling me?
Fish.
This walrus is gonna take care of us, dude.
Yeah
Okay, I don't know so before you move forward the gelatinous cube hasn't offered anything obviously and never will in case you're curious but
If you decide to go with the walrus
You can fight the walrus if you win against the fight you can still feel the other offers
If you lose against the fight you don't get the walrus
Can't feel the other you can still feel the other offers, but they might be a little ticked off
Obviously you can go with the walrus. I guess he's offering offering to fish or you're offering him to fish
There's no real we can work out the details
It's a legit fight though, but I want to let you know okay, so before we make our decision
I guess we have to we should probably deliberate so I feel like maybe we should leave this stage
and maybe leave you guys to hang out with the all the idiots and to see how funny
they are and we can go talk for maybe 10 20 yeah hey watch this I just like take
out of like my rations at my inventory I pick out like a chicken bone or
something I'm like hey this is $100 and I just throw it into the crowd yeah they
all just like start bumping into each other like... Now imagine that in a cage
wouldn't that be nice to see? All the investors nodding like thoughtfully
about it and you guys wander off to discuss internally. Yeah what are you
guys thinking I mean... Well here Sullivan what do you think? Yeah let's hear
let's hear from you. What do you think? You are our most trusted advisor, we listen to
everything you say so yeah tell us what you well honestly oh okay oh come on no
I okay maybe he's gonna do a weird fart noise but I genuinely want to hear it
all right well um we're okay all right hold on I'm gonna you guys you guys
it's gonna be all right I'll take five Lucy with the football situation all
right you with the what hold up nevermind childhood just did you know a
girl named Lucy who would when you would go to kick it that is so sad tears yeah
Yeah, it was pretty blue for me.
Take five.
Alright, I'll cool off.
I want to hear what you
I want to hear who you think we should invest with.
Okay, well,
so after hearing all the
uh, uh,
I thought you guys were taking five.
You have five farts in your mouth.
That's all of it.
They're taking five, you keep talking.
Okay, well, uh, so
the well I think all up on as a nasty that was real up like has a pretty
proven trials are you to Patrick oh man all right that's it it's the walrus
we're gonna go back over the walrus it's gonna be the walrus you guys rush ahead
you solve it just like defeated and they just like some walks until he walks by
You guys okay you see a fuck you and thorax just like make their heads in their temples
It's a double like Oh fucking shit like what were we thinking all right, so?
You guys go back there the idiots are
They formed a pyramid
like it like a like a
card castle
And we push one of the carts
Funny as fuck you can do that whenever you want
And that's funny shit, okay, so who you want
Want me eenie meenie miney moe catch it
Let him go my mother told me to pick the very best one and you are it walrus
Okay, so the walrus
Which is gladness gladness Cuban at this point has?
Just been trying to avoid the walrus the walrus sort of waddles over to you all
And you see all the other the all the other orcs they they're they file aside and go to it you see the lighting
Magical lighting change in the arena you hear people shout and scream screaming for blood
The walrus sort of positions itself upright and for the first time it has a sort of lucidity to it
It's not just screaming about fish. It knows it's time for combat
It's next time we're gonna roll for initiative
Okay, but right now I get it. I gotta say this
You're the most beautiful walrus I've ever seen
And you wouldn't want to hurt little old me I'm only four years old
(laughing)
You're getting to be a big boy!
I'm just a kid who's four
Each day I grow some more
I like exploring, I'm Caillou
So many things to do
Each day is something new
I'll share them with you, I'm Caillou
My world is turning, changing each day
With Mommy and Daddy I'm finding my way
Bye!
[MUSIC PLAYING]