[Dramatic music]
Last time on Trebuchet Village, our heroes continued their voyage through the seas in the body of the submarine Changeling Chuggie.
Deftly avoiding a Squidward and his ranted shark, the gang settled on an island of magical fun with no DM parental supervision.
Afterwards, they headed back down into the sea to play a shell game with a friendly croc-topus and his infant, gathering some very neat and very strong items.
After a few more days of uneventful traveling through the perilous sea-bomb, the gang rests atop an island for their latest in a string of nappies.
This is the first island in a while you guys have been doing the thing where Chuggie is
a submarine and you guys rest on top of him.
For context for the listeners at home, we did, you might not be, we did about 8-ish minutes
and I've never imagined what would happen if we, if you lose, you can't like undo I guess
story stuff, but we didn't do any story stuff.
All we did was establish that they're on the island, that Chuggie had cast Leoman's Tiny
Hut so it just gives him a little hut to rest in. And it was not called Liam
and Stiney Hut it was called Chuggie's Big Ass Pad. Yes Chuggie's Big Ass Pad.
It's not that big though and also um... It's big for his changeling form who I
was which was Mr. Cutie Pop Star. Yes. Sounds like Robot Drake.
Robot Drake. But also he can change the voice if he's not feeling it.
Yeah right. Which I think we kind of established. I think that's fine. I'd also
So just to catch us up to speed one more thing,
we put up a picture of Patrick.
Yeah.
And the recorder stopped right when I started drawing him nude.
He's drawing basically under the picture.
It was a good bit.
And right before that too, we found buried under the sand,
we found millions and millions of gold pieces.
We found millions of it.
You can't talk at the same time.
12 million snippets of gold.
We found a golden snitch.
Yeah, a snitch and several snippets.
And by several, I mean 12 million.
You found a golden snitch, and he's telling on you,
when he's telling me that you guys are lying.
- Who is? - You're a fucking snitch.
- Who told you? - No, I'm telling the golden snitch.
- The golden snitch can't talk, it flies.
- And the only noise the golden snitch makes is...
- A play on words.
- Oh my god. I hate that sound.
- And when Harry eats it. - Swallows it.
- Yeah, and then his arm turns into jello.
- Yeah. - And then...
- That's in a different movie, but...
- He is a seeker.
- Chuggy and Evil and Dogen find 12 million golden snippets.
- Right before that though, it didn't happen.
- Before that it didn't happen, right,
'cause it hadn't happened yet.
And then it happened.
- And we will start the scene--
- So then afterward it had happened.
- Okay.
- We will start the scene where we find 12 million
golden snippets and a golden snitch.
- And we can never--
- This can never happen again.
- Snippets and a snitch.
- We found it and we found a gubber.
- Yeah.
- A gupper?
- A gubber.
- Fucking gubber.
- I remember we found it.
- It's a gold gubber.
- A golden gubber.
- Underneath the snippets and snitch.
In a separate golden layer.
- Okay, ready?
Three, two, one.
Oh my god, we found a golden snippet.
- Oh my, wait, is that a golden snitch next to it?
- That's a golden snitch.
- I wonder what's on the layer beneath it.
- Wow, it might be a gubber.
I hear that those are common in this area.
- The gubber is under the snippets.
- Oh my god, I just moved the snippets and snitch
and the gubber's underneath.
- And look under the snippet.
- Okay, and so then, after all that.
- Okay.
- Okay, after you guys get weird,
So, you guys, you know, you fall asleep.
You take your little long rest.
And as you begin to rouse from your sleep,
you-- - Oh no, I just woke up
with big boobs.
(laughing)
- The fuck is, come on.
- I gotta play with these things.
- Well, as you get up to play with your huge tits,
you look through--
- I look like that woodshop teacher.
- You look through the small window of your tiny hut,
And you notice that it looks like, kind of like,
the sky is whipping past the trees
that are inside this wooded area.
And--
- We're not underneath the fucking thing anymore.
- No, we're on a giant turtle.
And...
- Maybe.
- We are.
- We have to, we are.
- Fucking asshole.
(laughing)
- And as you walk outside--
- It's not an island, it's a fucking turtle shell.
- As you walk outside--
And the hut--
- That was underneath the cover I saw that turtle--
- There's turtle guts.
- And the hut dissipates.
You notice that you're surrounded by a few monkeys,
and one monkey king.
- That was my second guess.
Were they picking up the hut and moving it?
- No, 'cause when he steps outside the hut,
he's outside the area.
- Okay.
What is a monkey king?
Monkey is a big like, what if there's a monkey king?
There's a monkey and a monkey king.
And because for this session I'm focusing on us trying new things.
Uh huh.
And- Whoa!
Holy shit.
And because I left my stuff at home.
Don't tell me you have figurines.
Because I left my stuff at home.
Holy fuck.
Okay, which one's me?
What the heff?
Fire ass map, brother.
It's not a fire ass map, it's the worst thing I've ever done.
No, this is- we need a picture of this.
No, please don't take a picture.
No, we're taking-
I had no time.
Please I left my shit at home.
I'm gonna hide it.
I seriously won't take a picture.
You're gonna take a picture.
Why'd you make a...
Who's the green one?
You guys are the green guys.
There's only one green guy.
That's me, I'm a goblin.
I can be green, I'm a goblin.
There's three that look similar to me and there's four that look different from those three.
You're saying you look this color?
No I...
We were actually colorblind?
Yeah.
I didn't know that.
I'm so sorry.
It's fine.
I mean it's not...
I'm so sorry.
It's not the worst ever.
How the fuck are you...
I'm surprised you're alive.
You haven't killed yourself.
I mean I've thought about it but that's for a different time I guess.
Bro you just made it dark as fuck.
So yeah.
I call green guy.
Yeah roll initiative.
Green goblin.
Oh I'm so excited.
13 plus my initiative, but 14 so...
I got a 37.
You got a crit one?
I mean a 38.
I can't believe that.
Forgot to add my bonus.
You can't believe that?
That is some horseshit.
I hate that number.
One.
Patrick reacts.
That is, I can keep that number.
That is some horse shit.
I hate that number.
Patrick reacts to numbers.
What did you get, Caleb?
I got a 14.
And what did you get, Caleb?
38.
How many dice do you have?
Come on, bro.
18.
You don't need a more than 8.
You don't need to pick them as you need to be careful.
Yeah, but I like to have them.
Don't worry about it.
Okay, well, I don't, I mean, you have the whole, all of them.
And then Patrick.
I have all of them.
Yeah, you got all of them.
That's a good check.
That's Mr. Kitty Pop Star, and then that over here is evil.
Patrick reacts to colors.
And this is, unfortunately for you guys, a news item.
And then that over here is evil.
Patrick reacts to colors.
And this is, unfortunately for you guys, a surprise round.
No.
So, if I had expected this and said, "Oh, we're definitely surrounded by monkeys and a monkey king,"
it would not have been a surprise round, right?
I don't know. I guess.
I really determined that. So, yeah, if that happened, maybe it wouldn't have been a surprise round.
Nice.
[LAUGHTER]
That's a nice thought.
Is that what happened?
Nice.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
The first thing that happens--
This entire code field was spilled on me earlier, and I caught it really quick.
He just keeps crying about this.
Nobody saw--
I saw it.
You saw how quick I caught it?
Yeah, I don't think it was spilling on you, though.
No, it was just spilling towards Caleb.
Also, it was almost completely--
What do you mean it was going towards me?
I saw it.
The spout was towards me.
The liquid flew.
Flew onto Caleb, in fact.
I'm wet with it.
All right.
This is okay by the way, I'm like moving the mic around a lot. Oh my god
You are being
What
Okay, I've had a busy few weeks and I wanted to do a lot of different stuff for this session
I didn't have a lot of time to prep
But I have enough time to do
I think pretty much everything
I can't even look at it
It's so shitty
It's the worst thing I've ever done
I'm so sorry
I need to make you guys new character sheets, organize the cards
I wanted to have a battle today, and then I was like fuck I didn't make a map. All good. It's it so
It's going on Pat's be real right now, that's right
Okay, so let's do this shit. Alright, let's do this shit.
So the monkeys are gonna go first. You see the monkey king
Gesture and all of them you see jump into these holes
that they've dug up.
Wait, what?
Um, M-K-M-M, that's all the holes.
Monkey, no, that's monkey, monkey, king, monkey.
Oh, got it, got it.
Monkey, monkey, king, monkey.
Monkey, monkey, king, king, monkey.
And then the king is going to cast--
Can you describe the king visually?
Yeah, sorry.
I should have done that.
No, no worries, I'm just very curious.
I think I would.
So the king is, the king is kind of baboon-esque.
He has like the uh, the long face with those blue and white stripes all along his face.
Uh, and he has a wreath made of uh, bamboo.
A wreath?
Not like a, uh, like a crown.
A sheath?
Around his head.
Yeah.
Um, what?
What is sheath?
Sheath or a wreath?
A wreath.
I mean, does he have a red spurting anus?
He does have a red spurting anus.
Aww, fucking...
When he casts this spell, you can see it faintly glowing behind him.
Um...
Weak spot.
If I know anything about video games, that's a weak spot.
An anus is everyone's weak spot.
Mm-hmm.
That's not true.
Video games taught me that.
It's a really good place to get shot.
In the asshole?
Not the hole, but in the ass.
The anus, though, I say.
My asshole is a good place for a penis.
[laughs]
That's good, man.
What the fuck?
Wait, what?
So...
And so, let's roll some dice.
What ones do you want?
D20, as always.
Okay, and...
Okay, and your AC...
My AC?
Your AC, yeah.
I got a...
It's 18.
Okay, yeah, so you're gonna be able to dodge this.
I got a 19 on my roll.
I mean, you didn't have to roll.
But I got to --
Well, that's great.
I mean, we can use that another time.
But he shoots -- he waves a staff around and he points it towards
you, and his red anus glows in the back.
And you see a bolt come out.
It's like lightning, and it's like black.
It looks like a black lightning.
And then like as it's approaching you,
it almost turns into a flame.
But you're able to pretty quickly get out of the way of
it coming towards you.
And then the ape is going to also then -- the baboon is going
sort of start to run towards you guys and then jump into that king hole.
And now we're at the top of the order.
The surprise round is over.
Okay.
And you're up, Dogen.
Alright.
I'm going to walk up.
Can I walk to this king hole?
You certainly can.
Okay, I'm going to walk right up to the edge of the king hole here.
And I'm going to use my big oar ability to just pump water in there.
Cool.
There's a huge wave of water down into the hole.
I wish we had some kind of liquid metal ability and make one of those ant hill statues.
Monkey Hill.
Yeah.
Not your turn, Patrick.
Yeah. Not your turn, Patrick.
So the big ore attack, if you look at your other page,
you'll see what it is.
It should be listed there.
It's not.
It's not, but it's right here.
Yeah. I mean, it's just a range attack.
So just roll a d20 and add your dex plus your proficiency.
Okay.
Which will be plus 3, I think, and then plus 2?
Plus 1. So that's 11.
Okay. Go at 11. Yeah.
So you shoot that like wave of ore.
That ore.
You like whap it against the wall of the hole.
Yeah. I'm massaging the edge of this hole with my ore.
And as the --
And I'm filling it with liquid.
As you're filling it with water.
A wave.
It's spurting into the hole.
It's filling it.
A little bit's dribbling out.
Most of it just fills up on the hole, overflows, and then sort of spills out along the rest
of the ground and the sand and dirt kind of around you.
And then some of it squirts out of each of these monkey holes.
Dude, right in the eyes.
You just stuck the landing on.
hole. Some of it squirts out of each of the monkey holes. I squirted into the king hole
and all the other holes just cream pining out. And roll for damage, which should be
2d8 I believe. I think you guys, if Patrick was able to share his dice this would be a
That's going to be a lot easier.
Still pretty good.
Six.
Okay, cool.
So, yeah, you hear the faint groan of monkeys from elsewhere.
After you do that.
Groan?
Faint groan.
Yeah, can you demonstrate?
Right?
Something like that.
Okay, cool.
Also, though, on your turn, after you do that, though,
the monkeys jumps out of this hole and shoots the same thing as that other monkey, the king
monkey you shot at, and misses also.
That's right.
And goes back into the hole.
His legs are shaking too hard.
That's right.
Oh my god, he can barely walk after squirting.
Yeah, yeah.
Holy fuck.
And now, uh...
His mascara's running...
[LAUGHTER]
It's got long acrylic nails.
Yeah.
Is it my turn?
No, it's the monkey's turn, actually.
And so the king monkey pops out of this hole
and goes over to swing at you, Mr. Cutie Pop Star.
Oh, no.
You sounded like Cleveland.
That definitely hits you.
I sounded more like Cleveland.
Hey guys, it's me, Drake.
He deals 8 damage to you.
8?
Yeah.
As he sort of batters you with his...
Motherfucker?
You just did an earnest motherfucker?
I've never heard that from you.
Motherfucker.
Under your breath.
It's another Patrick reacts to numbers.
something crazy is happening
something is weird
the electrical field in this room
that's why the recorder turned off earlier
he's gonna hit you again
me?
yeah
for another 13 damage
he's just beating the shit out of you
god damn
holy shit you're getting fucked by these monkeys
you're getting rammed
now it's your turn
can I use my action?
I have one non-attack action, right?
Uh, yeah, you can like... well, so it depends.
Like, you can... you have like a free action to say something.
Like, you can definitely do that. You can use an action, and then if you have a bonus action...
Can I only say something?
Uh, you can say something and then take...
Can I do like a check or anything?
Um, I'll let you do a check, yeah.
Can I do... we're on an island, right?
Yes.
Can I do an investigation check really quickly?
Investigation typically is like a... you can do like an insight check.
Can I do an insight check? I just want to see if there...
there
okay
i'll i'll i'll tell you you have to do a check you know there is a banana
Banana tree.
Roll banana magnet.
You have that in your cards.
Banana tree is over here.
I saw that earlier.
You have banana magnet in your cards.
Oh my god, a banana tree.
That must be why they're here.
Oh, you better use banana magnet.
I don't have...
I'm looking through my snow book.
I don't have banana magnet.
No, you definitely have.
I remember when you learned about the magnet.
Well, there it is.
There it is.
Banana magnet.
The banana magnet tree.
The banana tree is over here.
It's a magnet tree.
And the tree is also made of magnets.
Can I go up and hold my knife?
Do I have a knife?
I can't hold my knife to it.
You should have a dagger.
If I didn't put it in there you should have one.
I'm going to hold my dagger to the banana tree's trunk like I'm holding a hostage.
Like I'm going to slit its throat.
If you do, the only thing is that you will provoke an attack from this guy.
He's gonna hit his fucking gun in the tree.
No, he'll hit you.
If you're leaving his...
I'll dodge it, asshole.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Okay.
Use disengage.
So you can use, yeah.
You can use a disengage action.
Thank you.
Yeah.
I don't know why he didn't tell you you could use that.
He wants to see you fail.
Well, the only thing is that...
I mean, you're not gonna attack or anything, right?
You're just gonna threaten the tree?
I'm just gonna threaten the tree.
Yeah, so you can use disengage.
Don't take one single fucking step closer...
or else your banana tree will be cut.
I'll cut a hole in it.
- And I've seen this guy kill the child before.
(laughing)
- You can roll deception with advantage.
- I've definitely killed,
Evil Steve has definitely killed a child before.
- Roll again with advantage.
- I think we probably did kill a child like during this.
- You've definitely killed a child.
- Yeah, that's 25.
- Okay, cool.
So they definitely believe that,
so you see, as he says that,
You see two of the monkeys come out of this hole,
pop their heads out over here.
And one monkey can look its head out of this hole.
And as you say that,
you're like, "Let's go over to see what you're saying."
- That's right, I will cut a little,
I'm not sure that I can cut the whole tree in half right now,
but I will cut like a little line on it,
or I will carve my initials.
- Just like my eyebrow.
- I will carve my initials,
plus Cutie Pop Star's initials in a heart.
- Roll intimidation.
with probably advantage
I got a 15 and a cure 1 so I'll take the 15
yeah you will take the 15
and then
let's just try this
yeah alright cool
you see the monkey king trying to gesture to the monkeys
like trying to calm them down
like pointing to his ass
like it's fine
you see the monkeys are actually kind of worried
You see the monkeys are actually kind of worried.
One of them kind of crawls out and goes up to you to try to get you to stop.
I tighten my grip on the banana tree.
Slow your roll there.
Banana, or no, monkey.
While this is going on, can I just look, I just remembered that...
I'm mostly just trying to distract him for you guys.
We're going to kill these monkeys.
So one of them is out here.
I had a move.
I have a man is a lure what you have managed to do is lure one of them out and it's pretty
distracted the other two are like the other two are still peeping out of the hole and
haven't like been fully like and what time of the year what pretty right there grape
bananas okay rape bananas they're grape bananas just a little bit of green at the top a couple
spots you know a few spots yeah ready to go banana bread territory yes no no no I just
Let's have a quick, before the next action.
Do we know what was going on when we saw the sky whizzing by?
Have we figured out what that meant?
Did you?
Well, when we came outside, was it still...
Yes, we already did. We're on a turtle shell.
Is it still going? Like, would we see...
Here's what I can tell you. Yeah, so what you're seeing, you're still seeing the sky whizzing by.
I would say that now that you've gotten out, and you can peer a little bit over the...
Can you hear me still?
Yeah, but you should just still talk.
Sorry.
As you can peer out over, like, a shallow, like, hill.
you're kind of like up a little bit on the island,
you peer over a shallow--
- Run up that lady's ass.
- You can see that the water is whipping by
at a speed that is like insane to you.
Like if you dipped your hand in it,
it would like come off kind of fast.
- We'll figure that out later.
I was just curious.
I just thought we would have been able to see that
and I wanted to know what was up.
- 'Cause I got these monkeys by the bananas
and I wanna see them squirm into there.
I wanna see their holes squirt squirming kids.
That's right, we're gonna abuse those monkeys' holes.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Yeah, so uh...
Whose turn is it? It is now your turn.
I'm gonna use um, dissonant whispers.
Oh, describe that to me.
So you whisper a discordant...
Say that in drag, say "dissonant whispers."
Dissonant whispers.
You whisper a discordant melody that only one creature of your choice within range can hear.
Racking it with terrible pain.
This doesn't sound like you.
This doesn't sound like him, this is a bad image.
The target must make a wisdom saving throw on a failed save, blah blah blah.
How much damage will it take?
That's the important part.
It'll do 3d6 psychic damage.
It must immediately use a reaction if available to move as far as its speed allows away from
you.
The creature doesn't move into obviously dangerous grounds such as fire or a pit.
a successful save, the target takes half as much damage and doesn't have to move away.
A deafened creature automatically succeeds in the save.
So here's what I would say to you.
Well I was going to use that on the king.
Yep, because if it runs away from you, you get an attack of opportunity also.
So I was going to do that.
Perfect.
So he's going to make a wisdom saving throw.
Your spell DC, what is it?
I think it's 15.
It should be on the other page if it's on this one.
On the top of the other page.
Oh yeah, it's on the other page.
Yep, okay.
I knew it.
I want you to see it though.
Okay, it's wisdom.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, it's not that good. So he does fail.
Yeah. So roll for damage. 3d6. The Monkey King is not wise.
He is just a monkey. He's a king of a dinky little...
He's a king of a... He's not the real... He's not like a real monkey king.
Two fives and a six? Wow, holy crap. That's 16 damage.
That makes 16. Woo! Okay.
Motherfucker! So now, and we'll...
And now Dissonant Whispers, what level spell is that?
is, oh I'm going to use it in the second level.
Okay, so you're going to add another D6 to that.
Yeah.
That's four.
That's very good, that's still 20.
So, second level, then that means you take out a second level of your spell slots,
that's on the second page.
We won't worry too much about that, I can keep that, like, track of that, really, this session probably.
But we're going to start getting you used to tracking that.
I didn't get to go over that with you yet, so don't worry too much about it.
But I'll keep tracking it over here.
So, these two dots right here?
The two dots, so these, this is like first level spells.
Sorry.
Second level spells, third level spells.
So right now you should have...
This whole thing filled out?
No, no, no, you'll fill out one of these right now.
You'll fill these whole things?
Yes.
There you go.
So, now.
Now that you've done that, and the king is now afraid of you,
so he's going to try to run, which means you have an attack of opportunity.
Can I say what I told him?
Oh, absolutely. What's the melody you whispered?
And what was it?
I know you don't wipe that ass.
You see the king get like really bashful and go, "No man, no man!"
He's like very upset.
Wait, do the other monkey... Wait, can I address the other monkey real quick?
You address the one who's in front of you.
So do you... So, he's embarrassed. Does that mean that you are wiping your ass as a monkey?
Why did I even try to do that?
of these monkeys like their asses
yeah i've been on the whole area and then they're
so yeah uh... and now do an attack role
so you have a rapier you can use what
sills that's really
uh... i've got a lot of that i'm not just a bit uh... it is going to give you a
different weapon after this
you've rolled into a d_n_a_ was i think we got started on sets in this campaign
nineteen
was
okay nice
the pre-k_c_a_c_ stabby as is running away holding its but you poke it right
the but
so
rate
just
and
monkey jumps out and claps its hands really loud and makes like a thundering clap.
I'm going to clap you monkey!
And he jumps back into the hole and disappears.
Now you can't do anything with it Pat.
Also no one can hear you so I sound crazy or unusual.
So you want to attack this guy or what?
Yeah I'm going to whack a mole on his head.
That is a...
Where's my attack stuff?
or
I mean you don't have a shield so.
Okay, that is 5 damage.
And I'm just going to whack them all again.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's 9 damage.
Nice.
Okay, so you do another, you do a good hefty amount of damage to this guy.
This monkey is still alive.
He's 12, but he's not looking too good.
And now it is.
Does he have a looney tunes on his head?
Yeah, you know that.
know that. It looks like a dash roll but it's on his head. Yeah, two of them. And now, three,
two of them, ones. Two ones. Two ones on his head. That monkey is going to try to attack
you back though. I gave him two ones. Okay, he does hit you, but he just barely hits you.
Okay, he does nine damage to you. And then another monkey is going to jump out of this
This
What's your HP right now?
Seven.
Uh oh.
You're fine right now.
Uh oh, does another five damage to you.
You're not looking too good.
Oh no, oh no, I need help, I need help so bad.
Oh no, I'm dying, I'm dying, oh no, no.
And this other one's gonna jump out and go after you, and is gonna run for the tree right
now.
So he's not-
I sliced the tree.
As a reaction?
You could use it as a reaction, I'll let you like, start to like dig your dagger into the
the tree.
Yeah, I, I, and a banana tree as far as I know is pretty fucking thin.
Yes.
So I'm going to just, I'm going to slide it all the way through.
You're going to cut it down.
Yeah, I'm chopping this down.
Okay.
The monkey goes, "Whaaaaaat?"
George Washington.
As you cut, cut it down, and it gets distracted and runs away from you and towards the tree.
Yeah.
As it's falling down, so it doesn't attack you.
And the monkey king now is going to jump back into this hole and go away.
And now it's your turn, Evil.
Okay.
Um, I think that I...
So there's one monkey that is looking... that is near me.
Yeah, he's looking towards his fallen tree.
He's sort of wailing like an old Italian woman at a funeral in Sicily.
Okay.
That's interesting.
You know what that's like.
I'm going to do...
I'm going to do Vampiric Touch.
Hell yeah. Tell us what that does.
The touch of your shadow-wreathed hand can siphon life force from others to heal your wounds.
Make a melee spell attack against a creature within your reach.
On a hit, the target takes 3d6 necrotic damage and you regain hit points equal to half the amount of necrotic damage dealt.
Until the spell ends, you can make the attack again on each of your turns as an action.
Hell yeah.
Okay.
So, make that attack roll.
You see, it should be a kicker add plus 6 to it.
Okay, so it's a 20 now.
It's a 20?
Yeah.
Alright, that does... so you go over to this monkey that was...
You go over to the monkey that was running away from you?
Mm-hmm.
Or do you go over to the...
I get that fucking piece of shit.
Yeah.
That's me right there?
Yeah, that's you.
Okay.
Okay, I kill him.
You go over to that monkey and you use this attack on him.
So roll for damage on it.
So it should be on the top there.
I think I put it...
3d6 is what it is.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Let's do all ones. Yeah, why not? I'm in Rome.
I got a 1, 3, and a 6. That's not bad. What if we turn the 6 upside down?
That's a 9. That's still pretty good. It's still a 10. Let's turn that 6 upside down.
And you also gain 7 HP back. I'm gonna turn the 3 upside down.
You haven't taken any damage. So nothing happens there. But you can now
continually use that as your attack, as it said. And now we're gonna go to
Is it my turn? Your turn. Okay, so you said that I get
get as a bard I get one of these. Yes, bardic inspirations. Like a feat, yeah. I also may
also have. Does enthralling performance count as. So enthralling performance you would use.
That's a full move? No, it's no it's more like it's more like in a roleplay situation
you would do a performance and then like at the end of it people could maybe be charmed.
Okay, because I have an eye perfect. But that takes like a minute, it has to be like a minute
of
Oh my god.
You can change- He saw the bananas on the tree!
That's not how a changing works.
Uh uh.
No, I got it wrong.
No no no no no.
I'm changing into the form of a banana.
No!
That you met before.
Oh you kid.
That I've met before.
Peanut butter jelly time.
Absolutely.
Who sang one of the- You knew right away.
Peanut butter jelly time?
Who sang one of the greatest songs I've ever heard.
And I look at the monkeys and I say- I mean you're making it hard for me to say no to
And I do peanut butter jelly time.
You think so? You think I should?
Yeah, have a little bit of self respect.
Alright, well now it feels like the self respect I should have is to let him do it.
You think so?
No, that's...
I guess not.
Yeah, no, I mean, I'll let you turn into a peanut butter jelly time banana, but that's not going to have any effect on anything.
Well, except for his fucking yellow skin.
He'll look cool.
look cool.
Ok, Barton, I will still use enthralling performance.
No because that's going to take a minute of time.
So what you can do, you just have to pick something you can do.
So you have a few-
What do you mean I can't do that?
I wish I could fall asleep on command.
So you can do that, but it takes a minute of game time.
Oh it takes a minute for me to prepare you?
Yes.
I thought you meant it takes a minute for me to do the whole performance.
Even then, the turn is six seconds.
I'll cover my body in banana and they'll jump on me ravenously for one full minute and you
can prepare.
No, no, I know what I'm doing.
You also have like spells.
I'm going to use bardic inspiration.
Yes, you can do that as well.
That's like a good bonus action thing to do.
You can use mantle of inspiration.
Look at your spell list and see.
I'm going to cast invisibility.
Okay, I like that.
Because I'm so low in health.
That's a good move.
I'm casting invisibility, but...
Wow.
It's like the opposite of becoming a banana.
Yeah.
He became a banana and then turned invisible.
[LAUGHTER]
We're just like, OK.
All right.
That didn't make a lot of sense.
So then I'll use Bardic Inspiration
because they can hear me, right?
Yes, they'll be able to hear you.
OK, so invisible banana sings to you.
Like, we're all looking at him.
It's his turn.
[LAUGHTER]
He turns into a banana and then he's gone.
And then we only see him as a banana for like the equivalent of one frame.
It's like a subliminal message.
Yeah, exactly.
Tyler Durden.
As a banana.
So then I'm gonna...
Anybody within 60 feet of me, if they hear me, I can give them a die for an ability check
at that roller saving throw.
So you're up next in the rotation?
I think so.
Yes.
On your next turn I'll give you...
Give him a D8 for an attack roll.
What do you say?
You became a banana and you disappeared and then we hear your disembodied voice.
It's P!
Yeah it is, yeah.
I knew it, that's all I said.
It's P!
It's P?
Wait, what's P?
Oh my god, the stuff coming out of the monkeys holes is P!
This work is P!
Oh my fucking god.
But you are inspired by this, Dogen.
inspired by this dogan yeah I'm not only so now you know what to do pnm or monkeys
okay I know how to do a crazy attack yeah it's P that's how it's big so I mean
this is good because you can use it for an attack role it's squirt but also
also
it
like
of
This turn though, you'll be able to use that.
And I think that should break invisibility though if you do an attack.
But that'll be perfect because it'll gain your health back.
So we're back to the top of the order.
Dogen.
Okay.
I'll just whack a mole again because I have the bonus on my attack roll.
Hell yeah.
Whack a monkey, I should say.
You should say that.
I should say that.
You're going to have to say that.
I'm not going to, but I should say it.
What do I roll to give him the bonus?
Well now, okay, it's a good thing you gave me that bonus.
So I need a D8.
He gets to roll a D8.
Not you.
Not you, Pat.
He's got it.
That was very useful and that does make sure that's a 15 total.
Yeah, that hits now.
That's why Barak's version's great.
That's why it's great.
Okay, that's 11 damage.
That's great. Two.
Is he dead? That monkey is almost dead.
Okay, I'll attack again then.
Do I get to add the D8 to... he talks?
He just said "please."
Please, please.
He just talked.
it
I mean, he's scared.
Okay, I'll just hit him again.
Yeah, go for it.
Do I get to add the DA both times?
No, no, no.
Okay, yeah, that hits. I mean, he's dead.
How do you kill him?
Can I whack him on the head so hard that he goes down?
Yes.
Down into the hole and then he shoots up out of another hole and he fly up.
And there's squirt leaking out of his butt from earlier as he goes.
And it's like it's raining when he flies away.
So
to be top one feelings on your penis.
No.
Is there anything else you want to do?
Even better than fucking sex.
For me, it's the jizz.
I think that's all my action. I guess I can move.
It's jizz!
Come on, stop.
Pat wants to hear the kids sing that.
Oh, bonus actions.
Yeah, I mean, I...
Yeah, you're just gonna chill.
I'll walk over to the next bunkie.
No, I won't. I'll let him come to me.
Okay. You are up now, monkeys.
That's right. Let him come on me.
The king monkey hops out.
Other way around. Other way around.
The king monkey hops.
Let me come on him.
Let me come.
I'm not going to you. I'm letting me come on you.
What?
The king monkey hops out and starts to slam the ground like Donkey Kong.
And you guys feel the ground shift underneath you.
Slam that monkey with my donkey cock.
Monkey
crit 1. So he's going to swipe at you and then also like move at a range and then give you
an opportunity to attack with that 1. That was cool. Okay that's a 23. Yeah that hits.
That's an 11. Nice. Okay. That king monkey is not. Spank him. That king monkey is not
looking good. He's looking good to me. I'm going to put these up against him. Good enough
He's a banana.
Good enough to...
That monkey you did vampiric touch to is gonna try to grab you back.
Bro, you look good enough to squirt on.
What's up?
You did fucking terribly.
You gotta try one more time.
You're terrible at grabbing.
Let me show you how a real monkey grabs.
Or no, I guess I'm not a monkey.
Okay, I'll just...
Oh, God.
And that's how I grab my penam up against a banana tree.
I see that and I go...
The other monkey is trying to throw a doo-doo at you, Cameron.
I eat the doo-doo.
God, he's missing.
I catch the doo-doo in it.
All the monkeys fucking just whiff.
Can I catch the doo-doo in my mouth?
No, it's your turn though.
Okay.
Throw the doo-doo at my...
[laughter]
Try to knock my teeth out with it like a carnival game.
Um...
I mean, when it's my turn.
Okay.
Well, for now, I guess I'll just fuck this monkey.
Are you gonna try to fuck them? No, I'm gonna finger him with the chill touch. Mm-hmm
Like I remember what that does. Yeah, so it allows you to touch them chilly and you can roll
Roll d20
Okay, 1d8 necrotic damage, but I'll cast it at a higher
Mm-hmm
Where are you up casting it?
20 as a crit. What do you up cast it to the third?
level. So that's adding how many d8? Two more or three more? None. None more? Yeah it doesn't
increase until you get to the fifth level. Oh no, so this is um... Okay you're stealing
my cards now. No so once you reach the fifth level it does 2d8 damage because it's a cantrip.
So you're just going to do 2d8 damage but spells do have crits until, I know D&D changed it
but it does.
That's not a D8.
You're right.
It's the, yeah, it's like two triangles.
It's the one with eight sides.
Yeah.
So you roll that four times now.
Four?
That's a three, that's a six, that's a two, and that's an eight.
That monkey's dead.
You just like grabbed that, you fingered that monkey to death.
I fingered the monkey until he's fucking dead.
It's like, as you're fingering it, and it's like looking at the fallen banana tree, and
like eyes are just going wide with fear and sorrow.
And it spurts jizz out.
And then it calms.
Like when a dead body shoots shit.
Yeah, but except for this monkey, it's jizz.
Yeah.
Bye-bye, jizz monkey.
Jizz in my pants.
Yeah.
Yes!
Still in the banana form.
In the final--
You're invisible.
Yeah, but I'm still in banana form.
The final monkey?
The final monkey--
The final monkey.
Is the King Monkey still alive?
Oh no, both of them are done. All their turns are done.
Yeah, the King Monkey is still alive.
It is your turn.
I want to interrogate the King Monkey.
I'm not going to give you that chance.
You can use the bludder.
I want to see him sharing stone base against me while I'm interrogating him.
So roll a d20 and add your dex.
Plus proficiency.
My dexterity is 13.
So it's a plus 1 and then we're going to add your proficiency, plus 3, so it's a plus 4.
You're all proficient with firearms.
And who are you shooting by the way, the monkey or the king?
I'm this far...
Probably that one right there.
Yeah, okay, you mean you hit him with a .14?
Uh-huh.
It's a now roll...
Oh shit, I don't have my stats.
I wish I remembered what I wrote for the bludder, because I don't have it now because I left my computer at home.
Let's say it does like a million damage.
does
monkeys
aids
he can't remember the numbers he doesn't get to keep you said he was dead
you say he's dead it doesn't matter
you get eleven points of health back
yeah we'll say that
you know let's go with track
moving on
i mean i think you track it becomes an actual issue where you start to die
all the sudden
but uh...
now i don't want to answer i i i'm stomp strutting myself on what i'm
strutting up to the king monkey
push 'em down the ground missionary
hit 'em with my shovel
Right on the belly.
Alright, roll, roll attack roll.
That is a 17.
That hits.
That's 5 damage.
Okay.
He's still alive.
Alright, flip him over monkey style.
Okay.
Sick.
That's a 13.
That does not hit.
Alright.
That's fine.
So you just flip him over.
He's sitting on all fours, looking back at you.
(laughter)
come on
which is going to go attack who
okay
you know we've had those
that's reasons in the that's right i have fixed that
uh... many missus he missed not happen again
uh... never touch machine every that's it's true i'm not
and is your turn now
I will just kick him.
What's in a name?
Alright, yeah, you're going to kick him, you're going to do an unarmed attack.
Do an unarmed attack, just to disrespect him.
Okay, so that's going to be just roll a d20 and add your strength, which is I think a -1, or a zero.
I got a 3.
to
you find it
uh... yeah that's it and then you're up now checking
your visible by the way
on visible now okay uh... so there's still been a
no
you turn back from a turns out
you know what i do it is obviously to open it
you quickly to
and then because i don't know because it's a it's an eyelash in case the gum arabic
in the eyelashes from people
the original
here
arabic stuff
on the news
hello section
mhm wailing word
uh... you can use creature of my choice that you can see within range of gains
hit points to equal... oh well I can't use that on myself.
You can't use it on yourself.
Let's kill this monkey king so we can move on and funderstand why the island is moving.
We need to find the funderstand.
I will use vicious mockery.
Why don't we just offer this monkey king some snippets.
You unleash a string of insults laced with subtle enchantments at a creature you can
see within range.
The target can hear you, though it need not understand you.
must succeed on a wisdom saving throw or take 1d4 damage and have disadvantage on the next
attack roll before it hits the next turn.
So it did succeed on the wisdom saving throw, but what did you say?
I see a little bit of poop on your butt.
Yeah, that's probably why it failed.
He didn't even know what it was.
Yeah, he's sorry to shrugs.
He's like, I'm a fucking ape.
Okay, so with my bonus action.
you
inspiration
is
a_t_d_ i would say you're better off using just part of inspiration because
mantle of inspiration to try the new york people
yeah i think you're going on and you're if you're thinking of giving me some
protection right now and i thank you
i don't need protection like that but maybe like some spicy blue or something
okay so if you say this little slow with tamarind
and show more
and that i mean and this description of the lube
inspires you
uh... so now you have a d_n_a_
using its tackle which is
maybe now ok
it's your turn
uh... you can get it at your advantage but if you're flanking
okay uh...
yelled as a uh... this polarizing ramon
market
what's up you can ram him the other ram him
okay and i've advantage and see if you can
tonight i guess i would are quick was the first number of the truth
yes if i wrote this could i get a critters that count as you know
all right then you know both of them
because was a plus like five plus five people in the midst of a year ago
do it
that's uh... six damage
director will get the next attack of the
with
Okay, that's a 20. Not a natural 20.
30-20.
That's... yeah, so okay, that hits him, right?
That hits. I'm gonna tell you you're gonna kill him.
Okay, that's 4 damage.
That kills him.
Can we Pukaki his corpse?
Yeah.
Sure.
Yeah, and I hit his... I was whacking his nuts too.
I didn't want to say it while he was alive.
Oh, mama!
I put a banana in his tailpipe.
Arrooga!
He's dead.
I'm just masturbating in the corner.
You freak!
Get in here! Yo, get in here!
here
You guys defeated the monkeys.
I take his crown, I put it on.
Okay, yeah, you put it on.
Oh my god, you're the monkey king now.
I take what I think is his crown, but it's his asshole.
When you put that wreath on, you feel like you maybe have advantage against wisdom saving
throws.
Whoa.
Holy crap.
Add that to your inventory.
That's right.
Oh my god, wait.
This monkey's got a, he's got special stats on his stuff.
I take his eyeballs out and put them in my mouth.
You just have eyeballs in your mouth.
I'm stronger!
I cut his butt off and I tape it to my butt.
The butt does seem magical, but
right now it's just one...
So the monkey crown has an advantage on wisdom?
Is it acrylics?
Wait, wait, what does he cast his spells with?
His asshole.
His staff was his spell casting focus.
Yeah, you can add the monkey staff to your inventory.
It's just a spell casting focus.
add um it adds plus one damage to any range spell attacks you use with the staff if you
use it as a spellcaster.
I'm gonna knock all his teeth out.
But this is an advantage on wiz saves?
Yes.
With their prowler but maybe I'll get a dollar from the two fairy.
He can save himself from my wizzer.
So yeah you guys uh after defeating the monkey.
So just add the monkey staff and write plus one range and I'll remember what that is.
I put the monkeys face in the water.
You put the monkeys face?
Yeah uh as you lower its head in the raging seas.
Let's see just how fast this puppy's going.
And you pull it up and you see the skeleton of the monkey.
That's how you measure speed, is if you can touch a monkey to the ground and it turns
into a skeleton.
That means you're going really fast.
That means it's going exactly 900 miles per hour.
We are going at breakneck speeds right now.
And just as you guys are starting to feel settled, playing with the corpses that you
So oh before I
Yeah, I take the monkey's leg
Right, and then I I put it in like a bag
Okay, and I try to sue V didn't knew you were gonna do sue V'd. He said a bag
So what do you you're gonna? So yeah, we're trying to sue V. What's your sous vide set?
I do you're gonna see me in the shooting fast water
Where are you gonna sue V to you fuck in my head?
I think this works, but then all that happens is the plastic bag just like plastic. Where's the plastic plastic bag?
I made a plastic
made up plastic
That's something I invented because I was bored
And as you guys are fucking around with the monkeys body
You hear a terrible roar
Of something that has tracked you
For so far for so long and with one of your party dead feels that much more
Oh, I forgot about this fucking thing
He came all the way here the yeth town roll initiative
He came all the way here any flute and while the are the island was moving so fast you could get here
How did he get on to the island yeth town can teleport?
That's how we pour
And I got one initiative this game sucks. Oh, I got a better initiative. We need to distract patches
I got a 75 patches. What color are these?
Dark green or gray this is green. These are black really yeah, I
Got it
Yeah, I'm mentally it's real. I don't remember what your initiative role was it was a 20
Oh, okay, I guess you're going first. I got a new go 18. I guess you're going second
I got a 19 Caleb actually got a one. Oh, thank you. You're cuz I want to go first
You're like a little I go first. I want to go first. Just say you got 21
Okay, I got a 75. I mean and Caleb got you got a stop. There's no way
There's no way that can get to you. We should get one of those towers you do not get anything
I was thinking about getting the dice tower if you guys want to get the dice tower
What is that you like put it the dice in the tower it rolls down?
We do
We're like decisive rolls yeah
I bought this guy on tick-tock who rolls a d20 every time that he makes a sandwich and he makes it sandwich based off
My wife was telling me about that guy. Yeah, yeah, you made a really good sandwich
Yeah, he's something about she was talking about somebody does that with drinks where they like roll different dice
Drinks, which ended there's these two guys who bust myths on the Discovery Channel. Yeah
I heard there's a guy who I heard this this t-shirt that says there's a ninja on this t-shirt, but the t-shirts blind
You're up to good
I just like to enjoy stuff sometimes, you know
Okay, I run up to the F town. Am I gonna do am I in walk? Yes, you can
Yes, you remind me. What does the F town look like? It's a this yet. Town is like a giant dog with a man face
like an ugly furry man face
If you well, you wouldn't remember him because you weren't there
This is new to you. Yeah, this is new to me. Can you at least give me a
Can you give us a celebrity touchstone that would be maybe what what what the face looks like the most you said ugly and hairy
Like Nick Nolte. I knew you're gonna say either Nolte or Busey. Yeah, Busey. No Busey's like too comical
Like okay, he's a little more. He's hanged on
Is the dog hanging dog can we see it
Yeah, yeah ten inches but for him that's kind of small yeah
That's weird.
He's fucking huge, right?
How tall is he?
He's like, you know, 20 feet.
10 inches.
He's the second embarrassed enemy today.
Is he neutered?
Is the yeth hound neutered?
What do you think?
Yes.
If it's got a 10-inch or not.
Most certainly.
Okay, well I'm trying to think about my dog knowledge as a dog owner.
Maybe try the banana tree.
Is there a bone tree?
I don't know.
No.
Can I go pee real quick?
Yeah.
You can go ahead, it's my turn.
He's taking his phone into the bathroom.
But you have to take the bathroom pass.
Take the bathroom pass. Take the hall pass.
Thank you.
Alright.
You have to return it.
Okay.
He took the girls pass!
What did he say?
a
be crazy. And then I guess I will use my divine smite. Which I think I have 4 spell slots
right? Yes. So I will use one of them to use this divine smite. So it should be adding 2
the
which is 11. Nice. And then I have another attack. Okay, cool. So it's 11 plus 6, that's
17. No, it's just 11. I added everything. You added the 6? Oh, okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll take the 17. No, don't you do that. Okay, so that's 7. Okay, yeah, that doesn't add.
Yeah. But, okay, cool. So you slam your oar against the side of the Yath Hound and then
Patrick didn't bring the bathroom pass back from the bathroom.
This radiant light, sort of with water swirling around it, like from your water god, crashes
into the side of the, once you make impact, and just like blasts it.
It was a good hit, but he's still up and he's looking fine, ultimately.
And it is now your turn, Chuggie, the singing submarine, aka Mr. Cutie Patootie.
I'm Cutie right now, not Chuggie.
I mean if you're Chuggie, you're just a giant submarine, you can't do anything.
If he's 20 feet, oh right, because I'm on an island.
I was going to say if he's 20 feet, Chuggie's 30 feet.
Yeah, but Chuggie can't do nothing.
I'm going to fucking sat on him.
Well, I guess we did give you weird...
I sat on him and buried him in my asshole.
You could eat him. You could just open your mouth and swallow him whole.
Exactly.
your
Why don't you attack with your blutter?
Does the blutter cost anything to attack?
He can do that blutter move three times a day.
So you just roll an attack roll and add your decks.
Oh, I forgot it's supposed to do dot.
But that monkey would have died anyway.
in
Okay, so then with the bonus move...
So you shoot the blutter and the bullet flies by
and like a helix of blood sort of like trails behind it.
We should just try to escape again.
This guy's too fucking...
He's too annoying.
He's too much... we need a cat to defeat this thing.
We can just dive underwater.
Oh.
We can't, Chuggy.
You saw what happened to that monkey's face.
Oh, fuck you.
You make everything hard.
Then we'll fly up in the way.
the
last four minute uh... airplane
no
i think i got a very upset with my life you are getting i think i think we believe
you know that it is that
it is very funny
okay well i guess we'll just
or you can you can try to fight back
It is the Yeth Hounds turn though and he is going to attack you, Dogen, so if you go for
him.
My abilities.
Oh yeah, that's going to hit you.
So he's going to do a couple of things.
Okay.
Yikes.
That does 15 damage.
15?
Yeah.
Damn.
And he has marked you.
He marked me.
Which means he'll have a-
Bro, did he pee on me?
-attacks against you.
He's gonna attack you again.
I know what it means when a dog marks something.
Yeah, but he misses even though he marked you.
And you are now up, Steeble.
You have a number of spells in your freaking arsenal.
Yeah, I know.
I'm looking at them, asshole.
Okay.
I'm gonna use Guiding Bolt.
It's a great spell.
Why is the water going so fast?
We don't know.
We don't know, but basically I know that we're on a fucking giant ass turtle.
We're on some giant ass thing with all this...
It's a fucking sea turtle.
It's a yellow sea turtle.
It's a turtle.
If it's not a turtle, he changed it.
Yeah, he did change it.
He did not change it.
Okay, so I'm going to use guiding bowl.
Whatever it is, I didn't change it.
I got a five.
That's not going to...
It's not very good, is it?
No.
It's not good at all.
I'm going to take it easy.
Right?
Okay, so I pretty much just fucking sit there.
Yo, yo, chill.
We're going to go back to the top of the order and just wipe it out.
I start burying my feet in the sand.
Dogan, you are not.
Okay, I'm just going to swing again.
I'm just going to go through it.
He's going for it.
Yeah.
It's the only thing I know how to do in this world is be strong for my friends.
That's okay.
That's a 19.
Oh, a 19?
Sorry.
I thought I saw it.
It's a 24.
I'm sorry.
I thought I saw it wrong.
Bro, he said a 24 doesn't hit.
It does hit.
You hit.
Okay, I'm gonna do another Divine Smite.
Okay, that's 10 plus...
10 plus 5 is 15, plus 6 is 21, plus 2 is 23 damage.
And that's my first attack.
you just like fucking slam your oar against his side of him
you can feel the presence of your water god
no side conversations guys
presence of your water god burrowing down further into its flesh
just ripping it asunder
pretty good man
sorry i was just saying my mom used to think lubega was a ja rule
she used to think that was a ja rule song
a little bit
(laughter)
Pretty kinda funny.
You don't do apologize for that.
I had to break the news to her one day.
That's not Ja Rule, Ma.
(laughter)
That was a great attack, Cam.
Yeah, you have another attack.
Oh, that's a crit.
No shit, really?
Yeah.
Bruh.
Alright, roll, roll, uh, fuck.
I'll smite it too.
Yeah, roll the fuck.
Do I get to double the smite?
stupid shams. He said roll fuck. What the fuck does that mean? You fucking idiot. That means
roll a d6 because 6 rhymes with sex. No I don't think, I'm pretty sure with smite crit it
should just be you just add whatever the um. Put that smite crit on his white clit. Yeah
it
the
on
the Smite, that's 3d8. So that's 6d8 for the Smite. I'll start rolling the 3 and then you
tell me to start or stop.
I might as well. I'm almost positive it's what it is. I really have a rarity with which I
deal with critical hit Smites.
So that's 15 plus 1 is 16 plus 6 is 22.
Wow, that's crazy.
Plus 1 is 23. Do I get to double the Smite? I do. Oh my god.
Bro.
Plus 6 is -- what was the last number I said? 23?
23, yeah.
Uh, 31, 35 plus 2, 37 damage.
Bro, that "yes" sound is gone.
And I already, and that was, so this turn that was 50, that was 60 damage.
Describe your kill.
Holy shit.
Yeah!
I don't do, I just.
I didn't even have to hit it.
Yeah, you just regularly just kind of hit the guy.
I'm not even paying attention. I turned they went today. I heard I heard um Steve will say something about about medieval
What a general
Jaw ruler, and I turned to hear what he was saying and I turned in my
My my war or just hit him. What if he just?
Disappears he goes to a place where like no one's around so he'd die without anyone seeing yeah
Yeah, and I follow him wherever he goes
As he, uh, just this thing just like, fucking like it almost explodes in death, um, which
is fucking nutty as hell, um, it's vile groans stink of pain and an implacable salivating
envy.
Um, it's master blessed it with the good sense to know wounded prey, but, you know, it's kind
of, it's kind of, it's like.
As it tries to stand over you, its shadow giving context to maybe a certain...
This wasn't the idea that you guys didn't kill it, but you did.
This is crazy.
But either way, this is going to happen.
A faint hissing sound rings in your ears.
All of your ears.
But the instant you can meet the sound with comprehension, its origin wraps around the
neck of the yeth hound, but is slowly dying.
It is a tentacle, not unlike the one you saw those weeks ago when your adventure began.
Not you, Jack, but everyone else.
What the hell is that thing?
The hissing gives way to a rumble as a familiar white mist echoes the return of whatever this
creature is.
The F-hound, within that same moment of your appreciation, is yanked violently through the
trees and the island.
with the cracking
here's bodies
whapping up against
is the apple
that like something
uh... is a bit of pop
made of pulp
Let him read it.
No.
It's a pulpy puppy.
The mist rolls in further with a clear will.
This thing, whatever it is, this thing that had to reach out to you that last time, it
does live.
You have no time to act.
The thrust of the fog washes over you and lifts you along.
It fills your body and is tasteless and oppressive.
You live in like a new, it's like you're floating basically.
You feel very weightless, but you're completely paralyzed in this fog.
We're lost in a cloud.
[laughter]
As you're lost in a cloud.
The Yharb Sail.
And you catch a glimpse of what lies beyond.
The size of this thing can only be really seen now.
With no boat to steer or crew to captain, a yeth hound long devoured, now before you,
with the supernatural certainty that comes with seeing a thing, possessing a truly ancient
bearing, you know that this is a kaiju manji.
Long thought passed from this world, and while you can't make out its full form, you become
aware of it regarding you.
In floating amniotically through its haze, you're helpless.
But then, once it's done regarding you, it slowly removes itself.
The mist recedes over the island, and that low rumble follows in that hiss, and the tentacle
whips back.
And the island with the yellow sand holes suddenly comes to a stop, and you all kind of jerk
forward.
You all kind of jerk forward.
You raise your heads and you look.
You've made it to the outskirts of Post Port Loseberry, in a hidden cave along the shore.
So the island just took you there.
Then you hear one last cry as you deposit yourselves
Yeah, I'm ready I'm ready
As this yellow island rears its pretty eyelashes
By the holes
Can I and it goes back into the sea can I cast up of me
What?
What's up with me?
Nothing much homie, what's up with you?
Oh my god.
And you guys have made it finally to Berry Berry.
Wow.
Bye.
Spongebob.
Spongebob
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]
[music]