Avast ye landlubbers!
Blackbeard the Patch is here to tell you the story of three hearty lads, lords of the sea,
hailing all the way from Trebuchet village.
voyage. Brim with Darren Do's and Darren Don'ts. Wondrous woos and wobbly whoa whoa
whoa did you think I was done with you? Oh for that I should have you
crip walk the plank. That's right we're talking gangster pirates. Not the actual
setting or characters although that sounds cool now that I'm writing it but
an attitude because these three salty sea dogs have found themselves face to face
with their nemesis, Weirdbeard the pirate.
And they'll show him no quarter.
They'll blow the fiend down to dance with Jackie Ketch
seven nights a week at Davy Jones' Locker.
And Davy Jones' Locker has a three-drink minimum.
And all the drinks are poopy.
Trebuchet Village, Tales from the Seabomb,
Sinbad, Virtue Good, Ladybetter.
Roll for initiative!
Oh my fucking god, we're in here, huh?
That was a high energy intro.
I got a 17.
That was honestly a very high energy intro.
That was so high energy.
This is so cool.
I got a 6.
Do I add to the initiative score?
Oh, then I got a 20.
I got a 19.
And what did you get Cam?
6.
Don't oof me.
I burped while I was making a fart sound just then.
You recorded that. That's going to be crazy to hear.
you guys are on. This is what it sounded like. It sounded like a phone ringing on
silent. You guys are on your galleon, the Royal Caribbean, your privateers right
now. Who named it that? Who came up with this name? Caleb. I was the only person
who sent in a name. You were the only one who answered him and I saw it later
and I was like, yeah, it should be fine. I thought it was pretty funny. Just
wanted on the record. I didn't. I wasn't trying to make a funny. Nobody else came
up with a name. I was like, I was like, hey, I'm going to get the ball rolling.
and say was a royal caribbean just i want to know the record and i don't know i'm
making a comment either way i don't want to know who came up with it
you can't everyone will be fine with it
i didn't say they wouldn't be or they would be
mission so i was on everyone in a
if you don't like it just call caleb and tell him yeah
you should all of his number
so you guys are now uh... yes you guys are are about to approach the uh...
sorry my
limited
families that
Please stop. This is like that you're so near me now.
Remember when we used to do this on the computer? Now we can touch you and hurt you if you make us mad.
Yeah, it's true. I forgot about that.
So you guys are on your ship.
You are face to face with Weird Beard.
He does have a weird beard. It's like different colors. It has like braids in it.
What's weird about braids?
In your beard?
Okay, sorry.
That's not what you said. I think braids are weird.
no i said we're doing things that were weird it's going like you said
braided hair is a weird color nope it's a it's a wall
and i have a serious head
you know we've got colors in it
you guys are are fighting him so you're all for initiative
you've boarded his ship
what's his ship named
his ship name is uh... well i did not give him a ship name
i'm sorry about that
i should have here i'll do it
films are getting a good you do it
uh... chris
Chris, isn't that weird?
Is what he says.
Because he's got a weird ship name.
So yeah, you've got your crew on there. They're fighting some of the pirates.
But so, you and Weird Beard.
He comes to you guys and he says,
"You three have been hunting me
for too long now."
I agree. I think I'll
stop now.
Yeah, well I think the hunt's over.
Yeah, we found you. Yeah, we're here.
No, but now I'm...
I was going to say it's time for the hunt
hunted a big we already and i want to
yeah we're done we're done with you
all right well we're here to tell you that we're done with the who's who's
first in the initiative and that's me okay
it is you
do i have any lackeys
do i have any lackeys? uh... yeah you can take one action to command your crew to do
something okay
uh... what is it what's our crew? yeah what's up with the crew? yeah who's in our crew?
yeah i mean your crew is... describe our crew
I mean they're-- Give them names and talk about their attributes.
Okay, yes. I have names for some of them. So, most of them are just sort of like nameless
crew who you got with the ship, who you've accumulated over your months of sailing in
the sea. Are they slaves?
No, none of them are slaves. They're not slaves.
Are you putting slaves-- How can we possibly afford to pay them? They
must be-- I mean-- You guys are very successful privateers.
That's true. And you have the theme park money that's been rolling in.
That's true, but I mean, I haven't been paying any of these guys. Have you guys been paying any of these guys?
Hell nah. I haven't paid a single person.
So they're slaves. Okay, well I'm about to become a hero. Slaves, you are all free.
They're literally fighting with another crew right now.
You're all free and you can go into the ocean.
Or you can stay.
Or you can stay but we cannot pay you.
One of them just starts to walk away and he just gets stabbed.
He just stops fighting.
Nah, crap, he shouldn't have listened to us.
One slave down. I mean, there's no slaves here.
One free man down.
Yep.
That's what it is.
30 to go.
Okay, then you have your Boatswain Scurvyneck.
His name is Boatswain Scurvyneck?
No, his name is just Scurvyneck.
Well, that's his full name now.
his name is yeah he's a goblin he's sort of a young goblin he has a lot of a can
we have a french fry guy or be I mean you have a chef if you want he's made of
french fries what's the chef's name his name is a Oli he's not made of french
fries I'm a different he's a fat elf okay fine then you have Wayne
yeah Wayne who's a Wayne Wayne Wayne's a half or so we have both he's a quarter
way it works I say that when I see him when it way hey Wayne all right what you
doing Wayne I'm fighting off some of the idea I know I've known you for quite
some time but I just thought of this when it wanes it orks Wayne you one of
our best friends on the ship that thank you sir you're welcome continue continue
with the list. I hope he doesn't die so I can say that again. Me too. So well it would be
good if he doesn't die because he is also he's the quartermaster so he's in charge
of navigation. Oh he's our SMEE? He's your SMEE. He's our SMEE? I mean in that sense.
Is SMEE the fat one from Captain Hook? Our SMEE his name is Wayne. Is SMEE not the first?
Wait we have a SMEE named Wayne? Oh he's the first mate. Yeah you guys don't have a first mate.
What? Three captains. We need to find a SMEE. Three captains. Wayne we're promoting you right now
you are a Smee. You're Smee now. Your name is Wayne Smee. What is a...
When it Smee's it orcs... No, you're still Wayne. He's like fighting off...
When it Smee Wayne's it Smee orcs. It smorcs. Okay, when it Smee Wayne's it smorcs.
Yeah. Okay. What do you want to do with your turd, Patrick? So I'm supposed to be
fighting weird beard yes I remember this character sheet yeah yeah I gotta
memorize my shit do I still I have a bow and arrow how far how close am I to him
you're within range when you guys boarded all right I guess I have to
fight him with my sword oh yeah you can do that too I'm gonna try and do like a
Zorro thing and take his pants off okay yeah roll roll roll an attack roll what
you get and that's add your sword your pluses on that I should actually have
you add my sword to this don't do this to me please yeah I believe you have a
rapier yeah that you probably are using for this you're gonna add plus five to
that so would you roll I wrote an 11 so it's a 16 yeah that hits him that hits
yeah does it does it do the pants thing I don't know roll for damage okay it's
It's gonna be a d8.
Which one's that?
With the d8, you don't have one there.
It's this one.
Okay.
7.
Nice.
Oh actually I should also say, shit I didn't even realize this.
It's gonna be a sneak attack roll.
So add another 2d6 because there are other crew within 5 feet of him.
I'll go 7.
Nice.
So 7 plus what?
6, right?
What was that, was six before?
Yeah.
- Seven plus seven.
- Plus seven, oh, 'cause you added,
did you add three to the other one also?
Or no, so 10 plus seven, so that's 17.
- What are you saying?
- Just let him, let him cook.
- You did 17 damage, so you just like,
yeah, you slice him weird beard up
and you do make his pants go down.
I mean, with 17 damage.
- Ha ha ha, it's not funny!
- Guys, look, everybody look, I pantsed him.
Hey, slaves, look, I pantsed the guy.
- Slaves, look at his penis.
He's got a weird beard down there, too.
yeah it's also colored and braided oh that's weird we don't wear underwear in
these times it's the olden times we don't they all said the crew all nods
except for me we don't wear underwear we are pirates underwear underwear I do
wear a condom all the time you're raising morale of your crew with this
chant nice you're a you have like a crew mechanic I'm not I am gonna slowly
implemented over the course of the session he's not gonna make us give us
too much to do we're already getting a little curry all right so with the 19 is
you all right I'm going to use inflict wounds ooh baby and I rolled that's
right as a 16 nice yeah I mean that's also gonna hit yes he's gonna die cuz
I'm rolling 3d tens now yeah it's gonna be pretty bad and these guys 19 damn
Wow shit. Okay. Yeah, I mean, I mean describe this to me describe inflict
wounds to me. Um, we used to talk about this. What did it used to be? I forgot. It was like a green thing. Okay, a green thing
comes out. A green thing comes out and it goes into him. And that's as good as we
can be at describing it. That green, some green stuff. I like that. Flies out of my
body. Green stuff flies out of your body. Yeah. It courses through the air until it
finds purchase you not know don't try to add don't try to know no no okay you're
not purchasing a damn thing right now okay so what happens is some green
flows for me into him and it hurts green flows for me mm-hmm you got it yeah okay
he's not yeah he's not looking too good you guys have done a lot of damage him
where's he's green I flip him off right now for yeah to add advantage to Cameron's
rules it's almost how that works okay he's up though now so he's going to yeah
oh god he's gonna go after you Patrick bitch don't even try shit give me a
d20 little ass bitch fuck you okay okay not that good good and that does hit you
What? Yes, he swipes at you with his
His shimitar and he misses. It's a shimitar. A shimitar and then he does it again and he does hit
And he just slices into you for eight damage
He dropped his phone on his wiener when he said fucker
And you are now up Dogen. Okay, I'm gonna march right up to him
Mm-hmm, and I'm going to hit him which with my melee weapon that was it was a war shovel
But and then it was this war spoon and now I think it's gonna be a war or a war war
Or because it's like a born a boat love it. So a war or your new guy and I'm a war or who's your new guy?
water
Well, I used to like dirt and then I liked Oreos I think I'll split the difference and do water this time
yeah i'm
basically right in the middle yeah sand would be salt water specifically yeah
sand there was some tough and it's basically dirt yeah same was a type is a
type of dirt yeah yeah so it's water now in salt water all right such but i'm
gonna hit him with my um my war or your war my war or uh what you're that's an
18 oh yeah that hits okay that's money i'm gonna reroll that with my savage
attack that I gained on level 4. That's right, you did. Thank you for telling us. Okay, it's
the same roll. Same roll. So that's 4 damage. Nice, okay. You sort of whap him in the stomach
with the ore. I guess... The war ore. The war ore. Yeah, I mean, okay, yeah, I mean,
that's, is there anything else you want to do? I'm just thinking about what else you
could do there. You could also add smite too. Also to it. Okay, I'll add smite. How much
could do smite add should add sprite I think it adds to the it says yeah yeah
okay I'll add smite this might do it okay this smite do it fuck man whoa Wow
where you get these though 11 scribe your smite okay I smite him off the boat mm-hmm
he I swear I hit him I hit him with the war roar and he flies up in the air and
he's grabbing and he's grabbing his butt that turned red from pain and it's
Steaming from pain and he flies down he lands in the cannon and his hot butt sets off the fuse and it gets launched into
The ocean white flag
Star good in the sky like tinny rocket. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. How are the waters right now salty salty and
Choppy, but not too choppy. You're out to sea. Oh and a shark gets up him and gets him
I was gonna say is there like a big big like kraken?
I could a shark a shark he's flies in the air and he's about you can tell he's about to do the star thing like team
rocket but before he can a shark gets up and eats him and then a sea serpent eats
the shark a funny thing you should say that oh really did I do that a little
bit as you see him fly up and you see the shark eat him and we say we think
he's about to do the star thing oh he's about to do the star thing exists in
this timeline. Yeah right, Team Rocket are a bandit gang. And Pokemon are real.
Pokemon are real, yeah. But we won't see them because we're in the sea. Yeah, they're on another continent. Can there be a continent that's Pokemon?
There's stuff, there's lore. I just saw a Tangela. There's too much lore here. I just saw a Tangela.
Well you are about to see, you're about to see Tentacruel,
Tentacruel I guess maybe, because as you see the shark eat him, you see a
tentacle fly up, grab the shark down, and then flop onto the boat.
Oh my god, it's a Pokemon.
Wait, is the shark on the boat now?
No, the shark is gone.
As long as it's not a damn shark.
It's Kyogre.
I'm really scared of sharks.
You can't see the rest of the beast at all, you can only see this one tentacle flop onto the boat.
I kiss it.
It is your turn.
Do you want to kiss it?
Okay. I kiss it and I say, "I love you, baby."
Sometimes it's like you just do things to do them.
"I miss you so much, baby."
Yeah, I mean that's your action. Is there anything else you want to do?
It doesn't like react. That didn't hurt it. You're too small to have really affected it.
This is my wife I'm talking to.
Is there any other action you want to do with your wife?
renew our vows. Only you do that next turd. You're up, Evil Stiebel. Me? Yeah.
I'm not sure that this Octa thing is a threat yet.
Yeah, it's a Pokemon. Just because you have tentacles doesn't mean you're so bad.
Yeah, it's my wife. You just rescued that shark from flying into the Sun. Yeah, we
could tell the shark was about to do the star thing. Yeah, and you saved it. So I
I would I like to also if you would let me Patrick mm-hmm kiss your wife
Just on the cheek you son of a bitch
Shit I'm doing it. Oh my god. What the hell reaction you could try to stop him
I push him I push him away from a contest. Okay, you rolls strength. You're sort of prompting this Pat
I'm gonna have you do a reaction to stop a kiss. It's not exactly how that works, but it looks pretty low
Yeah, it was a three.
Man, how I do this bullshit.
Let's roll a d20 and we'll add your flat strength value.
This isn't something you would really do.
I got a four.
What did you get?
You got a three.
You guys very weakly push past him and plant those lanes.
They just walk into each other.
I take off my white gloves from my admiral's outfit.
I'm kissing no girl. You are a bastard. Oh, I have a hook hand. Okay
Right now just what I thought of it. I'm dressed up like I'm in a full admiral's outfit. You don't have to hook
Okay, I have a peg head
You have a peg head my head's just a block of wood
Yeah, I
Have my head replaced with a book. It doesn't really change anything for me. I don't think no, so it's just looks cool
All right, hold on so I got a role for this tent this tentacle
Yeah
Man, is there any way that I can be married to a giant squid in this camp giant squid?
What are you talking about? There's just one tentacle here. That doesn't mean there's any other ones it
Flings its tentacle around and knocks out some of weirdbeards crew and your crew
But you all are able to dodge out of the way that is not my wife
Andrew, your wife's hitting the slaves. Control your woman!
That's not my wife. Control your bitch right now!
I wish it was. Do something.
I don't remember. I put a big ring on her tentacle. That wouldn't be...
That would not be her. There's a big ring on the tentacle.
There's a big ring on the tentacle? There's an iron ring on the tentacle.
You know what, first of all, let me say I'm sorry.
Control her! She's had a few...
I'm pretty sure she's had a few to drink. Hit her right now.
You can like hear her nagging from way underneath the water.
I'm not gonna hit my wife.
Why not?
'Cause she just, she just gets like this, okay?
She's, she's hitting all these other guys.
Hold on, hold on.
[Muffled]
I stubbed my toe. Hold on.
[Laughter]
You can't be hitting my crew.
I mean, there's no, there's no response.
You can't be doing this.
It's just a tentacle.
I think you need to go make love to her.
A white mist in the deep, it is just from the deep.
follow this tentacle start slurping this tentacle like spaghetti.
I just grabbed the tentacle. Well it's it's Dogen's turn. Okay well I grab it.
You know I'll keep that in mind when it's when it's your turn again you can grab it you already
use your reaction to try to stop him from kissing. Yeah. And I did it. I'm gonna I'm gonna hit. That's
why she's mad. I'm gonna hit Patrick's wife. Yeah. I'm gonna look I'm gonna give him a really
meaningful look that's not I'm not like I'm not gonna say hey if you're not gonna do it. But it's
I will, but you know what it's saying.
I don't want to have to do this.
I look at him and I go...
I give him a big wink and I hide it.
I hide the side that I'm winking from.
Please hit my wife.
Please hit my wife really hard.
Please hit my squid wife.
Okay, I think that's a 7.
What's your squid wife?
Yeah, that's a 7.
Total?
Yeah.
Okay, no, it doesn't hit.
Basses off of the damn the tentacle you're up now Patrick do I hit the ring and it goes?
Yes, I I
Man someone must be flying into the sky somewhere. I
Crawl up the tentacle and I try to pull the ring off
Okay, roll a strength check
So just real strength
Yeah, I mean you just sort of like you just really scrape your fingers on it
It kind of hurts you can't win, but I'm holding the tentacle still what I mean you're still on the tentacle
It hasn't shook you off yet. You have successfully mounted the tentacle. I whisper into one of the suction cups
Knock it off. It smells bad knock it off. This is getting pretty
Domestic okay, you're up. Yeah, I think we should just leave and let them sort it out
I feel like I'm watching an episode of Gerard of Spinger
(laughter)
- What am I doing?
- It's your turn, you can do what you want.
I mean it is on Weird Beard's boat, not yours.
- Oh.
- Oh shit.
- Oh, wait, I thought we were on our boat the whole time.
- No, you guys boarded Weird Beard.
- Oh, wait, I look back at the boat and I go,
ah shit, my bad.
(laughter)
I've had too much grog.
Okay.
- All right, you guys tell your crew to go?
- Yep, all right.
- Yeah, I'm gonna try.
- Everyone, come on.
- Quit fighting's over, just quit fighting.
- Wait, hold on, hold on, get all the,
get their loot and then we'll bring it over to our boat.
- Make sure you win the fight.
- Make sure you forget.
- We won the fight.
- We already killed the guy.
- We just killed the captain.
- Oh, what, we gotta kill everybody?
All right, boom, dead, dead, dead, dead.
Everybody's dead, come on, let's go.
- Everybody's dead but our crew.
- No, I don't care if you guys die, honestly.
We don't even need that much loot.
- We need two or three of you to carry a treasure chest.
- Everybody who has a name,
to the boat with us yeah if you don't have a name stay here and fight. Steve Wayne and the
other fuckers just get the treasure chests and walk over. Also we don't really need any
more treasure I'm gonna be real. I'm good I kinda want it. Weirdbeard was your rival but you were also like
hired by the government the governor of port I just remembered something a port
virtue good so you might not yeah I should have said this to you so you guys
might not have to it's like there's not this wasn't necessarily like a treasure
like adventure oh you're just hitting the guy is there a big oh we're just
assassinating him your privateers you get hired to this guy's what does he
have on his boat he does have treasure on his boat what do we get hired to do to
kill him what if we get back to port if we get back to port and that damn shark
just take care of Ward I'm quitting pirating forever if the shark has if the
shark is that's why we got a shaking fins with the mayor except why we gotta get
all the crap off the boat. You're right we at least need his ID. Yeah. Okay we can get
his ID. We need his boating license. Yeah. Okay wait wait the deed to the boat. You
could go to his captain's quarters. Yeah. Not that one. And you could try to see if
you can get some sort of proof. Yeah his driver's scroll. His driver's scroll. I will go
down there and I'll. Okay so you're gonna have to. I'm still on the tentacle. Use your turn. I'm
trying to say all this to you guys and all you nears like. So you just have to get by the
the tentacle it doesn't seem to be able to send you though so like you probably
could just make the captain's quarters yeah you're in there you see it's got
pictures of his wife and kids yeah good and yeah you sort of rummage through the
drawers and you are able to find more a deed to his ship that it's his ship the
Chris now belongs to him okay and so that would be basically proof enough
that you guys like at the very like common do we get a little bit of candy
if we if we show there's a little bit of candy and there is 17 gold pieces also
okay if we show anything with that if we show like the the ship insurance agency
that we owned the Chris when we get reimbursed for everything on the Chris
there is no ship insurance agency that I know of in the damn olden times let's
well let's found a ship insurance agency and then claim it yeah yeah that's not a
- That's a bad idea.
- That's our new move is we, every ship that we board,
we find the deed.
- Don't tell us to the god.
- We find the deed and then break the ship
and then reimburse ourselves.
- I head up from the captain's quarters
and I just start walking over to our boat.
- You can just book it, yeah.
- All right.
- You can put it over there.
- Bye everybody.
But like kinda slowly like I'm leaving a party.
- Yeah.
- All right, good to see you.
- Yep, the tentacle's still here.
Yo tentacle, yo.
Forever man, we'll always have this night.
- Where would the treasure be?
treasure would probably be in the hole like further down the hole maybe in the
probably in the you know the treasure be well there we go
lower deck don't need treasure bro we literally said we have enough money what
okay patches what's what would the treasure be I mean the treasure would
just be a sizable amount of gold pieces I mean this is not gonna have like a
magic item he doesn't have like a magic sword not that you have a job not that I
I would know so this is weird.
No, it's weird beard, dude.
What are you probably like a freaking a freaking beard oil?
What if he had a candy cane sword?
Oh, he doesn't like the like the like that's in the candy cane
mountains.
What about sweet beard from kids next door to be has something
like that.
He's not sweet beard.
He's weird beard.
That's in that's not even like that's not even his name.
I think sweet beard.
Anyway, how do I know he doesn't have like a crazy good sword
because he's telling you he doesn't okay, but you said not
that I know of I'm saying there was there's a very little I
can't say like what you wouldn't like I can't say that you know for sure he
doesn't have a crazy weird sort I'm saying it is very unlikely that a guy
like weird beard who is sort of like a mid-tier pirate okay anything dope all
right you had all you had to say was mid-tier I'm yeah I'm climbing off that
only understands we will say things are made or based yeah yeah so yeah you guys
are able to escape you see the tentacle as you guys leave slink back into the
water and you see like a huge form does it go here out of it no Bob into the
white mist and you see the white mist disperse and see the huge form
disappear Bob bye honey Bob her name's Bob and yeah you're back on your ship
the road as your wife Bob and my wife he seemed one of them and you're gonna
doesn't know sail back I wouldn't want to tell her you'll sail back don't tell
her to the to port to port virtue good so and while you're sailing back I will
inform people of what's what's what's going on the sea bomb long before it
became an uninhabitable uninhabitable hostile milky alabaster was a rich and
vibrant part of the planet it connected the stray islands off the terrifier
kingdoms continent held mysteries beyond the reach of the kingdom. Only the
bravest of explorers were dare to venture to these waters. Those who first did were
rewarded with whatever land they could find where they'd act as a lord. No land
was more rich in the sea balm than the Virtue Good archipelago.
Pirate King Virtue Good sailed under the Terrifier flag hundreds of years ago and
made his way westward until he stumbled upon this rich chain of islands that you
guys are at now and they took his namesake. He ruled over the
Archipelago as a king for decades. Some say the height of his power he could
have challenged a terrified kingdom itself. But the call to the adventure
stirred in his heart once again and he vanished without a trace. In his absence
the Archipelago was ravaged by war over the spoils until the kingdom at the
time led by a young King Nardwar in his first landmark diplomatic act put an end
to the fighting and create an uneasy truce among the warring micronations.
Virtue Good Archipelago is now ruled over by governors and lords all strictly
under the Terrifier banner. Peace is maintained in a flimsy arrangement. So it
has been six months since you guys saved the kingdom from a mad sect within the
Terrifier Church that tried to bring back a villainous god. You know him as the
Terrifier. Since then you've been privateers on behalf of the easternmost
part of the archipelago in the capital city of Port Virtue Good where the
eponymous pirate King first landed you've been sailing your ship on the Royal
Caribbean which you got from trunchbull who is Patrick's Yoda ours beloved uncle
who passed away shortly after the previous campaign and oh yeah yeah yeah
he died yeah didn't he turn into dust not necessarily no turn into worms
incursions the worm does so much he turned to a force ghost though he turned
went to what a force ghost only for you yeah fart ghost nice green it's so
captain weird beard what had sworn himself to no governor or Lord and
attacks indiscriminately instead of being a proxy war you know properly
doing it through proxy wars which is how the there's a bunch of competing
Oh great, here come the politics.
Um, no. I'm tuning out.
Oh, I did a campaign for Chappo.
(laughter)
These guys are like the Democrats.
Yep, and this is Hillary.
The Democrats are coming, let me tell you.
They're gonna have a whole arc just you wait.
(laughter)
Um, god damn it. Alright, so,
so yeah, you guys are friendly with the governor
uh port virtue good uh governor gracias mi amigo um yeah and uh as you guys what's he sound like
he sounds exactly like you what you would imagine i am governor gracias me that's not what i would
imagine would you imagine something much worse okay well i'm not going to do that okay i would
imagine i would imagine him on a stick i can't i can't do that the good conscience all right
I was on Chapel Treppas.
(laughter)
That's fair.
Um, yeah, he says to you guys, uh,
wonderful job you three.
Thanks.
Gracias, mi amigo.
Yes, that's my name.
Gracias.
What?
Yeah, gracias.
Mi amigo.
Gracias, mi amigo.
Gracias.
What is it?
What?
Oh, wait a second.
- That's his damn name.
- Oh, my bad.
- Oh, that happens to me all the time.
- What's his name?
- Gracias. - Gracias, mi amigo.
- Mi amigo. - You're welcome.
What's his name?
- Gracias, mi amigo.
- You're welcome, what's his name?
- What's his name?
You're welcome. - I can't remember.
- Oh, Gracias.
(laughing)
What? - No, that's his name.
- What?
- What? - Wait.
- Que? - Gracias.
- Gracias. - I'm gonna leave, I think.
- Wait, could you guys just leave and then come back in?
- Yeah, sure.
- Yeah, okay. - Oh, what's up?
- Okay, hello. - Oh, gracias.
- Yes. - Mi amigo.
- Thank you as well. - That's great.
- Yes, so, I have one other task to ask of you.
You have been amazing privateer since you came here.
- Gracias. - Six months ago.
- Yes.
(laughing)
- I didn't receive this at all.
And he says to you guys, "There has been a strange series of banditries, robberies, in
Isle de Kool.
This is an island that is a bit off of Port Virtue Good.
You'll see.
And don't, this is a private, yes?
We keep this between the four of us?"
Between me amigo.
Just us amigos right here.
Yeah, just me and me and me I didn't know you bet I've been meaning to tell you I consider you me amigo
I consider myself me amigo as well grass. Yes
prego
You'll see
My city has a very rigid trading relationship with the kingdom
But we're trying to adventure out. Okay. I know it is boring by making it
- Oh, my God.
(laughing)
- In Isle de Cool, we have struck up something
a little bit more adventurous,
but it seems that they have been plagued by,
well, people have been robbing
and causing supply chain issues.
- They're robbing each other? - Are you saying rubbing?
- Rubbing? - They've been robbing?
- People have been rubbing?
- People have been robbing.
- Oh, hell no. - They've been robbing
each other? - People have been
getting robbed. - Each other or selves?
- They have been getting robbed themselves.
- Oh! - Oh, jeez.
- No, no, no. - Stay over there
rubbing themselves. - Wait, wait.
Where were they getting rubbed on?
- I don't wanna go there.
- Themselves, he said.
- Where, where?
- I will dig CK. - Downtown.
- Oh! - Oh, God.
- In downtown, behind us.
- They rubbing themselves downtown?
Oh, God. - Gracias, me pico.
- No, man, no. - Do not, no.
- I don't wanna even, I don't even wanna do this anymore.
(retches)
- I throw up on the ground
'cause I've been drinking so much salt water.
(laughing)
- You're just doing the same shit.
Hey, for the information, gracias mi amigo.
Yeah, yes.
We, I have--
Si.
I have, yes.
Si?
Si what?
Gracias?
The si is over there.
I see me, yes.
Gracias.
Mi amigo.
That's him.
No, he's gracias mi amigo.
Oh, you're welcome, mi amigo.
That's him.
Gracias.
I have sent a councilman there to handle it,
Councilman Granada Weintraut,
but he has been having some difficulty,
and I can't send any of my official forces over,
or again I'm going to let the kingdom know of my my business on the side so if I
you three privateers if you do this for me you will I can give you a parcel of
land that can be yours alone so you want us to go over there just take care of
the bandits take care of the people who are rubbing themselves downtown take care
of the people who are take care of them well run you want us to take care of
them while they rub themselves. I'm not rubbing anybody there. We won't rub.
They'll rub themselves. You want me to go over there and start rubbing people? No, no, not rub. Rub.
And I don't want you to rub anybody. I'm not. Hey, I already told you I'm not
rubbing a single... That's good. I don't want you to sit there and watch while they rub themselves.
You don't want us to rub? No. What? No, don't rub.
Gracias. So I kind of want to be able to rub though. I don't want to rub, so gracias for that.
Yeah, sea.
Yeah, sea what?
Over the sea?
Yes, you have to travel by sea to get there.
You have to travel by sea to go, okay, alright, I think I have it completely 100% in my head
now.
So we're supposed to rub the sea.
No, no, no, don't rub anybody.
The sea is a buddy.
Okay, but see, because they're already rubbing themselves.
That's a buddy of damn water.
So we don't have to rub them because they're rubbing themselves.
They're not rubbing themselves, they are getting rubbed.
Rub me amigo till he says gracias.
No, don't rub me.
You want me to rub you?
No, no, no.
Huh?
Who should we rub?
(laughing)
- No one, do not derub anyone.
- Now I'm damn confused.
- I'm gonna have a role wisdom saving throw.
- Okay, he did okay, he got a 16,
he's still sane as this is going on.
- Okay, just be discreet about it.
- Can you just say this, just say it bluntly
because it's not gonna make any goddamn sense if you don't.
- Say what?
- What are we going over there to do?
- We're rubbing, we got it, all right?
- We're rubbing him when we get back.
- When we, okay.
- We're gonna go and then come back
and we're gonna rub him.
- We go on the sea to see mi amigo, see?
And then we will see what we rub.
- And then we rub gracias when we get back.
- We rub mi amigo.
And he says gracias.
- No, do not rub me.
- And then he says gracias and we go in the sea.
- Is there any way you could have this conversation
away from a person?
- Gracias rubs me.
- And mi amigos are there watching?
- Hold on, wait, let me try to--
- Mi amigo says gracias for the ref.
- You three are going to go to over the sea.
- Okay. - Sea.
- Yes. - Sea.
- To Isle de Culo. - Yes, sea.
- Sea. - Isle de Culo.
- Where people, no.
Where people are being rubbed.
- We're gonna rub it.
(laughing)
We're going to the isle.
- So people are being rubbed across the sea, see?
- Yes. - And you want us to stop it.
- Yace.
- Okay, so we gotta go-- - Yace or C.
- We gotta go rub some Kulos on an aisle.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
All right, let's hop to it, boys.
- All right. - Wheels up.
- You don't have to tell me twice, let's go.
- I start rubbing.
(laughing)
- That's one down.
- And you leave immediately.
He writes in his notebook,
"Another conversation knocking out of the park."
(laughing)
Perfectly.
No one was confused.
- While we're walking. - Tear diary.
No one was confused by my name today.
- Now, while we're walking out,
just go like oh I get it now cool yeah
oh man we can get some chips yeah some chips yeah we'll take it take five
seconds to have a chip break Cameron edit this out edit out that shit it out that
shit I'm not editing yeah I'm for I do stuff we're kind of like a cool punk
style now where everyone can hear us eat and talk I leave in all the bad things
everyone says yes I'm lazy you guys gotta be careful now I just inhaled inhaled
something that has I just like it's bad for you no no you got a drink and
unhealed yeah I was trying to like I guess like no there's like a little bit
on the rim and they're right next to each other and then I yeah yeah you guys
sail across the sea and across to Isle de
Coole which is sort of a it's basically
like where Port Virtue Good is like an
actual like port you know it's like an
actual city this is clearly just
supposed to be a trading outpost that is
kind of masquerading as a just a regular
settlement it just it doesn't want to
draw any attention to itself again it's
trying to trade with colonies that
aren't associated with the the Terrifier
Kingdom. What makes what why is an isle
different from an island I actually wish I could tell you that I've read a lot
about islands before this but I didn't read about that it's a circle and I
think it's literally just like an island is an island so it's when there's an
aisle and something else sorry I can't I don't answer cuz I'm I'm looking in my
my my spyglass yeah I'm scanning the shores for rubbings I'm looking in also
spyglass but not backwards just sideways I'm looking into the side yeah mm-hmm
I'm just I'm just so anxious to get rubbed yeah I I am like fully I left
that exchange fully believing that we are going here to stop people from being
rubbed I think that we have to he thinks that he's he thinks you have to stop
them from being robbed and I think that we're going there to rub people I mean
- That sounds exactly in character, yeah.
Okay, so you guys show up at the dock
and Councilman Granada Weintraut is already waiting for you.
- Gracias.
- Are you mi amigo?
- No, my name is Granada.
- And Granada to you as well.
Are you mi amigo?
- No, mi amigo is the governor.
I'm Councilman Granada Weintraut.
- Gracias. - De nada.
- De nada.
- Granada.
- De nada. - Bless you.
(laughter)
- They nodded to you as well.
Now listen, would you--
- Where do I get rubbed?
- Yeah, and who am I supposed to rub?
Good plan guys, we'll fool them into thinking we're robbers.
- I see what happened here.
- Yeah, we'll fool them into it.
- I'm very familiar with when the governor
tries to talk to anybody.
No, so there are robberies going on here.
- Robberies?
- No, not robberies.
- What the hell's a robbery?
Isn't that when something's all jiggly?
It feels kinda rubbery sometimes if it's an Audi.
You're close. It's when people have goods that are stolen from them.
God damn it.
Okay.
Um, like maybe the dead skin on their arm 'cause it got rubbed off?
Um, not, not, not as related.
Oh, so everyone on this island has eczema.
And that's why they're here, 'cause they're exiled.
That's pretty good, but no. I'm afraid not.
I'm going to... I'm not gonna not write that down.
Though.
I'm rubbing you basically no do not rub stop stop stop stop. I tackle him
Right we want 3,000 coins, okay, no no first
Give me your car. Give me those coins. I'm taking them if you don't give it to me. This is a robbery. I'm robbery
No, we already did that
so I'll introduce you to
one of our one of our
sailors
Yeah, and you see a guy who's a
sort of a just a regular-looking guy who
Who looks a little shaken up and he has described to them what you saw last night
Well, well I was by the docks and um, I was just shipping some cargo over and um
what we saw looked like up these guys riding on top of dolphins and
And then the guys and the dolphins were just... they attacked us and took our goods and...
I mean, they rode away. It looked like they were working together. I'd never seen anything like it.
The guys with the dolphins? Did they rub you or no?
I don't know. I don't know. I can't... Please, please, relax.
You don't know. Just whatever you can say.
I mean, they robbed me. I don't think they robbed me, though.
They didn't. So why are we talking to this guy? He didn't get rubbed.
Yeah, this guy just got robbed.
You see, wait, Secretado leads over to the guy, he goes,
"Tell them, they talked to Gracias,
"tell them that you were, oh, okay.
"Yeah, I was rubbed too."
Oh my God, we need to kill him.
- Wait, okay, so he's done already, so we can skip him.
- Yeah, we don't have to talk to him.
- So you're gonna rub me.
- But it's the dolphin guys who are doing the rubberies.
- Okay, so we need to find the dolphins.
- 'Cause dolphins are rubbery, that makes sense.
- Oh my God. - Oh yeah.
Yeah, and dolphins love sex.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
Alright, so any clue as to where these dolphin men might be?
Do I have to put it in the blowhole?
What do you think rubbing is?
Sex?
I actually don't know.
I don't know.
Um, well, I don't know.
It seemed like they just came from under the dock.
It didn't make any sense.
I'm gonna get rubbed under my dock.
Alright, under the dock seems like a nice seedy place to get rubbed.
Yeah.
Or to stop someone from getting rubbed.
Or to rub somebody.
(laughter)
- All right, let's go check it out.
- To interface with rubbing in some form.
- Can we head to the dock?
- Yeah, yeah, I mean you guys are at the dock.
- Okay, I pop my head under to see.
Can I investigate a little bit?
- Yeah, yeah, do an investigation check.
- I'm gonna also investigate.
- You can give him advantage.
- Okay, I'll give him advantage.
- Roll again, roll again.
- Roll again, oh I have advantage.
- Oh my God, my beautiful life.
- What, I don't get to roll a thing?
- Oh, did you both get 17?
Well, just 'cause you--
- I got an 18.
- Well, that's 17 plus--
- Your investigation's pretty high.
Yeah, let me look.
Oh, my passive investigation is 11.
Oh, my password.
My password to my--
I thought your district was higher.
--7, 6, 8, 9.
But anyway, so yeah, yeah, yeah.
So you're both actually at 18 for this.
Hold on, hold on.
So--
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, you're both at 18.
Yeah, I'm at 18.
I mean, looking under the dock and sorting through,
with that 18, you can see that there
is a grate that looks like it's a bit askance.
open open sorry grass yes and prego and you can see that it doesn't look like it
would be big enough for for most people to fit through but it does look like you
could sort of squirm your way through it but it is also like you know filled with
water I'm small I'm filled with water I love water way my things water now oh no
wait I'm not small anymore I'm tall yeah you're not long now and he's he's small
- I'm small and wide, I'm small and little.
- How tall am I again, I'm like six, five or something?
- Foie?
- Six foie.
(laughing)
- I'm so tall I can't even say it.
- Oh yeah, Pat, Pat, you have a, wait,
I made sure to write down what you have,
'cause I realized I didn't write it down
when we first did it.
You have a giant eyeball on the back of your head.
(laughing)
- Man, it's been a while.
- You're kinda regular size now, like five nine.
- Regular size, so like six two, right?
- No, I mean, well, five seven,
would say is regular size. I don't know if people would say that. I just read about
this how people have been saying that actually. Really? On oppositeday.com? No
it's actually on Cameronstinky.web. Okay so yeah that was a subdomain of
oppositeday.com. That's why it's called that. Yeah. Anyway. Okay so I'm gonna put my big
eyeball in the crack. Also your hair is silver. I'm going in the crack. Also your
face now you have like a Michael Jackson nose. Do I really? I don't remember that.
I thought I looked like Alan Alda. No that's what happened part of your
puberty made your face look no longer as much like Alan Alda. You could still
sound like Alan Alda. I start I come to the realization. You're like warhead Alan
Alda is what we said. Okay so I come to the realization. Like what you said and I'm
like all right I'm just gonna put my eyeball under here. I'm crawling into the
crack because I I'm water now so you could it's like a Tourette's tick now
I know what's your what's your Constitution I can't wait for this
campaign this is good you don't need a going you don't dare to go cam what's
What's your constitution bonus?
For modifier rather.
It is plus one.
Okay so you can hold your breath for one minute underwater.
Okay but my God is a water God.
Do you think that gives me anything?
You might have to pray or something.
Yeah I mean I don't mind praying.
I mean I love praying.
I mean can't get enough of this stuff.
So we'll have you pray to your new water God and if you get above a ten when you pray you'll
get another minute is that a religion check no it's gonna be straight d20
because this is this is a bullshit thing I'm doing here it's a water god I feel
like that's not too far it's not like I picked that only that today I didn't I
didn't tell you like after I knew I was gonna like it's fair go into a crack
like a metagaming here I just think that I should get something something here
all right all right switching gods willy-nilly 11 okay yeah so you pray to
your water God what is your who is your water by the way the reason I switched
to um to the water god is because i was eating a lot of oreos for my oreo god
and i was dipping them in milk and i was like oh the milk is kind of better than
the oreo and there's no milk god so i just chose the water god instead
right of course water's an oreo
what?
wario
yeah your guy your water guy goes wow
okay
i know that voice
wait a second
Okay!
I know that voice.
Wait a second.
Uh oh.
My god, I love him so much.
Who is that?
I wish he was here right now.
I wish he existed at this time.
I wish he was born already. Oh my god.
Is there a penguin around here?
We all have a collective vision of thousands and thousands of years in the future.
That was amazing.
Of that dude.
Of this mysterious dude.
I hope he's in this campaign so badly.
There's love when you say oh yeah.
Oh yeah.
So you guys have two minutes of breathing that you can go through and that is enough to - I
thought your concentration was higher but so it's good that you did that.
You're good that you made me do that.
That's enough for you to kind of come up with like a little bit of air and have a little
bit of a cove in front of you like an underwater cave.
Sure.
Yeah.
And you could see that there is, it's dark, dank, and you could see that there is a way
forward.
It's very hard to see in here though.
I think you have dark vision though.
Is it dank in here?
Yeah, it's dank.
We're recording on 420.
Oh wee!
People are not going to hear this for like four months, I feel like.
Not true.
Yeah, so.
It's not true.
So.
He's just making shit up.
So yeah, what do you want to do?
You're here for a while.
You're here alone. It's just a cave. There's nothing as it is. It just like is there it goes on forward. Oh, okay
It's like a tunnel. Yeah, I feel sorry. Yes. Yeah, and in turn with shallow water
And yes, you can feel a bit of air do have any way I can communicate with them
From in here. I guess I'll just can you guys hear me? Yeah, okay
Perfect. Okay, you know I hear you they can't hear you. Okay. Can I do I have like a messenger fish?
(laughter)
- Well, let's see--
- A messenger mackerel.
(laughter)
- Let's see what you have as far as spells and abilities.
- Oh wait, no, I can make my voice really loud.
That's one of my abilities.
- Do you have thaumaturgy?
- Yeah, I have thaumaturgy.
- Can it go through water?
- Yes.
- Duh.
- How loud is that?
(laughter)
- Duh.
- It can be three times as loud,
and you can also make harmless tremors
on the ground for one minute.
So you have things you can do with that as well.
- Oh, I didn't even prepare my spells,
but I feel like I could prepare do I have create in a spring water or do you
have that I do you want me to destroy the whole ocean? Yeah, can you just
yeah, I'll do that. No, I guess I'll just use the amateur g and see how loud I
can get see if I can get them to hear me. I'll stick my head underwater and
then I'll talk like a booming thunderclap. Yeah, it sounds good. You
guys are going to you guys are
roll perception both of you. Let's do that.
*gibberish*
Me too.
Four.
Hold on.
Just hold on.
Uh, I got sixteen.
That's pretty good. You can hear a faint
sounds like Dogen. You can hear that.
I put my head in the water and go
*gibberish*
You're talking at normal volume.
(gurgling)
- Dogen must be thirsty.
- I stop, I take my head out of the water.
- He wants me to do the moonwalk.
(laughing)
- Well hey, give the man what he wants.
- Alright, I try to do the moonwalk.
- Roll performance check.
What's 14 plus seven?
- Very good.
- You crushed the moonwalk.
- Wait, wait, so if he's down there,
that means that there's something down there.
yeah so I I I'm gonna quick save and then walk down the tunnel yeah sure I feel
like we should go and try to join him yeah yeah I mean you can look at the fact
that he's like oh he's still I thought he was dead I thought he killed himself
that's such good news that he wants you to do the moon wait maybe that's his
dying wish hold on I got a moonwalk down there I'm gonna try and do a moonwalk
into the way um he how tall is he it's not about the height it's about like like
well how tall is he and how long is the tunnel I mean the tunnel is like what are
you planning you think you're tall enough to just it's not about being tall
it's about being like swam for two minutes you think it's get there yeah
okay maybe I don't know okay you're not tall enough to just get there okay how
long we we can both hold our breath for a minute each you what's your what's your
Constitution my constitution basing it off of your modifier for that my constitution
You guys probably both have higher than him, I don't know where to see you don't it's your my constitution is
13 minus plus plus 2 plus 1 and you have plus 2 okay, so I can get down to the cave you can get down
There's a cave, but you can you destroy the water in there so that we can go into the cave easy create and destroy water
I think only allows you to destroy like
feet. Just use it a bunch. How much water is down there? 30 cubic feet, right? 31 feet
of water. Could I really quickly - What you could do is you could use - Could he jump
down and it could just destroy 30 feet of water? You could use multiple spell slots
and if you do it twice, I'll say that you can destroy enough that he can make it through
too. Alright, I'll do that. It's not a bad idea. I don't know if I have over - Destroying
- Creating water is such a funny spell.
- I love, I just want to picture it.
- Destroy water.
- It's so many times it's coming in handy.
- You're skipping over some stuff that's pretty tough,
so it's not a bad idea to be honest.
- I don't, I actually don't think I have two.
- You do have two spell slots.
- But I already used one.
- You used one, you have four for first level spells.
You can actually create, oh my God,
what happens if you upcast, create or destroy water?
- You can create or destroy.
- You can create or destroy an additional 10 gallons
if you do that, or the size of the cube increases
by five feet.
What does upcast mean?
Upcast means when you cast something,
a spell that you get at like say level one,
and like a level one, you cast it as a level two spell slot.
So usually like spells like that,
you end up doing multiple,
so if something would be doing 1d6 damage,
you upcast it, it does 2d6 damage.
All right, I cast--
Certain spells you can do that, others you can't.
I destroy 60 feet of water.
Yeah, you do that.
And all life forms that are in,
that happen to be sadly in that 60 feet.
Yeah, I mean--
Are vaporized.
messenger fish that was swimming towards you was killed mm-hmm cool yeah yeah you
just see like fish just like just like are just swimming no they don't die
they're destroyed oh they're destroyed - yeah is this creator destroy fish no
it's created a water oh okay oh okay you also destroy me oh okay yep and they're
annoying fish okay fine so you guys make it through you up in the coat you quick
save right yeah okay so you guys are there and yeah you see a dark tunnel in
front of you I'm marching my green ass down I think I'm Alan Wake do all of you
have I'm Alan Wake wait I'd fun fun cut we're just here right now right can I
all have dark vision I have dark vision I know you do I have words I think do
because they're always that's the only one I'm wondering he's a guy he's a
goblin type deal which I would think it would mean he would yeah can I do
something real quick yeah you can do it before we walk into this dark cave can I
use detect magic not a bad idea yes you can okay I cast detect magic okay first
of all yeah Pat you have limited telepathy but you might I lift up my
pants cuz they're sagging that's that's telekinesis you talk to you I just use
telepathy to lift up my pants okay telekine okay they telepathically hears
me in my head go thank god I was sick of that bullcrap I hear that and then I'm
gonna try and then I'm like oh my god I have telepathy and then just realized
yeah seems like Verdans don't have dark vision which is weird so I'm gonna
listen for some crazy it's fine you can just follow us anyway so you you use
detect magic yeah okay cool so when you do that you do to detect some kind of
enchantment magic that is we make sure I make sure I'm accounting for everything
to tech magic is able to there's a lot of stuff in there that means there's a
lot of stuff in there we see that means this tunnel ain't empty do I can I have
a spell called detect bullshit?
Yeah. Um, no. Okay. I mean, I'll maybe later we'll figure that out. Uh,
yeah, you, you are able to tell it's enchantment magic. Um,
you could tell that it's just sort of generally aligning the walls of the
tunnel, um, upwards of 30 feet. Um,
but there's nothing else around like there's no other schools of magic you sort
of sense. And it's only like faint traces around that. Um,
but you don't see any creatures who are radiating magic,
just sort of a general like vibe of that.
Okay, so there's some kind of thing on this on these walls. There's a thing here. There's stuff on the walls
Oh, no, I just detected it
Well, I did it only one way to walk down the tunnel. Mm-hmm. I walked very carefully down the tunnel
He is walked down the tunnel
And when you get to the very end of it
You see you're sort of rounding a corner so you haven't been seen by this group yet
but you see a group of people who all have the skin of
Dolphins and you also see
Robberies and you see them just sort of with the goods that they must have stolen just to enjoy the goods
You see a couple of them who are dolphins and you see them talking to the people who have the skin of dolphins
You guys will recognize these as were dolphins
Okay. Yeah, here's a dolphin sound
it's
actually spent time with dolphins. Yeah, I've watched plenty of videos. I haven't.
I've actually looked at a lot of pictures. Mm-hmm. Yeah, and I imagined what they
would sound like when I looked at the pictures. Yep. Okay. Nevermind. Keep going.
And it's not like that. Okay. It's nothing like that. Okay, that's fine. So yeah, you
guys see that there. You also see a kind of an effigy to, in the shape of some
kind of like, looks like some sort of like robed woman, but like... A rubbed woman?
- There's a rubbed woman up there.
- Wait a second. - A rubbed woman.
- That's funny, we don't hear it, we just see it.
- A rubbed woman? - Wait, that thing's rubbed.
- This must be the rubbing. - That woman's wearing a rub.
- This must be the rubbing room.
- It's an effigy. - These guys are rubbery.
- They're rubbery. - In the shape of.
- They're rubbers in the rubbery.
- Oh my God. - And she's, so wait.
- And I got the rubbers.
- So we gotta rub them then.
- Don't worry, I brought rubbers.
- You rub them and I'll stop you.
- Now that's a damn good idea.
I'll make one of them rub me all right can I start walking towards all right
break all right hey wait I mean that worked they say out loud I think I gotta
sneak up on them yeah I'm gonna cut a roll stealth yeah I mean they know you're
you're there like you did do all of us oh wait actually you know what I'm gonna do
you just dip back into the darkness but they did see you all right well the
jigs up I walk back so basically let me tell you what I was in here because I
need to rub you and also I'm the only one in the entire room besides you guys
he's the only one in here. No wait, and I love doing weird different impressions and voices as well.
See look, I'm the only one in the whole room. He's the only one in the room. See I'm talking to my damn self.
I'm crazy. I'm crazy. Please don't hurt us, they repeat. But I'm friendly and I'm here to rub you.
Okay, okay. Okay, what do I have to roll? Deception, yeah. You're the only one in the room.
14 yeah I mean they think it's weird that you said that but they don't disbelieve
you what do you want what do you want you want to rub us yeah come over here
and you see the man I hope nobody stops me
you see one of them like one of them it looks like he's he started the leader of
the group. He says okay now give me your arm. He holds out his arm. I here I go.
I'm gonna go. Thaumaturgy, booming echoing voice. Stop! Oh God!
Thaumaturgy, I alter the appearance of my eyes for one minute. To what? Cat eyes.
- Oh!
- Cool.
- Ah, someone spooky's here!
- You will not rub him.
- Okay, well.
- And then I dust my hands off and I turn around.
- I think that's what we had to do.
- Well, I had to rub him.
- Yeah, but I stopped you, so.
- I don't really care.
- I use my limited telepathy and I say to
both of them, I say,
okay, figuring how to get me in here.
(laughing)
I think, okay, also that there's,
so there's one more guy.
(laughing)
And he has something that he bet.
- I'm moonwalking.
- So this is our friend, so basically--
- Roll performance.
15 plus, what's seven, 22?
God, yeah, you do another great moonwalk.
- This is our friend, he's very talented, obviously.
And he, I think, I believe he is looking to get rubbed.
Yeah, I think that's the...
So if one of you guys could rub him...
'Cause you're rubbers. I heard you guys were rubbing.
Shimona!
And obviously that's the rub, girl!
You were committing rubberies.
No, no.
Shimona!
Well...
Hee hee!
The people here reject us. We're were-dolphins.
It's so much worse than being a werewolf.
Have you tried not, like, going around rubbing people and shit?
Yeah, seems rude.
How else are we supposed to eat?
Wait, no, they should rub one guy here.
Eat? Wait, what the hell you eating?
CUM!
Nasty ass!
*laughs*
Why do you think we're eating-
'Cause you're rubbing people so you can eat-
-what? -No.
Their cum!
-Aww, goddamn, that's nasty as hell. -Nah.
-Nah. -And it is-
I would hate-
I would hate if I got rubbed until someone ate my cum.
-No! -I don't wanna eat no damn cum on a plate-
We're not eating cum!
Well, what the hell comes out of these
damn dicks and cocks?
That you're rubbing.
-Well- -Hold up, let-
-Just- let's start over- -CUM!
-Listen, listen. -That's right!
You just tell us your whole deal and we'll be quiet and then we'll say all our stuff at the end.
But just say your deal or whatever.
Why don't you roll deception on me and just see if...
See if...
Anyway, so yeah, they say...
Oh, I can't?
No, I'll just try to talk and see what happens.
So, they say, "We were chased down here and the good witch, the good sandwich, she..."
Okay, I mean come on who's covering my mouth
It is my fault right I guess right yeah, uh, they say uh, she she gave us an opportunity to
Well, she she she helped us organize and find a way to
To take back some of the the goods that that should belong to us. We get it. You were on chapel
No, no, no, no, don't that was not. No. No, I was not on chapel trap house
he says. Don't listen to the word organize and think that automatically. Sometimes people just say the
word organize and they mean - Get in you rubber! - getting together and he says, so we meant no
harm. We didn't think anyone would - we would just try to - we would never try to hurt anybody. We
just took the goods and brought them down here. Just rubbed them. Robbed them. Rubbed them.
- Rub. - Rubbed them.
I'm doing a Jedi mind trick hand.
You rubbed them.
- Okay, rubbed them.
- You need to die.
- You gonna attack them?
- No. - Okay.
- What are the goods that, can we see what the goods are?
- Yeah, I mean, it's just, it's rum, don't--
- Rub.
- It's my fault.
- It's rum. - Rum.
- Hard tack. - Okay.
- Some fruit as well. - Okay, what kind of fruit?
look at the goods and then I'm ready my parents of course okay my pants up past
my ankles yeah there's no fucking rubbing going on down here you've just been
exposing yourself yeah my dick's been out this whole yeah I mean that's that's
about it I mean it's literally just like do you read this from people yes we did
and okay so look why are we down here again are we I think I guess when I was
gonna get rubbed I mean I don't know why you're down here why are you looking at
me so basically I think generally we're supposed to stop you yeah what are we
supposed to do yeah you guys have to knock it off yeah whatever you're doing
that's you're not supposed to be doing don't do that or if you're not doing
something you should be doing do that and then I think yours or so how about
you just get jobs at our theme park or do you have any information about
anything guys we have been wanting to open a kind of SeaWorld type part to our
theme park yeah it's a SeaWorld type theme park where people go and they get
rubbed you could rub world yeah we could give you jobs you can give us work we
can give you jobs we feed our family yeah we only turn into dolphins when in
the when high tide then that means it's a special show and we can charge more
that's good that's good thinking I don't mind being a freak if it's for money
yeah don't forget you're ugly too okay even when you're a normal human form
right that's right yeah our first theme park is the one where it's all it's the
idiots yeah and now it's the rubber idiots and the rubbers okay well okay
we'll come with you and yeah they'll can you like come out separate I don't want
it to look like you're with us yeah you kind of are disgusting okay when should
- When should we come out then?
- Probably a hundred years from now.
(laughing)
- We can't wait that long.
- Okay, count to 10.
- Okay, we leave and then you count to 10 Mississippi,
then you come out and then you,
you know you can follow us.
- Okay, you guys can come out at the same time,
but only if you wear signs around your neck
that say I have no friends, so no one thinks we're friends.
- Yeah.
- And lipstick.
even the boys.
Well, I guess we could try to...
Wait, who's the lady?
Oh, that's the effigy of our good sandwich.
Oh yeah, who's the rub girl?
I'd like to have her, G. What's up?
Why is she wearing a rub?
Oh, a rub?
Well, she's rubbed whenever we see her.
You rub her when you see her?
No, I don't.
She's rubbed whenever you see her.
See?
Her?
Rub?
Gracias, mi amigo.
So wait, who is she?
She's a rub girl.
So wait, who is she? She's an effigy? She's just an effigy to our... I mean, she is the
Sand Witch who... Oh, that's her, okay. Yes, well that's her symbol. You don't have to say
anymore. Yeah, okay, yeah, that's fine. Which witch? The Sand Witch. Sand Witch. Which, right.
Alright. Which Sand is it? Which Sand? So here's... Wait, say what you were gonna say.
lipstick on your face okay here's your sign you might be a rubber if you're
wearing this sign get her rubbed so you all tater salad wait I forgot that they've
tried to make him just like a normal stand yeah they call me tater salad yeah
so yeah I mean you guys all go I mean the lipstick and the sign which was must
have been drawn in like I guess like lipstick like lipstick also it all just
washes off like I mean you're swimming through it like a tunnel that takes two
two minutes to swim out of and they all come out. How does he get out because
I'm tall I'm out of slots.
We already did the water doesn't come back. He destroyed it. Yeah, it's not
it's not temporarily destroy water. What are you doing? Yeah, I mean I guess
are you could just stay in there, though actually
what do you want to do man? I was tall enough to get out. It's not about
height. I don't know why you keep referring to if you put a tall person on
side they're going to be very long. You're not that much taller though. Yeah you're
like a regular height. Also like the thing about traveling for two minutes.
You subtract 30 seconds from it. No way. 30 seconds from me? It takes you 30
seconds to walk? You guys are like three feet tall. You're two feet
taller than us. Yeah. So it takes you guys two minutes so you'd subtract
30 seconds, 30 seconds, and now I only take one minute to travel through this tunnel.
That's pretty sound math actually. I'm actually a mathologist. I take it all back.
Caleb, you do have two more spell slots by the way. You have three actually
additional level, second level spell slots you can soak in. Well how is the water
came back though? How did the water come back? Well I have to say, here's the thing, I have to say.
Well if you got rid of water, wouldn't the water just fall into the place where the water went?
Eventually more water would come in. Well then, no, no, it's destroyed. That means the
the water. If he was destroyed then how would he have gotten in the first place?
I imagine he would destroy the water and then in that moment of gap like he could
swim he could sort of move through. There's no moment of gap the water's gone forever.
Well no I mean like it would fill in though from the ocean. How is it a tunnel then so we were
just in the ocean? Well you're coming from the ocean that's where the grate is
and then you destroyed some of the water in front of you while you were swimming
through I guess I could have illustrated that a little bit more. Yeah you did.
I think the water's gone permanently.
It's fine.
Either way, it's fine.
You're through.
I don't want to do that.
So you're through.
And yeah, I mean, he sees you, obviously, the councilman.
And he's like, he turns to the guy, "Are these them?"
Wait, who are you talking about?
You've got to wait ten seconds.
You told them to come.
They would be able to go out at the same time as you if they wore lipstick and signs.
Who are these freaks?
I don't know them.
Oh my god.
I don't know.
We should just get them out of here.
like it once said I have no friends good I see you've captured them yeah yeah no
there and they're gonna see send them to jail yeah we're putting it we're putting
them in our private prison yeah we run a private prison on the mainland yeah roll
roll deception both of you it's really not even a lot it's actually I think
about it cuz it is like literally a slave park I think I remember I'll still
role deception just hit park pretty much basically the idiots just don't know
their walk around characters I got a nine I got an 18 all right cool yeah
they're they're mad to see 18 plus 7 yeah yeah yeah so he's fine he's like
okay good well as long as you've apprehended them and make sure nobody
knows and trace back because we couldn't really even keep them here we need this
to be a quiet operation we appreciate it and you lot you get out of here me us
No, that's not right. No need to be rude. We just captured your rubber. No, it wasn't it wasn't
rubbers
Thank you very much. You sure you don't want me to rub you one last time?
No, don't
And they're going into the chain we're taking them to the clinic to be derubbed. Mm-hmm
So yeah, you bring these guys onto your ship. All right rubbers. Welcome to the ship get to work get to work
(laughter)
We start laying down on the ground.
What can we do? Start rubbing.
Rub the crew.
Rub everything.
Start massaging the crew.
No, don't massage them.
Rub them.
We didn't just capture some massagers, we captured rubbers.
Now rub them.
When you guys get back on your ship, your crew is
doing their best to deal with
the sudden influx of dolphin people.
Rubbers.
Rubbers, right, yeah.
What do you guys wanna do?
You're just sailing back.
I wanna get rubbed really bad.
Someone, I could really use a rubbin'
after all that adventure with these fuckin'--
Yeah, I bet you would, you bald bitch.
You barely did anything.
Yeah, you didn't do shit.
Are you kidding? You need a rubbing?
Who destroyed the water so that this fuckin' asshole
could get down there?
Yeah, who destroyed the water
so this asshole could get down here?
I didn't need any water destroyed.
I mean, I'm better than you guys.
I just went right through it. Who destroyed the water then?
Do you need me to rub somebody?
Yeah. Yeah, rub me.
No rub me!
Rub me!
I'll get my, I'll get my, my brother and my sister to come.
Oh, and you'll get your two damn friends!
Go get your rubbing kit!
Oh yeah!
What?
Listen, I had to destroy water so that this fucking guy wouldn't get chlorine in his back eye.
You, you, you barely, you destroyed the water and it came back right away.
And who's the one who stepped out of the darkness the first?
He stepped in the water.
And I'm the least-
I swam in the water.
I stepped out of the darkness because I'm the least shy, because you two are too shy to hang out with.
You stepped out of the darkness because you're so fat your stomach stepped out of the darkness on its own?
on its own yeah your mom is so fat she has her own area code you're dead uncle
are you fucking kidding dad uncle he's got that I shoot him with the arrow that
makes you poop yourself okay roll attack roll can I really dodge roll you will
see what you're a what's your AC what do I what do I add you're gonna add your I
can check your sheet but you should add your whatever your attack roll is to this
so go to your attacks actions your actions yeah and then you'll see on your
on your, I don't know how much it is,
you'll see whatever the modifier is,
it's the middle number, the middle number
with the plus next to it, I think, for you.
- Okay, so 14 plus five, I got a 19.
- Yeah, that does hit you.
So you do start crapping yourself,
or you're about to crap yourself.
- Stinky, stinky.
- What are you guys talking about?
He just shot a normal arrow at me?
- That was not a normal arrow,
that was the arrow that makes you crap yourself.
- No, that was a normal arrow,
and he's just crapping himself.
- No, I'm not, it was the crap arrow,
I have defeated it with my mind. I've overcome it. Why are you running to the bathroom? I'm not running
I'm just running to the bathroom. Yeah, right. Let's follow him into the bathroom. Let's go. Let's go follow him into the bathroom
Lock my phone. I smashed down the door
No, you did. It's splinters. I'm
Here's Johnny
Can I just have please one second alone from you? No, you want to see you shit?
Yeah, we want to see we want to see the fact that I made you poop yourself with an arrow. I'm casting
I'm going to cast
Which it does no damage because I just wanted to make a deafness to them right now, okay?
Yeah, what he has that yep. He's gonna not if I cast something first
Casting that I'm using telepathy to listen into his thoughts. We'll have to roll for initiative at this okay, okay?
I'm listening in to see whether or not he's saying I pooped myself
All you guys roll for initiative this is kind of 16. This is okay. All right six
Jeez, even this is the second six you got
Yes, okay who is higher deck you definitely have our decks yeah, he listens to me say I poop myself
So he listens you listen to him say about sweet. Okay, we're gonna be initiative or that's all we need
I heard you you said you pooped yourself. I'm still create making them blind and
Okay, so let me see what that spell with blindness and deafness it is
But also use them super smelling so they smell like
Yeah
It's super so we have one yeah
And you could use one creature you can see within range to make a decision saving throw if it fails the target is either blinded
Or deaf in your choice, okay?
I know and you can't upcast this is this is the the level but you also to choose one of us
to be either blind or deaf. I think next spell level you can choose both of them but this one you have to pick one.
I pick both.
So how about this, let's play with the spell. One of them can be blind and one of them can be deaf.
What? No, that's not fair. This is like see no evil.
Why are you siding with him? The Gene Wilder movie. That's funny.
Why don't you guys just let me poop in peace please.
No way. No we're not going to let you poop in peace. Pick one of them.
I choose Patrick because he has more eyes. Absolutely, he does have more eyes.
Alright, so Pat, roll a Constitution Saving Throw.
I'm going to add one to whatever that is.
Yep, that's an eight.
Yeah, okay, you are blind.
I'm blind, but I heard him say he pooped himself in his mind.
You're blind for one minute.
He pooped himself. I'm not blind and I'm looking at it.
Your third eye is blind too.
Yeah, the third eye in the back of your head is blind.
Third eye is blind.
(both singing)
- That's what I'm singing while I watch Evil Steve-O poop.
- All right, I--
♪ Steve-O pooped, Steve-O pooped, yeah ♪
- That's what I'm singing now that--
♪ He just crapped his pants ♪
♪ I heard Steve-O poop ♪
- Okay, so I pull my pants down
and I take the log of crap out of my pants,
which is a perfect log,
and I apply it to the toilet seat like lipstick.
- Okay, yeah.
The toilet seat looks vaguely fami--
As you're doing that, the toilet seat looks vaguely familiar.
Can you roll a history roll?
Something about putting shit on the lips of this is making me think it's something else.
Roll a history check.
Okay.
History...
I'm looking for history...
Here I go...
I think it's pretty bad.
You got four.
Four?
Yeah, you're just sort of rubbing shit on what looks like some sort of...
Looks like an amphibian of some kind. We don't have any recollections to what it is.
I don't know what this is, but I'm sure having fun doing it.
Put some on the... put some on the... it's the inside of the bowl.
I'm watching. I'm like, what if I'm watching through the keyhole?
You want me to put shit on the inside of the toilet bowl?
What are you, an animal? Or just all over it, maybe.
Alright, that's... I'm more familiar with that.
I walk... I'm so blind, I walk through the door.
I start doing bathroom graffiti with the shit log on different parts of the toilet.
Okay.
Just writing like, "Stevel was here for a good time, call Patrick."
Yeah.
Both of you, actually, yeah, you roll a religion check.
You roll a history check.
Okay.
What history? What? He can't see shit.
History of the shape he's feeling.
He's feeling it with all the purple.
Okay, I got a three.
- Or wait, no, I got a five.
- Okay, yeah.
You guys don't really, you guys are just sort of
hanging out in this bathroom, just treating this toilet
like shit, that's all.
But it's starting to probably make you feel a little good.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I feel a lot better treating this toilet like shit
than when I was being mean to my friends a few minutes ago.
- And I broke the door down somehow.
- I'm sorry for making-- - 'Cause I felt like
I had a magnetic attraction to treating this toilet like shit.
Listen, I'm sorry that I made you blind and that I made you stupid.
Okay?
That's... that was wrong of me.
You're well gracias, mi amigo.
No, that's that guy.
Rubbing.
Oh, I'm rubbing shit on this toilet.
Now I kinda get the appeal.
Okay.
is good yeah this toilet not I kick it roll attack roll that's a 19 six oh it's
a six but add your um add your strength to that too
so I'm still you miss yeah you just sort of with kicking it that made me even
more mad yeah you should try kicking it again I'm gonna try kicking it I'm gonna
try we're gonna do the ultimate kick no I'm do I'm kicking it you can't take my
kick okay don't even dare oh my god I'm getting such bad rolls today now you
wish he did the fucking ultimate kick well you can do your ultimate kick I'm
gonna do - I got a six I add strength to that yeah mm-hmm I think that's a plus
zero. You guys keep whiffing and rubbing shit on it. Yeah, I'm gonna kick again.
That's fine with me too. Okay, that's a 20.
Yeah, that you don't have to roll for. I got a 20 on my kick, so I kicked it.
Yeah, eat the poop. Yeah, you kick it, you keep kicking it, you're shoving the poop in its mouth.
My pants are still down and covered in shit, by the way. I'm flushing the handle a million times.
Yeah, I'm so blind and like I'm trying to kick and I keep kicking the poop out of his hand.
Come on. Yeah
You hear you hear when a bit of the poop slips slips out of your hand you hear it hit the sides of the boat
You know, so this the chute that goes down the rest of the boat you
Suddenly it clicks for you. There's is somebody missing here or something missing
Sullivanate poop
Sullivanate
most evils poop baby where is this coming from so
baby baby poop poop poop poop poop poop poop poop poop poop poop poop poop poop
What is happening to us? They're ready to party the crew starts singing the song yes
There is a frog shaped hole in the universe and suddenly you guys for once
I start crying kind of miss it a little bit
So is this is this toilet like it's like how the universe is like coping with
With a missing element. It's like kind of turning into other and my third and my third
I was blind and I saw it. Yeah, there's some lore as to why that toilet exists. Yes. All right, we can we can approach that
Next next session. We have to get Sullivan back. We have to get Sullivan back. This song was too beautiful
We have to get a normal toilet installed instead of this weird thing.
This is a dead body and there's poop piling up on it.
This is really starting to scare me.
Say goodbye
[Music]