[Music]
Last time on Trebuchet Village,
the boys realized that Gigi the Shaman stole the Prince Jumanji and took him for sure somewhere fucked up.
So they asked/interrogated their frenemies tit and for tat about where Gigi the shaman
went and through questioning, they found out he likely went to St. Anthony's Parish, a
smaller sect within the Terrifire Church in the city of Gal Gadot.
They traveled there, where they harassed a snake man who led the church, and met someone
named Gil, a friendly "orc" who told them where Gigi likely was, the baby kaiju manji
temple a little ways out of town. After traveling in that direction and getting an ID of the
temple and getting um, what the f- an ID? I must have been-
Idea.
An ID- I don't think I even-
Identification is what that stands for.
Yeah, getting a look at the temple, a visual of the temple nestled into the mountains.
It's so frazzled.
Yeah, I'm very annoyed by that. I don't know what I was doing.
you used his divination magic to see what was going on.
Why'd you say that to him?
No, the character.
You guys, he was-
Take it back.
We're playing it a little fast and loose with this intro.
Let the man finish.
I'm enjoying it.
He used his divination magic to see what was going on inside of it.
And it was some fucked up, clearly evil ritual type of shit.
Our crew waltzed in quietly, but not quietly enough, because some type of screaming, flaming
skull had charged into the main hall of the temple.
Dogen, possessed by insane prowess, blasted this thing to shit with one swipe of his battle
shovel, launching it back from where it came, with nobody even really knowing that that happened.
With that dealt with too quickly, they continued to rush forward down the hall, only just in
time to watch the ritual take place.
Many awful naked men biting and killing each other, sucking magic from a woman trapped
in a magical cage, and the poor Nard boy Prince Jumanji teleported with the
Terrifier's magic to Trebuchet village. Giggy, with his final breath, told the gang
the plan. That the boy will be the Terrifier reborn after the heartbroken
King Nardwar, tricked by the members of Giggy's crew at the St. Anthony's parish,
perform a ritual that brings a Terrifier back from wherever he fucked off to. He
then said to Evil Stevel you were not supposed to be there,
Echoing the cackler fiend that was in Mount Honest Doodle all those sessions ago
The woman trapped in the cave turned out to be the sister of the white woman of the woods the white woman of the caves
Misnomer of sorts since they were in a temple who told the boys that she could make them go
Really really really really stupid really really really fast. I don't think it's stupid. I think it's a cool story
Can you just be transported into a new world for once in your life
*laughter*
I'm in the world.
Oh look at that, a butterfly.
I can see my ceramics so clearly.
Tree?
Well no, it's a cave.
Cave tree.
I do remember there's cave trees.
So our heroes and Sullivan
arrived back at Sticky Fingers Joint
where it seems an uneasy alliance
between Sticky Fingers gang, Pleasure Men, and the Brave Lions.
Plus, Trunchbull has begun.
Their plan is to kill the king.
And so you guys have arrived, and Sticky Fingers has just told you,
"You've arrived just in time. We're here to kill the king."
Um, so, you guys know now that what's going on here.
You don't know if they know. They just know that, in the words of Sticky Finger.
The king's been getting too crazy, okay? He's starting to kill people, he's getting really
fucked up. Even the pleasure men decided to join up with us and these brave lion guys.
So uh, we got a plan ready and in the works if you guys want in. Since you proceeded to,
I guess, destroy my wall, uh, Kool-Aid Man style. Um, who is a dwarf. Also.
Oh yeah, I know him.
Yeah, I bet you do.
He's red.
Yeah. He's red, he's completely red.
He drinks a lot of Kool-Aid and he loves Kool-Aid the famous drink.
Yeah, that's why.
Okay, well, I gotta watch what I say.
Uh, so uh, yeah, you guys want in or what?
Hmm.
Yeah.
What?
No, I don't care. Let's just kill the king. I don't give a shit anymore.
You really wanna kill...
I mean, I've gone through enough bullcrap.
Why are you guys killing the king?
Because things have gotten crazy here.
You guys haven't been bad to your own flank.
That's a pretty good reason.
That's a great reason.
That is a good reason. I'm sorry.
Oh, I'll explain.
All right, I'm with Patrick now.
First of all, I thought you guys were dead after that mountain-
We are.
-honest-
I'm dead tired.
I'll tell you that.
Wait, are you dead or dead tired?
Yeah, I just flew in.
Boy, are my arms dead tired.
You did not fly in.
I saw you run in.
I just ran in.
Boy, are my legs tired.
Okay, I believe that.
So, ever since the prince died or whatever, and you guys, I guess-
No, he's not dead. He's just-
What?
There's some bullcrap that happened.
They're trying to turn him into-
God, we should have ridden the hell-
Yeah, so they're making happen. All right. I'm gonna tell you this scary the terrifying there's actually all right
So the terrifier is trying to come back into a boy
Yeah, the terrifier is a pedophile. I can I can I could try to all right Sullivan
So you talk about if you mess this up? Oh my god. I didn't see that Wow you just have like no presence
That's amazing. He kind of blends in. Yeah, he walked all the way here. We were transported
He just got you. I keep thinking he's a rock. Look at Sullivan's legs, it's like realistic
Spongebob calves, just like super jacked. Yeah, well, so from what I understood is
that there's a group of guys who are trying to bring the terrifier back by
having him enter a boy in a word or three words and yeah so we knew the boy
He was with us. We were trying to bring him back here.
Yeah, it was his boyfriend.
No, it was not my boyfriend. Please don't say that.
I'm already the, what am I, the sucking dick guy?
Sucking penis guy.
Yeah, the sucking penis guy.
Alright, well, so, anyway, that's what we think is our movie.
Look at me, Sullivan. Look, I'm you.
Yeah, they're you. They're being you.
That's what you do.
You like to choke on it.
Well, regardless of what he likes to do with penis, this is interesting news.
He was also making that up. That's not true.
[Laughter]
He's a liar, too.
You see also the-- a handsome blonde fellow turned to you guys,
wearing the Brave Lyons armor on, and he's--
Patrick's trying to break my chair while we record.
I always sit in this chair and it makes that sound.
I'll tell you what, not as loud as it's in tactics, but it does make the sound.
So, and he says to you guys, "Ah, chum to meet you.
My name is McElwee Highlander.
I'm the lieutenant of this area of the Brave Lions.
I'm glad we have three brave advantage--" and it looks like a frog as well.
This is exciting.
"You guys are going to join up with us."
He's taking a picture.
He's like, "Sorry, he's a bit eager."
I want to put that guy's face in the toilet.
Yeah, no, I don't want to use his body like a boppet. No, this is all these are all sentiments
I'm gonna paint some real quick. Well, don't do that because we do know and I won't do that
We just do we do need him for this fight
So look look regardless of whether or not the boys alive or whatever the terror fire is coming back
The Kings been mistreating everybody, you know, if you're a petty thief, you're supposed to be doing grand larceny
He wants everybody to both do more crime and then you get punished harder for it
He just wants everything to be completely debauched and insane like before
Well before they freed the slaves before they freed people like myself and evil Steve. Oh
Basically, he's trying to bring it back to the way it was word to my slaves. Yeah
What well we've all been waiting for that
You held your finger up so long before you said that I did let make sure I got it in
So, um
Basically, he seems to have gone mad because his son is dead. I guess if we can tell him that his son is alive
That would be really good. So where's his son?
He's dead
But not really all that dead
so, uh, and you see also listening in is a
one of the pleasure men
Who says my name is Barnabas pleasure. I don't want you going near the child. You're not the first to tell me that
Just based off my face and sort of general demeanor
I'm the high priest of this region for pleasure, man
I believe I can explain what's going on here based on what you've said seems
they've sent the boy into the terrifier realm a place where you are trapped in fear and
That would be probably where the terrifier would have access to him and be able to air
Use him to come back
So he's not dead. He's sort of a stillborn
But, uh...
So it doesn't matter if we kill the king, really,
because the Terrifier's going to come back.
I mean, well, if the king is somehow part of this ritual, then...
All right.
We would have to stop the king from doing his part of the ritual.
Sullivan, do you remember if he was a part of the ritual?
Well, I mean, he was...
Yeah, I mean, they said that the ritual's going to be carried out.
So I imagine the king is a part of it.
So we got to go to the Terrifier Realm and get the boy out of the Terrifier Realm and then kill the king?
Yes, but to get him out of the Terrifier Realm is quite a difficult task.
So we shouldn't do it?
Well, no.
Can you do it?
I can try, but we're going to need-
I'll give you 20 gold pieces.
No, I mean, I don't want the terr-
Look, I want the Terrifier back, but on the Pleasureman's terms, not whatever the hell these St. Anthony's people are doing.
Okay, so where he was the plan
Today the the king is doing his like a serum
We didn't know what the context of it was, but he was trying to honor his dead son or whatever some jerk-off shit
Who cares?
but anyway
he was gonna climb on top of the claw and he was gonna do on the claw castle and do something with that and
Anyway, we had snipers trained ready to go
We've got some people with some real
Ballistas ready to sort of take him out and then we were gonna have the brave lion dildo over here
Bring his troops out front and sort of storm the castle
I was gonna go in the castle sneak in there just in case the king didn't die and also to you know
Loot do things like that
Meanwhile the pleasurement over here had an inkling that something was going on back where Honest Mount Honest doodle was now
This makes more sense about what was going on
They're probably trying to do something with bringing back the terrifier. So we're Mount home. Yeah, we just said that
Well, no, I'm doing well
I'm just saying that we picked up on that they were doing something there and now it makes us down
We kind of feel like we know what they're doing. So we have this sort of three-pronged
Plan look I just need some some or coffee or something. I'm
I'm beat. Well, I think I could help you with that. Who's this guy? Yeah trunchbull
Yodar crap, that's my uncle. Yeah, how's it going? How's it going Patrick? How you doing? Yeah. All right
We gotta talk too, buddy. It's time.
Are you mad at me?
No, no, no. I can never be mad at you. Look at us.
- You look exactly the same. - We look exactly the same.
We're in different ages and we look the same.
Not even a question, except I am two feet taller than you.
And it's time that you become two feet taller.
[Gasp]
Not than me, but you know.
I'm gonna grow?
It's time. You're ready for puberty.
[Laughter]
Your uncle's gonna put you through puberty?
Congratulations!
I'm gonna make you a man Patrick!
I've been waiting for this day for so long.
Look, it's not a pleasant process.
But it needs to happen.
If you're gonna do this whole thing...
Come here, come here.
Go to him!
Don't hesitate!
I wanna see this.
Yeah, you guys can figure out sort of what you wanna do
for the whole
terror fire plan in a second.
second. Let's-
We got important business to take care of.
We got important business to do.
So Verdans in the Forgotten Realms lore have mutations and growth spurts that they go through.
In the Trebuchet Village lore, there is sort of a passing of the torch where an uncle and
his nephew have to slow dance.
That is so lovely.
That's so romantic.
And during the slow dance-
platonic during the slow dance. You're going to undergo the mutations that you
were meant to undergo at this stage in your life.
Mm-hmm. So is it painful? It will depend on the mutations. I have, I scoured the
forums and found a number of mutations that are out there. We're going to
roll some dice. Oh yeah, we're going to roll some dice. And you're going to go through some
mutations. The first one that is going to happen regardless, you know what it is.
I think we've talked about it before.
- You don't want to save it for last?
I think we should save it for last.
- We will.
- I think save it for last.
- Well, I'm not going to say it.
- Yeah.
- And then there's a couple,
there's one other mutation that's going to happen,
which is that you're going to,
we know already, which is that you are going to grow.
You are going to be the first tall member of this party
of all short characters.
- So.
- I will grow a cardigan.
- Come over here, come on Patrick, come on.
Come on, I drew a little circle over here.
We're going to dance.
- Yeah, right, I'm getting in the dancing circle.
- Okay, you got to put your hands on my hips,
put my hands on your shoulders okay? Can I do the shoulders? Hey yeah all right fine
I'll put that I guess that makes more sense now that I think about the way that
meant means you gay. No Dave you better watch it and you guys start to you guys
put your hands in there. You better hope he's not gay. Look you know well you know
when I knew that we were able to. They would have faked it? Yeah that ruins the whole
puberty. You shrink. I shrink if my uncle's gay? You shrink to the size of an ant. Look I'm not gay you saw me fuck those spirits. I didn't see you
- Did you fuck the white woman, did you fuck the cave lady too?
I don't remember if I asked her.
- Yeah, I tried to.
- You fucked a cave lady?
- The white woman of the caves.
- I fingered her for a bit and then she was like,
"I got work in the morning."
- TMI, Uncle Trudge, but I don't know.
- Tell me more.
- Well, I was trying to, so I was looking for the--
- Can we just get through with the dance?
- 'Cause not every woman likes the same thing, you know?
So like the white woman in the woods had sort of a like,
"Yo, you gently rub the clit
"and then you gotta go in a little bit."
And then the cave woman had a thing where,
I really had to go in there and sort of go up, right?
- Oh, I know the up thing, yeah.
- Yeah, the up thing.
She liked that.
Some of them, it's like too much for her, like that.
And so I was getting kind of tired, to be honest.
And then she was like, "Oh, I got work in the morning anyway.
"You seem tired."
And I was like, "No, I'm not tired."
But I was.
- You ever hit the elbow with a bitch?
- No, no.
Oh, well.
- You know what I'm saying?
- Well, we can talk about the white woman
of the forest later.
Different than the woods, let me tell you.
- There's a different forest at work?
- There are so many white women.
White women are sort of one of the many spirits of this world.
Anyway, let's slow dance so you can get taller.
(laughing)
So you begin slow dancing,
and we're gonna do some rolls.
So I have my dice here.
Just should've had these out already.
- I know, right?
I can't believe you.
- You're the worst DM ever.
- I am the worst DM ever.
So first, you're gonna start,
as you start slow dancing,
He says, "You know, I knew the second that you were just
"sipping on juice while you're watching me fuck that lady,
"I knew that we were gonna, you know,
"we're gonna be homies, you know,
"uncle and nephew kind of homies."
And as he's saying this--
- I said we were before.
- Oh, that's my boy, and you start to grow a bit taller.
And so you are now two feet taller.
- How tall does that make him?
- Probably like five one or something,
which is probably the tallest,
I think 'cause you're probably five, maybe like--
- I wanna be five seven.
you're five seven which is a great height by the way and yeah so you're five seven
and he's like whoa look at you pretty tough over Dan you guys just love
dancing you're like a inch taller than your your uncle trunch ball or the
famous adventure yeah and you still have these like heavy ass son now dragging on
the ground as you're dancing and now what we're gonna need to do is okay first
First we're gonna roll a d20.
- Okay.
- What'd you get?
- I got a redo.
- He got a three.
- What'd you get?
- I got a three.
- That's fine.
Okay.
And now roll a d100.
- Do we have that?
- Yeah, you roll these two together
and then one of them is the tens place one.
- I thought the ones place.
- Dude, I wish.
- What'd you get?
- 21.
Okay. Okay. It's kind of weird. And then roll the D100 one more time. What'd you get? 94.
Okay, roll that again. What'd you get? 18. Okay. Why'd I have to roll again for the 94?
I only have so many on this list. So, okay. So, first thing that happens is, what color
was your hair?
Well, it was gray like an old man's.
Okay. It changes.
To what?
What color? Imagine a color in your head.
Silver.
Silver? Your hair changes silver. Okay. Next, this one's weird. The proportions of your facial
features change really so your nose just gets really small like Michael Jackson
small your eyes get huge your mouth stays the same you still look like like
normal but like within reason I look like I look like Alan Alda with like a
like a like he ate like a warhead yeah yeah exactly yeah he looked like the
out all the warhead. The last one, it's my favorite so far. You gain an eye.
(Laughter)
On my face or can it be somewhere else?
It doesn't specify so I'm going to let you choose.
Gigantic eye on my belly.
Okay, cool. Well I guess we'll figure out the mechanical implications of that later.
You should put it on the back of your head.
Okay, gigantic eye on the back of my head.
my head okay yeah so it's just like like it just opens up and there's a big eye
in the back your head and your silver hair is falling behind the eye and it
blinks and it kind of parts the the hairs behind it you know it was like
whoa that is that is a weird one why the why do you look so fucking normal oh all
my pubes are tentacles it is not great I see you yeah tell you what it's great
for the girls but for just looking at him yeah I'm in front of you dipshit yeah
you see me and of course I'm talking to people behind me there's no I even
fucking works last but not least hmm your balls your big heavy balls start to
rumble and scrunch crap and then you start to become more and more normal
sized. As they start shrinking I jump in a motorboat and one last time.
It's like as you're going like it's getting like your the pitch is getting higher as the
balls get smaller.
And there you go now you got those regular balls pretty nice right?
I miss the old ones.
Yeah I missed mine too. Would you ever do the thing with the skin where you? I would do
shadow puppets with mine.
Me too yeah.
It was good times good times.
- Did you ever keep a coin in there?
- Oh, I kept so many coins in there.
I think, honestly, when they shrunk,
I feel like I lost $700.
Not even kidding.
Don't know where it went.
- I was about to sit down on his balls
and they like shrank out from under me
and I fell on the ground.
- All right, we don't have to,
you can stop, we can stop slow dancing now.
That was fun though.
- All right.
- Oh God, I miss my balls so much.
- Where does balls go, demon?
- Well, the balls, they go to all the other mutations.
sort of how it works. You tell me that eye on the back of his head is one of those balls. Yeah it's a ball.
I can smell it. It's sort of a ball. And your face, don't worry about that too much.
You look like you ate a warhead though. Yeah, it's fine. All right, yeah. Cool, all right.
Where do I start getting acne? So now that you've done all that, so you have this eye on the back
your head. So, I mean, I'm going to say that like, God, any like perception checks that
require visuals, I guess like any dexterity saving throws that involve like visual cues
you have advantage on, like period. Like there's just no reason why having a third eye in like
a literal blind spot.
What's my other, my regular eyes are so big now.
Yeah, right. You're just-
You get a lot of vision here.
Yeah.
Patrick, Patrick Yoda was more ear focused. You're a lot more visual focused. Yeah. I like that one.
Yeah. There are some funny ones on here. If we keep doing these characters, I want to like,
every time we do this, I have more mutations to you. But yeah, cool. So, you see Sticky Fingers
like, "Okay, so, uh..." "Hey, I see you." "That was great." "I see you." "No, I..." "My eyes are big
now? Yeah, get used to it to be honest. Wait, hold on, I'm gonna turn around.
I'm never gonna get used to that. I'm gonna be honest. I still see you. Yeah, no, I'm aware now. What is
that like? Is it sort of a... what is that experience? Well, the back... I mean, it
sucks. I mean, there's one big eye in the back and then, I mean, two. They're also
So pretty big.
- I'm also gonna say that you're gonna get expertise in--
- Seeing.
- In perception.
(laughing)
And seeing in general.
So expertise is just you add your proficiency bonus again.
If I'm correct about that.
I haven't played a bard in a long time.
So let me just double check.
Yeah, you just double your proficiency bonus on it.
- Okay.
- So just when we roll,
you'll just add your proficiency bonus again.
So I think your proficiency bonus is still,
I think it's plus three now.
Perception?
Yeah, so whenever you do a perception check, you'll just add an additional +3.
And he has advantage?
On dexterity saves, yeah.
Oh my god.
Yeah, no, it's cool to mutate.
Why can't I get mutations?
You didn't go through puberty.
You didn't go through and kill everything in the game.
No, I don't.
You killed the Screaming Flavor.
You don't remember that.
The Screaming Flavor.
I think we called it that at the time.
I don't have my notes here.
I'm pretty sure we called it the speed screaming flamer.
No, because every time I do a session I delete my notes after.
So I can't confirm or deny what we called it.
And what Cam did to the screaming...
He heard a screaming flamer for...
Cam heard a screaming flamer and he immediately got...
Yeah, he took out his shovel.
He took out his shovel.
He's fucked up, brother.
You made Ruth the screaming flamer.
So far, you two are the most problematic of this episode.
It was a flaming screamer, okay?
Yeah.
[Chuckles]
Mmm.
That's a pretty good trick.
So anyway, uh, he goes up to you, uh, Sticky Fringe and says,
"So, I was thinking, based on the sort of the expertise we got going here,
you, Dogen, you could join that asshole out in the field of battle.
You, Patric, you're coming with me. We're gonna sneak into the castle.
Mm-hmm.
You, you go with the Pleasuremen.
I want to be with my friends.
You could, I guess you could join up with one of them if you want to instead.
Fuck you Pleasuremen. I'm going with Dogen.
Okay, cool. You'll join Dogen in the field of battle.
The Pleasuremen will just sort of go on their own in that direction.
You're gonna sneak into the castle?
With me? Or do you wanna go in the battle too?
I'm gonna sit in the back and I'm gonna look through a big telescope.
Okay, so you're going backwards?
Yep.
Oh my god. Damn. That's cool.
We can just send... We'll send the wizard.
He'll teleport here and he'll go with you.
What wizard?
The wizard.
That guy knows about it, I point straight.
Yeah, I mean, I don't know if he knows where you guys are.
He can scry us.
I guess he could, he might have done that already.
But, I don't know.
He should do that.
He should do that already.
He did that and he's on his way.
And then Sullivan will go in the other, whatever other place.
Sullivan, you're going to be the front line of the battle.
No, no, no, no.
You can sneak into the mountain.
Sullivan, you're going to go with the pleasure men and they're going to touch you.
Yeah, Sullivan, the pleasure men are going to treat you so right.
so right no go ahead
going to come little frog yes Sullivan you're an agent of pleasure
yes I've heard tell of the sucking penis man make sure they're there they're
ready that's a that's a not my name that was just a one-time thing as a one-time
name not like that was never I think it was a thing he did no I've never done
anything like this is what he does
in your religion. Oh yes we like all kinds of pleasure and all the different forms
that comes. Here's a piece of candy. That's ooh butterscotch. Oh my god. I knew you'd like that.
Yes I did. So yeah I mean you guys want to like start doing this so the order
yeah because the order of it will be that the people going out to battle are
gonna sort of kind of conceal themselves and get ready because the king is gonna
to go do whatever ceremony he's going to do.
You guys, the people sneaking into the castle, you can either
go in through the front before like the king is assassinated
or attempt to attempt to assassination.
Are we going to the Terrifiers realm at all?
Right now, it's well, I guess you could keep talking to the
pleasurement about it, but it sounds like he doesn't have
what he needs for it, but you can talk to him about it and
figure out what that is.
Because should we I feel like we should right?
I feel like that's the correct thing to do.
I feel like there's like a three-pronged plan here.
Yeah, I actually heard that.
That God set into place.
No, you could try to go into the Terrifiers' realm now.
You have a connection to God.
You could try to go into the Terrifiers' realm now.
You could talk to the Pleasure Man about how to do that.
Does your, wait.
There's all different ways you can go about this.
The Oreo God, does he know the Terrifier?
I could ask.
He could be in a kind of similar realm.
Maybe the Terrifier realm and the Oreo realm are like neighbors.
Well the Oreo God's evil too and the Terrifier's evil, right?
So probably the Terrifier.
Wait, you didn't bring a ring!
Yeah, I put an Oreo in my mouth.
Yeah, you went Oreo-ing.
That's how I...
Okay.
Alright, and the Oreo God appears.
I have not thought of a voice for him.
Okay, here we go.
Wazzup!
He's cool as hell.
I love Oreos!
You definitely already did have a voice for him.
It wasn't. It was this. Just keep going.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, the mop voice always.
What's going on, Dogen?
Do you--you being evil?
Oh, hell yeah.
We're totally not gonna try and kill the
ultimate evil god or anything.
Definitely not doing that.
But do you happen to know where he is or how to
get to his realm by any chance?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, like from--I can just sort of
walk next door, but for you,
You're gonna have to use some sort of magic.
But the particulars of it, hold on one second.
- What if you just pulled us up?
- Yeah, just reach down here and--
- No, I'm small, you can carry me.
- I just grew.
- You might need-- - I'm still pretty small though.
- You're gonna need-- - Five seven is a reasonable--
- Five seven, it's tiny.
- To find the vessel. - Might as well be one inch tall.
- It's true, if you're below five nine, you're a midget.
- You're gonna need to fuck, no.
We're gonna need to fuck what?
You're gonna need to find the vessel wherever the thing that's trapped into the realm.
And we fuck it?
No, do not fuck the vessel.
BLEGH!
Because isn't the vessel the prince?
Is the...
Patridge?
Oh my god.
I don't remember.
That's what the lawyers tell you to say.
[laughter]
Oh, I don't remember. I'm crazy.
And from there,
You're gonna need to probably try to...
...uh, sort of coax it out.
Make it try to become whole.
Sometimes it's just something intimate needs to occur, not fucking, you creep.
What are you saying? Whole?
When you're saying something intimate, now I'm weirded out by you.
No, something sentimental.
[Evil laugh]
Like...
...the tears of a father.
That could help.
What about the blood of a father?
That could do it too, it'll just look different.
Okay.
Alright.
It's gonna be different if it's the blood, but it is possible.
Baaaaah!
[Laughter]
Sorry.
Sorry about that.
So we gotta make a daddy cry.
[Laughter]
Baaaaah!
That's a yes.
I'm gonna go get that double stuff back!
(laughter)
- It was good talking to you.
- Whatever.
(laughter)
- Why so rude?
- What is it?
Whatever, it's my God.
- You're one disciple, dude.
- No, he's gone, he's gone.
- What?
Maybe I'll go back to dirt.
- Hey guys, I just came up with this.
Wazzup!
(laughter)
- That is amazing.
- I'm gonna keep doing it.
- Okay, cool.
Yeah, so, you hear the pleasure man, he's like,
no that old chick's out, that's what I was gonna probably
something like that. It's crazy we all heard him. Yeah, no, yeah, well you sort of
established that as what's happening in the fiction so I'm just sort of rolling
with it. I like the Oreo God better than the dirt God. Yeah. Yeah. This guy's wassup. Yeah, he lets me eat Oreos too.
Yeah, the Oreos have dirt. Oh, you follow, you follow Dogen? Yeah, the Oreo God.
Dogen the Oreo God. Oh, okay, never mind then. I was gonna say that would have been
hilarious. That guy makes his disciples eat dirt and you don't even need to. Yeah,
I never did that before. Okay. So yeah I mean you guys can, in that case, I mean
you can all go to the castle if like your job, if you feel like, like it's up to
you what you want to do. I need to make that king cry. Yeah. You make him cry?
And I have a beautiful song I can perform for him. I can cry with laughter from my
famous comedy routine. And I'll stand in the room. Okay so uh. So I guess what wait
should we all sneak into the building then? Because then we can go see the king.
Yeah sure I mean you could do whatever you want I was just. What's the quickest
way to make the king cry? Onions I don't know what the. Whoa hold on what is that?
Wait, what are onions?
Yes.
Oh, they're like a-
You've never heard of onions, Patrick?
You've never heard of a-
You've never eaten an onion?
Is there one here? Can I see it?
Yeah, there's one right here.
It's literally right there, on the ground, in front of us.
It's been there the whole time.
It's a native species.
Hold on, let me take a look.
Anything stinky pretty much grows in Trebuchet Village.
Let me take a look at this real quick.
Yeah, you're looking at an onion.
Oh my god.
Do you like the onion? I'm like peeling it. Yeah. Well you don't really want to
peel it too much. Yeah because in this fantasy world an onion is a type of
animal. I'm just I'm peeling it. You hear the onion go... That's right hot dogs and onions are both animals in this world.
shit out of it. It's like oh my god it's like a shallot but big.
All right what you guys want to do? You guys want to, what do you guys want to do?
First of all I'm eating this onion. Yeah but I feel like we don't need all
three of us to go make the king cry right? That's true. Whatever man I'll go
with the fucking pleasure man dude. Yeah but we need the king's tears.
Yeah so you go get the king's tears. Okay.
I'll fight in the battle you go with the pleasure man. Whatever. I sort of line
this up just to have but like you guys can do what you want I'm already with the
pleasure man okay already at the battle yeah I actually finished the entire
thing you know me too I saw the entire I can mean me me it was such a sad ending
- might as well just turn this off now all right I'm gonna get a drink all
right cool so yes you guys are all sort of a lining up to your locations the
newly tall Patrick Yodar. I hit, can I, hold on, I hit my head on a shelf immediately. Yeah, you just
like keep, why'd you do that? He's tall now. Ah crap, I'm so tall and I hit my head on a shelf.
It was because I was so tall. Actually I hit my head on the ground. I feed him my dookie.
Feed him a piece of dookie. Yeah, he likes it. Yeah, he likes it. I mean
And so you're you guys I mean, I don't if you wanted to go through the dungeon passage or try to go just through the front
door
Either those are valid to try though Patrick
Probably gonna go dungeon. Mm-hmm. Okay, so we'll resolve that in a second. You are Dogen are lining up with
McElwee
Highlander
in the sort of lining up with his soldiers. So I'm lying outside you see
like a huge crowd of terrifier born and also scaredy cats.
Yeah and I will really quick I like tap Macaulay Highlander on the on the
shoulder. Hi! I have an idea for you. Okay. Abolish ice.
That's a... let me write that down my ancestors will love it. I mean the other
thing. Progeny? Descendants? Descendants! You're welcome. Yeah, he writes that down a
hundred times. I came up with it. It's millions of years ago. I did it. And so you guys are
sort of like staking out the location because basically what it is is there's
a ceremony today to bring back to sort of honor the prince is what the like
ostensibly what it is. Now that Mount Honestoodle is gone, he's doing it on top of Klawe Castle.
So there's all these people outside of Klawe Castle, mostly Terrafire-born, but also Scaredy
Cats. And the Scaredy Cats are slaves again, which wasn't true in Trebuchet Village. So
they've been turned into slaves again, the king's madness. And you, Evil Stevel, you and the
Pleasure Men are sort of just going back around. So the way you came when you first got towards
Honest Doodle, that first session, you're going with them towards Mount Honest Doodle, which is,
you know, sort of on the other side of town, sort of away from Claw Castle, or where it once was,
right? So, the first thing that's going to happen is you, Patrick, you're going down to where the
dungeon is. And so, you're with Sticky Fingers and with a couple of his guys, and he's like,
"Yeah, so this is the way I used to break people out of all the time when we had to get them out
out of the dungeon because they got caught doing one thing and another thing.
Yeah, so you know that we won't get caught down here because you know everything
about this place. Well yeah, things have probably changed since I've been down here.
That's shit. Yeah, sorry about that. And as you sort of approach this like
sort of underground dungeon entrance you do see like an orc like standing guard
outside of anything. So for example that's new. Okay. I mean we
We could kill him.
Do you want to kill him?
Do you want to talk to him?
You know, it's a day of celebration.
I think we should kill him.
You want to try to talk to him?
Kill me?
Okay.
And so, yeah, you guys are about to, we're going to line you up for that.
By the way, did we get any kind of short rest before?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You, yeah, sorry about that.
I forgot about that.
Yeah, you guys should have had a short rest while you were in the area, so just roll some
of your hit die.
I think you have like full hit points. A short rest or a long rest? It would be a short rest.
A long rest. How many hit die do you have?
I have 21 out of 21. Does a short rest restore any abilities or anything?
It depends on the class. For paladins... I guess I can just do it on here and see what happens.
What menu is short rest on here? I'm trying to find it. So yeah I think it might be a little weird on the...
I think it's this campfire thing. Yeah on the app. Is it weird on the app or no? Okay good
Yeah, you would just get I mean short rest for
Paladins they they don't think they get their they don't get their spells back. I think until a long rest if I'm correct
Yeah, I can't wait. Where is it? I can't find left. Mm-hmm. Oh, yeah. Got it
Short rest. Mm-hmm
Yeah, and I think clerics also don't get their spells back until a long rest. Oh
(WARLOCK NOISES)
I should really have just like a chart for this.
It just never like...
Well, it just automatically does it on D&D Beyond.
Yeah, I think it's just Warlock is like the only one that gets it.
I got back my Fury of the Small, that's all, but it doesn't matter.
Yeah, Warlock's the only one that got it by short rest, right?
That's the whole thing. Okay, cool.
I always like forget to remember that.
That's a good long cramp.
Yeah.
What the hell?
So, yeah, I mean...
You can't hear me.
So you should have three hit die to spend, EvilSteevel.
Huh?
have three hit die to spend. Yeah. So and your hit die is I believe a d8. Yeah. It just does
it on D&D Beyond. Oh, okay. So that's it for you. That's what I was trying to tell you.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You are a monster. You are a bad person. That's right.
Okay, cool. So meanwhile, yeah, Evil Seal, you've been walking with the pleasure men and,
you know, probably talking about whatever it is that pleasure men talk about.
And you see out of the corner of your eye
that little cackler fiend that you first saw when you were in the mountain.
What do I see out of the corner of my eye? Oh, I think it might be that cackler fiend.
You! You! Cackler fiend! Step no closer!
No, no, no, no. I mean no harm. You better stop cackling right now.
I can't, I'm cursed, that's what we do!
If it's a curse, well, you're welcome to hang out with me.
Okay, listen, listen, listen, you have to-
You weren't supposed to be there, okay?
But you were.
Beware!
At the mountain, at the mountain!
He's like trying to find the words, he's like struggling.
I'm under there?
The Terrifier doesn't want to come back.
He's-
Master's tummy hurts.
He's sick, sick and tired.
Does not want to come back if he comes back we'll all be killed
You have to stop it. You have to how can I trust you cackling?
fiend
See, I don't know
I'm scared. I don't want to get killed by master
He's so hungry now
He can't get through the ramen. He wants the ramen though
Let me see the cacklers looking like despondent and just looking around
You see the pleasure man, the head of the pleasure man, Barnabas, goes,
"Hey, is this guy bothering you?"
"Yeah, he's fucking cackling while I'm trying to think."
"Hey, why don't you fuck off? We're trying to do something here."
But he did say something crazy about some terrifier.
Well, he said, I think he said, "Terrifier, ah-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha, doesn't want to come to here."
"The terrifier doesn't want to come back."
"Oh, okay. I mean, we don't want him to come back anyway."
"Good, good. I just, just, he wasn't supposed to be there."
"There, okay, I don't need to know.
You're just, okay, fine, come with us."
And takes a fiend along with you.
You, Dogen, you're standing by ready for the battle.
And you see the sort of field of all these like baddies
and then they have their sort of scaredy cat slaves.
And you look up at Clock Castle
and you see King Narwhal come out.
And you know, he looks like tired and like fucked up,
like angry, like a kind of like deep anger and sadness
from what you can see all the way on top of Claw Castle.
And he shouts like some sort of chant
that you can't understand.
And he holds aloft the sort of like semi corpse of his son.
And as he does.
- Ooh, that was a close one.
- Yeah, it was.
It shouldn't count.
Yeah, it almost rolled off the edge.
A ballast, like a ballista, shoots from across the way and you see McKelvey turn to you and
he goes, "Now's our time!"
He's like so excited for battle.
And the ballista fires out and you see the king and he's like doing his chant and the
giant fucking arrow just like gets him in the gut.
He's gonna take some damage from that.
Oh, ooh.
Ooh, okay.
And he just gets fucked up in the gut,
and you see all the people now in the front are like turning around like,
"Rrrrraaargh!"
Those are all monsters.
And then you see McKelvey goes,
"Brave lions, attack!"
And you all sort of get up and run out.
And now you guys are all informing up,
getting ready to fight.
You see the other, there's these trolls and these goblins
and these ghouls and zombies and no conscience
and they're all sort of getting ready to fight.
And so now we're gonna do two roll initiatives,
one for you, Patrick Yodar, and then one for you.
And then we'll do you soon too.
- I love that.
- Oh yeah.
- Pat got a four.
- I saw.
- I got a four.
- Okay.
- See, I should have just done that.
- I got a seven, two roll.
- You roll.
- I got a four.
I got a three. Four town.
No, that's a four, that's a seventeen.
What?
There's a three and I added one for my initiative.
Oh, well I didn't add anything for my initiative. Hold on.
You guys are so bad at this game.
I'm insanely good at it. I'd do a backflip.
My initiative.
Roll.
Alright, fine. You wanna see how good I am at this fucking game?
You're gonna have to roll though.
Roll. I'm rolling it.
Roll. Oh, wait, so that's just seven.
Three. So you also got a three?
Uh, but I gotta add my backflip score.
Yeah, I figured it was a seven.
Plus seventeen is a natural twenty.
- And Natural 20.
- Nice, okay.
So--
- Have you been adding the initiative
or whatever, like all the bonuses?
- Yeah, I always add it.
- Oh.
- I have your sheets up too here.
- Have you been shutting the fuck up?
- We talk about it every single session.
We say, I say, remember you add something
for your initiative.
- Well, I always forget to add it,
but it's nice--
- Every time I say it.
- No, I'm just saying that Patches is a good DM
because he adds it for me.
- I do everything.
I do everything.
(laughing)
I do it all.
Okay, cool.
and then who we are what's that going to be who yes
or use
yes it should be bad for you
it should not be a good time for you call it is
so yeah all this is happening at once you would stick your fingers charging the
work
sticky fingers is going to go first on this or disorder like my uh...
completely taken by surprise
you are sticking fingers he's a gnome
uh... he's pretty fucking fast and he takes a he's got dual daggers
he's running up to this guy
And you're running up with him, so you're both like...
Can I just be walking with my hands in my pockets?
Yeah, you're walking with your hands in your pockets.
But because he's getting a surprise round on him, he's going to have advantage.
Um, okay.
Six plus five.
Okay, that's going to hit because of his plus on his daggers.
And now, his double daggers. What do I have him doing for damage?
Ooh, baby. Okay.
Da da da da.
And...
Nice, okay, so he just like runs up to this organ just like
Like just like jumps up around him and slices him up
And meanwhile you were cut
Dogen Dogen you have a you and and McKelvey are squaring up on a troll like a pretty big troll, okay?
and it's gonna be
The trolls turn first unfortunately. No, he's going to attack
He's gonna attack actually the soldiers in front of McKelvey first
So, let's get that up. Oh yeah. And so, he's going to take like a giant fucking club that
he has. And there's all these other battles and skirmishes going on. You see the brave
lions are trying to hold their own, but they're going up against like giant creatures. It's
like going too hot. So, Troll's going to attack. Awesome. Where did I get? Four. Nice. Okay.
That doesn't count. It rolled on the floor. That's - no, what are you talking about? We
don't play it as it lies. What are you talking about? That's bad for the Tim. Yeah it's bad
for the troll. Why are you making him re-roll? I'm re-rolling it. Don't re-roll it! Oh I
want to. Oh my god. Patrick's trying to get me to lose the game. So yeah, the troll goes
in and he swings down on the soldiers and the soldiers are able to sort of get out of
the way and are sort of able to dodge. The troll's going to try to attack again. And
yeah, the troll is just like sort of swinging his club and missing. He's taken way too much
by surprise. I hear I hear Patrick's voice in the back of my head trying to get me
to walk into the club but I'm resisting it. Oh shit! Walk in there motherfucker!
I am gonna actually am gonna retcon something because I should have mentioned
this before. Each of you has these walking talking stones. I totally forgot.
I was like I was so excited about that just in case you guys decided to did
decide to split up. But you all have these walking talking stones so you can
communicate with each other throughout. They make an insanely loud "kshh" sound
whenever they start up though. So if anyone's sneaking anywhere you just have
to be careful about it. But uh... Okay then no one talk to me.
Patrick how's the dungeon going? Shut up. Are you sneaking yet Patrick? I'm in the
middle of killing some of the things you're still at
just tell you there's a lot going on right now i just
i need time i'm gonna throw this thing out just tell me when you're speaking
also i don't know over i'm sneaking right now over
okay i want to know if you have a good
okay thank you for not talking to don't make my mission any harder
patrick come on
fucking fuck up this or you can't hold on i'm talking to my best friend
yeah i i i like i like put it in my pocket call him your best friend i have
to best friends who are they name them right now over over
the dogan and steve-o
uh...
she didn't say over yet you can talk it over over and not so little over
the does everstone
that box all of the night i i i don't like that all that over just right now
that we have the time for the chest
right now that we have the time to talk about this
do you notice that day
home like that and i really don't want to be nice to him over
uh... yeah it was coming you know he was my boss for a little bit and you know
and as soon as we got blasted to the
fuckin
channel where we were over the fuck happened to be plus what is he's like a
monkey
so that's not
i think he's a i think he's a type of kid
i think i think you put some kind of enchanted ring on my finger that drains
my spirit over yeah I'm starting to remember that over what oh god let's
just wait till after the battle over Roger Roger
over and then I put the stone in my pocket but it's like pressing against my
legs so it's just going permanently. So you, so now that the troll went so now we're gonna go cut to
evil stevel. Evil stevel you and the pleasure men and the fiend are looking
our get to Honest Doodle where it once was and you do see a circle there of
similar to the one you saw in the temple. Nobody's naked yet though, but it's
members of the St. Anthony's parish as well as Kitsunes, those creepy
long fox creatures from the woods. And you see in the middle of them all, in the
middle of their painted circle, they've sort of painted on the dirt ground, is
is the jester's hat.
The jester, the spirit jester who vanished
or was destroyed.
- Is the jester the terrifier?
- And you see it there and you see the pleasure man.
He goes, "It looks like they're trying to summon
"some sort of shade of the terrifier,
"a spirit, merge it with the vessel.
"This is not good.
we should we should probably try to kill them
i'd be more like them
will talk to him too
now we should kill them and i'm sorry
we can do it we can talk of course
or have a question
yes to meet who
you know me what's on the word is date
to the people in the circle have the vessel
no the king of the vessel
all got it got all of the okay yeah
i've okay this whole time i thought the vessel was like a a stone
thing like a big diamond? I mean some would say children are diamonds. I forgot that vessel
meant child. In this it does but not in like anywhere else. Okay so I heard vessel and then
you said that the white woman of the caves. Well in this context. I thought that the, I
think you said that the white. Everyone kick your feet up this is going to be a while. I
You said that the white woman of the caves was in a vessel.
Oh no, she was in a cage.
Okay. Alright.
But cage means child, you're saying?
Uh, well, let me tell you. Marriage is a cage, alright?
And he's married to a child.
Child is a prison guard who's torturing you.
Oh, I get it.
Come on now.
Is everything clear though?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll have like a sort of like dictionary ready.
Like I'll have like sort of a wiki made with all the terms.
I just forgot that one thing.
No, no, no, you're fine. Yeah. Yeah. Cool. So, all right. Yeah. They heard like
summoning some sort of shade of the terrifier to merge with the vessel and
they I think I'm going to walk in and use my Kimbo shotguns on them. Okay.
Cool.
Can't believe I gave those to you. It was so stupid. That was a big misstep.
It was.
It was a auto crit too. Yeah, all head. 10d 10 damage. Yeah, it was so dumb.
I should have given you a sword or something instead. No.
Okay, uh, so yeah, I mean you see them. They don't seem to see you. I should be a bit more diligent.
Can I at least roll something? I haven't rolled anything this entire game except for a backflip roll.
You rolled for a backflip? Nobody else rolled for a backflip. That was special.
Yeah, you got a special roll. You think so?
Well, there's things you can, so you can, I mean you can try to sneak up on them. You can...
Do they hate water? Due perception.
You should ask.
Hey, pleasure man guy. Yes, what's going on? By the looks of them. Would you say that
maybe they might not be too fond of water? I don't think they think sort of
about water in terms of fondness. That's good enough for me. I'm going to
I'm going to create as much water, more water than any of you have ever seen. I
I think the limit of that is like 15 feet, a cubic feet of water.
That's a lot of water.
They're in a pit, right?
That's probably a million miles of water.
What?
Aren't they in a pit?
They're in a circle.
Well, they're in a circle.
You can do 10 gallons of clean water within rain.
It's so fucked up that the world is so bad when you could create water.
I kind of just want to freak them out.
Yeah, alternatively, the waterfall-
Well, couldn't you drown all of the-
They're not in a-
aren't they in an empty pool with bars over the top?
Are they handcuffed to the bottom of a pool like David Blaine?
Okay, maybe I might have put this in my mind palace.
My own thing. Well, let's take a look. I thought that, so you said it's where
Mount Honest Doodle was, so I imagine that there was a crater.
No, no, no. It's almost like it was never there. That's a good point.
It's very bizarre. I thought that there was a big crater that they were sitting in.
Um, the water...
'Cause I was gonna say, you could just drown them.
Yeah, 'cause the water...
With 10 gallons of water.
You could create the, uh...
Yeah, alternatively, the water falls as rain in a 30-foot cube within range.
I think I'll actually...
You could just...
You could just get them wet.
You can make fog, too, right?
Oh, I can make fog.
I've done that before.
Yeah, I did let you do that.
I'm gonna make fog, you bitch.
Let's do it.
Okay.
Let me go to my spells.
There is, I think, a spell that deliberately creates fog.
But that's magical fog.
Yeah, you know what?
I don't need any fucking crazy fog.
I'm going to create and not destroy water.
Okay, cool.
So you create that, and you create that fog around them, and you see them start to freak
out.
I thought he was creating water.
They're kind of confused.
They're looking around, and Pleasure Man goes, "Good job.
Let's strike now."
and they start to run up, and so we're gonna roll for initiative,
you're gonna have a surprise round on them.
Yes!
'Cause you see them, they're like, "What's going on, huh? What's going on?"
Nine.
Okay.
Well, add your...
I don't, I have a zero.
You have a zero, there, alright.
Alright, cool.
Let me get your shit up here.
Sucks.
Goddamn.
This is...
Wait, where's your...
What the fuck?
I thought I had the, uh...
Steevo, what are you up to?
There it is.
Okay.
I'm in the fog.
Over.
You just made a bunch of fog?
Yeah.
Patrick, you really need to say over.
Over.
I'm trying to be quiet, y'all.
Well, I just like to hold the button down.
Stop doing that.
Just in case I need to say anything.
I gotta be quiet.
It's getting so loud.
Over.
Under.
You can't say under without saying over after.
Over.
Underwear.
I just said underwear.
He said underwear.
Over.
I said underwear.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Over.
Ha ha ha ha.
over over over over over over over over over over over over over over over over over over
over over over over over over over over over over over over over over over over over over over
the other, the shaman and the kitsune's in there,
and they're going at it,
they're like casting spells at one another,
and like, sort of like using their stabs
to like fucking beat each other back.
And you and Barnabas go and run toward,
and Barnabas is sort of running towards
the jester's crown in the center.
And he's like, "Let's, we move it
so we can disrupt the ritual."
And as he's getting closer to it,
the jester's crown starts to shake.
And as it shakes, and you can sort of see it
a little bit through the fog,
and it shakes and vibrates,
And you see it like become the jester's face
and then kind of warp into something else
and then back to the jester's face.
And it becomes some sort of like black shade spirit,
sort of shimmery and staticky.
Kind of looks like, it was mostly for Cam, I guess,
but like gone when he becomes evil
for a second in "Hunter x Hunter," right?
And it's like this weird shimmery shade
And he's like, "Okay, okay, that's the terrifier shade.
"Okay, it's not as strong as the terrifier,
"but we're going to need to kill it."
And yeah, you guys are scoring up against that.
And the spirit though, you do have a surprise round
on the spirit still.
So Barnabas is gonna go first though.
And Barnabas is going to, what did I have Barnabas to?
Oh yeah. - I'm so weak.
I've never done any damage to anybody in this tournament.
- Oh, you'll do damage.
- You don't, you have a bunch of spells.
- You have a bunch of good spells.
You just use the same one.
- You use chill touch every time.
My best friend over touch is cool. You can't be complaining over so Barnabas sort of like stops himself and
throws his staff up in the air and
And
from the from the sky you see sort of a like a
Silvery like beam of pale white shoot down and
it's a it's moonbeam is the spell and
Roll the dice on your phone.
He's gonna have to try to avoid it.
Why am I doing this?
Okay, cool.
And what do I have for Mr. Shade?
I think Patches does whatever we say, guys.
[laughter]
The Shade's Constitution.
I thought that the bevels of his phone case
would stop the dice, but I was wrong.
Okay, yeah. So...
The moonbeam shoots down,
And the shade is able to sort of resist the full power of the beam, but it still takes
some damage.
So where's a D10?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm trying not to touch nothing.
Here we are, oh no, it's 12.
Oh, where are you?
Your shape is annoying.
Wait, it's the one that looks...
This one?
D12?
No, D10 I need.
I always forget, yeah, there we go, thank you.
Right, looks like that.
all right and it does 1 million points yeah okay so it just takes a little bit
of damage as the moon beam comes down and evil steve well you can do something now
too okay I'm going to so bravely cast inflict
wounds onto this evil shade cool so for inflict wounds you have to be in you
have to do a melee attack I think I will do go for it so you have I think a mace
If I'm correct, I think I'm gonna use it
Any problems with that big guy? What's um, what?
No, no none. Hey better not any problems with it. So what should I roll?
I don't know. You should just roll d20. Okay, I will
12 nice that
Plus it's plus
Was for us for 16 that hits so over damage is 3d 10 damage. It's 4d 10 on my screen
Oh, you're casting it at level 2. Yes, sir
Around here. I want to kill this fucker
Go my shit kill him for kill him for dead. All right, here's here's I'm rolling 3. Oh, I got all for that's nice
I don't think that's it. No, they're all
tensile like top series
- They're scary.
- They're scaries to me.
(laughing)
- Five, 11, 19.
- Nice, yeah.
So what does your inflict wounds look like
when you hit this thing?
What do you do?
- I'm gonna, so I have a mace.
So I'm gonna hit him with the mace.
- It's a melee spell attack,
so it can be technically like your mace,
it can be whatever you want.
- Okay, I'm gonna use the mace
and I'm gonna hit him a hundred trillion times.
- Yeah, okay, yeah.
- Yeah, just sort of go.
(imitating mace)
sound like yeah, this shade is like
like as you keep punching it is rock. Yeah. Yeah, and it's got
the moonbeam coming down on them and as you're punching him
through and like the shimmery light on this thing, it's like
pretty beautiful and weird, especially with the fog going
around. It's like with this weird beautiful violence happening.
Yes, you beat the shit out of him and that's pretty good for
the surprise round. We're going to go back to the top of the
order in a second first though. We're going to cut back to
Dogan Dogan it's going to be Sean whoops. It's going to be a Mckelly
Highlanders turn.
He's going to try to attack the troll okay, and that's going to hit the troll
for fucking sure and he's going to he's going to be like my sword of data and
he's going to try to attack. He's going to attack the troll for
got 12 damage in this 12 out of 12 so the troll is just like slashed through like
gutted and he's gonna attack him again that trolls ran through and this time
you know he he's a little overconfident he misses but you're up now Dogen all
right I'm gonna swing my my battle spoon mm-hmm
Spoon shovel. Right, it's a spoon now.
That's 11 plus...
So that's a 15.
That hits.
Okay. Is it D8?
Plus 2. That's 5 damage.
Nice. You can also do Divine Smite still, if you want to do that.
Do it.
I only have one spell slot left.
Okay, then don't do it.
Oh, okay. Yeah. Right. I forgot about that.
Yeah, you conk him in the gut where the slash was made.
So you're sort of like rubbing in the wound.
in the wound yeah I rub it yeah you rub it and we're gonna cut back down to you
Patrick Siodar so you're still finding this troll this orc that's outside the
you just been walking slowly over there yeah I have my bow and arrow out okay
cool yeah shoot him all right I'm just gonna you know I mean I've been I've
been very casual about the bow and arrow this whole time I just roll a d20 right
shit actually even before you do that oh wait is there new stuff cuz I hit
puberty? Well, yes there always is but I just realized that because he got a
surprise round he actually got a sneak attack so he actually does 3d6
damage also. He does? No. The gnome? Yeah yeah yeah. Oh yeah, sticky fingers? Yeah so he's
gonna also do... all right nice he's gonna do an additional nine damage fuck yeah
okay you're up now. And this is my sneak attack? Yeah it doesn't count as a sneak
attack oh well I guess because it's a surprise round so you're yeah this is my
- Yeah, so yes. - So go for it.
- All right.
- So you get advantage.
- Right. - As part of the...
- Ooh, 19. - All right, plus.
- Hold up.
- What do I add to that?
- I think it's gonna hit.
- I think it's probably fine.
- Yeah, I know, but it could be like a 24.
(laughing)
- It could be really big. - Well, anyway.
Yeah, it doesn't matter.
So I got a 19 plus how much?
- I think plus, I guess plus five or four.
- Our six, what is it?
What is your shit?
- You can just look at it on your phone.
- Oh, I guess they don't technically give...
- Well, what would I be looking at?
- That's annoying that they don't give advantage
to surprise rounds.
They really should.
I give it.
So it's a 19 plus five.
They really should just give,
why wouldn't you also give advantage?
I guess 'cause you're already getting to get to go first.
But I give it because I think it's cool.
- Okay, yeah, and you hit him. - And this is also a sneak attack?
You hit him, yeah. So roll...
- So I just... those three dice? - Yeah, so you're gonna...
- These three, yeah, 'cause you have two d6 for your sneak attack. - Okay.
And then you're gonna add the additional, I think, that...
That is a... nine.
Nice. And then you're gonna add also, for your shortbow, plus three, so twelve.
So yeah, um...
God, between all that, yeah, you guys... you finish off the orc.
- Yeah. - You just, like, get him square between the eyes.
after sticky fingers like a slashing him up and you think and just like
don't and it's just these is dead
as a figure sort of waves you and the other guys and
like you're just like going
and uh...
evil steve work at the u_n_ where's the court uh...
i guess i'd find this out later
because it's gonna ask where the king is all your speaking now patrick
you know that
who had been doing a lot of sneaking around the country at me
i told you to come with or be over
which i told i told the both the could come with me
but you guys decided to go the other way i mean we could well do this together
and anyway
uh... i'm going up
a set of stairs right now and i'm going to sneak up on the came that the short
over it's sort of something like that i don't know where where is the king now
because he's got no ok over so that he retreated what you would i mean you
wouldn't you don't even know that he did retreat back into the castle will you
probably told
No.
So, okay, you don't know where he is at all.
So we're cutting to Evil Stevel.
Now the shade is going to go.
And so he's going to look to you, Evil Stevel.
This is a shade of the Terrifier, so it's like taking some elements of the spirit, the
jester who serves the Terrifier.
And he's going to look to you.
Yes, very cool.
I'm just very boredly looking into his face.
Yeah, you just like beat the shit out of him.
You're gonna roll a,
ooh, what did I give him?
Oh yeah, okay.
- Oh, that was a crazy.
- Scary.
- Oh yeah.
- Sorry about that.
- You sound like George Takei.
- Oh my.
- Yeah.
- That's what he says.
- Yeah, that's what he sounds like.
You're going to roll a--
- A real George Takei impression.
(laughing)
- You're gonna roll a,
a, what was that?
Yeah, wisdom saving throw.
So roll a d20 and add your wisdom saving modifier.
Which, oh I think you, do you have an advantage on that? No, just against poison.
Okay. What'd you get?
I don't know what to say. You got a 2 plus 4, that's 6?
You know what, it's not enough.
The Terrifier Shade looks at you, and he projects a, or it,
projects a phantasmal image of your worst fear.
Hmm what is your worst fear? My friends getting hurt. You see images of Dogen
stubbing his toe and Patrick hitting his head on a shelf from before you see that
what happened earlier just like play over and over and over again. No demon
release me no and you're getting like super frightened so you drop your weapon
on the ground while you're getting friends on the ground boys are you okay
over and you are my head on the doorframe
Patrick didn't say over so you should have waited before you said over and you
You are now afraid of the Terrifier Spirit.
I'm so afraid!
So you're going to have to run away from it.
I'm running!
Not yet.
I'm going to wait though.
So, alright, we'll cut away from that and we'll go back to the battlefield where the
troll is there.
So the troll is going to go now and he's going to swing at you, Dogen.
Okay, I don't think that hits you.
No, he swings at you and he just misses,
and he's gonna try to swing at you again.
That definitely hits you.
- Oh.
- Yeah. - It doesn't.
- That troll's gonna do some damage.
- I think the troll's about to hit me, over.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- Just, just, just don't let it, over.
- I'll let you guys know how much damage it does to me, over.
I don't even wanna know, over.
- You should tell him if it does or not
because I feel like that's something
he could coach you through, over.
- I know, I'm already really frightened and upset.
- So it's 14 damage to you.
- 14 damage, guys, over.
- He's getting gashed.
- No!
- And as you take that hit--
- Is that good or bad?
- Let's see.
- I'm at 11.
- So probably bad.
- So after you take that hit--
- That might be bad.
- You're looking around at the battlefield
and it is looking kind of dire.
The Brave Lions are just not up to snuff.
Just a reason why their rebellion hasn't happened just yet.
And you're watching the trolls start to play
with the bodies of these like little puny little humans
and slap them around and you know,
like the Hulk or whatever.
- You should have just come with me,
we could have been good sneaking partners over.
- And then, Dogen, you recall something
that definitely was said by Fuck You a while ago,
where he said, "Look to my coming at first light
"on the fifth day.
"At dawn, look to the east."
(laughing)
and as you turn your head
i guess it has been five days
you see cresting over the hill i'm looking at the west at first i don't see
anything i got turned around on the battlefield
and you see
riding
sullivan
i brought him and you see fuck you
and a hundred idiots
compressing over a hill.
(laughter)
And they're all doing the Monty Python silly walk.
Are cresting over the hill.
And storming the battlefield.
And you see Fuck You, who's on top of Solveigns,
and he's like, "Can I stop killing you?"
"No!"
And he's casting insane spells and wiping the field,
not completely clean, but he's helping
turn the tide of battle.
and you're gonna get to go again.
You're gonna get to try again,
one more time, to fight this troll.
- Okay.
- You're gonna get up and fight him again.
- I'm gonna do it right now?
- Yes.
- Hey, Dogen.
Have you tried using the troll spray?
- I'm waiting for you to say over, over.
- Sorry, I'm trying to walk up the stairs right now,
and it's just, I gotta be so quiet, over.
(mimics gunfire)
- Heard you loud and clear, buddy.
Over.
(laughter)
- I'm gonna swing my battle spoon.
- Yeah.
- That's a seven plus, I already forgot what it's plus.
- I have a 100.
- Four, it's 11.
- Ah, just barely missed this.
- You get kind of inspired,
but you still just gotta whiff this.
- Oh, yeah.
- I'm sorry for distracting you, over.
- Uh-oh, guys, over.
- And we're gonna cut now to Patrick Yodar.
So you are in, you are, you have sort of like crawled up
through the dungeon now, which are empty.
Everyone's been, there is no jail.
Everyone's just killed now.
It's terrible.
And--
- Why was the guard even there?
- 'Cause he knew it was an entrance, I guess.
But yeah, nobody's getting in or out.
Well, now you guys are getting in.
And as you're growing up the stairs, roll perception.
Is that a 9?
What about his big eye?
And you have advantage on perception.
Oh yeah, you're going to have plus.
Oh, and I have advantage on every perception roll.
Not advantage on perception, you get additional, but you do get additional.
Oh, dexterity.
Oh, okay.
And dexterity saving throws, yeah.
So, my perception is...
What's my perception?
Perception is pretty high, and I think you also have...
Well, I have plus 4 perception.
Yeah, and then yes, you get plus four perception and
all right. Yeah, I forgot you can use a bonus action spot.
That's cool. You have that for your other thing.
You plus four perception. You got an additional, um,
you had your proficiency measures too. Not three. I don't know.
I thought it was three. So you had to see at six to eight.
Would you get again? Would you get a nine, nine? Okay, cool. So yeah,
with 15, it's pretty good. Um, so as you're calling up the stairs,
you notice through the door,
but there are two guards inside the atrium.
Like you're able to sort of spot that out,
like you're able to hear it or see it rather.
And Stickyfinger sort of gets the message
and he, Stickyfinger goes like,
you know, does like sort of command shit,
like two fingers move forward
and two of his gang members burst through the door
and take out the guards.
I mean, he waves you in, he's like, "Come on, let's go."
And so you're able to sort of go
into this main atrium of the castle
you see the guards are just dead already. Like, Sticky Fingers crew took them out. It's,
you know, lots of bones. It's a very spooky claw castle. It's kind of Romanesque, actually,
like, as far as the architectural style, where it's like a lot of simple things, but then with,
like, bones interspersed. And the only thing that's, like, not this, like, early medieval
thing is that there's, like, this ornate skylight that when you look up at, you can see the rest of
the arm of the claw. And you see in front of you, there's double doors that lead to this, like,
spiral that's going to lead to the famous, like, spiral staircase where you walk up the claw's arm.
to the top of the claw which is where you think maybe the king would be working
anywhere after getting wounded could I do an investigation check yeah you could
certainly try to do a yeah tell me do investigation to see if you can
understand the layout of this place that was a nat 20 on that 20 Wow um yeah so
shit so you look around and you're trying to get the sense of like okay
looking for blood because he got hit in the stomach right mm-hmm okay you're
sort of like trying to get the sense of what could have happened where he could
have gone. And from what you know, like Arkham Asylum style, like vision and shit, like looking
at the floor. Yeah. And like you get a pretty good sense of the layout of this place now.
On either side of you are two is a room. One is a storage room of some kind. The other is
like a library. You know that if you go up the tower, there is a small like sort of church
room and you also know that at the top of the tower is the throne room by where the palm
of the claw is. So, if he were to sort of hide somewhere, he'd probably end up going to the
throne room. Like, you would have to climb up this thing, you know, and there's also
like a barracks, you know, too.
Yeah.
So, you'd want to avoid that, obviously, because there's probably soldiers in there.
Is the barracks in the staircase?
This barracks is also one of the offshoots of the staircase. It's sort of like the whole
castle's like this spiral staircase, like this thin spiral staircase and then like all
these rooms.
How many floors?
God, I didn't even put a number on that, but...
So it's two floors?
It's two floors.
No, it's like...
I would say...
It's two floors, but the stairs are very long.
Yeah, it's probably like 25 floors, I would say.
It's a massive staircase.
But those are like the main rooms that you would know about.
The other rooms are probably just like...
And where is the dumb waiter?
The dumb waiter?
The dumb waiter is in the center of...
I'm looking at him.
dumb waiter that you know there's multiple dumb waiters that go from
different rooms to send down different gruel and stuff and also Patrick is the
dumb waiter mm-hmm I'm sorry so I can't so so because you said that I can
transport anywhere in the building that I want to because I'm a dumb waiter and I
can actually go to the dumb waiter goes up and down it goes up to the throne
readers mostly go down I think well I think a dumb waiter could go up to
well they can't run around to the house and the family i think i think i was
down forever and just all i guess it makes sense
uh... so it don't we're read the dumb waiter
not yet you're done
well among so i'm a dumb waiter
so i can go all the way up to the throne room
we could ride the dumb
actually problem past rightman
can you write it down and all i have to do is make the king cry in front of his
half-dead son
yeah yeah yeah you're right yeah and you have to ask and i'm also a dumb waiter
so i can go up all the way all right you're not a dumb all right take it back
you're not a dumb okay so well you can start climbing the stairs you want to go
to the or you want to go to explore the other rooms or do you want to do i mean
should i explore the other rooms i don't know i don't know over i'm having a hard
time because there's there's two rooms here doesn't it seem like patrick is
talking somewhere but not into the stone. I have taped the button down so I can
hear everything that you guys say and I can say whatever I want over. The other
button on the stone yeah that's there you did that. I forgot I put tape in your
inventory too. Duck tape. Yeah you can do whatever you want we can cut back to you
too you can think about it you can chew on it.
Mm-hmm evil Steve. Oh, yes, sir. Well, I'm thinking I'm
I'm thinking just go just go straight to the king go for it start climbing the stairs. Okay, okay you and you and
your homie
Sticky fingers are climbing the stairs together now
evil Steve Oh
You are now
In the middle the Honest, it'll fly you're really scared of this thing
And now but the the your your buddy's gonna try to attack him. So he's gonna do
He's gonna keep up the moonbeam
Barnabas is
Because the thing didn't move it just like took damage it doesn't maybe not like smart enough to really move at this point
Oh, okay. Yeah, it should take damage. It should actually take some damage
So we roll constitution saving throw here
Yeah, it's not enough. So let's go so I'm gonna take some extra damage now these details. I love extra damage
There it is. I got it. Oh, no. Yeah, they're all over there. Give me that
Okay, nice, yes, it takes another another 10 damage and
And now he's gonna I mean, he's just gonna keep the beam there
He's just gonna concentrate in the beam and he's trying to like wave you back over but you're too afraid
So it's your turn and you're just running from this thing. You can um, can I turn around?
No, you just like I'm just so scared
Yeah, as long as it's in the the cone of this thing's fear like you have to use your steve-o. It's okay
It's okay. Don't be scared. What if just a shade of the terror fire?
It's not scary over you use your when you run out of range. You do have now
a
a chance to um because it's within 30 feet cone and then i'm gonna cast uh because i'm like worried
about my friends i'm gonna cast friendships delight i'll succeed on whispers yeah wait what what is
that oh it's a it's a spell that i don't see it what you don't see it it's on mine it says it on
on my phone. It cures me of all fear of my friends and actually gives me more, oh it
says here more power because of the delight of me being having so many friends. I think
what we can do is I think you can try to roll to do at the end of your turn I think because
you're kind of moving outside the cone it's vision cone. Okay. And I know that fear I think
is supposed to technically be like once you're in the cone you're kind of frightened for
the duration but if you move out of line of sight and you have your friends by your side
I want you to try to roll for this.
Okay.
Yeah.
Roll a d20 to see if you can, and we'll see if you beat the wisdom, his wisdom DC here.
I cast friendship delight.
Yeah!
Over.
Ten.
What do you add?
You add your wisdom.
It says I add my friendship score.
You don't have a friendship score, man.
Friendship score is 100.
Somebody doesn't know anything about D&D.
Friendship score is 3 because it's 3 friends.
My wisdom is...
Oh, fucking shit.
is
So it's a 12.
Okay.
You're still scared of this thing.
It says you can cast Friendship Delight twice.
And we're gonna cut to...
Turn.
Uh, Dogen?
Yeah.
Uh, so now you're bu- you're- you're friend, I guess.
Am I about to get fucked?
McElwee is gonna attack.
Cast Friendship Delight, Dogen!
McElwee does hit, so he's gonna do some damage now.
Where is that?
D12.
Oh yeah.
Okay, not that much damage. Uh, he's gonna attack again.
That also hits.
And... damn, okay.
The troll is not looking too good.
Um, you are up now, uh, Dogen.
Okay.
Alright, here goes.
Here goes.
I'm casting my Friendship Delight attack over...
[mimics attack]
Can you guys teach me that over the microphone real quick?
Don't do that. Do your regular attack.
It's it is it says it's my regular attack, but it deals plus 1,000 damage
Okay fine
No, it's not what I that's a 19. Okay. Yeah, that hits the troll. Okay, so this is d8 plus 2 plus
It's not plus 1000 plus 1000 and you know, right? It's plus 1002 and you know
8 and 2 plus 2 no is 10 1,000 and 10 damage 10 damage is very good
and you should be happy with that.
So you do 10 damage to this troll.
- And you know that's 1,010.
- 1,010 damage was just dealt by me.
- And now, Patrick Yodar.
- That's how much damage I just dealt.
Guys, I dealt my damage.
- Patrick Yodar, you're climbing up the tower.
Do you wanna stop at any of the locations?
- No.
- Cool, yeah, so you're just shooting up this tower.
- I have a song in my heart.
- Yeah.
- And I'm gonna make that king cry.
- Yeah, and with your new gangly legs,
You're able to get up really fast.
You're doing two steps at a time.
Yeah, you're doing some real--
Like someone trying to fuck.
I'm looking at Sticky Fingers
and he's having a hard time getting up the stairs.
I'm looking at him like,
"Grow your legs."
Oh, shut the fuck up.
This is awesome.
Look at this.
And I just do like the elf--
Your fucking eye is weird.
You know the elf on the escalator?
Buddy the Elf on the Escalator
where he's got like the one leg.
Oh, of course.
I'm familiar.
It's a good movie.
- Yeah, I do that up like four steps.
- Yeah, roll a stealth check.
- You know, four steps is really not that many
to do that up, actually.
- No.
- It's actually quite a small amount.
It's like--
- Actually, it would be pretty impressive
for someone five, seven to do that.
And it's also--
- Oh, right, I forgot we're talking about a, yeah, child.
- But it's also like actually easy to do
if you're five, seven.
- I forgot we were talking about a garden gnome.
My bad.
- No, it's not what you're talking about.
- 18.
- All right, cool.
you're able to do that without a warning of like a well no one notices found the
words almost you keep coming up you're rushing up the steps evil steel this
this thing is coming after you this terrifier shade he's gonna try to slash
at you I don't want to be slashed that was a zero you know zero but he did miss
he did slash at you and missed and now he's gonna like open his mouth and shoot
His mouth says zero and it doesn't want to.
He's going to shoot some sort of like dark necrotic spell at you.
What is it?
Just roll it on the...
It has to be re-rolled because it landed on the floor.
So that hits you and...
Why would you tell him?
I think it was actually...
Wait, no.
It was Caleb's bad.
It was a 1.8.
It's actually a .18.
Yeah.
Sure.
No, you don't take that much.
You take 5 damage from this thing as it's sort of chasing you around.
I can't really do anything because I'm so afraid.
You're still afraid of it so you're still running from it.
This is your arc.
But now as it's moving, Barnabus is going to move his moonbeam over and chase it and
he's going to be able to see if this thing can get hit by it or not.
That thing does not resist the damage.
It's gonna take a good amount of damage now.
Oh boy.
That's ten.
That's one thousand.
That's not one thousand.
That's plus three.
So it takes another thirteen damage.
This thing is not looking good.
Even as it's chasing you it's like slowly dying and it is like you know, it's making
like *roar* like horrible sounds, like terrifying sounds.
That's only making me more scared.
That's right. Your turn. Roll again. Roll Friendship's Delight again.
Let's see if you can not be scared.
Are you doing Friendship's Delight?
Yes, I need my friends to send me energy.
Over. We're right here. Over.
I'm here too now.
Shut your fucking mouth.
Who the hell got that stone?
He's just like right next to you, Dogen. He's like, "Hi!"
Hi, you!
Dogen, kick him. Over.
I attack Sullivan.
21 right team yeah it's all good I hit Sullivan it's five damage yeah I'm sorry
I thought you were a troll it's a good cover over to believe that over he's
gonna believe it so much and yeah you're no longer scared of the same you look at
it I turn around I just yeah I was basically pretending to be scared the
whole time you see your friends holding hands and smiling and playing that song
from the lost boys and they're just like eating chips and and they're like we're
not in pain and they're just so happy and so go for it try to attack this
thing if you want to basically I'm so not scared I'm gonna hit you with my
a
Roll 3d10 man.
Alright.
Gimme one.
Aye aye aye aye.
Or 4 actually, sorry.
Roll 4d10.
Are you doing level 1?
I mean, describe your kill.
I'm seeing a 6 and a 7, describe your kill on this thing.
So here's how it's gonna go down.
Shane, Jester.
Basically you tried to scare me and I pretended to be scared.
So that you, I would chase you.
You would chase me over to over here.
over here and then I could reverse myself with a friendship and then I could use
my hand which I have already used. It's nodding. This shade is nodding. Yeah that makes sense.
And basically I'm gonna do this. And I just go like this one time underhand punch right
to his stomach and kill him. He goes "D'oh!" And basically everything happened exactly how I planned.
Do you see the shade sort of fizzle out and dissipate and and shrivel up and
you see the battle around you and you see that as the fog is starting to
clear from this battle, the Pleasure Men and you won this battle. So the shade is
gone for now. So there's no, seems like there's maybe no-- There's no shade.
There's no shade and there's no risk of the Terrifyer coming back right now.
Okay. Now, uh, uh, Patrick, you get to the throne room and you see the king there and
he's like holding his side and he has his son, his like sort of fucked up weird
half-alive son, and he looks to you two, he goes, "Sticky fingers and are you
Trunchbull?" I'm his nephew. You might have heard of me, I'm a beautiful singer.
"What are you two doing here?"
- I look at him, I look at him and I say,
♪ Do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do ♪
♪ Understand the things I say ♪
- What's he doing?
♪ Don't turn away from me ♪
'Cause I've spent half my life out there
Trunchbull is somewhere else singing along with you
You wouldn't disagree
Do you see me?
Roll performance check
Do you like me?
Do you like me standing there?
Seventeen
Do you know ten?
I'm getting the sense something beautiful is being sung over
Do you see me?
do you see me does anyone care you see the king
hand on was when I was young cradling his son and he just starts to cry and he's
hearing the song so good and we didn't give it all right Patrick is muted for
the end and he's crying and tears falling on his son's body and he's crying sticky
fingers like looking at you like oh okay like I guess this is working and all
three of you where you are you start to you guys hear my song you guys start to
shimmer yourselves and and from what anyone else can tell you look like sort
of like negative image versions of yourselves standing completely still in
place did you guys hear my son and yes over you have to say over that's why I
didn't respond over all three I didn't say I was planning this song the whole
time that's why I put six before - over I was playing this song the whole time
that's why I had tape on the thing I just wanted you guys to hear my beautiful son
you are now over gave these adventures walking you three are now all together
we're still doing that still doing it and you look sort of like in like this
black completely black realm and you are have like this you look like kind of
like if you're like negative images of yourself in the middle of the field and
we'll go to people's reactions to that but we're with you guys now. You're all
like kind of like gold now. You look like gold shimmery versions of yourself in
this black realm. I open up I like pull like the drawstring on my my I pull my
pants open I look down I go that's what I like. That's what I like to see. And you
see in the distance you see what looks like the scene from when you were at
Honest Mount Honest doodle and you see
The Prince Jumanji
You see him with the knife you see Sullivan there like lying on the ground scared
He's about to be stabbed 500 times in the leg or so
He thinks and you see the king like gesturing out to the audience like you know
We're all excited to see it. You don't see yourselves in this scene
You just see everybody else around and as you guys walk towards this scene
It's like it's hard to tell how distance works, but it's it's getting closer. You can tell right
And then you notice that everybody in the scene is completely still except the prince his hand is shaking
As he's holding the knife. He's terrified. He's really really scared
And he's saying he's like I don't know what to do I don't want to
I'm gonna snap this frog. I don't know what to do do it
Should I do it? Actually never mind, hold on.
So yeah, I'll just tell you, in this realm, you can decide what the prince would have done
in this moment, which will alter things in the story, depending on what it is. It could
be big, could be small, but you're essentially helping him conquer his fear of, in that moment
of I don't know who I am, I don't want to hurt anybody, but I seem like I'm meant to hurt
people, what should I do?
And you can sort of talk with him in like that weird way that you could talk to ghosts in
movies and stuff where it's like you can sort of try to commune with him in this moment.
Well, I'm evil and I hate Sullivan.
So, and I'm evil and I hate Sullivan.
I mean, I'm kinda neutral.
But I god damn do I hate Sullivan.
*Chuckles*
But, let me just say...
Jumanji.
He's like, sort of looking around, right?
Like, doing the thing he do.
You pocket that knife...
You sell that thing.
That thing is worth...
Ten grand.
That is a ceremonial knife.
You don't even-
You- You just gotta pretend to stab that fucker.
And I leave it in mint condition, you mean?
You can- I mean...
you leave that shit in mint condition you could sell that thing for ten grand I
mean you know you're Prince already but I mean we can go to the casino together
after this I want you to look at that frog look at him you looking yeah I'm
talking I'm looking Prince you see you see his eyes yeah there's nothing behind
it uh I guess if you say so he's I mean he's
He's basically nothing. He's a speck of dust.
He's fucking dog shit. Okay?
He's lower than fucking dirt.
Just like the-
Oh my god, I was married to him!
*laughter*
As you're saying all this, the camera's like just lingering on Sullivan's frozen face.
Look, he can't-
And then you say the marriage thing and it just like goes right to your face.
It's like, oh god!
Sullivan, move your face if you're not just a complete piece of shit who deserves to die.
Well, I feel like it's settled.
So I should stab him 500 times and kill him?
No, you should pocket the knife and pretend to stab him, and then we can go to the casino and turn that 10 grand...
We can turn that 10 grand into 20 million.
Dogen, is there anything you want him to do?
I don't know.
Well, I...
He does suck really bad.
But also I'm married to him.
So I kind of wish I wasn't married to him anymore.
So I think, you know, I'll just let you do with that what you will.
Both of you roll persuasion checks.
Okay, your dice.
We're rolling at the same time, baby.
Oh yeah.
Okay, so mine is this one.
is the black dice because you're doing the evil roll.
Or the angel and devil on his shoulder.
Alright, you said it, not me.
What?
Hold on, can we cut that out?
Please?
Roll!
Please can we cut that out?
Oh!
Well hold on, it changed his to a 9.
But it was still lower.
It was still lower.
It was a 9.
Well, evil.
What did you have?
You had a 9?
I had a 9.
I don't think I have very good persuasion.
Oh my god, did you guys just tie?
Oh no wait, your persuasion is crazy high.
Mine is 8.
Yeah, plus 8.
My persuasion is...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh my god, what's your persuasion?
Oh my god, this is pretty intense.
My persuasion is +2.
Oh my god, they tied!
Alright, I guess it's a re-roll.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm staring at...
They're like both...
Yeah, he's not sure what to do.
They're like...
I'm looking at Sullivan,
and I look at the ring on my finger,
and I'm thinking and I look at Prince Jumajanga and I go, "Yeah, kill him."
[Laughter]
Oh man.
Okay.
Sullivan's never died in any of these campaigns.
That's not a good move.
He looks to the frog.
It's what the characters would do.
And he looks up at his father and you see the knife go down and we fade out of this.
[Fade out]
Oh, I wanted to see him fucking die.
And we return to the real world and you see the prince. You see the prince now
fully formed and you see him and he looks different. It looks like he did
something that he'll never forget that he did. He's a terrifier isn't he? No. And you see the
king who's so happy now and you see the troops in the battle it's sort of
Peter Dow, the idiots and why me, fuck you, really turned the tide.
Wait, hold on, was that the real Sullivan?
And you turn to your left.
Just let him talk for a minute here.
Oh my god.
And wherever Sullivan was, he's not there anymore.
[Laughter]
- Steevel, Steevel, I mean, no change really around you.
- Barely even noticed.
- But the war, the fight is over.
The king, his army has been defeated.
And, you know, the ending here is really
about reconciling this, figuring out how to,
what does the king wanna do?
What does the pleasure men wanna do?
Brave lions, there's a lot here to figure out, I think.
Is that what you were gonna say?
i look at my my hand to everyone now
chilling
grace
the acts
and
and i don't have to pay shit
so to be given at least his inventory
the business is so it is in my life at the present up the will make you kill
the frog
but
I think we could we could end there because what I was gonna do is I'll write something that's like a bit more
And so for now our story ends the battle was over
With the return of the Prince Jumanji King Nod Wars madness was no more and he ordered his men to step down
All members of St. Anthony's parish were immediately excommunicated from the Church of the Terrifier,
which now had to earn the trust of the people, as did the King.
See, Nardwuar refused to relinquish his throne.
But he knew that his temporary madness had forever tarnished his once sterling reputation,
at least with those outside of Gal Gadot,
and so in an effort to maintain peace and make amends,
as to the demands of his challengers heretofore unthinkable.
For one, the dreaded pleasure men were now full members of King Nardwar's court.
Their worship of the minor god Discharge and their vision for a vile world built on the
principles of pleasure at all cost became almost customary and in some places bordered
on the prosaic.
While debauchery is often appreciated in the Terrifier kingdom, the differences between
the worshippers of Discharge and the church of the Terrifier spelled a cultural tension
to come, especially since the pleasure men were not so concerned with whether or not one
was terrified or born like the church was, nor did they stage a destabilizing coup or
try to revive a god who would have been really upset about being revived.
Meanwhile the brave lions were granted sovereign territory in the western part of the kingdom
in a new land called "It is real".
Perhaps a step back in their revolutionary fervor, but for many scaredy cats this was
enough.
Of course, hardliners still demanded more, and continued to organize and militarize around
the goal of the total annihilation of their former slave owners.
Sticky Fingers gang, meanwhile, have been given full pardon for their crimes, and a position
in the kingdom as members of the clandestine organization, the Night Terrors.
To what end, who knows?
Fuck You, meanwhile, ran the theme park idiot land, Stupidville, where he was finally given
his wizarding tower of terror.
While his home doubled as a ride, he was pleased as one could be, acting as a surrogate father
and leader to hundreds of idiot slaves.
Ola, meanwhile, still helped fund and advise on the theme park, but she also became business
partners and more with Thorax, whose gang grew in size and now acted as a private security
force for her conglomerate.
She used her considerable influence and association with the three heroes of Trebuchet Village
to expand her business and the influence of the city of Gal Gadot, whose ruler, the tiefling
Gorgonzola, was now poised to make a move on a weakened Nardwar.
The Prince Jumanji was forever changed.
The decision he made in the Terrifier Realm turned him into an ice cold warrior prince.
Everything his father thought he wanted him to be.
He'll never forget the time he spent with the three adventurers and the lessons they
taught him about what it means to be a man.
As for those three adventurers, Patrick, Dogen, and Evil, well they're heroes.
They ended a war that could have torn the kingdom apart before it even began.
They halted the resurrection of a beloved evil god who would have probably killed everyone
were he brought back, at least according to one particular creature.
Each of them were made minor lords of the Terrafire Kingdom, given a plot of land and
tons of gold.
They had their theme park that gave them a tidy profit, and they had their friends from
Whippet Woods to Gal Gadot and Trebuchet Village and the Walrus.
They had plenty of company and love.
Something else is always on the horizon for these three, because adventurers can't sit
still for long.
The legendary Trunchbull, who finally gave his nephew the slow dance he needed to grow
up, passed away peacefully, surrounded by his beloved friends and his white women.
His parting gift to Patridge was a galleon, one he christened the White Woman of the Sea
Long, long ago.
The promise of a pirate's life is almost too great to resist.
So only time will tell what the boys do with that.
Much has changed in the Terrifier Kingdom,
since our three heroes were called, or rather launched,
into action by the force of ten thousand dragons.
Many mysteries still remain.
Mount Hodus Doodle is still missing.
Spirits that litter planet E-Bomb still confound.
And while our hero's place in the surreptitious trappings of capital-D Destiny seem assured,
the meaning of this and its relationship to powers beyond the veil remains as elusive
as ever.
Only one thing feels certain in every single respect.
There's a frog-shaped hole in the universe.
And Lord knows who's gonna fill that hole.
Will it be you?
Are you gonna do it?
Are you gonna fill the hole?
The End.