penis in my but alright recording so
last time on uh...
will change the title now it's a end of the e-bombs
'cause uh... his because we choose
so we have a little while yeltsin yet the old one was
was a lot longer
well yeah sales and c_-one
area
we don't even need to know that it was a little bit forward
it was a delay had a uh...
loop if you ask
so anyway what happened last time was
you guys saved
uh... rubbers
uh... all the robbers
the rebel oh yeah i'm starting to come back to my house i was at the end of the
first i think it's a rather
people i said i don't use no rubbers buddy and i guess i think i guess also
depends on the paid to find saved decided to take them on his slaves you put into
to your slave theme park as an aquarium.
You said we slaved them.
We slaved them.
Yeah.
That's what I said.
So we have a slave theme park.
Yeah.
Well, you've had that for a while.
We already had one.
Yeah.
We had a second brain.
It was a -- we made a stupid --
A sea world version of it, I thought.
Yeah.
And so when you guys got back from saving them or --
Slaving them, yeah.
Slaving them, actually, yeah.
kind of started fighting again and then you realized that Sullivan was missing
and in the beginning of the second session you forgot that you
remembered that but you went to Gracias Mi Amigo who's the governor of Port
Virtue Good who you guys have been privateering for for the last six months
or so and he directed you to fuck you fuck me fuck me he directed you to fuck
me. He directed me to fuck you? No, fuck you. No, fuck me. Why me? Why me? Why me's
brother fuck me who you guys changed to fuck you. Okay, yeah. Yeah, it's coming
back. Yeah. So, um, and this is the worst possible thing to come back to.
It'll be a lot simpler, I think.
I think.
So, FuckMe showed you guys
a piece of metal that he said
was from another realm. So, similar to the
Terrafire's realm, which is where you guys
decided to execute Sullivan.
There are other realms that you can go to.
Patrick Giottar quickly
ate that piece of metal, and so, through
that, he has like intense recall of everything
up from when Mount Honestoodle
exploded until now.
Like, he just has like perfect, until he
He's like perfect recall. Okay of all that total recall. Yeah total complete recall
and than total you guys now all kind of remember Sullivan and
Fuck me told you guys
To get Sullivan you'd have to go to realms deep which is through the archipelago. That is
Virtue good archipelago, which you guys are on which is the west part. So
The trebuchet village is the same as gun city where it's shaped like a gun because it's just yeah the same landmass
Mm-hmm West a big village. Mm-hmm. The big village West is
The the virtue good archipelago that was like established by the pirate virtue good and what does that shape like?
It's just like a scatter Hawaii Island. So it's kind of like Hawaii kind of like Hawaii. Okay
Hawaii, yeah, I guess yeah. No, nothing
Well, there is hot babe Island, which we established last time and that is shaped like boobies. Oh
So talk about that later
But you guys decided that once you realize that to sail west
Well, you would have you would get to realms deep which is how you would rescue
Sullivan who died dying not in the realm he originated in means he's actually not fully dead
He's just trapped between realms
But you guys decided you actually wanted to sail as far away as possible from Sullivan and so you're gonna sail
East as far away as possible and believing that the world is flat you
think you'll just get to the end of Zeebombs world and we can be as far away
from Sullivan as possible. Yeah, believing the world is flat. Yeah. We all believe
the world is not flat. Yeah, the world is not flat but nobody knows that
it's not flat for the most part. All right. Including you guys. Yeah. So it's a... I
don't know shit. Yeah and so you guys started sailing, after we figured that
head out. You guys started sailing east, back towards the Trebuchet village/Gun City, like
landmass, and you ran into a group of sirens who tried to woo you away.
Oh, yeah, Gangnam style.
Yeah, and then Patrick did a roll that I let him do that made me upset, so I just ended
the campaign, or I just ended the session very early and abruptly. But we're gonna just
say that you bested the sirens.
was the roll again. Gangnam Style. It was Gangnam Style and I let you like do a charisma roll
that I shouldn't have let you really do but I was in a mood. Can you just explain again
what I did? It was Gangnam Style. You just you won okay? You won. Now button your shirt.
I could tell you. The shirt's half buttoned. I like your petticoat. It's just goofy. Just
button it. No you're not. It's a new style. If you want to be a cholo you have to button
just the top. Nope. He's being Napoleon. You look stupid. Put your hand back in like that.
kind of like okay you look like Napoleon actually. Yeah, it looks like Napoleon
right now. So yeah, you guys are now sailing. So here's the thing, you
guys would understand that the way the world is, there is the known like
continents are the trebuchet landmass, which is the Terrifier Kingdom and
associated like sort of smaller countries that exist with around it. Then
between that and there's two continents that are the kissing continents and then
there's like a sea between them so have a very rudimentary map of this that I have
to I have to put a lot more details into it but like I just started it's very
like literally like nothing I'm still working on it you guys really shouldn't
be seeing this side of it yet. I already see that. I'm memorizing what's going on over there.
You guys don't know but the world's round. But this is... That kind of looks like the
old guy from Courage the Cowardly Dog. Straight up I couldn't see... I can't see it from this
side. There's too much light. So your dog drew this? Yeah, my dog drew this. And so this
is kind of where you guys are right now. So you got a long ways to go along the coast
before you get to, and I will upload a actually good version
of the map, one of these days into the Discord.
And these are the Kissing Continents,
which are known continents.
- It's kind of Africa.
- Yeah, no, I don't, maybe.
And then this is the Kissing Sea,
which is between the end of the Terrifier Kingdom
and the Kissing Continents.
- Is Africa on this map?
- Where is Africa?
- There is no Africa.
- Oh, interesting.
- Strange.
- Wow.
choice planet he's just getting rid of Africa Africa is like a different
planet okay tread lightly here patches I don't think Africa is a different play
okay seems like the right but you so you think Africa's on ebombs world and also
I've seen a few clips of Africa bumps world so but yeah so you guys would be
are you guys so you guys have a couple things you guys said that you were you
were thinking about dropping off your rubbers at your aquarium in the trash
yeah if you do that you will have to either you could do that now but that
would require some extensive land travel probably - if you dock in it is real
which is the new brave lions nation that's called what it is real okay it is
real mm-hmm it is real yeah and it's new brave lions nation that was carved out
for them after the end of the last campaign. And you could dock there, they're not an easy
nation to deal with, surprise, surprise. And you could go across by land. That would take
less time than to go around through the sea, but you would also then have to get a new
boat like the other side of it can we can we delegate somebody like just a crew
member to bring all the rubbers on land a we can just because I just want to be on
the boat forever yeah yeah I've got my you guys can just keep the rub like you
have enough supplies inventory where we can wait or can we just keep saying like
oh yeah we're taking you to the your new home don't worry so what's there yeah I
mean they're not they're pretty gullible like but you have enough food for them
on the boat so I was about to say so you have right now you would
you probably have like a week's time before you should go to a port. Okay.
Um, and, but we're at, it is real, right? You're not in Israel. No, you're out at sea.
You just got past the side. Why don't we just bring them to the, the theme park?
Cause we'll have to travel across the theme park. The three park will be like weeks of like
traveling. If not more, we just, we should just bring them with us.
We'll see them with us as extra. If the food thing is tough in, it is real
Make a new theme park?
Yeah, we double our income.
The issue, the issue I would say is that, so Galaga-
Well, they, well, okay. I don't want to say it.
No, that's not the issue.
Technically, the rubbers are our slaves. We could make them build the theme park in It Is Real.
The only thing is that I don't think It Is Real will like that.
So we...
They have to deal with that.
Your theme park is in like near Gal Gadot.
Like it's in the Gal Gadot area.
Which is a very pro
terrifier, pro...
We could do... I mean...
Six slaves over it is real.
We could do like an expansion thing.
Yeah. I don't know.
Yeah, maybe we drop... I think we should keep a bunch of them on the boat.
Because it's nice to have extra guys around.
And then if we run out of food or something,
we'll eat them or throw them overboard.
overboard okay I like that idea yeah I don't have to travel over land.
You guys have been talking about this in front of everybody by the way. I was gonna say we do
this on the on the port so like you go into the port and it's like sandals the
port so we do like a sandals thing mmm Atlantis yeah so I would say that on the
port of it is real. If you go south which will take a little bit longer time but
there will be port towns on the way if you go south you could probably
probably establish them somewhere that would be less difficult to build a
slave aquarium theme park because it would be more in line with...
Let's do that then. Let's just go south and then build a new one.
Yeah, let's do that.
Well, do we have money? We're gonna need to call our girl, right?
Yeah, I mean, I think we'll have to...
We don't need money. They're slaves. What are you gonna pay them?
How are we gonna get all the materials, asshole?
Just take it.
Take it from who?
Everyone.
Well, there are... Yeah, I mean, there are towns you can raid.
You guys could just go pirate.
It's fantasy world. It's like Minecraft. You can just get stuff.
is it like minecraft patches or can we just what then what how do you how do
you mean it's you can get some wood from a tree so in that way is a lot like
minecraft okay you sold me it's mine and the slaves do that okay you don't even
do that but but it's Tom go this and they go get all the stuff is there
happen instantaneously it takes time we're gonna leave them and then I get
them started so then you should pick a place so so I mean there are well
well wouldn't we I'm saying we should do it in it is real because I feel like that
would you know it would it would forge a good relationship with us and it is real
he just said it wouldn't he said they would not like they would hate it
they're very anti-slavery and it is real but are they anti theme park no who's
anti theme park yeah maybe okay maybe we build the theme park and we just said we
set up a whole operation we make it look like we're paying like we have a very
public thing we're like and they were like and here's your paychecks everybody
it's a piece of it's a piece of wood and they're not getting paid so everyone in
Israel doesn't doesn't put it on to the thing like the theme park they build a
slide out of it so as are the people watching gonna know but it's a piece of
wood - no it's an envelope duh Oh inside the awful there's a piece of wood
in the envelope. Giving your building materials through envelopes. Yeah. It's not such a bad
idea. I'm saying it's a paycheck. They'll think they're the most well-paid workers.
Let's do that. We're gonna do that. Okay. We can't talk anymore. Yeah. So that's not
gonna happen though for a little bit because you're-- Okay. Let's just scrap that idea.
Well, no, no, no. I mean, you can-- so you can go on your way over there. There are--
it'll take probably about-- it'll take probably like three or four days travel to get to--
to get to Yid Israel?
- To get to Yid Israel, to get to the coast.
- That's fine by me.
- Yeah, so, all right.
You guys wanna start sailing?
- Yeah. - Let's start sailing.
Okay.
Yeah, so we're going to, before we do the,
we're gonna start sailing in the midst,
we're considering this while we're sailing.
I'm gonna familiarize you guys with your new--
- Would the citizens of Yid Israel even know
that these robbers are our slaves?
We could just say they're our friends.
- That's what we already decided on.
We're gonna say they're our employees.
That's the whole plan.
- Well, we don't even have to say we're gonna pay them.
We can just say, oh, these are our friends.
- You're just getting way too ahead of yourself.
- Yeah, you're trying to explain the things.
- I'm trying to tie up everything you say.
- You try and spend 45 minutes before we even do
a character voice. - I wanna play the game.
- So you guys have new equipment and stuff,
'cause you're pirates.
So I changed, I think you two, I added some new equipment.
I'm not sure, I think your mace,
we're gonna change to a hook.
You're gonna have a hook hand.
You two, I added new equipment for you.
I changed your battle axe into a big oar.
- War oar.
- A war oar.
I call it big oar.
- I have the Cutlass of Cortez.
- Yes, you have the Cutlass of Cortez.
- What is that?
- It's a Juni-
- It sounds cool.
- It's a homebrew.
- That sounds cool, Patrick.
- It's a homebrew item I found online
that I like the name.
Very unique.
(laughing)
- Who is Cortez?
- Who the fuck is that?
- It's supposed to be Cortex from Crash Bandicoot.
- No, it says right there, cut this off Cortex.
- Yeah, it's a typo.
- And then-- - Neo Cortex.
- You guys have guns.
- Yo.
- I shoot you.
- No.
(laughing)
- No, I'm kidding.
- You have three guns total.
Guns are extremely rare, extremely hard to come by.
- Where's my gun?
I don't see it in my inventory.
- Extremely expensive, I haven't added it yet
because those are kinda homebrew-y
and are gonna be a little more specific.
- Okay.
- But there is a musket, there's blunderbuss,
And then there's a pistol.
So, I'll explain, I mean, I don't know if you guys
are familiar with how those guns look and do.
- I do, I do know what they look like.
- I know.
- Musket, long range, in this case.
Slower, it has a fire rate of,
and I'll explain what fire rate means.
I made a bunch of gun mechanics.
A four, and does 1D12 damage.
It is the gun that will allow you to,
it's sort of for your ranged shooter, whoever that is.
Blunderbuss is a range of very short, 30 feet.
- I have no ranged.
- It is for forceful, you know, shooting,
like sort of shotgun kind of thing.
Like it kind of explodes out of it.
- Like strength-based?
- Yes, pretty much.
Pistol then is more of about disarming.
It's a little bit more about being crafty.
And has the highest fire rate.
So. - So, how many bullets?
- I would say that--
- How many bullets per minute?
A thousand?
So the way that I do guns is that you only have to deal with
reload or like missing a turn if you have a misfire.
And we'll explain what misfire is when we, later.
But, and then the fire rate is how many rolls you do.
It'll make more sense when we get into a combat situation.
And I think where Cam was pointing makes sense.
- That's right, where I was pointing, Caleb.
- But you could do whatever you want, obviously.
You guys can talk about it in character too.
- What if we all have one blunderbuss?
- I grabbed the, yeah, I think we each get a blunderbuss.
- I don't even want a gun.
Okay.
Does anybody even care?
No, okay.
- I'm taking a blunderbuss.
- I'll take the pistol.
- I don't even want it.
- Okay, I'll also take the musket.
- Fine by me.
- Okay, cool.
- Can I have the musket?
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Okay, cool.
So you have the musket and the pistol,
and you have the blunderbuss, you have no gun.
That's fine, you have magic.
So the way that gun, we'll see how gun combat works in a second.
I mean also melee combat has been overhauled.
I...
Whoa.
Overboarded.
Come on.
Yeah, in a lot of ways.
I ain't leaning over.
I'm comfy.
I'm literally leaning over for you.
I don't know if that was going to be for me, but I'll take it.
So in 5e there is a class called the, well it's the fighter class, but there's a subclass
for the fighter that is the battle master.
And they have all these really cool maneuvers.
I don't know if cool is the right word, but I like them.
And I decided to just rework them so that you can do them too at any time.
And what they will be is sort of like, you'll be used, you can spend a bonus action to do
one of these things either before or after a successful attack. So before an attack,
let's say you can do a lunge, you can prepare for a lunge, which will give you extra range,
do extra damage, but if you miss, you'll take more damage on the next attack. But after
an attack, you can do something like a distracting strike, right? So you land a successful attack,
and then you do something to distract them, and then that can give other attackers advantage
or disadvantage. There's all these like little tricks you can do or like tripping somebody
or parrying or reposting. And I'll explain those. Like what we'll do is we're going to
end up in a we're going to end up in combat this session so that these will make more
sense. I'm scared. And and the one other thing about that, all this is that if you nail three
of these maneuvers on a target, they are then staggered, which means in the next attack
will automatically hit for no matter what it is. So it's sort of like this idea of trying
out all these maneuvers, getting them to fall, getting them to, you know, getting them to
be goaded into attacking you, doing all kinds of things. And then once you kind of do that
to them, they kind of like stagger and then whoever wants to attack them will get to have
to automatically.
Kind of Sid Meier's Pirates.
I love Sid Meier's Pirates. Yes, it's similar to that. It's similar to Sekiro, which I've
been playing a lot. Then I mean, just because it has staggering, I
guess, but then with the guns, there's also special shots with
them. I took some of that from Matt Mercer's gun slinger class.
And then also added something to make gun combat way more fun
because I don't like the idea of just you're using a gun, it
should be it should feel a little bit more fun. So we'll
get to that. We'll get to that. We'll get to that now actually.
as you guys are sailing out
who is actually where it where it's everybody on
on the royal caribbean or the caribbean royale from behind the driver's seat
behind the kind of a guy i'm not a man
you're in the house and the driver's seat in the back of the driver's seat you
have somebody who typically will it would pilot the ship are you planning on
his lap where the robbers
you're steering the ship
the robbers
they are i mean they're wherever you guys want them to
to do work their stowed their barrels their stone in barrels and i'm driving
the girls for grog in the ground here we are going to let the barrels
what you doing i'm swinging my pistol the barrels no carrying
when he is a senior not shooting please stop
mhm please let us out
man
all if you guys don't shut up back they'll turn this whole boat around you
do you know i'm driving back to their to
yeah i don't know where they are the bear barrels of grog barrels could be
anywhere that you know you know i mean it's a real sick on the deck of him
sorry yes that's what i meant
the uh... i don't know that i did not assume that they can allow the same
place and it's a small ship yes what is it fifteen feet long it's a lot it's a
galleon
uh... i don't know what i want to know and i am right so
here there's a gallon of grog galleon of grog and all the barrels in a moment
So all of you roll, well actually you,
actually 'cause you're the one driving, right?
- Yeah.
- You're steering rather.
And you're kind of, if you're by that,
you're looking out, you should roll only perception right now.
- I'm rolling perception.
- So only him.
- Oh well, well, look at me.
I'm about to save the day with my perception roll.
- Oh you were pointing a gun at a barrel.
- All right, it wasn't a good roll.
- And I got a 15.
- 15, okay, it's pretty good.
- 15 plus what?
- Not so bad, it's 15.
- Oh right, 'cause it does the math for you on the phone.
- Yep.
- Cool.
- Oh wait, no, 17, 'cause it does the math
for me on the phone. - Oh, let's do,
okay, wowie, wowie zowie.
Is that true or?
- Okay.
- All right, so.
- I wrote a 15, but I thought it would include it
with the roll for some reason.
- Oh, it didn't?
That's goofy.
- No, I mean, it did underneath, right?
- Oh, okay. - 17.
- 17, so yeah, okay.
With that, you see the sun beating down, it's day,
and you see some of it--
- It's day.
- This is day.
(laughing)
- Oh man, I'm so perceptive.
It is day.
- You notice some, that sort of out in front of you,
the light coming in from the sun is kind of refracting
and shifting among the waters, like right above the waters.
And when you get a closer look at it,
it looks like it's in the shape of an object,
like of a object floating on top of the water.
And as you sail a little bit further closer,
it looks almost like a ship,
but like a trans, almost like a transparent ship
with like sort of this like sun refracting
and beating through it.
And yeah, I mean, you notice that.
- I think I need a glass of water.
- Why?
- Just thirsty.
- Okay, yeah, you can go.
So I mean, well, getting, you have some,
you have water skins probably on the lower deck.
I'm gonna go drink that, 'cause I think I'm seeing things.
- Okay, cool, so you go downstairs and drink that.
Now as we're getting closer to it,
I will say that you can now hear
sort of a creaking sound.
- Okay.
- And I'm going to need everyone on the ship
to roll a...
Strength saving throw.
- Strength saving throw.
Strength saving throw. You could argue its constitution. It takes so long to roll.
Okay I got a dirty 20. Oh I almost had a 20 I got a 2. It rolled onto the 20. It hit the corner and then it rolled onto the 2.
Okay. What the fuck is the physics on this stupid shit? And what about you? I got a 6.
Okay, cool. So, something hits the ship and makes the hull nearly shatter. The force
of it, you hear an explosion, the force of it hitting the ship, you can't see it. You
see sort of a sheen of light kind of smash into it. I shoot my gun in a barrel.
You hear a rubber go "Ahhhh!" and grog starts pouring out of it. You also fall over, you're
knocked prone, you fall over, you're trying to drink the water and it spills on you
like with Phil did earlier and you are knocked prone as well.
Okay. You now, because you're still up, Dogen, Raw Dogen, you and you can now
sort of make out what's happening here. What he was seeing that he
thought was an illusion was a kind of a it was a glass ship pirate ship look
across and you can see all these like like pirates but they're all made
entirely of glass and they're easy we have the easiest fight of all time
what happened to their their ship hit our ship no no no like spilled it when
he's not a good shot probably glass cannon glass cannon mm-hmm
Yeah. Glass cannon. And you notice them and you see that one of them is looking
over at you and sort of and points his cutlass towards you. And it's made out of
glass. Yeah, it's cut glass. Yes, it's made out of glass. Cut glass. And he's
turning towards and the ship is turning towards you. So in this instance with
ship combat, I mean you could either you can try to position yourself to
retaliate and shoot cannons back and order your crew to do that. You can try
try to board, start trying to board the ship and maneuver around it. It's up to
you what you want to do since you're the one steering. I feel like it's just shoot
some cannonballs at it and it's gonna shatter. Yeah, it's a good try. It's a good
idea. I think. You already said it was a good try which means it's not gonna work.
No, no. You know what I meant. He slipped up. I meant to say good idea. He said good try.
Actually I'll melt it. You'll melt it with what? The cannonballs. Okay. The heat.
Yeah, the heat from the cannonballs. Okay, cool. So in that case you order your crew to do
that yeah what do you say what do you do it go do what do it you see one goes you
know what that means they all know what that means they light the cannonballs
they make an attack on the ship I'm gonna roll a roll a sexy check
where my D set yeah okay one it the cannons connect with the glass ship and
And instead of shattering what you thought it might have,
they like lodge into the ship, the cannonballs.
- So it's plastic instead of glass?
- Okay, so this is bullshit.
- Well, you can see that the ship
has sustained some kind of damage,
but there is this sort of like,
it's thicker than you had thought it was.
But it is taking damage from the cannonballs.
- It doesn't even crack?
- Well, it's like, it like gets lodged in,
there's cracks that are--
- There's like a bullet and like bulletproof glass
yes, I can I'm all right yeah like bullet glass. So what do you do to
bulletproof glass? Don't you use or that's car glass. They have a special
tool or you do we have that special tool. I go up and I hit that ship with
my elbow. We're gonna die your own ship. No, that's how you turn the ship into
you're so far from like can we ram it? Yeah, you can try. So we ram it. Can I
do a really quick perception check to see if there's like a single little
vulnerable spot where if I touch the entire thing I'll explode.
Yeah, you could do a, yeah, let's have you do a perception check on that.
It's really more of an insight check.
Let's do insight actually.
Insight?
Yeah, you're kind of insight into the condition of the ship, what could make it do that.
I would say investigation, but you're not, I guess it could be investigation.
Because you're inciting an attack.
So I got a one.
Okay.
But plus two.
Plus two.
That's good.
But you got a crit one.
Yeah.
know that ship might as well be made of. So am I still drinking water then downstairs?
Like Wolverine. Okay. Oh man. You are drinking water still. I mean no you're not prone. You
heard cannons going off. So yeah what do you two want to do before he steers the ship into
the glass? Like do you guys want to? Well I put my mouth on the hole in the barrel. The
barrel a bit of blood and a bit of grog also I would like to load myself into a
cannon that's actually I you know what I do I'm walking up to him and I'm
grabbing the no no actually I'm walking up to I'm walking up to Dogen mm-hmm
give me the blunderbuss no just for one single thing no you don't want to know
all right give me the other gun that none of us would fit in that gun give me
the gun I don't need you to fit in the gun just give it to me which gun you
didn't even know whatever the musket the musket you would know I lost that you
lost the money all right did you lose it no roll deception roll inside it gets
this direction now we got a crit one last time on inside there's no way I get it
again. 26. 20. Natural? Not natural. 30-20. You're both like, you have like a monster
weapon. Super raised, sort of like veins popping out of our heads. Like the scandals battle.
You're out trying to out think each other
Fine I guess you really don't have it
Yeah, I lost it cuz I thought so hard about it that I decided there's no way you have it
Yep, you'd have to be seriously good at lying poking out of his shirt
That must be some kind of it's a broom it's a broom
What I thought okay
Well, then I'm going to just load myself into a cannon and let tell one of the rubbers to fire me
At the the glass ship. Okay, cool. I'm getting in there dog. Yes, sir
I'll help you and it goes up to the road to the cannon and lights it
Wonder how this is gonna go. You should roll really well. Yes
I mean awesome all will you should probably you're just gonna take damage
What that's kind of true we have but how did evil Knievel to do it then holy shit? I even think about asshole
How did evil Knievel do it and he just did it they do it as - he doesn't hurt to fought to be shot out of a
can
Doesn't hurt no
Guess if they do it in Jack's just fast show where no one gets hurt makes you go fast
Well, they didn't get hurt in that way usually when I get hurt they throw up and like cry or whatever, okay?
happy. It doesn't hit your nuts. It doesn't hurt. It might hurt, but it's
probably not doesn't do damage. It doesn't do damage. Yeah, right. It doesn't break skin.
It might like hurt your feet a little bit when it's... It's like having a headache.
Like a headache doesn't want to take away your HP, but it hurts. Yeah, it's
anyway, I'm fine. I believe you guys. So if he lands on the ship, he will get a
headache. That's fine by me. If that's the trade-off. That's the trade-off.
Alright, if I land on the ship, I do get a headache. Okay, cool. But not that bad for one.
He does damn so I'm gonna have to do is roll um I guess I have to roll dexterity for the rubber
Mom cuz he's got a press a button well
He's gonna unless you're are you gonna set up the cannon before I set it up perfect
So you're gonna roll wisdom check so you roll just a wisdom just a straight wisdom check
Religion has cuz he's got a pray that this shit works
He's a cleric where the hell is my wisdom I found it whiz wait, that's insight right
uh... and well it might be the same value if you don't have to conditions both of
them right here
and when he was inside a scroll up
you have to go to the way it is a huge
yes i don't know if there was a little early check your
freaking boomer can use an app
you know
and uh...
uses and because he's being shot at a weekend and it doesn't know how to use
a good nineteen while okay you name that really really well you can i mean
directly at one of the glass guys headache yeah absolutely okay and before
and as I get in don't say headache incoming there's no
detected a headache yours is a nerd robot what was I supposed to do just
don't do a robot man you're supposed to be the yeah sorry the fuck ever man okay
so I would like to cannon explosion I'm gonna hold I'm gonna hold my mace in
front of me okay okay I don't have a sword I'm gonna hold my mace in front of
me as I'm shot out of the cannon I'd like to aim myself directly at one of the
glass man I was saying that the the mace was gonna be a hook and oh yeah it's a
hook now it's even cooler look what spike all right so I'd like to aim my
hook with spikes right at one of the guy don't you feel like a you're like a
hooker flying at one of the guys don't you aim towards the hooker with the
moves fool just can't is there like a dent on the ship that's made out of
glass when you just aim for that and then
I won't have anywhere to swim.
Okay.
You're gonna fly through the air.
So you got, okay, you launch out,
you fly through the air.
I mean, let's do this.
I'm afraid of heights, I die instantly in the air.
(laughing)
Okay.
Let me see if, I guess they're gonna roll
dexterity saving throw.
I'm just always doing the coolest stuff, guys.
This is pretty cool.
I do like this.
You two are just like, you're shooting a barrel.
I mean, I'm driving the ship.
I could, I could.
You're driving, that's awesome.
I'm ramming a ship.
I'm literally like flying through the sky
with a mace in my hands.
- It's not a mace, it's a hook.
- Okay, good.
- A hook in my hand.
- So you're a hooker.
- And I'm a hooker.
- And that's all you got.
- You got 19 on your wisdom, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay, yeah.
What's this gonna be?
So your mace is usually what, 1D,
is it 1D6 or 8 damage?
- The mace is 1D6.
- Okay, 1D6.
Roll that, 'cause it's probably the distance.
Roll that five, roll a D6 five times.
A D6 five times?
Because I'm thinking like you're probably a certain number of feet away, probably like
30, probably 50 feet away.
And so usually it's plus one D6 for each like 10 feet of fall damage.
Oh yeah.
I'm thinking of it that way.
Quick maths.
Let's see.
29.
Wow.
Uh, yeah.
You just fucking fly through the air.
hear like a like it's like a whistling sound because I'm going so fast yeah and
it just shattering through this guy's head oh my wow did you guys see that oh
my god I didn't see it scope of my musket and I'm like wow that was awesome
you have to roll initiative though because now you're on a ship surrounded
by glass pirates guess what fucker I fucking got it oh and also when you
shatter through him he shatters and then turns to sand and then falls whoa so
fucking sand man so no no no it's just a random why do you aim for the captain I
didn't know which one is oh my god okay well I didn't know that nobody helped me
in any other way well he doesn't have it that's okay
he's screaming across like a dot jumping up and down.
All right I'm gonna yeah I got a 19 on my initiative - okay everything's going
fucking gravy. Great so we'll come back to you you guys see evil Steve-o launch
in the air maybe shatter a guy and then like sand kind of appearing and then go
yeah I'm like oh he's so happy yeah I can see celebrating see him through my but
the scope of my musket he's uh he's really in he's really loving that shit
I like you have the scope on your musket on backwards and he's even smaller in
the scope of your musket at me there's fucking 30 guys made of glass I'm making
sure that you're okay and I'm looking around what would you do if I wasn't okay
what would you be doing you're sitting on a ship aiming a gun at me and I and I've
I've been drinking
blood. Yeah, you have been drinking yeah. Yeah, I mean do you want to steer this
ship and try to board the ship? Otherwise, like you can do another
maneuver as the as the wasn't I already ramming it wasn't I already doing that
and I'm locked in and I can't not ram my ship right into where Caleb standing. Oh,
were you already? Where did you decide you were going to ram it? I thought that
was what you said. Okay, I'll try board it. You need to take more. You both need
take command and do something awesome like what I just I was okay okay then I
ran the ship okay cool that's pretty cool so with that I would say roll okay
and I climb and why I set the ship to ramp and I climb out on the on the
figurehead and I hold out my my war or like you like Steve was flying so your
war or I don't know if you know you will know right now okay once per long rest
you can talk you can sort of commune with your your new god water uh-huh and
basically cast a wave spell from your ore whoa out and that's not gonna do
anything that ship those ships love water you can literally capsize this
thing and I just flew it and how big is the wave it's 30 feet high whoa
He fucking destroyed us, Chip.
10 feet by 10 feet.
Sorry, 10 feet like deep.
10 feet high. 6 feet.
You said it was 30 feet high. Shut the fuck up.
I thought you said it was 30 feet high.
Sorry, 10 feet wide, 10 feet deep.
I feel like that's not big enough to cap.
I won't cap size.
30 feet high and 10 feet wide for a wave?
Oh, the other way around.
Jesus Christ.
If you aim it towards that spot
that you hit the cannonball, I think you'll hit something.
I apologize. Yeah, it's supposed to be 30 feet wide. Sorry. Yeah, 10 feet deep. I was excited.
That'd be cool. Yeah. I don't think I feel like... If you swing the oar vertically, it
does that. If you swing it horizontally, it goes the other way. Let's do that. Okay. Well,
I feel like that's not... It still won't probably be enough to capsize, but you can do a bunch
of damage to the people on board. You can swipe them away. I can swipe them away. Yes, well,
there is also knockback if you successfully land the attack. Oh, okay. Can I still set
the ship to ram and then do that if you want to do that you'll have to coordinate
with your um oh yeah I'll tell the boatswing do it what if you
scurvy neck shoot the wave behind our ship so to make you go faster we surf
the wave I'm doing that ship that is fucking awesome yeah so I sir we surf
the ship up in the air and then ours comes dead lands and smashes the other
one in half also somebody corrected me on the discord it's like boats boats win
or something it's not boatswain it's the way you call his boat swain is a dumb
idiot okay also if anybody knows how that word is actually pronounced you
shouldn't ever listen to them yeah I want to do the right is there probably a
freaking pirate yeah facts we got some I don't live with pirates no yeah also
boatswains or boatswains don't their fixtures mechanics it would be the um the
not the quartermaster what's their fucking name I mean it's dear or something
I mean, it doesn't matter because I'm not doing that anymore.
I'm making a wave behind,
I'm making a wave behind slash under us to lift us up
and surf and smash into the other.
- That's good.
Okay, 'cause I was gonna say, okay, so,
all right, so in that case, you're gonna,
'cause to do this,
I was gonna have you do an athletics check.
You can do that with advantage now,
to steering the ship and like making sure
that it goes into the right direction.
- Yeah, I want the ship to lift up
like it's surfing like a surfboard.
And then I want it to smash down
and smash the other ship completely in half.
- Yeah, I would say do an athletics check.
Completely in half.
That will be interesting.
Because I'm on the fucking ship.
And I'm gonna get fucking owned.
Just get out of the way.
Okay.
Athletics.
I didn't think about that.
You might fucking own Caleb.
Okay.
With advantage, right?
Yes.
Alright, well the first roll is 21.
And then the second roll, this takes so long to roll, is 19.
So it's 21.
Blackjack.
Whoa.
The pirate?
So anyway, yeah, you steer your ship, you line it up perpendicularly perfectly and it flies
up in the air, crashes into the middle of this.
You have to roll a dexterity saving throw, evil Stievel.
To avoid-
Wait, does this ship have cannons?
The glass ship?
Yes.
Oh my God, doing some Bugs Bunny bunker hill shit.
Can I just shoot myself back?
You want to try to shoot yourself back?
I think I do.
That sounds impossible. It sounds impossible. But I'm not so sure that it is.
Okay, so here's the thing. The only way you'd really be able to do that is if
you saw the wave coming up underneath the ship and you were like, "I know what this is."
Not only did I see the wave, I saw a Musesaur. Okay? So you knew it was coming.
And I think that we've established this before that me and Dogen have a friend
link. Yes, we have. So what you're gonna have to do then is you're gonna have to
run past a bunch of people who are trying to kill you.
- Yep.
- And get into the cannon and have it lit.
So this will be a first time we're gonna discuss maneuvers
because this would be--
- Oh, the launch cell from cannon maneuver.
- No, no.
- This does sound like a maneuver.
- It's a little, it's not, that's not what I'm--
- It sounds like a whole load of maneuver,
just out of the way.
- So it's called the, let me find it.
It's (mumbles)
- Where are you?
Evasive footwork.
So when you move, you can roll one D8
and add that number rolled to your AC until you stop moving.
So that's something you would maybe try to move,
try to do so that you can get past--
- Roll one D8, you said?
- Add it and then basically,
'cause here's what's gonna happen.
If you're running, you're gonna have to run past
at least three of these guys to get there.
And so you're gonna wanna avoid attack of opportunities.
- So I'm gonna roll a D8 and do what?
- And add that to your AC.
And then we're gonna roll,
then they're gonna roll attack rolls,
all these glass pirates.
That's something you can do now.
- I've already done it.
What is my, my AC is 15 and I rolled a six,
so that's a 21. - Okay, wow, 21.
Okay, so now all these guys are gonna try to attack you.
- Blackjack. - Blackjack.
- It's blackjack. - Blackjack.
- I think that's fun.
- Can we get, every time we get rolled blackjack,
can we get a blackjack point?
- And then we can cash in at the end of the campaign
for prizes like at the Pokemon Casino.
- You should have prizes for us.
- I should have prizes for you guys.
(laughing)
You should you should have at the end of every okay. I'm gonna write down to like we should earn tokens
And you should have like bubblegum and pixie sticks and Chinese. Yes traps. I will keep track of blackjack points
Okay, I got you we got to I think we can collectively all share them
Evasive maneuver the end we divide them all up and spend them like arcade tickets
Okay deal cuz one of them would have hit you so you run past the guy who was immediately behind you as he was circling
in you sort of a
You juke him as you're running down the stairs towards where the cannons are in the hall
There's a guy hanging in the banister waiting to stab you
Yeah
He goes for a stab you very easily
sidestep it and sort of chin I go and juke him into the it's the wall and when you get to the cannon there's a
Guy standing in front of it. Yeah, very clear. Oh, they're almost gets you you slide under him knock him up
Yeah, a lot of cool shit, and then you jump into a cannon who's gonna light it. Is it gonna be you bugs money?
funny. I light a match okay. You have a match. There's matches around the can.
Of course you have. Yeah, of course. You have matches. I light a match and I
throw it up into the air as I get into the can and it lands perfectly on the
fuse. Fuck yeah, dude. Yeah. Okay, yeah. I'm okay with that. Okay, and then
also because I'm going towards my friends, instead of holding my hook hand
out, I like to hold a bouquet of flowers.
I'll allow it. The only thing I won't allow though is this to be perfect
without a wisdom saving throw. Buddy, you're gonna get- No wisdom saving throw.
Wisdom ability check to aim that cannon very quickly.
So not a saving throw.
No, I mean this would be Wisdom or Dex I would say.
Let me see which one I have better.
I think Wisdom probably because you're a Cleric.
I mean it could maybe be a combination of those two, but I'd rather just have you choose one.
Yeah, my Wisdom is better. I'll go Wisdom.
Alright, maybe it'll roll.
18 plus 2, 20.
Wow okay cool. Dirty 20. Dirty 20. Dirty 20. Dirty 20. Dirty 20.
Yeah so you're in the glass cannon and you fly out of it with a bouquet of
roses. Roses? No. Lilies. Lilies. That's cute. You fly past
you fly past Dogen. Can I bite one of the flowers? Yes. No I drop them
in your mouth. Okay, the entire book a like a dog holding a bone. They're just
sitting in your mouth sideways. Yeah, fuck. Yeah, and you are just
continuing to suck one in my mouth. You're sucking from the barrel. You
said that I was in that I landed in prone position, but you got up at the
flower goes up his. I got up. Okay, now he's still prone. Flower goes up his
body goes. Oh, and then the flower goes. Yeah, it was a flower that didn't bloom
yet that and it blooms and takes root in this.
Yes,
yes,
that's what's happening.
He has a fucking like this flower power for the fire flower in the
Super Smash Brothers.
Catch your ass.
It gives me fire powers.
No, that's not what it does.
Right?
It does damage because the flower just went up my butt.
I jump through up onto the onto the deck.
like Yosemite Sam I go and I go up in the direction of the boat
wait of my dad have to go and you guys crash land on the boat doing a lot of
damage to it it is not looking good the boat is looks like what it's not gonna
be completely crushed we're on top of the wheel on top of the landing on a
bulletproof glass boat so so the boat is
under it is it's a you literally boarded
the ship with your ship is what you guys
so cool that is sick so yeah yeah you
see the glass pirates and they're like
charge and they're starting to climb
your ship now okay I pray I do it I'd
like vent our sewage or whatever like
this you know like an airplane can drop all the poop I do that electricity just
spills out on to the yeah whatever I have to do to make that now we can visible
yeah now we can see them because they're covered in shit yeah yeah that's really
smart thinking yeah all you guys roll initiative okay not to do it again oh
no sorry you just can't keep your name on was 19 yeah did I roll initiative
already. What did you get? I got a 7. That's still better than what the glass guy's got.
I got a 13. Oh fuck yeah! Alright. Alright, so you guys have done some damage so I'm going
to take out a few of the glass guys. Yeah, you can't tell me that none of those guys
got it. Yeah, no you got rid of a good handful of them. Hopefully this is still somewhat
educational about the new mechanics. But if not, you know. Oh, this was supposed to be
an educational fight? Well to some extent. But also I have to say that also as you
crash into the boat, where the cracks are more severe, you do see also sand.
It's sort of turning water into sand. And you see any of the guys that have like, you know,
when they crash, when they shatter, like when it reaches like a certain
threshold of like how far apart their body parts have shattered, they turn to
sand. You're saying they're bulletproof glass? They're sand
man's there's there's sand man's sand man glass but if I were to fight them with
my gun it will based on the ship I would say it's a bad idea yeah okay so yeah
swing the musket like a bat is what you're saying you can do that you know
you have a sword yeah but a sword versus class that's true it's a good point I
mean yeah so I feel like it would do less damage and then it's not as then of
than a bludgeoning weapon. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, that's pretty good insight there. Um,
slashing and piercing will probably do less damage. Like I'll tell you that,
um, then bludgeoning damage, um, which is why part of why his hook was more
effective. Um, and part of why crashing into the ship rather than, you know,
stabbing it with our ship. Well, literally, yes. Um,
so anyway, you're up evil, Steve.
I mean, I feel like I already did the coolest possible thing I can do.
Cool. So there's the captain,
and then there's probably like a half dozen
other glass men that you can see. As the fight goes on,
I'm going to also be doing roles for your crew. Okay. And if your crew
is successful at pushing them back, their numbers that you have to fight will go
down. If they're not successful, their numbers won't go down,
and you'll have to reassess.
- Let me take a look at my spells real quick.
- Yeah, you have a whole suite of spells.
- How deep is the ocean that we are in?
We're right where we are,
like how far to the bottom of the ocean?
Are we in the deep sea?
- I mean, you're in, it's like,
let me actually, I should look up oceans.
- Do you have a fire spell?
- This thing is pretty, Patrick,
put three Altoids in his mouth if you can tell yeah - this okay so those been
there just today I don't know why I believe that Alex brought those here
like months ago tell me sorry what's up why we shouldn't all be putting Altoids
in our mouth sorry holding back holy mackerel now I feel left out I almost
just want to pop a couple Altoids right now. It's like the worst sound in the world.
Just so everybody talking like...
It's fine. Listen, so basically if we could do the same thing that we
already did and like throw our boat on top of this boat it would pretty much
break right? Like it can it's it's over halfway done. Yeah, I...
He's right about that. I would say... Well guess what, he doesn't have to worry about that.
because I would like to use create or destroy water to destroy the water
underneath this boat so that we both fall 30 feet and then it's like 30 feet of
impact yeah our boat onto that one as it hits the second water can you just 30
feet 30 feet by 30 feet says 30 feet I don't know that's up to you you're kind
of the boss so either way I feel like I'm in a really good position as long as
it's 30 feet in one direction the other dimensions gonna be anything yeah so I
I think I think by a hundred I think that if you up cast it. I think it literally does
Go up by like
Let me see let me make sure before I before I commit if you get if you get to high enough level can destroy the ocean
No
Maybe there's wish you can
Actually don't know all the rules around this if he's like level 100
When we get to level 100 can we destroy the ocean you know there's no 100
But if we get there if we did get that maybe be our blackjack points reward if we get 100 blackjack points
Can we just 30 30 30 cubic feet that makes the most sense?
I think for water so 30 by 30 by 30
We can I just look at your your character sheet because for some reason I got locked out of the he's using my phone
He's gonna text my mom. It's gonna do weird stuff. I'm gonna prank. He's looking at my photos being a funny face into here
He's literally roasting his tongue out on Instagram says hacked. Lol. No hatch by patches
is
Ten gallons of water is not going to be enough.
I did, did, did, did, did.
Asshole.
What?
Is it ten gallons?
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Ten gallons?
Yeah, that's going to--
Where'd you get 30 feet from?
It said 30-- oh, that's the casting-- that's the range.
That's the range, yeah.
All right.
It'll just make-- the ship will just, like, shake a little bit.
Like, whoa.
Your boat will slide off.
Can you create water?
You should create water inside one of the cracks
so it forces it open and cracks it more.
- That's a pretty good idea, actually.
- Yeah. - Would that work?
- You should flush all the toilets.
- No. - No, that wouldn't work?
- That's not really how that works, right?
- Yeah, no, yeah, you're right, just fucking--
- I mean, there's a lot of stuff here
that doesn't work how it normally works.
- I'm gonna go for the distraction angle here.
I'd like to use, I'm gonna cast false life on the sand
that was created when I killed that one guy, right?
It's still on the boat somewhere.
I'm gonna use false life on that
to create a beautiful glass woman.
So false life, I think, just gives you temporary HP. I don't think that's true.
Yeah, actually you're right. Yeah, okay, I thought that it was maybe actually
you could just trick me. Frankenstein's monster kind of thing. What about
guiding bolt? Could that do that? Yeah, that can't do that, but it could do a
damage. Do you have any like illusions? Do you have any illusions? Do you have
a fire spell? You could merge? I take my thumb and I do like this and then I
I take my other thumb, I do like that,
and I start to kind of confuse them with the solution.
- Okay, you do the thumb move.
- Man, I'm having a hard time here.
Let's see, let's look at my other,
my in-depth test, tornado. - You can also just whack 'em.
- I don't wanna whack 'em.
I like to be a little more cerebral
with my D and D flying than you, maybe.
I guess that's probably--
- No, it's not a bad idea.
I like that you're being cerebral.
- I'd like to use a hammer on their head.
- Okay.
So, well, the only reason why I would even encourage melee
Actually no. Oh I just got a great idea. I have one pound of oil. Can I dump oil all over
their deck so they get all slippery?
I can't say no to that. You want a pound of oil?
Yeah one pound. I have one pound of oil.
I should check my inventory.
You guys are going to have a bunch of random shit because of the adventure kit and shit.
I dropped one pound of oil onto the deck of the glass.
The glass guy's like, "Oh no!"
They're not going to be able to do anything.
They're glass and covered in fucking oil.
Oh my God.
And I have a tinderbox.
Holy fucking shit.
What do I have here?
Nothing.
I have a musket.
And a torch.
Torch is better than tinderbox.
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah, I think that might be true.
I have a candle.
Whose turn is next?
Uh, so yeah, you drop oil on them.
Do I have to roll anything?
Wait, wait, wait.
He dropped that oil?
yeah he dropped that I have a bag of 1000 ball bearings really yeah
500 ball bearings at me sponsoring this episode
yeah can I change my pouch of forever dirt because I'm not a dirt and not
your water
well the forever banana peels no but we definitely have the oil in the ball
bearing yes I have one day of rations maybe that's all bananas
and
and it's a little bit of an excellent day for asian one day worth of the
minutes maybe
no it's not it's not you don't have been in a pilot to choose what i'm eating no
okay so i guess i guess i guess this is a game where you'd make choices and play
roles i guess they're just i guess i don't have to master does it for the
dungeon slayings is the okay
and think about strong stand for slavery in this corner no
i think we call a mutiny
yeah i'm really mad i'm a captain or which one of my here a slave master
down at solving packages will be directed at me now
okay so the ball bearings in the oil around yes that it that will
he's
is your your for your okay or him
well so i don't know it did happen and and i will roll for after all for
analysts in a short period of a couple of them are gonna get affected by that is
before so return and it's not a good idea bananas are now
you cannot even
okay i'll i'm gonna get the oil with a torch
gonna hit the oil with touch the torch to the oil
i'm gonna like the oil on the news and it was wondered which one you do
uh... yeah for sure
so you can light a torch you toss it down actually way i guess we're on top
of that ship in the rest of its made a class i was looking forward to it
but uh...
and i think i think i'm glad
what food is my rations is it may be like heart and it's soup
it's hard tack
not simpson and i might not uh...
i don't know i think i definitely mentioned before my guide soap
yet i a m subsets yeah i do remember it makes sense because of water which
secure inventory i was i was i don't know why i had a little bit of a ship
and i also have address okay here tell me which thing i have is slippery
i have a shelter for ever dirt
I have a bedroll, I have a big oar, I have chain mail, I have a javelin, a mess kit.
I don't know what that is.
Hold on.
You say a javelin?
I said a javelin.
I have five javelins.
Okay.
I have one day of rations, 20 pounds of rations it says.
What is water skin?
Reliquary, rope, hempen, shield, tinderbox, torch.
Where you hold water.
Water skin.
It's usually made of like animal skin or like a.
Okay.
Or like a banana peel.
No.
Okay.
- Okay, I guess--
- You have abilities, you have--
- You also have, okay, so here's the thing.
This is where you can actually use a trip attack.
- I just wanna throw down a slippery thing so bad.
- We already have two slippery things.
- And you're standing in my way.
- We don't need a three.
- That's why there needs to be three.
- I know why you want to do it.
- I know why you really disagree.
- You can do stuff like, okay, but here's the thing.
So there's other maneuvers that you can do instead.
You can go do a goading attack, right?
- A goaded attack.
right you can do something where you uh knock them prone you could do a trip
like tripping you could do you could do little maneuvers that can make it more
fun I have thaumaturgy right you have thaumaturgy yes there's a lot of
applications for that you could turn the oil blue maybe well no I could shout and
scare them and they all slip that'll do that all intimidation I'm open to it
it okay. I'm going to do that. Let me find the intimidation here. I'm going to
scare the for the shit out of them.
Oh, twenty four now. What do you say
boom?
So you say boo and it thunders across the sea. You feel the glass almost shake a
little bit.
I should have saying note. We roll for another one. Okay, he's the singer and
now you're up at I think I am going to do that yeah you're saying you try to break
the ship like a yep like a wine glass yep what about the ball you're gonna also
drop the ball banger can I do both of that you only do one I would say ball
bearings is a really yeah come on I I didn't do anything cool cuz I was
- I'm setting up the-- - 500 ball bearings
out of my 1,000 bag.
1,000 hold--
- What?
- Bag.
(laughing)
- 1,000 hold.
- 1,000 bag, 1,000 hold.
- 1,000 pound bag and I drop 'em.
- I just got a 1,000 bag.
I'm so happy.
- Build a thousand or something.
- It can hold a thousand.
- It drops, I drop--
- I'm not a 1,000 bag.
I'm gonna do 1,000 hold. - You know what?
Then I'm not gonna do that.
- Please just do it. - Please do it.
- You already did it.
He already rolled.
- Yeah, he did it.
- I rolled for them falling.
Yeah, exactly. What they do they didn't do well.
So did they all fall and die off and one of them one of them is not is the only
one who didn't fall the rest of them all fell on their ass around their butts
then they didn't take any damage, but they are going to they are literally
gonna have to use their entire movement and their action to get up. It's quite
a lot of damage. So let's just keep doing that 30 glass butts falling onto
this ship. I don't know that I just strikes me as a whole lot of pounds of
course 30 glass but all right well however many glass also also I should
say that a couple of your crew members fell as well who were fighting that we
have a quick fat crew member dude let's just all throw our entire inventories
down at the same time to try to break yeah cuz I'll be heavy it's not gonna
work 20 pounds of food it's not how you would breaking things work it's like you
need like a single force right like it's not like a okay then why don't you take
like a glass that glass and draw like a lot of stuff on it sit on it. Go ahead.
I'm not going to sit on the glass sit on it right again.
So you drop the ball bearings they're all falling on their their asses. They
have to use their full action and turn to get up actually each of them have to
you drop your torch in it yet. No, because I our ship will burn our ship.
Yes,
I was
- That's not very nice.
- Well, hey, I have--
- It would have been a crazy thing.
- I have an idea then.
- I think that we should all sing in harmony and unison.
- Okay, they all, three of them get up
and two of them stay down.
But the three that get up,
I mean, they can't do anything else.
That's their turn.
- Okay.
- Is getting up and trying not to fall
with all the oil and ball bearings.
- And loud noise.
- And the loudness.
(laughing)
- That was a big part of it, yes.
- That was probably the biggest, most important part.
- Well, that was what made the,
I lowered the DC based on each of the things
guys were doing but then yeah the guy the two of the guys are still on the ground
just slipping and sliding oh whoa whoa like just kind of falling over and going
boom and it's my turn again and it's your turn again so what if I so so that
so that we can throw the torch so cool I was like here's a battle where you could
use learn about the new mechanics you've done none of that stuff sounds one he
I used one no it's so much bet. This is so much better. I was I was a I honestly
could better creating a common. I'm gonna create a shield of water. Yeah,
around the bottom of the ship, so that I'm gonna create water around the ship
a small layer so that he can throw his torch or fill the like the poorest wood
of the ship or I'll fill the poorest because then it will just steam and
smoke. Yeah, wet wood. It won't burn. No, that's not no. So I won't put the
ships already wet too and so probably already like
there's no fire, then. Is that what you're saying?
No, no, I'm gonna make our ship nice and wet with create or destroy water,
and then he's gonna throw the torch so that our-
At the other ship.
At the other ship underneath us.
So it won't burn our ship.
And then it won't burn the box.
It will simply smoke.
It will smolder, mainly.
It will simply smolder.
At the most.
No, I mean, no, no.
Okay, all right, well, then I'd like to make a water best friend with my skill.
Okay, yeah, you can do that.
All right, I'm doing it.
if this is the stupid shit you want me to do something fucking awesome whatever
I don't want you to do all right well I just did it I cast this creator destroy
water and I make just a clone of myself with water but you can't do anything and
you may be soon to cast him he just falls to the ground is that what you want
okay I'm stupid and wasting my turn I'm using I use thaumaturgy and I sing at
the I sing a really high-pitched note a booming voice well it's not boom it's
much more trebly than booming. It's not very bassy. It's a high. It's so
point. This is can be Caleb or just look. It's like a you got to break the
ship. You got to break the ship. You can't make a glass ship and then not
let us break it. That's kind of yeah. We've done so much to try and break it.
That's obviously every way. First of all shoot a cannonball. That's probably
what that's supposed to do here. So close and you won't let me fucking come
it's closer it's a little close to break it's getting close I want I want you
guys to earn it
amazing speed I we dropped our ship on top of their ship and now I'm singing
500 ball okay fine I'm just making myself blind and deaf with blindness
less definitely is that what you want I'm cat that's a boy that's good because
this is gonna hurt your ears I'm completely blind is that what you
fucking one for let's see how long I'm blind in death for.
Okay fine.
A one minute, for a minute I'm blind in death.
Alright.
[siren]
Let's do this. If you two, you two sing, if you're combined...
Hold on.
What? I'm singing really high pitched.
If you guys, if you guys combined a persuasion check is above...
32.
Okay.
Then, okay.
Then it breaks.
All right.
Not persuasion, sorry, performance.
Performance, okay.
I'm going to roll performance.
Because you're right, why not?
Why am I doing this?
That's what it's, oh.
What did you get?
I got a four, but don't worry about what number it was before I added anything to it.
I got a 15.
So you sing and it's very nice.
I don't think it's very nice based on the noises we were already making.
Yeah, I'm afraid we're done.
I'm afraid we're done.
- To sing and it's very nice.
- I don't think it's very nice,
based on the noises we were already making.
- So I'm completely blind and deaf.
- Yes.
- Yeah, so I just, I'm not even gonna.
- Yeah, you don't know what's happening.
- I mean, it's their turn now.
- I'm just sitting on the ship smiling.
- I mean, that's also, that's a bonus action.
- What?
- To sing.
- That's your full action.
- Well, bonus action's speaking,
or free action is speaking, right?
So what's the difference between speaking and singing?
as a new arrival i guess the intent of breaking it but alright
all it's ok what do you want him to try to break it
so what do you have to say it's the way you do you know i guess all to shoot my
blunderbuss at the other boat
at the boat
shed whatever it's a it is a spread rate yet another guns work
so there's guys below you you can she also to do whatever hits the most stuff
so these are guy you are a secret in that uh... there's two guys were sort of
cluster together he aims at a crack in the ship but if we hit it perfectly it
would just completely explode yeah oh okay I'm gonna have the credit wonder
bus works the way that fall on the way that this works I'm just charging up my
roll okay it's a fire rate of three what does that mean that means you can roll
up to three times. Okay. Now, roll, when you roll, each roll you get higher than the
last, you add bonus damage for every two, you can have an effect if it ends below
if you like, you can, so you can, basically what you can do, you can roll, let's say
you roll and you get like a nine. Yeah. When you roll and you get a 15, that means
you have plus six bonus damage. Okay. Okay. Then if you roll again and you get like
say a 10, then it goes down to plus one bonus damage.
And if the 10 doesn't beat the AC,
then you get a one misfire on the misfire table,
which means that next round your fire rate is only one.
That's like what happens.
If you roll--
- So it's better to have a low fire rate.
- Well, if you fail.
- Yeah, but the higher the fire rate is,
the way easier it is to fail though.
but also the better the damage is
and the more effects you get.
- You gotta get higher every roll though?
All right, three.
- You can also stop after.
- Oh, you can stop.
- You can stop.
- Oh, okay, I didn't know that.
- Blackjack.
- Blackjack, okay.
That's a 17.
I think I'm stopping.
- He's upstairs.
- Yeah, I think I stop at a 17.
- Wait, but don't you add?
- Yeah, do I add anything?
- No, that's the thing.
- Okay, that's 17.
- Okay, cool.
Yeah, that hits, obviously.
Roll. - Obviously.
- Obviously, obviously.
Roll 3D4.
- 3D4, okay, hold on here.
- You just get three of the triangles out here.
Dem, dem triangles.
- No, I got it right here.
It's rolling.
It's loading.
Oh my God, it's four.
- It's four damage?
- It's four damage.
- It's four damage, yeah, you just shoot it out.
It just sort of like,
like sort of splatters on the captain
and his first aid spaces.
- Splatter, is this a slime gun?
- No, 'cause it's just like a, you know,
the blunderbuss is kinda like--
- What is this, a water gun?
- Yeah, is it a water gun?
Answer.
- And it does bang into the ship,
it does, but it doesn't do a lot of damage to the ship.
- A little, one little more crack appears.
Okay, that's good enough for me.
- But not a lot.
- That's good enough for me.
- There is a way, there's a window.
- One little crack.
- There's a way you, but there's not,
not a way you can break it.
That was, that was part of it.
So that that was a possibility.
- Stick something into the crack.
- You're up, Pat.
stick something into the crack
no don't sing we already sang
we could have worked
stick your sword in the crack
i don't know about the sword, maybe the end of the musket
i wish i still had my mace my mace my mace
your hook is basically a mace
it has a crowbar it has the weight to it
i was just reskinning it
i have a crowbar
pry that shit open well where am I'm still on the the wooden ship yes so I
could jump
jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump
Patrick look at me do it. Do it. Do it.
Just seals up around him. Do it.
Jump. Do a fucking M bison jump.
We will save you. We got you. No matter what happens to you we will get you out of that water.
Jump dude.
Do I have you're looking down from the from the tallest diving board at the pool?
Okay, and if you jump off this thing you will be fucking legendary. We'll give you all
Which I can use to look at the crack in the ship and find its weak point jump into the crack
I don't we don't we mean with the eye for detail exactly that you can use a bonus action to make a perception check to
Check a spot a hidden creature or object to make an investigation check to uncover or decipher clues
I'll let that be that I like that. It's the clue of where the ship will break. Yes. I like that
So what is that? What kind of role is that?
that is a
Do you ask too many questions?
You just let it happen. I'm sorry that is a
Perception check. Okay. Sorry. Yeah, mr. I bet you said that. Okay. Yeah, so perception check. I will roll perception. I
I will do it now. Do it now. Where is that? Oh wait, that's not under. Okay, hold up.
Takes so long.
Boy.
I take this opportunity to take my hoodie off. Hey guys. What? Oh, sorry.
That's a do I get advantage say the number we've been waiting for a full
minute. I got an 11. 11. You can tell that the general area where it is, but
you can't tell the exact area. Like the area where it's already where the most
weight of the ship has been on and then a bit to the towards the helm of the
glass ship. There's a you could see that in that area there's like probably has
the most give. Okay. But you can't quite, like if you jumped off and tried to like
just pile drive it with the crowbar you can't guarantee that you'd be able to
actually drive something home here. Then I'm gonna try and sing. You, if it's just
you singing. Oh my god we already sang we literally already did it. What's your
performance again my performance is huge right plus seven wow fuck me um well
that's one of the characters you should you'll yeah just roll we'll see what it
does 16 you guys just keep sinking on top you guys crashed on this guy people
shipping just keep sinking yeah cuz I can't believe that we should have
already broken. All right. Uh, they're up.
I'm singing. We're singing cause we're celebrating cause we thought it did
break. Yeah. Uh, a couple of them are going to take out their glass guns and
those can't hurt us cause it's glass. Yeah. And shoot them at you guys.
We got a crit. I hope we all die.
Okay. I don't actually hope that that was horrible to say. I'm sorry guys.
And those that's evil. That's negative to bring into the world.
still on the ground, so one of them really hits you.
He does
is ten damage to you, Patrick.
Sorry, fourteen damage. My bad for that and now it's my turn. Yes, it's your
turn. Okay. I'm still deaf and blind.
Okay, jump. So I would like to stumble off of the ship.
Look first into the crack.
Yeah, let's try it.
What do I need to do?
You're deaf and blind. Deaf and blind. I don't know what's going on, but I have really good
luck. Stroll D20. Alright. I'm rolling it. Fifteen. You stumble off the ship, you fall,
And it starts to shatter.
Okay.
Before I hit it?
No, as you land on with the hook.
Oh, that'd be fucked up.
That'd be so funny.
But it's like you landed in a place that it didn't have the most give, so it's kind of
like another piece of it is starting to crumble off.
Okay.
Watch out, it's sharp.
And you don't...
You can't hear me.
I'm just still smiling.
And you take...
well it's how much damage could it realistically be it's millions of
shards of razor-sharp glass yeah it's it's not an insignificant amount you take
13 damage that's insignificant to me that's basically zero yeah might as well
be but yeah I would say that like you're pretty close to shattering it at this
point you're trying to see siflex of sand sort of spray out of oh okay now
now. All right. That's your somebody else needs to I'm jumping down or first or
first. Okay, roll D 20. So the 20 is it just do an attack roll? Oh, well,
that's an eight plus whatever my attack rules, which I think is four. But let me
double check. I think that's fine. I mean, the Yeah, it's plus four. So that's
a 12. Okay. Yeah, you land with the or it doesn't it doesn't like do any damage to
ship but you do get it lodged into a crack.
Patrick, I'm going to be up to you brother.
I'm levering open the crack.
Roll a strength check.
Just like straight strength.
That is a 16.
You start to pull the ship apart.
you're pulling it the sand starts to like fly out like in front of your face and
it makes it easier because now it's like the glass is giving way turning into sand
which makes it easier and easier to pull apart. The sand is giving me like PTSD
flashbacks to dirt. You hear Dogen laughing at you. I'm pulling way harder. You see the captain of the
of the sand ship and he he says we'll meet again the sandwich will have a
revenge and he runs off the bow of the ship and dive into the water.
I hope we don't meet again good. And as the ship starts to like flay apart your
crew members are scrambling to get back on your ship. I'm still on the boat?
You're no you're not you're still on the regular boat you're blind. And deaf.
And deaf on the ship that is now sinking you're kind of in like a rage fury as
you're pulling the ship apart. Yeah. Are you gonna try to save your blind and
deaf friend? I'm on a boat.
Everybody look at me. So you're just gonna you're gonna sing um. I'm doing this. I'm raising the roof. What are you doing?
Me? I'm deaf and I'm blind so I'm pretty much having very vivid colorful
thoughts. Yeah, I'm putting I'm putting ropes down, but he can't see a single
one. I'm the right rope. So I've grabbed in ropes, plus ten ropes off the ship.
Okay, okay, you have to roll if you're going to try to actually I'm going to
try to rope around him. Yeah, save him. You're gonna need to roll
first a
actually just two athletics checks to athletics checks. Yeah, heard that.
Hey, heard that
Let's see, athletics number one is an 18.
Nice.
And then athletics number two is a six.
So you get over there with the rope, you tie it around him perfectly, you get a nice little
rope tug on your body, evil Stevel.
Then as you try to pull him--
Why does it have to be the order?
Is it, do I get a rope around him and I miss my own rope?
What?
Is that why I did two?
No, you're fine on your okay. You managed to pull a rope over while the ship is
sinking and turning I say deafen lines. I think the rope is a snake, so I
chopped with I bite I start biting at it. Okay, it doesn't have to go through,
but just I want to be I want to be fished out up. It's around your it's
around your neck. So the ship biting the road starts to fall. Oh, yeah, as the
sand starts to form and you guys now are just like wait wait wait wait so there's
a bunch of sand going into the water and how big is gonna pollute the water how
big is this how big is the ship the ship it's like it was like about the same
size as your ship and our ship is a cruise ship so cruise ship of size
actual cruise ship it's all the Royal Caribbean okay well it's a boat size
amount of sand wouldn't there be a little bit of sand under our boat that he
could land on I'm already being pulled up on oh he's on a road fuck is going on
talking about what's gonna happen you think the sand would just stay on top of
the water created an island there I said it I mean he's wrong but he did say I
respect that you said I respect that you know mm-hmm that's really wrong moving
but anyway and I respect you I was so stupid but I do respect you that made no
sense this is the most fucking stupid thing you've ever said it's not what I
do respect and I love you and the boat falls and you two are gonna take me us
- sorry yes evil Steve'll and Dogen and Rod Dogen you are gonna take Rod Dogen
you Rod Dogen who you know okay you guys gonna take five damage oh that's
That's nothing.
And Patrick, you're going to have to try to pull them ashore, pull them onto the boat.
Can I do it with ease?
No.
No?
Really?
Roll a strength check.
Oh.
Okay, I just rolled and it says you do that with ease.
That's not true.
That's not how this game works.
Then you say what it says if you're so smart about what it says.
I can't see his phone.
I just don't want to say that.
Oh, and he can see his phone.
So maybe he has an idea about what it says.
He's pretending.
He never looks at his phone.
It's not working.
It's not working?
I got a 16.
Nice.
Okay.
Yeah, so you're able to pull them up.
You obviously are able to help.
With ease?
With ease.
Not with ease.
It's some struggle.
You have other crew members hop on and help you out.
Are they worth it ones in the game world?
I think we can say it was.
Yeah, and you guys are back on the boat.
I'm pulling them up.
I get them up and I'm like...
I did that with relative ease.
So you guys remember that the Sand Witch was the person that the...
Rubbers?
The rubbers were worshipping.
So those seem to be associated with her.
Let's throw them overboard.
Yeah, wait, did they seem...
How did they interact with these sand...
These glass guys, they didn't...
They didn't care?
No, I mean, they don't have any...
No allegiance to them?
It doesn't seem like they have any access to like...
Okay, we don't throw them overboard then.
But yeah, I mean, at this point now, you're back on track,
sailing towards the, where were we sailing towards?
Sorry, it is real.
But before you do that, you see coming up on your right,
and we'll go to this next time.
- If this is another glass ship,
I'm gonna actually fucking kill you.
- No, no, no, no, no.
(laughing)
- No, it's ice this time.
- What you would recognize--
- But it doesn't melt, that's the crazy thing.
Patrick Jodar, you guys are dicks.
As Hot Babe Island.
Oh my god.
Oh wow.
Perfect.
That's, I come right out of deafness and blindness right as we see Hot Babe Island.
And I think I died when I fell off the roof.
The rope was you going to heaven.
Why is Dogan here?
[Laughter]
Okay, nice. Cool jam. Sounds perfect.
[Music]