[Music]
Last time on Trebuchet Village, the heroes came face to face with Connoria, the warlock who served
The Jester and his nasty changeling familiar Impy. After nearly killing Patrick Yodar,
Sullivan's string of good luck and Dogen's decisive blow took out Conneria and granted the gang the
Yoni Egg of Yore. After raiding his hovel, finding a strange substance that the gang made Sullivan
drink, our heroes headed back towards the White Woman of the Woods to give her the Yoni Egg of
Basket. But not before The Jester attempted to make a deal with them. He'd gift them a magical
staff that had happy faces and frowny faces, much to evil Stievel's chagrin, and freedom
from the woods if they handed him the yoni egg of Baskin.
They, in my opinion, confusingly refused his offer, and instead handed the egg to the white
woman, who proceeded to do what you do with such a thing.
Her magical yeast infection spread throughout the Whippet Woods, which became more normal,
with squirrels and birds and little flowers and nice trees, nothing laughing or cackling
or being weird and dark crystal-y.
The crew stayed the night, morning, and a bit of the afternoon in her conch shell home in
the lake before she tossed them out and sent them to take care of the kitsunes once and
for all.
Arriving at the scene, they saw a massive tent made of terrible multicolored detritus,
organic or otherwise, looking like a freaky circus tent, with a massive foxhole underneath.
In the tent they saw the massive beast that belonged to the Vegas brothers, Dean and Luca,
saw that it was a massive Sasquatchian thing indeed, except its head and face were that
of a human clown. They saw him farting and pranking the Vegas brothers who were tied
up at the center of the tent. Also, the beloved Kubler elves were shackled and plodding along,
sad little slaves to the horrid kitsune's designs. Rather than remaining hidden, Patrick
Jodar fired an arrow at the tent for some reason, but it was enough to begin combat
and earnest. With the white woman of the woods power restored,
animal friends came to the aid of our heroes and set upon the
Kitsunes. The leader of the Kitsunes, Bussy Kitsune, faces
our heroes in combat, while a Sasquatchian clown seems to
ready himself for the eventual showdown between the outsiders
from Trebuchet Village and himself.
Should have cleaned up that sentence.
But yeah, so we're in the middle of a battle.
And looking at the.
Initiative order from last time, we're back to the top of the order.
It is.
Say I wrote BK, so that probably stands for Burger King.
Burger King. Burger King.
Ooh, I guess it's Burger King's turn.
Yo, and I think I am the burger king of the party.
So I really should go.
I realize it's Bussy Kitsune.
I'm sorry. Not Burger King.
So it is Busty Kitsune's turn.
So Busty Kitsune has been shooting those like darts at you guys from afar.
And so he's going to continue to try to do that.
So I'm going to roll for that.
Last time he shot it at you, Patrick Chiodar.
He's going to go for Dogen this time.
- No. - I jump in front of it.
- Do you want to do that as your reaction?
- No. - No, dude.
I don't think it hits. It's a guy. It was a nine. So the dart sails overhead. Dogen misjudges
your height as you're a goblinoid and he loads up another dart to launch it again. Now it
is the kitsune's turn. So two of them who started attacking you, Dogen and you, Evil
Stevel, one of them hops on the head of the other one. A third one from behind climbs
up on top of the last one and they sort of start to balance themselves like a tall man
at the circus but then they all sort of laugh hysterically and just fall to the ground and
so I need all three of you to make dexterity saving throws.
I'm on it.
Okay.
I'm doing it right now.
14.
Uh-huh.
Uh, 5.
Not a saving throw.
Hold on.
19.
Oh wait, I didn't do that either.
Yeah, I'll let it go.
Yeah, let's let it happen.
Go for it.
19. Oh, man. Can I reroll too? No, you roll to save. I shouldn't have let you do it.
Yeah, so this thing comes crashing down. Patrick Yodar, I imagine you use your
balls to bounce away. I'm just gonna hop over here. Okay. Evil, you are able to
sidestep it nimbly. I don't know exactly what you do. You don't have balls. Cart
Cartwheel.
Okay.
I'll just write that down.
Cartwheel.
And you, uh, uh, Dogen, are distracted.
I also, I also try to bounce on my balls and that's why I get caught in it.
Okay.
So these kitsune's fall on you and they deal a staggering...
That's never good.
Wow.
I didn't, well, they did ten damage.
Jeez.
Ten?
Yeah.
With a zero at the end?
10 with another 0.
10 with... hold on, a thousand damage?
This isn't even fair, Patches.
I've taken 10 damage.
How much health do you have left?
I got a new healing spell that I learned, so I got you, dog.
Actually, I didn't.
It is your turn, Dogen.
Okay, so are those kitsunes in range?
Yeah, so they're all, I should actually say, the side effect of that move
by them, because it deals a lot of damage, is that they all are knocked prone for the round.
Oh, okay. Because they all fell over.
So, one of them is in range of you, two of them are really in range of you, the third one's kind of a bit
far back. Yeah. Okay, hold on.
if two of them are in range
uh... well actually depends what you can do
i don't know yet
trying to figure it out
i guess
let's see uh... i guess i'll just
since i'm i'm i'm here right next to them i should probably just try to hit
them instead of like trying to
bless or no you know i i'm gonna get a blast out on my friends
over a blast and i bless myself as well
uh...
how shit
this is a says you bless up to three actors of your choice yes they can do
Okay, I bless I bless the three of us my three my three closest friends. It's me. Oh that feels terrible
Wow
So my foot hurts
So all your while your foot hurts you are you do now have the ability to roll
to add a d4 to any
attack roll or saving throw so
Yes, maybe your foot hurts, but it's pretty good. Yeah, I think my blessing is that I blow a kiss to
Have to accept it that was uh
That I didn't like that some magical force compels me to accept the kiss. Yeah you giant
And you got another one for no reason if you look at my if you look at my right ball here
There's a there's a kiss print on it now. Yeah, I aimed there. I don't know why
Cool is that all you want to do?
Yeah, yeah, okay
Patrick Yodar you're up
How close am I to these guys again
I don't know if I want to use bow and arrow or short sword.
For sure. I would say you're in range of one of them because you dodge out of the way,
probably not both of them. That's what I would say.
Yeah. Alright, so I'm just gonna swing my sword.
Yeah, go for it.
There's a crit one.
Oh my god. So, roll a d20.
Okay, hold on. I'll do it in...
I was about to do a custom roll in Beyond.
custom rolls.
Custom roll.
Okay, cool.
So you don't lose your weapon, but what does happen is you sort of, the sword's a little
bit long, so you kind of let the tip-- It's a short sword.
Yeah, it's a rapier is what I'm reading here.
I just didn't know how to pronounce it correctly.
Oh, okay.
So you just sort of like let it dangle a bit, you kind of just like scoop up a bit of the
dirt and kind of-- Hey, Dogen, I got some stuff for you.
and
it's
It's just how my uncle taught me.
I'm just doing it.
Don't flank me.
Watch this.
He's not going to flank you.
Oh, okay.
I see what you're doing.
Yeah, I'm actually not going to flank you at all.
Roll deception.
20.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
All right.
Yeah, don't look for me.
I'm not going to.
Yeah, you seem like a, you know, you just tried to stab me.
You seem like a stand up guy.
I am.
That is what people say about me.
When he said his uncle taught him to flank, I got completely the wrong idea and I'm very
- I think it's something very wrong that his uncle did to him.
Fanning your face.
Yeah, I'm quietly, "His uncle flanked him."
It is now your turn, Evil Stevel.
Okay, is there any water or lack thereof in 30 feet away?
Probably not, right?
Well here's the thing so like the key you're in the kitsune like civilization kind of like
little hovel so there are like smaller crude tents that kind of line the place and like
presumably some of them have some water inside of them because that's where some of the kitsune
live.
Um I can I can guarantee you that there's some water around.
Are they... do they hate rain for some reason?
Or no?
I don't... not particularly.
Not that I know of.
ARGH!
Fuck.
Okay, then I will use...
I will use Inflict Wounds.
Well, no, there's not like a big bad guy right here.
I will use Guiding Bolt.
Hell yeah.
On the three guys stacked on top of each other.
Did they count as one guy?
No, they kind of fell apart.
So not quite right now.
Well, hold on, let me rethink this.
Yeah, because there's a beast.
There's a big beast.
Oh, the beast.
Okay, I will use inflict wounds on the beast.
So inflict wounds is a melee attack, so you have to run over it.
Pretty far away.
Yeah, then I will go back to guiding bolt.
Yeah, you're just like flipping through your spellbook.
a two page spellbook.
Back and forth.
Create and destroy water? No, there's no water here.
Alright.
I'm casting it.
Yeah, go for it.
Oh shit.
23, yeah that hits.
17 damage? Yeah baby.
So yeah, you see that beast and
you know, as D&D
combat goes, it's all
within the last 6 or so
seconds. So he's pointing
Dean or Luca at you and like going like your next kind of thing and as he's doing that you sort of
Shoot your fingers sort of raid in style and shoot out a like a radiant like bolt
And that just like just gets him right between the eyes. Oh, is that why Raiden's called Raiden?
Cuz the radiant bolt now he has radiant bolts
He has lightning, but I think I don't know down think that's why he's called Raiden
I think it's more probably maybe like a ray of lightning could be maybe something that oh
Because he raised he's reying them in he reigned in I feel like it's probably
It's gotta be a reference to something I think it's just a name probably no
Riding it's based on not pronounced. Ryjin is a thunder god in Japanese. Okay. Yeah, there you go
Yeah, it's just a Japanese name. Yeah, cuz
So yeah, the bolt stopped in midair during that and then it completed it
And yeah, you see the clown like
His nose honks the Sasquatch clown and he's like holding his forehead
Yeah, you did a good amount of damage to him. He does not like that. Oh my gosh. You got the coolest idea
So that's like lightning, right? Yeah. All right, cool
Does it do anything else?
Well, it's technically radiant damage, so it's not lightning.
It's not like electricity?
No, no.
That it could make me travel through water?
No, no, not quite.
AHH!
But, just because it's a radiant type of damage.
But, yes, what it also does is it means that you have advantage on that thing.
Anyone who has attack rolls on it has advantage until your next turn.
Nice.
to the end of your next round.
I have a thunder spell that I can prepare next time.
We can team up.
Water and thunder, dude.
Well, thunder damage is different from lightning damage.
Yeah, I know, but I was hoping I could get that by you.
No, I'm a student of the elements.
You were drinking water, so I thought maybe you weren't listening.
No, I always listen.
I listen twice as well with water, because it's like my mouth is...
So, uh, it is now the top of the order.
And, um, 'cause I think I decided I wanted to leave Sullivan and the Prince at the White Woman of the Woods.
Just leave them there for a little bit.
Um, and, uh, I need, um, let's see, who is up for this? Probably Dogen.
Dogen, I need you to roll a Dexterity saving throw.
Me again?
Yeah.
Oh brother 13. Wait. I can add I can add two fifty. Yeah.
You're good. so you see like from your left a giant flower
sort of slowly poke its head and it sort of rears back and
goes and shoots like a jet of water at you which you're able
to like pretty definitely get out of the way of that. Wow
really Stievel you're not gonna destroy that water for me? I got away from my- I could
have been killed. He's gotta wait for his turn man. I'm in stasis right now, not supposed
to be talking to you! I blessed you. Shut up! You hurt my foot, you foot hurter. And
And then, uh, meanwhile this conversation's going on, um, uh, Patrick Yodar, roll a strength
saving throw.
Uh, this is my worst one.
Okay.
You add a d4.
It'll help.
You'll definitely beat it if you add a d4 to that.
Four.
Oh, wow, that's too bad.
So behind you...
How is that bad?
That's eight.
I...
That's not good enough.
cool that you got a max on it. So behind you, Patrick Yodar, you feel suddenly two long
hands, fox-like hands, clawing beneath your armpits, sort of grab you and swing you up,
and you realize that you're being, from a trapeze that has been set up between two trees,
being sent up into the air and caught by another kitsune. You can roll another strength saving
throw to see if you can wriggle out of it, though you might fall.
It appears I've been hoisted. 17.
Okay yeah, you can wriggle out of this before they throw you again, and I'll have you roll
either athletics or acrobatics to see how you handle the fall.
Yeah, pretty good. So I'll say that you take, with that 14, I think you're able to sort of brace yourself a bit more.
You'll take half of this fall damage here. So you take 3 fall damage as they throw you up.
That could keep going and going. They could have kept hoisting you up and up as a trapeze artist until they dropped you.
So that was good that you wriggled out of it.
That, uh, do not hoist me again. I'm gonna say that right now.
If I am hoisted, one more time.
one more really steve lear not gonna cast destroy hoist
come on yeah i haven't learned that yet
you have i i i haven't read that far into my spell book
how many how many pages is in the spell book right now a hundred and thirty
how many pages have you got filled out
like to
god damn it
alright well you hate me
no i don't i'm not i'm just
and just i wish you were a little disappointed
Yeah, all right. Give me 18 seconds or so in game time and I'll definitely help out.
Yeah, I didn't want to say disappointed. That's what he said.
Hey, that's what he said.
So you gotta laugh in this life. I still got it. It's very short.
Patrick Yodar, you're like 40 feet further ahead of them. So you're just sort of yelling this, I guess, across
the field. I have one tone of voice.
Yeah, and you're closer to the carnage of the tent as well.
So you can get a better look at what's going on.
Am I behind that guy still somehow?
Maybe he moved with me.
You're no longer flanking him.
Quite.
Am I flanking somebody at least?
No, no, you're sort of like in this in-betweeny space where
like Bussy Kitsune is like pretty close to you now.
You kind of fell off at a good point.
like like 10 feet from you closer towards the guys.
So I'm close to bussy kitsune.
Okay, I'll keep that in mind.
Yeah, and then behind you about like 20 feet or so is the tent
itself where there's like all this like carnage and bloodshed
between animals and and kitsune's and kubler elves that are
trying to hide and fear.
But yeah, and so now that we're back to the top top of the
order bussy kitsune's turn.
And he sees you Patrick Yodar and he whips his head around.
Hi!
Hey.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna try to kill you now.
Hello.
And uh, he shoots a uh, shoots another dart at you.
Mah Christ.
He loves to shoot those darts.
See how he does.
Nah, he just keeps whiffing.
Yeah, he just fuckin' like, like sucks it in a bit by accident and then like, and then
and
get
And now it's the Kitsune's turn. And so they're all just gonna have to use Hafter movement to get up.
And the one in front of you, Dogen, is gonna try to swing at you with its staff.
And it just misses, or you're able to deflect it.
it
is
I'm
I'm gonna save it. I don't think the beast is in range of me.
I don't want to run away. We have advantage on the beast.
I don't want to get an attack of opportunity on me by running away.
Mm-hmm. All right, cool.
So now it is your turn, Patrick Yodar.
And there's two people who are about to gang up on me.
Oh, yeah.
How close are they?
They are... Bussy sort of moved back. I should have said.
buses removed back five feet after they missed
uh... decided
that he doesn't have a gender on all some uh... and uh...
so and that thing is also the other key to news about also like about fifteen
feet from you
and uh...
amateur i'm just gonna try and shoot 'em
yet i don't know an era
twenty one pocketed hits
men damage
or maybe yeah
aptly so so i'd like i have the bow and arrow in my hand i'm looking at us in
I'm like, "Ned, you see, you're gonna wanna, you wanna look kinda, kinda close one eye."
So it's, you uh...
Yeah, yeah, okay.
Yeah, so you kinda close one eye so you can get like a better...
I see you doing that.
Yeah, better shot at your target.
Okay.
You gotta pick your target.
Right.
You gotta, I mean once you get your target...
Yeah, yeah.
Once you got your target picked out, you gotta, you just gotta, you gotta pray that it hits.
Okay.
And you kinda just...
Who do you pray to?
I just kind of let go and then I know what in particular
And I do it like that shut up
Blood just coughing out blood
Thank you though, oh yeah, no problem. Yeah, and it is now
evil Steve'll stern
Ok, I think I may do Guiding Bolt on this beast again.
Hell yeah, you have advantage too.
True, alright, so I cast it twice, yeah?
Uh, yeah yeah yeah yeah.
Ok, the 13, shit.
Is that an attack roll?
Does it count?
That's the attack roll, yeah.
Can you add Bless to it?
You can add Bless to it, yeah.
So you can roll a d4, Evil Steevel.
Oh baby, yeah that hits.
That ate damage.
I love blessing my friends. Yeah. so yeah you you
**** shoot another guiding bolt at this thing and it sort of
rears its head back again. You sort of knock it again while
it's fending off a bear and you see the bear sort of smile
gently at the while it's fighting it and this Sasquatch
is now completely like its sights are on you evil. It like
wants you next.
Bring it on.
Clown.
It honks darkly at you.
Nevermind, that was scary.
And we're back to the top of the order.
Bussy Kitsune is sort of like
in dire straits
and he sort of
throws the dart and the thing
and the...
what the f*** do you call that? Blow dart?
The blow dart, but what's the...
blow
I think it's a shooter is what I would call it.
A blowgun, that's what it's called.
No way.
I was right!
Oh shit!
It is a gun!
It's definitely called a blowgun.
It's also called a blowpipe.
It's called a gun?
It's not a gun.
What a gun!
You can buy them on Amazon.
Predator blowgun.
36 inches.
Yeah, you can buy the predator blowgun.
I think that's for your team.
Yeah, I use it on predators.
God damn, he's too good.
Yeah, shit.
He's too fucking good.
He's too fast.
That's what you get for being a predator.
Predators are fast.
These tactical blowguns are so cool.
Can we get some of these?
Yeah, let's do it.
Are you going to make the purchase now or do you want me to...
So yeah, Bunseki Tsune throws down his tactical blowgun
and takes out a knife and just charges you, Patrick Jodar.
a
You take six damage as he sort of a he sort of throws on the blow dart and
While clutching his chest with one hand sort of just kind of surprises you and gets you in the ribs with the knife
And he says how's that for aim? And he's just a coughing up blood while he's saying yeah, that is not
That is not what I taught you at all. Yeah, that is that that sucks. You teach me dick. I
Taught you I taught you how to aim
I'm actually I'm a very hurt right now. I'm actually it's not the the blade in my in my rib that hurts. It's actually the
Just the disrespect your heart. Don't tell me you're disappointed in me. I'm very disappointed in
And the kitsune behind him now is gonna also charge at you Patrick Jodar
He's gonna try to flank you so he's gonna get advantage. He's gonna run behind you. Oh
What do I do you get hit?
Why?
No one's here to help me for
Nine damage. I'm dead. You're dead again. Yeah, I got you dude. Don't even trip. I got you even better
I got you a million times better right now. Yeah bullshit. I have healing
Mm-hmm
So yeah, he runs up behind you
We'll get it flanking you getting advantage and just sort of bodies you with the staff until you just pass out
uh... match
you balls are up
can you lie in your back your balls are just like when i think when i see that
happen i'm like
uh... that's what flanking is
i don't have a lot of attention to my mother i'm ready to focus on the fight
again and then you advantage on every attack now
that that that you know i have really i don't mean that has been i don't know
that means that that is that it
i can't joke
I can't joke around?
With a DM you can't joke!
*sneezes*
Turn on the light.
Um, okay.
It is now the other two kitsune's turn, and they're going to just try to attack you,
Dogen.
I think they're just going to go back to back against you.
Let's see how they do.
Wow.
They both hit you.
I would hit them both from the back so they should keep that in mind. I
Will let them know they do nine damage to you in total. I'm dead also. Yeah, so they just fucking ko you
Yeah, and so now
evil Steve'll
It's your turn. It's doh. Oh, I know again Dogen and Patrick Yoda our role death saving throws. Okay, I'm rolling custom
*laughter*
How do I do test saves?
Oh here we go. Where is it?
Oh, okay that's a success. Nice.
Oh wait, okay. Top right, yeah.
If you just click on the HP.
I got a 10.
That's a success. Or is it an 11?
That's a success.
You made an invisible roll.
Oh you did a custom roll again.
Yeah, 10 is a success.
Awesome.
the
I thought you were just saying, "I'm doing a custom roll."
No, no, that's like, uh...
It throws a dice on your, um...
Your... fuckin'...
Your player... your player stats and stuff.
Screen.
No, it's not the screen.
It's the player sheet. It throws the die on there.
Screen.
You succeed!
You succeed, though.
So, it's two successes.
Now, Evil Stievel, it is your turn.
Okay, I'm gonna use Spare the Dying on Dogen so that he can heal Patric.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
That doesn't bring me back, though.
-Yeah, it just makes him stable. -It stabilizes you?
It does stabilize him, which is good.
What's the difference?
Stabilizing just means he doesn't do death saving throws anymore.
-Okay, I'm not gonna die, but I can't do anything. -So, if you wanted to...
Do I still have that cookie?
Uh, I think we all get cookies.
Think Patrick has Patrick Patrick.
Has can I rob him while he's down?
Yeah, you certainly could.
The other two went after Dogen, so you won't be provoking
attack of opportunity.
You would have to run over there.
You'd be able to run over there and then rob him.
You might be able to yeah, you could feed him.
I guess to just feed him and then get be later.
Okay.
All right.
I run over there.
Feed Patrick his own cookie.
Yeah, what does that do for me?
You're full
Roll 2d 4 plus 2
Me or him
Patrick that's how many hit points you get back. Okay six
nice
All right, so you get six hit points back. So you're back you're back to life
Christ that how many did we have do we have another one left? You have one more cookie. Okay, you should bring it to me
Yeah, it's your turn. So it's my turn not yet. We're back to top of the order. It's bussy kitsune's turn again
Bussy kitsune is going to try to attack you evil steve-o
Okay, we'll definitely dodge it
Yeah, you did. Well, let me double check your AC though before I say that that's crazy. They did that. Yeah, you got shit
Yeah, Tracy tries to swing his knife for you and you dodge it pretty deftly
The other kitsune now is gonna try to get you
And
Yeah, he whiffs
That keeps any just whiffs. He just did a really shitty roll
So you're just like fucking go over there shove a cookie in his mouth and just start dodging these guys
You're sort of you're a pro gamer right now for sure. Yeah, you're like ninja or dream
Dream. Yeah. Oh
My god, yeah, dude
And
The other two key toonies are gonna run over there thinking Dogen's done
So now they're sort of like this gang of them up on you guys
And back the top of the order Dogen roll death saving throw
Alright, that's a failure. Okay one success one failure
Patrick Jodar you're up. I just I I run over
to Dogen and I
I put the cookie under his nose.
[sniff]
[laughter]
I just instinctually go...
[smacking]
[laughter]
I eat it like one nibble at a time.
Like an animation of a cookie disappearing.
Yeah.
[laughter]
Yeah, it's good.
The nibble technique takes three rounds of combat to complete.
[laughter]
Yeah, and it only heals me half as much.
Yeah.
[laughter]
There you go.
Come on.
Come on, eat it. Eat it normal.
Dogen just goes, "Mama!"
Yeah, I take one bite that's slightly larger than a nibble and instantly choke and die.
Yeah.
Roll, roll, sorry.
Roll 2d4+2.
Oh wait, did I add 2 to the, I had a 6.
I don't know, did you?
I didn't add 2, so I think I'm at...
Oh yes, you didn't, okay.
Alright, I healed 9.
Nice, okay, you're back up, Dogen.
Evil Stievel, it is now your turn. You are sort of surrounded right now.
Okay, the beast is nearby, yes?
The beast is nearby. The beast is not looking too good because of the damage you did to it.
Alright. I used Guiding Bolt last time, right?
You used Guiding Bolt two turns ago, so it no longer has an advantage on it.
Gotcha.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Okay, then I...
Is the beast close enough that I could touch him now?
You would have to provoke attack of opportunities if you ran over there, but he is close.
Yeah, no, you kind of have like one kitsune on like one side of you in front and then
bussy on the other side of you in front.
Tell me something about this create or destroy water.
and
bad call out I'll allow it yeah okay I create just a thicket I mean ten gallons
of fog is quite a lot of fucking fog this shit is thick yeah and I I lay down
some serious fog on these fools okay cool so yeah you know I try to I I grab
wait Dogen is up yeah yeah Dogen's up over over in the back with
a
I just like shoot an arrow at BuzzyKitsune.
Alright, I'm gonna say we use the fog to reposition.
How many people are left? Real quick.
So yeah, yeah.
And can you tell us how bad they look?
Yeah, yeah.
So, you have,
including the
Sasquatch, it's
five total.
Two of them,
BuzzyKitsune and one of the other
Kitsunes look pretty bad.
The other two
to
that
I would prefer to be at 15.
So what I want--
yeah, sorry.
I'll heal you to 15.
I mean, do we--
I don't know how long we have.
Yeah, I was going to say--
I was going to say, so what we can do is let's do stealth
rolls in the fog, because you basically
have this moment where you can move stealthily enough
so you can get away from stuff and reposition.
I don't know how often I should allow that,
but I like this a lot.
so I want you to try it.
Wait, were you supposed to roll with advantage?
No.
I rolled with advantage automatically.
Pick the first number.
I did 13 then.
Okay, cool.
So I would say, yeah,
Patrick and Dogen,
you're already pretty far away,
but you find a way to reposition sort of behind
some of the, some of the tents,
the smaller tents,
and Brush that's around.
And you see Busty and the other Kitsunis looking around.
Um, uh, blah blah blah blah.
Evil Stievel, um, you're able to peel away from them,
so you don't provoke an attack of opportunity,
but they still have a good idea of where your position is.
Um, so, like, you're kind of, like, still near the big tent,
but, um, you're away from them, um, like, 10 or 15 feet.
Um, so that's, that's what I'll say.
I think that's, that's fair enough.
on
is
more. Okay, short rest.
Back to the top of the order Bussy Kitsune is up Bussy
Kitsune is going to try to come at you evil Steve but he does
not have he's going to have disadvantage because of the
fog. so I like that kind of thinking let me give you okay
and yeah, he just **** with he comes at you with a knife and
for you. It's like it's like he's swinging in front of you.
a
So let's see how they do. I'll give them like one roll for all of them.
But they got a really good roll.
So they...
Why are you laughing? That's not funny.
Because it's inappropriate.
As the DM you shouldn't be taking sides.
I'm not taking sides in the battle.
It's interesting. That's why I'm laughing at how interesting it is.
Yeah, okay.
I'm very interested in roleplay.
Crypto jester.
Yeah, yeah, no, no, I'm not the jester I would never do that. I would never joke like that
But yeah, they find you they sort of a fan out and they kind of catch where you guys are
But that's that's what they do for their turn is look and find you
And you caught me
Rats it sucks and
It is now
Dogen's turn.
Okay.
They found us?
Mm-hmm.
But they're like, they're like 15 feet, each of them.
All right.
Well, how much HP are you missing, total?
Me?
Yeah.
I am missing seven.
Okay.
I guess I will, I'll heal you for seven with my Lay on Hands.
Mm-hmm.
Okay. Um, and I don't necessarily want to be like in front of him
because I have less help him at this point, but I think I'll move at least next to like,
I don't, I want to make it like, so they will spread out their attacks maybe.
Yeah. Some way through the positioning.
Yeah. So you can, maybe you move like 10 feet, like.
So they can't, they can't all just like swarm one.
Yeah, for sure. Okay. So you sort of reposition there. Okay, cool. Uh, Pat,
No, yeah, yes, Patrick, it's your turn.
So there's somebody in front of me now, basically.
There's like a three of them are like sort of like in front of you kind of also like kind of like sort of fanned out from one another.
You could see the one that's like more gravely injured also pretty clearly.
So you know which one's the one that is injured.
Is there any way that I could
use the wind?
To shoot an arrow through all three of them,
that is crazy pants.
No, sir.
OK, can I shoot?
Can I use the wind to shoot two of them?
No, no, no, not gonna lie this time.
What about one?
How close is the gravely injured one to me?
Between 10 and 15 feet from you.
Okay, I am just gonna like stab him.
Go for it.
24. Yeah that hits, roll for damage.
Describe your kill, brother.
I just throw the dagger.
I'm like, "Ah, you caught me, crap."
And I just throw the dagger.
It hits him right in the forehead.
I'm like,
"It's my bad, I'm sorry."
"I'm gonna need that back."
And I go over and I pull the dagger.
Like, I have to, like...
Use your full movement to pull, go over, pull the dagger out.
It's like, like, to the hilt.
the
You guys, yeah, I'm gonna need help with this.
Okay, okay, alright. On three? On three? Or one, two, three, and then we do it?
Yeah, one, two, three, then we pull. Okay.
Alright.
Alright, one, two, three.
Yeah, there we go.
You said on three.
Well, I got it out anyway.
Okay.
Can I just attack one of them now?
I'll let you do it with disadvantage because it's funny.
Go for it.
Alright, then I just swing.
Oh fuck off!
Oh my god!
19!
God damn it!
I think that hits there, Mr. Dungeon Master.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Roll for damage, roll for damage.
7.
Hell yeah.
Yeah, you fucking-
And it's a sneak attack.
We can add that too, maybe.
No, fuck that shit.
You cut him the fuck up though.
I just like, I cut at his throat, but I think maybe I miss and I like get under towards the chest.
Yeah, but it's a deep gash.
Yeah.
He is not like, he's like, "FUCK!"
Like just, "UGH!"
I'm a...
You guys work for a trickster.
Hey, you guys have to help him pull that one out too.
Get real close to him.
And it is now evil Steve's turn
Okay, am I close to the to the beast now? Yeah, you're close to the beast. You're pretty close
All right, and he's aware of where I am though
Because of the fog and everything else going on around him. You know, excuse me less aware. All right
I'm I'm in I'm inflicting wounds on this motherfucker. Okay, cool. Yeah, I'll say that like bussy kitsune miss so wide
You can just sort of sides of that. Yeah. Oh
I don't know what role you have to roll bless to see if you can get that.
I shouldn't say that, but yeah, it's a d4, right?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, that hits.
Yeah, you you let's go.
You kill this beast.
Let's go do you fucking stupid ass beast?
Yeah, fuck you as you as you inflict wounds,
which what does that do for you?
You want to describe it?
Turn somebody inside out starting from their penis.
Turns all their skin completely inside out.
So the rule I'm going to let Wizards of the Coast know,
but they should update the text.
Yeah, there's not anything.
There's nothing descriptive in that that's I know.
It's literally just like make them do the damage.
Yeah, so tell them listen, but we had this idea they can turn
inside out from their penis.
Yeah, you know the guy who wrote each shit on his head or
whatever.
Yeah, he has an idea.
That's right.
Better.
Yeah.
So anyway, so, uh, yeah, and as you do, you see the beast, you see the slight flicker of life in this beast that isn't possessed by rage.
Don't care, fuck you!
[Laughter]
Fuckin' die, stupid-ass, bitch-ass beast, fuck you!
A thought bubble comes up from its head and it's just like a broken heart.
I close my eyes so I don't see it.
Just fucking die already, you stupid ass bitch ass beast.
Yeah.
So yeah, you just yelling at this thing as it turns inside out from the penis.
And you see a slight wisp of something leave its skull as it falls to the ground dead.
I grabbed the thing that left its skull.
It's gone.
God damn it.
All right.
I try to shoot it with an arrow out of the set of the air.
You have it.
You have a bow and arrow, right?
I think you do.
Yeah, I don't know.
All right, maybe I grab you have a crossbow.
All right.
Yeah, I use my crossbow to try to kill his soul before it
gets any.
Yeah.
And yeah, you killed the beast.
That's pretty good round.
I would say we're back to the top of the order and you
Busty Kitsune now is pretty furious.
And he's gonna take out his blowgart.
- Blowgart?
(laughing)
- I'm gonna take, I'm sorry.
He's gonna take out his fucking blowgart.
- What the heck is that thing you just took out?
Is that a blowgart?
- I've heard of these.
They're called blowgart.
- Oh, if only someone could--
- In real life.
- Guys, look out.
He's got a blowgart.
I've heard it.
Can somebody describe what this blowgart looks like?
What's a blowgart?
Oh, what are you ta- Everybody knows what a blowgart is.
Oh yeah?
He's got it up to his mouth.
He's blowgarting the thing.
Just about the most common thing in the world.
He won't share it with anybody.
That's one thing that your elders will always tell you, is never blowgart the thing.
That's a fantastic four.
Yeah, and he misses with his blowgart.
*laughter*
*overlapping*
And it is now the other two kitsune's who are still alive
One of them is gravely injured. He's gonna try to swing at you Patrick
I
See him about the swing. He don't
Point my finger at the cut in his chest
Don't you stops for like half a second like and then just like goes for it, but he really considers it
Okay
That's gonna be a hit
It might not kill you
God damn they're getting such good rolls though. What do you do? What's a damage? I'm dead. No, I healed you. Oh, yeah
Yeah, fuck you. You're full health. Yeah
I'm never healing you again
No, I just forgot to you just want sympathy. Yeah. Mm-hmm. Well now I'm at eight you're acting out for attention
so now the it was pointless for me to change it in my hit points because i was
just gonna go back to anyway
the other one's gonna try to attack you in a missus though nine because your
left ball which is much more nimble than your right
has been brutalized during this fight
uh...
and uh...
now it is tokens turn
okay so there's
bussy left and
to
uh... consumers yeah
okay i'm i'm going and i'm gonna run up to
to bussy and and and use my my war shovel
yeah go for it i'm gonna swing it like the tasmanian devil would
yeah let's see here
twenty three
the a role for damage
twelve ame's dead
yeah i'd be a kill how do you think it's all i have been around
i'm spinning around like the tasmanian devil and and each time i spin around i
like
i hate like another like i'm gradually going down his body so it's just like
first i hit him in the head
All right, and then the shoulder and then yeah, and then he's just all bruised and fucked up and then yes
And then he goes flying on the last way disappears in the sky with a star like Team Rocket and everyone cheers
And then they put a medal around my neck. Okay. Yeah, and then
right you cure cancer and
What's cancer?
Fantasy, there's no cancer. It's a young thug song. That's cancer
Yeah, it hasn't been invented yet. You just destroy that by the government's you just kill him evil steve will invent cancer
Evil steve-o will invent cancer during this campaign. I have it my way. Yeah, let's do it
So yeah, you just brutalized bussy kitsune and he falls to the ground
He's crumpled and as a kitsune see their leader fall and the beasts fall and the animals just coming in and just
fucking up the rest of them. You see one of the bears starting to pick the lock of one of the
kubler elves. It's pandemonium. The other two kitsunes sort of try to run at this point. They're
completely demoralized. Can I do like a... You absolutely can. I'll go for them. I pull out my
the
Can they run in a single file line?
Uh, hold on.
I snapped my fingers.
Yeah, it just happened.
Okay.
They're in a single file line, what do you want to do?
I'm going to shoot them.
I'm going to shoot the one in the back through the neck.
Okay.
And I'm going to hope that it goes through, I'm going to, like a double tracheotomy.
Hell yeah.
If this works.
I love that cannibal corpse song.
Double tracheotomy.
If this works, I will be the greatest marksman of all time.
Oh yeah.
There's no doubt.
Fifteen.
That hits.
Yeah.
Does it hit both?
Uh, yeah.
I think it fucking does.
Like, why the fuck not?
I was gonna say you had every right to just give me one.
Nah.
I had every right to give you one a long time ago, man.
I don't believe in those rights anymore.
So I just hit both of those kitsune's.
Fuck yeah.
The other one doesn't die.
The other one just has like an arrow in its neck.
Yeah, he's got one on the back.
It's still attached to him.
It's stuck.
Yeah, I just pinned him to him.
I just pinned him to him.
It's like, you're gonna be slow now.
Not what I wanted, but...
He's just like crying and laughing.
He's just freaking out.
Having an episode.
The permanent piggyback.
I've heard of that technique.
That's very impressive.
That was a good one, Patrick.
Yeah, that is exactly what I was trying to do, too.
Don't let anyone tell you
that's not what I was trying to do.
Mm-hmm.
I won't let anybody tell me that.
Cool, I mean, like, yeah.
Don't let any kind of voices on the outside...
Another kid comes over and taps me on the shoulder and I say, "No!"
Can I attack that one?
And the fight slowly ends.
Yeah, I mean, you guys won, as far as I'm concerned.
Like they're there that I didn't want to have to play that out. You guys sort of would have beaten the shit out of them
nice
And yeah, the coobler elves are freed
You see everybody is like pretty bruised and battered from the fight, but they're pretty happy
With everything that's happened. You see the coop coobler elves come over to you and they're like, thank you so much for freeing us
Thank you. We I don't know how we can ever repay you
to
excuse me the tent and they get out 500 gold pieces that the kitsune stole from
the kooblers and robbed from people who came into the woods they also bring back
some just general clown detritus that they think you might want um I don't
want that clown shit what are you doing man I don't want that shit anywhere near me
the
investigation and all rule investigation. Yeah, sure.
9-5 goddammit. So yeah, you guys sort of explore the compound
you see sort of scattered debris from from travelers who went
through the woods and were attacked by the kitsune's you
see Jack in the boxes. You see other clown where clown where
it's I like to call it. You also see like scarves tied together
that seemed to be what was holding the Sasquatch
when they were captured it.
And you also see a Dean and Luca Vegas,
the brothers who were used as battering rams
or used as weapons by the Sasquatch and are fully dead.
- Man, I was gonna kill them.
(laughing)
- Yeah, they're fully dead just like in the tent.
You don't really find too much else in there.
Besides, I mean the 500 gold pieces, which was the coobler sort of scrounging around getting up all the money that they could get for you guys in there.
You see one coobler Elf sort of go up to you guys and go.
We're going to head back to the to the to the the woman and the white woman in the woods pond and we're going to have a big party.
If you guys want to join a party.
Wow.
Yeah.
And I don't I'd love that.
I'd love to I stepped on something.
Hold on.
if
the
Ha ha ha ha! Wee! Yeah!
Okay, put me to hell! Put me to hell!
Yeah! Keep going!
Spin him some more! Spin him way more!
I'm still spinning, yeah!
Spin him so fast that it starts looking like you're going the opposite direction!
Okay! I'm spinning so fast it looks like we're standing completely still!
*laughter*
O-okay! We're okay!
We're drilling into the ground!
*laughter*
And then I let go by accident and he goes flying!
He goes flying.
He goes dead.
He turns to paste.
No!
He's dead, but the G-Force killed him before he let go of him anyway.
He's like in the Spongebob Fry Cook games where he falls splat and he just turns into
the number one.
Yeah.
And he's made it.
He's okay.
Yeah, everybody's super excited.
The White Woman of the Woods greets you all.
Thank you for freeing my Kubler elves and the mudmen will be so glad to hear of the dead
Sasquatch.
This is wonderful news.
You've truly changed the Whippet Woods for the better.
Yeah, we did.
You got anything else?
Can we leave this party?
I have social anxiety.
*laughter*
I'm starting to become uncomfortable.
Yeah, hold on a second.
Is there, uh, is there like, uh, anything...
You have like a fidget spinner.
Yeah, maybe...
You have any like, uh, you have any silly putty that he can play with?
I need something tactile.
You guys have like a quiet room or like a sensory...
Hold on, hold on, I got this.
An Etch-A-Sketch.
You could use...
I pull like...
It's a hot day, I figured I could do this.
And I pull like...
A bunch of like...
Ball skin?
And I hand it to Steven.
It's just like a big...
It's like a big like thing of silly putty.
Like a six foot long string of silly putty.
I'm not sure where you got this,
But it is seriously soothing my anxiety right now. Do not do not worry about it at all
I'm gonna focus on this and I will not follow the trail. I want to play with that too, and I start oh, yeah
Here's a scalpel
a lot of little pieces
Great idea. Yeah, do you guys have one of those molders where we could turn this into like a star?
circle you see the
Amazing it's amazing. I can't feel any of this Cooper. Elves come with a cookie tray
I thought you'd never ask it's like all these cookie cutter things you can use on these balls. You know I taste
I've
Hopped around and enrolled on these things so much. I actually I feel nothing yeah
Catalyst like a marathon runners heel
So yeah night begins to fall on the the affairs as things are you know getting on their way?
And the white woman of the woods she unveils she's gonna rename the pond because now she is
Not just from the pond. She's the whole woods are hers once again
She's renaming it to the trebuchet pond after the heroes who came from trebuchet village free the Cooper elves and restored the forest glory
Yeah, can you name it after us? I mean, that's that's just a town. What about working? Yeah, I don't think we
It's just a long it would just be a long name
The Patrick Steve old Ogun pond, I don't think that's too unwieldy
What about the Patrick's you owed our evil Steve? Oh and dog in the dirt goblin heroes pond
So the first one sounded doable. It's just they just we just announced it. Can we wait till tomorrow?
What about get it? I've got an idea. What if we name it the awesome zone?
You know what you guys picked the name. Let me know by the end of the night
Alright, you will will will work very hard on this
You don't have to worry. This is in great. I'm not worried
Inserts the west end of the pond there's like a big bonfire
There's a game of limbo that's being played, but everyone's really fucking short. It's all just
people are healthy guys people it's just people walking
yeah
they're just running
it's just
they're not
they're not lowering their head at all
cause they're too small to reach
they're just walking back and forth
yeah
and just like clapping and cheering
it's so much
they're having so much fun
their limb by limb by limb
There's one guy who's really tall and he hits it every time
and they have to him.
Oh rats.
There's like one tall Koop or else.
He's like three and a half feet tall.
His hat knocks the thing over.
There's also drinks being served by the sword in the stone
who returned to his true form of the woods have reverted
which is a guy with a sword in this head.
He's just there sort of serving drinks to everybody the mud
men are in the shade towards the east. They're enjoying the proceedings from afar. They're
trying to avoid the heat, you know, but they like the company of everybody. They showed
up as well later in the evening. Some of them fuse together by accident when they're exposed
to the flames. So they try to stay away as much as they can, but the white woman in the
woods just sort of gently sort of pulls them apart. There's also a group of people, a group
of Koobler elves telling stories, turns into impromptu dramatics and reenactments of their
time as slaves and the times to come.
Many of the Kooblers are so excited to be free that they immediately begin baking cookies.
Chocolate chip, oatmeal raisin, peanut butter, merry mint patties, lemon cream pie, caramel
nut dreams, jumbo fudge sticks, bite-sized snacking grams, elf fudge, elf witch chocolate,
The Amazing Spider-Man Graham Bites, Ripe Bites, Fudge Shop, Mini Fudge Stripes, and S'mores
Peanut Butter Original.
And Dirt Meal Raisin made my very own Grandma Kudler who joined in.
I was wondering where all my stuff was, but I'm so glad to see all my friends freed that
I don't give a fuck.
So hot dogs!
Hey, this granny swears.
is
it's bad it's a great deal it and it doesn't hurt
two-and-a-half minutes uh...
uh... any could it get any better than this
we guys do during the party what's going on
uh... i try to go under the limbo but my balls are too big
yeah i'd like to have been basically the the height of like a cooler alfred
yeah you're about the high but my balls make me just like a little bit yeah
- Yeah.
- So I'm trying to go under the limbo stick
and I actually have to like, I can't do it.
- Lean balls first.
Lean your balls first.
- You know, this sucks.
This, you need to make it taller.
It doesn't work.
You guys are not being,
- Is this ableist?
- I'm so mad.
- They all look very concerned.
- I'm so mad right now.
I'm just gonna go.
I'm gonna go.
I'm not gonna play this.
- Yeah.
- I follow Patrick around like a little brother
and i'm wearing like a like a goody that's like five sizes too big for me
yeah i'd like to wait past my hands on the sleeves
this is waiting for the person for the doll to be over you have a great
uselessly die like this
angle and i see the whole i'm just sitting in the corner creating a
destroying water over there
i i see
sullivan
across the party and he's not he's he's sitting alone kind of like
you know nursing his drink
and i i have a good sense of order and i i'd like
i like to have a lot of talk like a strand of like nasty ready goblin hair
behind one of my ears and i'm like
hey
and that
i'd rather it was that it was a
i think
it's not just
i reach out for
and i think i'd i'd take his hands
okay
Yeah, he's consenting to all this, it's all happening.
I'm holding his hand, and then I cast the spell Ceremony.
[laughter]
Oh wait.
And I choose the spell Ceremony, which is,
you perform a special religious ceremony that is infused with magic.
When you cast the spell, choose one of the following rites,
the target of which must be within ten feet of you throughout the casting.
And I choose the final option, which is Wedding.
[laughter]
So you are now Mr. Sullivan?
Dogen Sullivan?
Dogen the frog?
You hyphenated it?
Yeah, I did a middle name thing.
I made my last name my middle name.
Sullivan does not know this is happening.
And he just feels a sudden shift in the universe.
Like, uh, hey.
For the next seven days, each target gains a +2 bonus to AC while they are within 30 feet of each other.
*laughter*
That's when you're married.
For a week.
God.
As soon as I realize that this is a wedding, I let loose, I start drinking champagne, I'm on the dance floor, I'm fucking doing the worm.
Go Steve-O! Go Steve-O!
Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
I run over to Dogen and Sullivan and I go,
THIS IS OUR SONG!
And then we get on the dance floor. That's like the first time I've ever yelled
And I get on the dance floor like
Listen listen, and then it plays Busta Move by uh
Yeah, medieval version. Yeah, the version of Busta Move, and then we just do the dance scene from the movie grind
Roll performance check
All of you. All of us? All of you.
I got a 10. I got a 16.
Uh...
I got... a 19.
I gotta roll for... ooh, I gotta roll for Solvin' too.
Dude, my worm is crazy right now on the dance floor.
Okay, let me get Solvin' up.
I roll out a giant cake.
And I'm like, "Yeah, hey, go ahead. Dig in."
And then as soon as someone touches it, the white woman of the woods pops out.
She's in a fucking black bikini.
*laughs* Yeah.
You like cast a spell to create that.
She's like, "Don't! Don't do that!"
Like, she's like somewhere else.
Um, uh...
"Get in the cake, you idiot!"
*laughs* And, uh...
"What'd I hire you for, you worst stripper ever!"
*laughs* And, uh, yeah, the performance...
You guys all do pretty solid.
Even Patrick Jodar, you did okay.
You guys are fucking living it up.
This is a jam for all the fellas.
The white woman of the woods.
Trying to do what the white woman of the woods tells us.
The white woman in the woods is dancing like a ho-ass in the fucking ass cake.
Like a ho-ass bitch.
I throw the bouquet. Who catches the bouquet?
Now you got it, got it good.
Grandma Koobler does.
She looks over at first a boy, and she's like "whoa!"
And then she...
And then who'd you look at?
Then it looks at a mudman.
Um, uh...
I do not want to see that child!
[laughter]
That is a fucked up...
I don't know that that's legal.
That is a man made of dirt!
[laughter]
Take the bouquet back.
You might as well be fucking a puddle, bitch.
Let's try this again.
Yeah.
And, uh...
Throw the bouquet again.
And as you throw the bouquet, it sails in the air,
and everything sort of slows down. Nothing bad's happening.
But the jester is no more. That spirit that you saw, had seen
Evil Stevel, that leaving, was the spirit of the jester leaving that Sasquatch.
It's last defiant act was to possess the Sasquatch.
You can hear the last gasping chortles and
chuckles of ethereal erasure, complete annihilation and particle loss.
loss, the end of the Jester's comedic play on the denizens of the Whippet Woods.
And unbeknownst to all of you, however, there's a great shift in the cosmos.
A small stirring works its way through the collective soul of the mortals that walk planet
E-Bound.
The particularly sensitive to these great magical adjustments grow a little aroused,
but nothing they can point to is particularly unusual.
However, secret knowledge has infected the hearts and minds of the immortal spirits that
litter the planet. The long forgotten angel of virtue too, the police, possesses this special
knowing, and perhaps lies in wait.
Patrick, Dogen, and Evil, you have made yourselves aware to the conscious and unconscious forces
of planet E-Bomb. There is an unseen counsel, an imperceptible communication made between
the elements, a quiet, cosmic acknowledgement of the destiny of you three mortals. You have
become worthy and that worthiness would frighten you if you could sense its implications.
And as the bouquet flies slowly into the air and that sort of cosmic knowing goes across
the universe, it continues again and it lands and Prince Jumanji catches it and uh...
Oh no.
There better be another baby in this room.
I'm sorry!
Don't look at me!
Get the boy!
I didn't mean to.
Close your eyes!
Okay, I'm closing my eyes.
Look at that bug in front of you.
Oh, where?
Should I open my eyes?
Yeah, look at the bug.
Okay, I'm looking at...
Alright, boys, we're safe.
Okay.
Should I kiss the bug?
Yeah.
Yeah, go ahead, kiss that bug.
Okay.
And the night goes on like that until we return today.
Yeah.
Yeah, go ahead, kiss that bug.
Okay, and uh...
The night goes on like that...
Until...
Uh, we return today.
And you guys all...
Wake up in just whatever fucking vile mess you- you're in.
Yeah.
We're all hungover.
Can I say that I- can I say that we- we've all co- we all got so drunk that we completely forgot that me and Sullivan got married.
*laughing*
You just get the buff.
Yeah, wait.
Wasn't there some kind of wedding last night?
I think- Something weird happened
there at the queen's throne.
Oh shit, you know what it was? That little kid married a
bug!
That shit just sucked up.
Does that make the bug
the queen?
Oh my god.
The princess. I think that's the next
story arc.
I feel like it's gonna die probably in like a week. I get I roll over and I'm like nah, man
We'll find that bug we'll take care of it
Flat on my back
Yeah
Yeah, you see Sullivan like Sullivan looks at his hand and he sees a ring and he's like, huh?
And he's like, hmm
Ling Sullivan makes it off. It puts it in his pocket. He's on my palm this way. He doesn't know what it is
is
Is there any kind of...
What's our achievement percentage right now?
Yeah, what's the word I'm looking for?
How many locked trophies are there?
His eyes go white.
At this time, I cannot disclose how many side quests remain.
Can you point us in the direction of one or is this kind of like a morrowind thing?
It's closer to the Elder Scrolls than it is to say Morrowind in particular, right?
It's not quite like a...
Yeah, there's no quest markers?
Yeah, no waypoints.
Crap, I think we leave.
Is that okay?
Yeah, I'm getting the fuck out of these woods, dude.
I'm out.
Okay.
Alright, well I'll still show you out.
The mud men lead you through back to their village.
And they clear a path in the mud.
They sort of do a Moses parting of the mud and you see sort
of a clear shot out through the woods.
And as you walk out, you know, you exit the whip at woods.
You've changed it from a cackling nightmare into a normal
place for kindly Cooper elves and a goodly womanly spirit
Trunchbull and other seasoned adventurers have maybe traveled
this far outside the village, but it's not something any of
you anticipated doing so soon.
Clock Castle, you can see it now.
You're two weeks away from it, but it's such a massive looming figure.
You can see it as a speck in the distance.
Black against a blood-red sky of the Terrifier's Kingdom.
It's familiar foreboding view.
It fills you guys with a sense of ease, like there's something.
We can get there.
We can get home.
But what you also see is that Mount Honestoodle, which once stood so high that it could be seen
from here much more clearly than the castle could. Can't be seen at all.
And you see Sullivan and the young prince's face fall at this realization that they don't
know where Mount Honestoodle is. However, outstretched before you is an endless
road, a new chapter, a new story. Returning the prince to the Terrifier Kingdom
is but a blip. Nice.
That was the blip. Yeah.
that
is
world.
What happens when Casey Anthony gets a hold of him?
Do you really want that to happen again?
I guess I was feeling angry at kids.
She's innocent, I just want to say.
She was declared innocent.
But in a small town between the Whippet Woods and Trebuchet Village, the sluggish humdrum
of life plods on.
The pleasant stupidity of the peasantry goes unabated by the death of Prince Jumanji.
Oh, yes, you didn't know.
The kingdom thinks that the young prince has died.
You don't know this.
With only our heroes and the brave lion seemingly knowing the truth, King Nardwaur has been inconsolable,
locking himself and his favorite bard in his room, who has been playing the medieval version
of Had a Bad Day for four days straight now.
But in this small town, this is nothing short of news that hasn't yet reached their ears.
But what has reached your ears is something of a bounty on three nasty little men who
killed a beloved bounty hunter.
And in this town, you see a person, dunk, dunk, dunk, nail something, reward 1,000 gold
pieces and three just awfully crude drawings of you three.
I thought it was going to be some other people. No.
Who do you think it was going to be some bad guys?
Yeah, you do bad guys and reward 1000 gold report to your late
nearest Brave Lion to collect the reward and we zoom back away
from that town away from all these little details about what's
going on in the world things.
you don't know about and we bring back to you guys here.
You are outside of the whip.
It woods the road ahead is there's lots of different things.
You can do I'll say this.
Do you want to go north?
Do you want to go South East or West which directions the
castle the castle is north of you?
Maybe we go just Northeast just the yeah, it's the throw a
little, little English on it. Yeah. All right. Little flavoring.
I'm writing this down.
And we'll pick up next time on what all that means.
That's a jam for all the colors. Try to do what those ladies tell ya.
Get shot down cause you're overzealous. Play hard to get females get jealous.
Okay, smarty. Go to a party. Girls are scantily clad and showing body.
[music]