[Music]
Last time on Trebuchet Village.
Our heroes finally bested the terrible Kitsunes, the clown Sasquatch, and the jester himself once and for all.
It was a long, hard-fought battle, but the win was secured by some clever use of fog, some well-placed arrows, and powerful thunks with a big shovel.
Afterwards, the gang freed the Kugler elf slaves and returned to the White Woman of the
Woods, where she named a pond, sort of after the brave adventurers who freed Whippet Woods
of its jester menace.
There was drinking, limbo, dancing, singing, and even a wedding.
While the festivities raged on, the world took notice, in some small, irreversible way,
of the impact Dogen, Patric, and Evil have had on the ye olde planet E-Bow.
Once they left the woods, the boys were faced with the awesome sight of their beloved Terrafire
Kingdom in the silhouette of a one-claw castle.
However, with the sudden disappearance of Mount Honestoodle, an unease fell upon the party,
but nevertheless they persisted.
Due northeast, specifically, towards Trebyshe village, but also a little bit towards the
disputed part of the Terrafire Kingdom.
While the west of the trebuchet landmass is largely left alone, and the south unexplored,
the east in large part belongs to the Terrafire Kingdom.
However, where the north contends with scaredy cats and brave lions, among other things of
course, the east contends with those who disagree with King Nardwar's leniency towards the
scaredy cats.
Sure, there is dissent across the kingdom in one small way or another, but the east lies
in the city of Galgadot, a bastion for all the most vile of the kingdom, and the rise of
a new lord who wishes to challenge King Nardwar. But Galgadot is quite far out, and although
its reach can be felt where our heroes are, it's nothing they need to concern themselves
about right now. In fact, what they should be concerning themselves with is that they've
been traveling for three days and haven't seen a soul. The road ahead and its signs do
suggest that there are some small towns nearby, but the lack of any other travelers and the
hours spent hunting and gathering food can be tiresome. Here's hoping the future brings
something more substantial to eat and to do as they get closer and closer to their home.
So yeah, you guys have been traveling to Northeast with you, you all, Sullivan, and Prince Jumanji
for a little bit of time now.
And you followed signs that have like sort of pointed to this town
or that a town, but
they're all always like another day out.
And so it's been like a pretty long journey so far.
But what have you guys how's the journey been?
What were you guys up to in those three days?
How did you guys spend your time?
I'm curious.
I was looking for a hotel
the whole time I'm looking.
Is there anywhere anywhere around here I can find it?
Dad, I just want to I want to sit in a sauna real quick.
I just want to get in a steam bath.
I don't I don't know why why we would ever
I would ever not stop somewhere that has at least a three star hotel.
I am. So, you know, there is the big Sullivan wedding thing that happened.
That's the elephant in the room.
But we don't remember it, right, because we got we had too much juicy juice.
Yes. But here's I.
I keep noticing that whenever I get close to Sullivan,
I get an AC buff.
Yeah, that's what they call it, huh?
Yeah, and I'm still, yeah, so my armor hardens a bit.
Yeah.
And I'm starting to piece together what happened.
Because I, and I'm also noticing that I'm missing, I was missing a spell slot, and I was thinking, which spell did I prepare that could have been missing?
And I'm walking like a goat trying to get as many blisters as I can.
as I can.
It's like walking like fucking with
fucked up feet.
It's like, oh,
fuck. Yes, I have hooves.
If they had soft feet and blisters
all fucking time.
I'm just walking around.
Yeah, good.
I'm walking like if a spider had two
legs, I'm pulling like a big,
big chunk of my ball
skin and just wiping, just
patting down my forehead.
Mm hmm. Is it porous?
My ball skin? Yeah. Can it accept water?
I don't know.
Well, I mean, I'm finding out right now.
Is your are your balls porous and can they accept water?
Yeah, I don't know. I mean, I can.
Here, let me spit on him.
OK, hold on. Let me make kind of like a.
OK, I'm going to rub it in after he spits on it just to see if it gets absorbed.
Yeah, go ahead. I don't I don't mind.
All right. I'm OK. Here we go.
Now I'm going to scrub it with this with my toothbrush.
Now, don't no, don't do that.
Anybody got some orange juice?
We can see if it will saturate.
We haven't seen we haven't had anything.
What do you mean orange juice?
Guys, we have to keep going.
I mean, crazy juice.
We're still we're still we're still walking.
We're doing this while we're walking.
OK, you don't have to be such a stick in the mud about it.
Do you think there's no such thing as oranges?
You guys, you guys argue like a married couple or something.
Y'all are weird.
And yeah, it's like you've known each other forever.
And you've been married forever.
That's weird.
I see some kind of tension between you two.
Yeah. Yeah.
You know, lately, I don't know what I don't really know what what went down
that that night that we all had more.
We all had juicy juice.
But strangely, I'm not interested in Sullivan anymore at all.
for some reason because of some event that happened,
I don't feel any more attraction towards him.
And in fact, I hate him a little bit now,
which is strange, but-
- I mean, saying this right in front of me kind of hurts,
but on the other hand, honestly, not gonna lie,
bitter relief was a little weirded out.
And I respect you sort of speaking openly about this.
- Will you shut up?
Oh my God, this guy doesn't stop yapping.
- Oh, okay.
All right, now I'm in trouble 'cause I talk too much, right?
is there is there is there is there is there is there is there is there is there is there
one inch taller. No, they also said that the rock I was standing on technically didn't
have any.
Okay, no, but does it doesn't even make any sense. No way. I don't and that elf and that
elf was a was just a was a and don't get mad at me when I say you were shifty. Don't say
it's like a racist thing because it's not. Oh, I don't have to say it. I mean, I think
we're going on. Okay. I think he's done. Are you guys done with this? I wish I could be
done with this freak.
Okay, I'm walking a bit ahead of you.
Yeah, let's-
Until you cool off!
Let's separate you two.
We'll figure this out later.
I keep flat-tiring him over and over.
When he walks out of the-
Prince Kibaji's like, "Please, mom, dad, stop fighting!"
And now he called you mom and dad.
I wanna live with Dogen!
What does that mean?
Now let's unpack this here.
Let's talk about this.
So the boy called you mom and dad.
So which one of y'all's mom?
Yeah, which one is the mom and which one is the dad?
And to that one, hello.
It sort of keeps changing.
I'm having a little bit of trouble.
Yeah, well, I didn't ask you.
Oh, okay.
I was asking the mom and dad.
So I don't think there's any mom and dad here.
So you know, right?
Well, it seems like maybe there's maybe it's more of a situation where there's a man and
a coward.
Okay, well, I would be honored to be to be the parent of a noble prince, my Prince Jumanji.
Then go ahead and have fun with it.
You know what?
That's that's father material right there.
That's the father in the frog has stepped up.
Yeah, Daddy.
That's right.
You know, and there's a lot of literature out there that says, oh, frogs be like this.
You know, we know how to step up and I'm just so tired of that.
I'm just tired of this shit.
Where the fuck are we going?
Oh, hold on. Hold on.
There's I've I've actually contacted somebody that I know.
Through what? Through what?
What are you talking about?
What the fuck are you on about?
Through magic.
You don't have a magic nothing.
Through magic, I've contacted somebody I know to administer a paternity test.
Now I think I want to want to just
I want to ask, are you ready to see the results, Sullivan?
Are you ready to see the results?
We didn't even take none of his calm.
It's the worst paternity test I've ever seen.
Are you ready to see the results?
Yeah, I think so.
All right. Sullivan.
You are not the father.
OK, honestly, kids cute, but huge relief.
Also, I feel like I'm just coming up with W's today.
Didn't we meet his dad?
Hey, you hear that Prince Jumanji?
Sullivan was really relieved to find out he wasn't your dad.
Yeah, did you see him?
Look at him, he's
he's spinning on his head.
Well, now he's crying because of what you said.
That's not what I said was what you did.
I'm just being honest with my emotions.
I just said what you did.
So it's like I didn't say anything at all.
It's like you just did something.
So this goes on for like another hour.
Yeah, it is a mistake.
I think we're drifting into Little Miss Sunshine territory right now.
We should keep walking.
We can't guess it, by the way.
We we've had a long rest since the last.
Oh, yes. You guys are all healed up on everything.
But yeah, so there's been a lot of bickering, a lot of confused children,
a lot of paternity tests, multiple paternity tests, magical paternity tests.
And you finally stumble across the first people that you haven't
that you've seen in a while.
And you see a sign as well that says this way to the
the strange penis in
great, great a hotel.
I'm so happy to finally find a hotel.
Yeah. And the people you see
you recognize from the distance that you're at
that they have brave lion emblems on them.
So in case you guys don't remember, the brave lions are
A band of scaredy cats who are trying to take down the.
The terror fire, whoa, and me, apparently the terror.
I attacked by one in the woods, right?
You got attacked by Gufus Tiedrich, who was sort of hired by contract on them.
So that's all you know about them right now.
There was a little scene that you guys know about of there being a bounty on you.
But you guys, the characters don't know about that.
But you do see them ahead of you.
But I want to tell you guys,
I'm going to avoid them.
I'm going to flip them off. Yeah.
Do they have like jackets that have like their names on the back?
Like they're just the name of the group and or.
Yeah, yeah.
Kind of like an old like kind of like an old 50s, like like tunnel snakes.
Yeah. Are they?
They're kind of like gatekeeping the hotel.
No, they're just sort of, they're not near the, the inn isn't right in sight. It's just
like a point, like inn is in like X amount of miles. It's like within the day's journey,
but they are around that sign where like merchants would normally gather around signs like that
because it's where people would stop off or something, but they are there instead and
And they're just sort of like have set up what little camp they happen or just sort of milling about.
They don't seem to have noticed you yet.
But if you guys want to, like, flip them off or do whatever you want, you certainly can.
I walk up to one of them, I say.
Hey, you. Your shoes untied.
Not seriously, your shoes untied.
Your shoes are not now.
I mean, two people have said it now, so it's got to be you've got to have some merit.
Just look down at it.
Hey, hey, you dropped your pocket and you dropped your pocket.
Yeah.
That one. What are you what are you eating under there?
And I well, let me just do this in order.
One second.
So he looks down.
He's like, well, my shoes aren't untied and I don't I don't think I have any.
I don't know. My pockets seem underwear.
Oh, fuck. OK.
Now it's I use.
I use I use thaumaturgy to make my voice three times as loud and I say
"YOU SAID IT UNDER A LADDER"
You see Sullivan sort of running to you guys guys stop let's just sort of move on here all right
let's not antagonize this guy. Hold on Sullivan. Hey. Hey. Yeah hey what's going on?
Come here for a second gotta tell you something. Okay sure. He starts to wander over kind of
of suspiciously at this point.
Hey, guess what?
What?
Chicken, but.
Oh, my God, he's dead.
Oh, he dies.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, no.
He's like, all right, why don't you guys piss off?
All right.
We're on official brave line business here anyway.
What business? What's your business?
Nope, you fool me once, you know, the rest of it.
Yeah, your business smells a little bit like up dog.
And you see some of them start to turn around, especially after
Dogen said, use said underwear like, like as loud as hell.
And you see one of them turned around and he has like, he sort of has like the same haircut as Guile
from Street Fighter. And he has this like, just this like awful like flat British guy face.
He's a wood elf of some sort. And he looks at you guys, and then you see him look at a piece of
paper and then look up at you guys, and then look at a piece of paper. And he sort of signals to the
the other ones and they all sort of knock their arrows and you see that's this yeah you guys
see that you guys see all knock their arrows you see that guy go up to you all and say
what do you think you're doing here you're wanted by the brave lions turn yourselves
in and come quietly or we'll have your heads where the where yeah we're on our way to a
the
what you're talking about.
What suck on nuts off.
Get them and yeah, roll initiative.
How many of them are there?
Five thousand.
Yeah, there's now there's like five.
I feel like this is the most pointless fight we've ever done in the history
of our D&D camp is.
I got a twenty one and then I said there was truly no reason for you guys
to start this fight at all.
We didn't start a fight.
We were just talking.
Yeah, the other one who knocked their arrows.
Look, we were...
That is true.
We were...
You said that we didn't know the bounties, so what are we gonna do?
That's true, you didn't know the bounties.
I guess you're right, you guys played as the arrows would.
We were all orderingly and we were all very upset from a long days of travel.
Yeah.
No, I mean, that's true.
I know that for a fact.
Yeah, plus you're the guy who put them there.
I did for a...
Yeah.
Hold on.
Fuck you!
Stop!
pointing fingers anywhere.
All right.
That's the worst thing you could do is blame it on one person
rather than you three. Right.
You know what I'm saying?
I think it's your fault.
I think. Yeah.
No, that's not my fault.
OK, what's the order?
Oh, sorry. Yeah.
Patrick Yoda is definitely going to go first with that sweet, sweet 21.
After that, it's going to be these brave lions.
They have pretty good decks.
Do they attack as one?
Uh, well, there's just gonna be a bunch of them attacking.
And, like, we're gonna have, like,
kind of, I split them into groups, so,
there's one group of Brave Lions that goes second.
Then, Blowtoss, oh, whoops.
And they've, like, cornered us, right?
They're not cornered, no, you guys are, like,
you guys are, like-- Like, we're surrounded, or cornered?
You're not surrounded, you're not surrounded.
You're not surrounded, yeah. They're, they're, like,
sort of in, like, a, like, just a bit of a jumble in front of you.
Okay, so like, Final Fantasy style?
Yes, that's a good way of putting it.
Yeah, uh, yeah, uh...
You're all gonna take turns, it's gonna be very similar.
Okay, I've got an idea.
Yeah, yeah, then it's gonna be Dogen, sorry.
Then it's gonna be the remaining Brave Lions.
Um, then it's gonna be, uh, Ray, William Johnson...
Fuck me!
What? My name is Evil Stievel!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, 'cause we just did...
did something. Can you at least put a birthday cake somewhere in this area? I will. Wait,
why? I'm hungry. I'll figure something out. And then Sullivan is last. Yeah, wait, it's
Dogen's birthday on this in-game day. I just want to specify that right now. Yes. And the
Brave Lions would know that because it would be listed on the bounty, so they would go easy
on
on him it's his birthday.
Hey the others all nod and go "oh yeah of course, of course"
Well I'm glad you respect his birthday.
Yeah I sit down and-
I'm gonna say that right off the top of the bat.
Real good move by you guys, honestly I think maybe we could talk this out.
Yeah, I lie down and I cross my legs and put my helmet over my eyes like Tom Sawyer style.
Yeah that fence sure does look like it might be fun to paint.
*laughter*
Uh yeah, you're up though Patrick.
Uh, right, so...
Why don't we just stop this...
this fight right now.
We all get together,
and we sing, uh, we sing "Happy Birthday"
for our friend, uh, Dogen here.
You turn yourselves in,
we can stop this fight right now!
Not now, hold on, we don't even know what the hell
that's about.
You're wanted for the murder of Goofus Teetrich.
Who's that? We killed like a million people, man.
Yeah, we've killed we've killed so many more people.
We pretty much kill people like every 10 or 15 minutes at this point.
Yeah, we're kind of we're kind of like a crew of puckish rogues.
This was a valuable bounty hunter.
Part of the brave lions.
I bet you didn't know that he actually had a bounty out on him.
Yeah. And we and that's why the pedophile hunters club.
Yeah, he was a serious freak.
Which is what we're a part of.
Yeah, look, we try to overlook his proclivities.
I'm just kidding in character.
There's no way.
Don't joke about that in character because that's a very serious thing we're about.
We're very serious about pedophile hunting and,
you know, we will not appreciate if you make jokes about our profession.
Yeah, we might have to take out a bounty on you.
Yeah, we might put a bounty on you.
I'm no nonce!
Also, if we do a single point of damage to you, you are officially a pedophile.
That is not, no, 'cause that, no, is not true.
I'm pretty sure.
I wouldn't push your luck if I was you.
I'm getting a little nervous, but...
Can I roll persuasion?
Yeah, I mean, 19?
[laughter]
I feel like that's probably a 20, is the...
is
it
over to you. Okay, but I don't you don't you move. We're just saying my birthday. I it's
his birthday. Oh my okay fine. I'll lie down on the ground. I'll close my eyes. I'm not
touching any weapons. Come make a circle around me and sing happy birthday to me. Now. Making
demand. Oh, it's my birthday. I can't everybody everybody put down your weapons. And then
we'll get in the circle. Okay, yep, they're down. First of all, I mean, first of all,
It's a shovel, not a weapon, but you know, I'll put it down anyway.
Put down your spell book, Cleric.
My book?
It's not a book.
Now this is my diary.
Yeah, that's a diary.
Put down your diary then, Cleric.
But I'm reading...
Oh my god, please, just, I'm...
My birthday's gonna end by the time you get around here.
I'm gonna remember that this was his birthday party.
What do you mean?
You could just sort of...
Hold on, I gotta write it down first, but let's start singing
in while I write it down. Also, this has the lyrics to the birthday song on it and I can't
usually remember them.
I just need that, I, you know, Steve-o, please just put the book down. I'm gonna cry pretty
soon. I'm gonna start crying.
Alright, alright.
Alright, I'll put it down.
You want this man to cry?
Okay, now gather around.
You wanna make a grown man cry?
And can you link hands around me and do, and like, do like maybe skip around in a circle
while you sing?
Yeah, let's go.
Yeah, let's do that.
Everybody has their weapons down.
Yes.
Yes! Oh my god, you with the weapons thing.
I mean with the weapons thing.
Are you like planning something?
No, are you planning something?
Why would I be planning something? It's my birthday.
Birthdays are really important to Brave Lions.
We respect it.
Well, you're not respecting it right now.
I can tell you that much.
Alright, they all gather around you guys.
It's our holy hands.
Word of Radiance.
And they all have to make constitution saving throws.
Yeah, absolutely.
Okay.
It's DC 13.
So...
Uh...
Yeah, three of them...
Yeah, three of them fail.
Um...
Two of them succeed, so what's happening here?
The ones who fail take...
Three damage. Three radiant damage.
Okay.
So, describe Word of Radiance. What happens?
Well, the word of Radiance is "dirt".
are
it's
weapons now. And you smell like one, two, well put the weapons, do we got anything left now?
All right, I'm Patrick, you should, you can go now. They're not going to do anything.
I take, I'm gonna hit one of them with a bow and arrow. That's all I'm gonna do.
Whoever's closest. The same thing I just allowed to happen. 18. Okay, roll for damage. Eight.
Okay, yeah, um...
I hit one of the ones who took, uh, however much sun damage or whatever.
Yeah, yeah, describe your kill.
[Laughter]
You're not very strong.
I shoot him, I shoot him straight in the throat.
Yeah, you just fuckin' like...
I'm standing there...
You look like a monkey,
and you smell like one, you just unleash an arrow,
and he's like finishing singing with you,
and then, "I smell like one..."
[Mimics monkey]
I'm
That was it.
Well, he was shinin' there with Lucy in the sky with diamonds.
Yeah, you know, stuff like that, but sometimes it's not needed.
Sometimes the original is better.
Yeah.
So yeah, you just killed that guy, and now the main guy is up, and he's like, "You cunts!"
And he is gonna come at you.
"I can't what?
I can't what?
What can't I do?"
And he's swinging a short sword at you, Patrick Giodar.
I dodge it.
For 100 damage.
You do dodge it.
And he's like, "Oh no, 100 damage!"
He just says that, he just has a tick.
But yeah, he misses.
And then another guy who's a little bit further back is going to leash an arrow at you also,
Patrick Giodar.
Oh, come on.
Yeah, he does hit you.
He does hit you.
How much?
He does 4 damage to you.
That is, now that, now that's my thing.
You don't do my thing.
That's me.
And now it is your turn, evil, no Dogen, sorry.
Evil Dogen.
Dogen, you are prone right now.
Oh true.
Okay so I guess, are they still around me?
No, they all like ran back during the birthday.
During the birthday interstitial that broke every combat rule in D&D.
How far away are they?
So the one who just swung at, you know, Patrick is like, you know, 15, 10-15 feet from you.
Okay, does it take my whole movement to stand up?
No, just half.
Okay, I'll take half my movement to stand up and the rest of it to go into melee range
to
I'm
uncomfortable.
Jesus, Jesus Christ.
Man, that's like a man.
You know, I get it's a, I mean, I get it's your birthday.
You're solid under his breath go, damn, I'm married that guy.
I mean, he's like, what?
Like some memory sort of just reared its head when he saw you.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, he's yeah, his head just like fucking like the time to unwrap my presents and his
head just like went into his neck and just like mushed all up in there.
And then right after he dies they go like "Oh, I should have said something about a pinata!
Fuck!"
And yeah, now it is the other, some of the other guys' turn.
One of them is going to knock a crossbow bolt and aim it at you, Dogen, after you did that
nasty thing.
And what's your AC?
It's something crazy.
18.
Yeah, just like bounce places off your armor.
I hit it out of the air with my shovel actually.
And I say, "Time to unwrap my present!"
Oh, not again man!
That was disgusting!
Oh, come on now.
What the hell?
And then another one...
You say it one more time, we're all going to be upset.
Another one is charging you Evil Steeble.
And he's like, uh, he's like, he's like, I'm gonna read your diary.
He's running towards you and what's your AC?
14.
Okay, that hits unfortunately.
He's using a, also using a short sword and he deals five damage to you as he slashes you
along your, uh, your arms trying to get you to drop your diary.
My diary, I'm like clutching it with both hands and I'm crisscross.
I can't wait to read it, I love secrets.
Yeah, he's a little weird guy.
And it is now, oh no wait, no wait, yeah, can you kill the other guy?
So it is now your turn.
Me, right?
Yeah, you.
Okay, I will use troll the dead on my friend, my creepy friend.
Oh yeah, do it man.
What does troll the dead do?
It basically makes a dolerous bell happen.
So... I wanted fucking cats, dude!
Yeah, uh, you gotta hit the um...
I'm hitting the B!
Oh, well because, well sorry, because it's A, it's not a...
It's like they have to roll against it, because they have to make a business out of it.
So basically, yeah, you make like a big giant bell sound that a target must sort of, you
know, try to save against it.
And they are missing some of their hit points, so they will, instead of taking a d8, will
take a d12.
Okay, so now I roll a d12?
No, so they gotta roll first to see if they avoid you.
And their wisdom is not very high, so...
Yeah, they do get hit by this for full damage.
Yes.
So roll that d12.
That you can just go into the thing and it will roll it for you.
Yeah.
Five.
Nice.
So yeah, you just do, yeah, this guy's like, "Oh, the bell!
Oh, he reminds me of mom!
No!"
And he's just like holding his head.
Yeah, he's not looking too good at all after that.
What does your bell sound like?
Um, it sounds like, uh, the, you said it's a whistle.
It sounds like the whistle from Blow the Whistle by Too Short.
It's like, *whistles*.
Yeah, he's hearing that and he's just like insane.
He's like, I don't like that kind of music.
You ain't getting in my diary, man.
I got tons of recipes in here.
*laughs*
I got crazy paellas in here and shit.
- Paya is in here and shit.
- Hey, you got paya in there?
You haven't...
Come on, man.
- You think?
We ain't got no ingredients out here, man.
We're in the woods.
- Hey, we're in an inn now.
We could probably make a paya here.
- Let me kill these guys first.
Damn.
- Good point.
Good point.
- Now it is Lord Sullivan's turn.
- Oh, Lord now?
- Oh.
- No, no.
- I didn't realize.
- No, you don't have to.
He's gonna take out his dagger and charge that one who you just
you just ring-a-dang-dang the bell. Let's see how he does.
Whoa! You got a crit! Oh my god!
Sullivan! No, that wasn't a crit.
Sullivan has the "everything is a crit" thing.
That was a 19. Oh wait, shit.
Look at this, plus 3. Oh no, wait, how did that happen?
looks like a crit it's the same thing from before anything that Sullivan rolls
that's more than one it's treated as a crit that was in a past episode I
remember that cuz I was editing it he's just a fuck god everything he rolls it's
not a one is green wait why is that happen I guess I'm from the frog
that happened that is okay well whatever now I have to fucking oh yeah I remember
that
this
before and honestly I'm uh pretty terrified actually I don't even know if
I can I don't know we'll have to talk about this later we're fighting we're
fighting fighting creatures this is awful and like he's like stabbing the guy's
stomach and like his guts are like coming out on the solvent just like so unhappy
That man was way taller than you.
*laughter*
Um, yeah.
And uh, that's his turn.
And we're back to the top of the order. It's your turn, Patrick.
There's only two left. Only two left?
Yeah. I'm gonna turn to them and be like,
"Look, why don't we talk this out?"
*laughter*
What did they say?
They're just like, filled with brage.
They are just like, like,
like, well one of them you see is like,
like
I'm gonna be forced to kill you.
Oh well!
Yeah go, go.
Nine.
No damage.
Yeah, I whiff it really bad.
Yeah, and there that one who was
like the awful voice,
"HA! You're not gonna be able to kill us!"
Yeah, that was actually a warning shot.
And I was doing it.
Oh yeah, were you trying to warn a ghost?
I was warning you. I was trying to do you a
favor, but uh...
know
and he like, this is the same guy who had shot you earlier.
And so he knocks an arrow and aims it towards you.
And yeah, that hits you.
- How bad?
- About to find out.
- Probably not too bad.
- Five damage, he just locks another arrow.
- All right, I'm getting pissed off.
I got two arrows in both shoulders.
- Hey, Banter, you're gonna have a third
and it's gonna be in another shoulder.
You know, not maybe, maybe the right one again.
- What the hell are you talking about?
- I don't know you guys, I'm not very good at these.
I'm pretty excited right now
and I'm getting you so many times.
So, I think. - You're a prick.
- You're, you're, you're fucking, you know.
- You know what, I don't like to use.
- Little fucking shit.
- I don't like to use harsh words often, but you're a prick.
- Right, and that means something coming from him.
He doesn't.
I'm a pretty nice guy otherwise.
Plus you're a party pooper.
Yeah, you ruined my friend's birthday.
You ruined my birthday.
You ruined it! You're eating something under there.
You're eating something under there.
Under? No! Not!
I think you accidentally ate some Fremunda.
*laughs*
What's Fremunda?
Yeah, Fremunda my nuts.
I did no such thing!
And you deserve that.
Alright, we're about square now.
(laughing)
- Okay, yeah. - Let's knock this off.
- Yeah, it's your turn, Dogen.
- Are the two that are left close to each other?
- Yeah, yeah, that's why I was able to hit him like,
dude, dude, dude, don't.
- Okay, I'm gonna run into the middle of them
and I'm gonna use Word of Radiance again.
Also something that I realized is that
I've had a shield equipped this whole time,
so I technically shouldn't have been using
two-handed damage, I only just saw when I opened
my inventory. - I was wondering why
your AC was so high.
- So from now on I will,
a
have
try to slice at you with a dagger that he's going to pull from his path.
And he's going to miss or bounce off your shield or whatever.
And now it's your turn, Evil Steeble.
Okay, I'm going to use Chill Touch on the one closest to me.
Okay, cool.
One closest to me.
Yeah, five.
Well, that's just the damage.
They have to do the attack roll.
No, I did it bad again.
Aww.
20!
Fuck yeah, that hits.
5, do you want to keep that? Let's keep that 5.
Um, yeah. You do it to the guy who was screeching.
Uh, like a numbnut.
And uh, he's not looking good either.
How do you, how do you chill touch him?
He doesn't die, but how do you like...
chill touch him? What do you do with your hand?
I... I...
uh, make him eat his own booger.
Yeah, it's a really cold booger.
Um, and he's like, "Oh no! That's actually, you know what? This is a little bit underrated."
"I knew you'd like that shit, you nasty ass!"
"Oh no, now everybody knows he's gonna put it in his diary!"
"That's right, I'm writing that down right now."
"No, don't do it!"
Um, yeah, and now it is Sullivan's turn.
And Sullivan is going to take out his bow and arrow
and try to shoot it at, um,
uh, the booger eater.
Let's see how he does at that.
Go Sullivan, go Sullivan.
Oh, he has a, he has a, what does he have?
He has a dart.
I gave him darts.
He has a dart?
Does he throw it?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, 20.
No, he got a 16.
That does hit that guy.
Okay, stop.
He keeps giving everything a crit.
He almost kills the booger guy.
He throws the dart and it goes right into his like thigh and it just like gets him down
and it's just like fucking is just like really just like doing this guy and he's almost gone
Patrick you're up they're both looking pretty bad.
All right I'll give you one more chance to knock this all off we'll forget this ever happened.
Um you can do it.
I don't know if you guys know any necromancers or anything we could probably bring these these
other three back. Given that you know a necromancer, I don't know any necromancy spells. I'm actually
a, not really a magician at all. I'm actually a, he has the closest magic trick I can do
and I do like the finger thing. I'm showing them that I'm removing my, the tip of my finger.
One of them like politely chuckles, coughs up a bit of blood. This is the only magic
trick I really know and yeah what do you guys think?
Yeah, go for it.
You guys still mad?
Alright.
Intimidation.
14.
Yeah, they sort of look to each other and they say like at the same time like, "Brave
Lions till the end!"
Right, then that is.
That is not good for you.
Can I do I attack now?
Yeah, yeah, that's fine with me.
13 that does hit them.
They have eight damage.
Yeah, one of them you just kill.
Am I? Yeah, yeah.
Whoever said brave lions till the end, I just shoot him straight in the eye.
Yeah, yeah, the bigger one.
Yeah. Is that the one who shot me?
Yes. OK.
Like, yeah, see, that's how it's done.
All right, you got to aim for that spot, not the fucking shoulders.
Like you thought that that would that would hinder me in any way.
No, it didn't. I'm an amazing dad.
And you're just talking. Yeah, I'm an amazing shot.
All right. Yeah.
I hope you hear this in the afterlife, too, because you were a prick.
The other guy, the other guy is is going to crap himself.
You're up, Dogen.
I punch him in the face on arm strike.
I
he's got tears and he's gonna come on drop your weapon yeah he's doing it too he's like gonna come
on his best yeah he just gets even worse of role than you and he just okay everybody else back off
i'm gonna come on we're this way this guy gonna duke it out all right do you think all right yeah
yeah go back to the board now yeah you're up another nine okay you miss he's gonna try again
Yeah he hits you. Oh no. I'm still not getting involved. No I got this. He does three damage,
he just gets you across the jaw. Yeah I spit out a tooth. I swing again. I kick him this time. 21.
Okay yeah roll for damage. It does three damage. Yeah he's dead. Yeah I roundhouse kick his head
I don't think we have anything to dig with, unfortunately.
So
We'll just burn them do something we got to get rid of this shit I do not why don't you?
Know I'm not that hungry
But if you were hungry you need to know I mean like I'm not that like I would never be that hungry probably
And I'm pretty hungry on this journey. I don't know you fucking figure it out. I'm going to the hotel
solvent I'm going to give solvent a is going to do a role to see how well he hides the bodies.
I guess it's going to be I guess that's a that could be a survival role or a it's exciting.
What is it to hide bodies? What kind of role is that? I guess I guess like survival.
If it's like digging. Yeah, it's like yeah, it's like a couple of things, right? It's like
Could be stealth.
Could be stealth, too.
I feel like stealth is is let me see.
Let me see survival.
Hot wild game guide your group through frozen ways.
Identify sentence. Yeah.
Yeah, I would say it's survival just because like it's like
it's something you would do out so you would dig holes outside.
It's something you would do.
I'm going to give him a survival role.
See how he does.
Pretty good. Pretty good.
So in regards to gets a 15, he does a pretty good job
hiding the bodies. That might come back later. So you guys head to the strange penis inn.
It's a like very homely. Wait it's called what? The strange penis. Oh. What did I call
it? Is it called the strange penis inn? Did I miss that? Yeah. I guess you did yeah. Did
you guys hear that earlier? Yeah I heard that earlier. It's the strange penis inn. Alright.
you
is
on
He's just sort of there cleaning glasses doing bartender II things
Obviously it's in and so you can also stay there for night if you'd like
But you can also get a drink beforehand or fraternize with many of the personnel who are there
I walk in the first thing I'm saying it's my birthday
Just to see what?
I'm friends with the birthday boy
Everyone's strengths are on themselves tonight.
- I usually feel with them go,
(laughing)
like some of them find it funny,
some of them find it funny,
but it's fine, it works out.
I think like, you want to do a persuasion roll with that
if you're trying to like sort of just
like finesse the crowd a little bit.
- Yeah, I'm gonna have these people wrapped around
my tiny little goblin finger.
That's a six.
- Yeah, no, you come off about as off-putting as you are.
I'm
a
simple that way seven right lucky number seven I like seven all right single
digit let me hold on let me and I get you a drink sir let me think here
cramp oh I could see you're doing math in your head what's going on I was I was
trying to look for that you know that thing where it's like okay pick any
number then divide it by this and then but I don't remember I don't remember
how to do that so I can do it here I'll feed it to you ready I'll feed it to you here we go
okay so tell him to pick a number tell him to pick a number tell him to pick a
number okay pick a number I should I pick seven again or should I pick something
yeah you should pick seven now tell him to multiply it by six multiply it by six
all right yeah now tell me why do you now tell him to divide it by the original
number. Yeah, divide it by the original number. Now tell him his number is 6. His final result
is 6. Now tell him his number is 6. He's just sort of like nodding. Yeah, you got that right.
I mean we have to have earned like one free drink there, right? Yeah. You know what? If
you don't do that again, absolutely. Alright, great. Yeah, and he gives you guys a free round.
Is there anywhere to gamble in here? Yeah, there are people playing cards
Like in the back that are like playing some kind of like
esoteric
Car game they're playing actually, you know what they're playing
They're playing wave race 64, which is what Patrick played in the first episode the classic trick-taking game
It's kind of like my version of cribbage
Anybody know cribbage? Yes. All right. Here we go. Now we're talking but there's no there's no fun roulette games or anything
No, this is
Sucks yeah, you say that just in earshot of the bartender it's the worst place
Yeah
Some probably could do some view some do with you some sprucing up. Yeah, you could the interior decoration of this place is seriously
Yeah, you got an idea. What if we give you what if we make you a painting and then you give us a couple free drinks
Paintings worth way more than drinks man
Now what are you gonna paint?
you
No, I'm doing here stand still and look towards me. I
Got a bad rich go behind him and get a bunch of drinks. Yeah, I got it. Take care of other customers. So get it
Okay, you're gonna try to you guys try to do this. Well, he's got he's got it
I mean, I I will say if we're about to hey, we're about to go to sleep. I got two spell slots left
I could command this guy to stay still with the spell. I'm sure that wouldn't backfire at all
all
one word command to a creature you can see within range. My command is freeze. The target
must succeed on a wisdom saving throw or follow the command on its next turn.
Okay. Mm-hmm. His wisdom is that. Yeah, he fails. So how long does he have to be frozen
for? I don't know. The rest of the night. A duration one round. Uh-oh. That's six seconds.
Okay, so I just go behind the bar and I grab it.
You just yell freeze and he just can't move.
I don't yell it, I whisper it.
You whisper freeze and he can't move for six seconds.
What are you gonna do Patrick?
I go and I'm behind the bar.
No you're not, you gotta do some rolls for that.
Oh fuck, okay.
If you're gonna do this in six seconds.
Okay, stealth.
17.
Um that's, I mean, you know, uh okay so you're,
are you doing this trying to do this without him noticing?
Yes.
You're doing this without him noticing.
Stealth 17.
Um, okay, um, yeah, I'd say like you're pretty, like he's kind of a little distracted by, uh,
by, uh, uh, Evil Stevel saying his place sucks ass.
Um, so yeah, and you're kind of little.
So you sort of run around the side.
Now, um, as far as getting the drinks, you can get the drinks without noticing.
Nineteen, sleight of hand.
That's, that's good enough to get like two drinks, I would say.
Okay.
In this moment where he's frozen.
and we are not free one so that's three drinks
okay that's all we need
but the stealth to get out now at the mean you can just heard dash at this point
when I'm curious about though is I mean he
yeah he's like frozen during this time
he said let you know yet but the hell did you do to me who
this one dark boy over here
The hell did you just do?
What the hell did you just do to me?
I didn't do anything.
Yeah, that's the birthday boy, not the dirt gay boy.
What are you saying?
Yeah, what are you saying?
You owe us some drinks, I'd think, for this.
Yeah, roll a deception.
This bartender's got pretty good insight.
He's got a crit one.
Nice.
Goddamn, okay.
By the way, you might want to go to the bathroom.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
Okay.
By the way, you might want to go check to a doctor or something.
You were frozen for a few seconds there and it looked really serious.
You might want to get that checked out.
I think the right side of your face might be drooping a bit.
He's like looking at you and he's like...
Just...
Go find a seat.
I don't want you guys near the bar.
Okay.
Alright, weirdo.
Alright.
Yeah, okay, yeah. So you guys can go find a table somewhere.
How many drinks did we just get?
Like six?
Something like that?
Yeah. So you guys got a bunch of drinks.
You can go find a...
There's a couple tables around.
There's a couple tables
open, but they all have like...
somebody there.
Hey, how about you move
for the birthday boy?
Who can we...
There's an elf.
An elf who's kind of dressed
just
other people there she's chatting with them but those people just are sort of
not of note. There's a massive like orc who's sitting at a table and like it's
like up against a wall with a bench and so the table has like other chairs there
but there's like his group is up against a bench by where that table is so that
table is unoccupied but it's kind of like his space. There's another table with a
The guy who looks like he has like seven brain cells and he's just sort of eating.
He's eating stew.
Let's sit with him.
Okay.
We're sitting with him.
Yeah.
Okay.
You guys go sit with this guy.
He is permanently cross-eyed and currently eating stew with a fork.
And he sees you all sitting with him.
He goes, "Oh, well, greetings.
It's nice to meet you."
Can I have your stew?
"Oh, yeah.
You can have a bit of my stew.
The whole bowl for the birthday boy.
Whose birthday is it?
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me.
Oh well happy birthday.
You don't look a day over.
And he just like stares.
He tries to come up with a number.
Well sure here's some of my soup and he just passes your stew to you.
My name's Timothy.
What's y'all's names?
My name is also Timothy.
Yeah, me too.
No way!
That's awesome!
I'm hot, I'm Christopher.
Okay, that's pretty cool.
And this right here is our associate, this right here is our associate Sullivan the Frog.
My name is Sullivan, and this is uh, uh, Gary.
I don't want them to know he's a prince.
Prince Gary.
Prince Gary, his first name's Prince.
yeah well it's nice to meet all of you Timothy Timothy this that complicated
name that began with a C I think and frog and friend and small friend well I hope
y'all are having a nice time here this is my favorite bar and in I love the
strange penis. I always get the stew. I bet you do. Yeah I really do love it here. Yeah I bet you love strange penis.
Yeah I do what's that sound? Yeah I bet you do. Yeah I do. Yeah you do.
Why you laughing? Oh I don't know cuz you're laughing. I'm always laughing when
other people are laughing. Hey do you like the strange penis? Yeah I love it here!
Oh man oh man oh man. Oh wow. You guys remind me of my friends, Evis and Butthead.
Well I really shouldn't be traveling with y'all I gotta get back home at some
point. Usually I have to stay here all night to finish the stew because I keep
using the fork I don't remember what the other thing is that you really should be
eating it with so usually I just stay here all night but uh but tonight I guess
I can make it back home go back to my home an idiot Volage you like strange
penis man I'm out I leave hey man yeah do you wanna go get get a get a room at
the end I want to get a room dude I'm fucking sick of this I want to get a
room with him. Yeah me too. Yeah so you guys leave Timothy. As you're leaving him, before
you leave he turns to you and says "Oh wait, wait, wait! I remembered why I was here! Hold
on! Uh, see, our town is in some terrible trouble." Here we go. Basically, we've been hit with
some awful plague, our crops are dying, and our village idiot's missing, on top of everything.
*laughter*
You want us to deal with that?
Yeah, I...
Yeah, well, I was supposed to try to find adventurers who could help with that.
Usually I just come here and eat my stew, but I had another job today.
And I've tried to talk to people, but every time I do, they usually say, "Down boy, down!"
And I just sort of stopped talking right away, I don't know why.
But y'all were so nice to me and actually listened for a change.
Please, our town doesn't have much right now, but if you could find a way to get rid of this terrible plague,
well, I'm sure there'd be quite a reward for y'all.
Can I go to bed first?
Of course you can sleep on it if you need to.
I sleep on a bed myself.
That's actually maybe overly clever for this character.
What do you guys think at home?
Please let me know.
DM me.
This guy's crazy.
I don't know what he's talking about.
Wait a second.
This guy's stupid.
What the hell?
Alright, I'm gonna go sleep for a little bit and then maybe I'll come to your house and I might, I don't know, I might help you.
Yeah, me too.
Okay. Well, hot dog, that's real nice.
Anyway, I'm gonna just stare here until I get hungry again.
Alright, good luck.
Since we're about to go to bed, I want to use my last spell slot, so I'm just gonna cast Detect Magic on him just to see what happens.
Mm-hmm.
I just want to see if he's magical at all.
Okay, uh, yeah, for sure.
So, um, I mean, it's any presence of magic within 30 feet of you.
So, uh, just zilch on him.
He is just, he is awesome.
I was hoping maybe there was like a curse making him stupid that we could like shortcut the
whole quest thing, but...
No, that's not quite what it is.
But uh, there's, uh, and then as far as 30 feet around you, right, so magical.
is
in
that's it.
Ok before I go to bed I go up to the bartender and I say, "Hey man, I remember you had an
issue earlier, I mean I just detected some magic from that table over there, so I just
wanted to give you a heads up before I go to sleep, so you know, stay safe down here."
He sort of nods at you in appreciation.
Thanks.
And uh, yeah.
Let you go.
Yeah, you guys wanna go to sleepy time?
I go to sleepy time.
Yeah, you guys go to bed.
Yeah.
Um, uh, it's gonna be, uh, uh, like basically just one gold piece in total for all of you
to stay here.
Um, so it's pretty, pretty cheap to be honest.
Um, but it's actually not cheap, but gold pieces are worth a lot.
So you guys are just kind of rich right now.
Um, yeah.
So yeah.
Uh, okay.
Okay, so yeah, you guys get up next morning.
You can go downstairs, you can hang out in the end room
we just went to.
We have a pillow fight first thing.
Yeah, super, yeah, in our underwear.
Yeah, sexy.
I'm having so much fun, all the feathers get in my teeth.
Oh my God.
This is exactly what I needed.
It's beautiful.
This is this is the worst.
I did not sign up for this.
So hard with the pillow. OK.
Yeah, it's like a roll attack roll. All right.
I six. I'm this nice. That's fine.
Yeah. Sullivan just like ducks out of the way.
Yeah. And he's like, OK, I'm having fun.
I like what I thought.
Yeah. I get in your underwear.
Yeah, he does.
And you see, there's just a child in the room also
go to the other room.
OK, or the hallway, whatever that shit is.
It's a hallway, but it's kind of just a long room.
Are you still talking to me? Get the fuck out there.
Oh, you know.
Yeah. So the prince goes out the hallway.
You guys have a sexy pillow fight.
Yeah. Nice. Awesome.
That kills about eight hours.
So it's cool. It's afternoon.
Perfect.
And you guys go downstairs after you've done.
Timothy is still there.
And he goes, I'm hungry.
And like I go like that.
And he goes to the bar, says, can I have Timothy stew and Otto's there?
He's like, yeah, well, yeah, we'll get you Timothy stew.
And he turns, he goes, Marge, make the beef stew.
And just yeah, he gets like a just a slop of beef stew.
And he picks he looks at he looks at a spoon for like a minute
and then puts it down and picks up a fork and starts eating.
And he sees you guys come down and he says, Oh, fellas,
I'm so glad you're here.
I forgot to go home last night, but here I am.
Would you like to accompany me, accompany me, accompany?
Oh, well, I guess.
Yeah, I'm just not going to try out that word ever again.
All right.
It's a bit due north, but that's all right.
I hope that's not out of the way of your journey, wherever you all were headed.
and
100% simple jack type.
Oh, no. Yeah.
Well, no, Jack.
No, well, not like that.
Just like the way he looks.
OK, Tim's that are right.
You look simple.
So yeah, you guys are heading over to what he called was idiot village.
And you see him like licking his finger and putting it up like he thinks that helps him with directions.
He's like occasionally looking at rocks and seeing where moss is.
and eventually you guys get to get to the town itself.
And you do see that it does seem to be beset by something it is a quaint little farm town.
And there is a lot of just ragged people, you get to the gate, it was a cut open, and
you see a sign there but says needed would sorry will repair.
all
how to do anything. They're all walking around with untied shoelaces, they're tripping all
the time, they're stepping on rakes, they're chasing around squealing little pigs and losing
in those chases. You see Timothy, "Well, this is our town. As you can see, we're in a little
bit of dire straits over here. I'm really glad y'all decided to come though. I would offer
you food to eat but right now everything we have is pretty much really bad.
We'll take it.
Alright well would you like I got I'm supposed to bring y'all to the mayor of Idiot Village
if you'd like me to do that for you.
Alright bring us there and then go get us some food.
You got it.
And so you go to the to the mayor's house in Idiot Village and you see that it's just the
the scaffolding with the door.
Um, and Timothy knocks and you guys can see the mayor.
Who's just like a fatter, older Timothy.
And here's a knock and you see him like put away something he was looking at on his desk
and just goes, uh, you guys can see him doing this, uh, come in.
And, uh, Timothy, uh, first thinks it's a push door, but he realizes it's a pull.
And then he walks in.
And he says, "Mr. Mayor, I've brought with me here four brave adventurers and a child
who've decided that they can help us rid the town of the plague and the failure of the crops
and maybe even find our village idiot."
And he says, "Well, that would be just great.
It's nice to meet all of you.
My name is Mayor.
I had another name but I forgot it the second I became mayor.
How y'all doing?
Well I got some bad news for you.
You're gonna forget your other name now because I've actually, I'm here to become the mayor.
Oh, well, uh, well that won't work because I'm the mayor.
How do you mean?
We're having an election.
I was sent here to become the mayor.
Yeah, roll persuasion.
11.
Okay, he's like, Damn, we're having an election.
Okay.
Shoot.
Can we have, like, a debate?
Make some speeches?
Yes.
Absolutely.
Perfect.
Yeah.
All right.
I love that.
You know, I've won every year since I was four years old.
I'm really excited to have a new challenger.
Okay, hold on.
I'll gather everyone in the town and you see him go to a conch
and he blows in it and it just spit comes out.
He's like, I'll just go try to talk to everyone.
And he runs out of his house, ignoring the door,
just running past the scaffolding to go talk to everyone
in the town.
- I go through his desk immediately.
- Yeah, you see a, what he was looking at
that he was ashamed of was just like a doll
that has no clothes on.
- Give me that, I might need to cast a spell with that
or something later.
Yeah, you also sorry if you keep you can keep like looking through his desk and when you
do you also see on it you also see on top of his desk a resignation letter.
And when you read it, it says like, Dear, dear Ted.
Your name is Ted, it's not mayor and I'm not calling you that anymore.
I've decided to leave this town.
I decided to leave this town because you people don't appreciate everything I do for you.
You'll see that you'll see the results of that upon my absence.
Don't come looking for me.
Don't come find me and like see you later.
Never liked you anyway.
And it says your beloved village idiot.
Wow.
Well, we found him.
He's stuck to the we can probably figure this out after we resolve the whole election thing.
And this shit can wait.
Oh wow, you guys can read that?
We've been having an awful lot of trouble.
It just showed up on the desk one day around the same time our village idiot disappeared.
Yeah, this is the letter that says that Patrick Yodar is supposed to become mayor.
You didn't get the memo and you received it? Yeah, see maybe that's why I'm here to become the mayor. No fucking shit!
Yeah.
Boy, okay. All right. That makes sense. Now. I should tell the mayor to throw off the turd
Just not do the election and just make you mayor
Yeah, we could still do the debate though. Yeah, let's still go through with that
Oh, I guess it's all good sportsmanship in that that makes sense to me
Okay
So should we just fast forward to that or do you guys want to do something here? It's just fast for you got it
Yeah, anytime. Yeah. Okay, cool. Yeah, and so uh
uh... a whole town is gathered most of them are facing the correct direction
uh... the pulpit
and that is patrick gilbert
and uh... mayor or i guess ted is his name
are standing on top of uh... uh... are you guys you standing behind a podium
can i be a moderator
yeah absolutely you immediately convinced him that you would be the most
impartial judge uh... you know
and i don't know what he's got on the
I'm the person who gets called on in the audience to ask questions.
They call on me every time I ask a bunch of different questions.
Perfect.
Okay.
Yeah.
That makes sense to me.
Okay, cool.
So, yeah, you see...
Yeah, so, yeah, go, moderate.
Moderate.
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen, to the mayor debate.
I'm your moderator, Christopher, and I'd like to start with some questions.
This first question is for both candidates.
What hotel did I stay at last night?
That is the Strange Penis Inn.
Okay.
Gosh.
And the mayor, now your turn to answer.
Well I have no idea where you stayed last night.
I mean, ladies and gentlemen, the results are speaking for themselves right now.
Oh dear, I did not look good when I said that.
I would just like to say for every question that he gets wrong, he loses one LL's point.
I'm raising my hand in the air.
I'm waving my hand around.
I'm jumping up and down to be called on.
He gets to lose his podium.
He doesn't get to have a podium now.
It's like hangman, but he loses one article of clothing for everything that he gets wrong.
Oh, it's like strip hangman.
I remember this.
Yeah.
Everybody played that.
Absolutely. I got robbed that way.
Hey, dirt guy up in the front, you can say a question.
Hi, my name's Timothy and I'm from this village.
My question is for...
That's... My name's Timothy!
Get that guy out of here!
Get that hippie out of this fuckin' debate!
Oh, okay. I'll go back to the strange penis to have some more stew.
I have I have to find adventurers. I have two questions. Uh my first question is for mayor.
How would you plan to solve the plague that is attacking this village and where can the
village idiot be found and how will you solve all the solutions to all the problems that
are happening here? That's an excellent question and I understood one quarter of it. Let me
me do my best here.
First of all, the way that I was...
Okay, what's up?
I'm the mayor.
Oh, no, that's not your name.
My name's mayor.
Your name is...
...Tempest-y?
Your name is Ted.
My name is now...
You watch as something unlocks in his brain and he's like, "My name's Ted?"
name is Ted and my name is Mayor Patrick Yodar and I am now the mayor of Idiot Village.
My name is Ted.
I think I kind of walked into something here that I don't realize.
I forgot that my name was Ted.
Thank you so much.
Anyway, my second question is for Patrick Yodar.
What's your favorite color?
My favorite color is green.
That's a good color answer.
Um, wait, wait, uh, uh, okay, hold on.
You're the mayor now.
You got to solve this problem then.
Because I don't know where the village idiot is.
He deputized him.
Deputized.
You're the sheriff.
Oh, really?
Now make him make it his responsibility.
Delegate.
And it's your responsibility to do that.
Callum's name is Sheriff Doopki.
Your name is Sheriff Poopy Dookie.
Okay, I'll take it.
No way! That's your name?
Okay, well...
Oh my god!
If I had to guess where that, the village idiot is, uh, well, I guess it's kind of funny.
He kind of wandered into this town a few years ago.
And we were, now that I think about it, we were sort of in a similar state back then
as well.
But he does have this cave he likes to go into sometimes.
he
I have no that that I cannot help you with.
I have just found out what North is yesterday.
So it's is it North?
That's why I really I really cannot help you there.
As the mayor, somebody has to tell me where this cave is right now.
I'm gonna freak out.
Everyone's like, oh, you could freak out.
fifth
and he's like, "And maybe it's, uh, maybe it's, maybe it's up?"
- Maybe it's up.
All right, this is actually,
this is like one of the worst things
I could have asked everybody.
- Maybe it's down.
Yeah, oh, it could be under the ground.
- Oh, a cave underground would be great.
- That would not be a cave, that would be a hole.
- I've been in a hole.
I've never,
I've never seen a hole in my life and I plan for plan on it neither.
They're just like completely unhelpful, completely stupid, impossible to reason with.
How are we going to find this fucking cave?
I put some dirt in my mouth to commune with Dogen the Dirt God.
So you know about like dirt right?
So it stands to reason you might know about holes in dirt?
Yeah, pretty much.
So how about caves? You know, caves?
Caves? Yeah, I'm pretty familiar with caves.
I mean, I also I want to I'm getting so sick of it.
Can you just speak normally?
You know, I've always I've always got to have dirt in my mouth, man.
That's just sort of how I'm made.
All right. It's really pissing me off, though.
I mean, I know I'm your paladin, but, you know, I'm asking you nicely to knock it off
because I can't knock it off.
This is kind of the way I am.
Well, I'm good.
I'm just not going to commune with you that often then because I mean, which is part of
OK, I haven't been.
You know, where's the where's the cave?
Just tell me that.
But where's you know what?
Right.
Can you write it in the dirt in front of me or something?
Just make a map of all the caves nearby.
I just don't want to hear your voice anymore.
OK, me off.
All right. I'll do.
OK, hold on.
So. All right.
Let me try to get a sense of the area.
And yeah, he sort of is like
you start to see on the ground in front of you.
Like only you can see it for some reason,
like a drawing of a cave that is a bit due west of here.
And it's just sort of is like a little hole. And then you see another cave. It's a bit further
north. Those are the two caves. I see about there's like two caves nearby here. Part of the
rock faces around the West. Oh, my God. Okay. I spit out the dirt. I hang up on him. Okay.
OK guys, so there's one cave north and there's one west.
I don't know which it is, but I think it might be north.
They said they learned about north the other day and they said up first.
North is kind of up.
That's a good point.
All right, let's go north.
All right.
Yeah, and we'll figure out
what that means next time.
Yeah, that effect.
Perfect
I go on and on, can't understand how I last so long
I must have super powers, rap 225,000 hours Get a calculator, do the math
I made a thousand songs that made you move, yeah
And for the last three hundred months I made sixteen albums with me on the front
And they bomb, where you get your beats?
I heard ninety-three rappers say
[BLANK_AUDIO]