[Music]
Last time on Trebuchet Village, our heroes awoke from a night of bronzing each other's body parts
and having some good fun playing music.
Their fun that next morning was rudely interrupted by Thorax,
who just wanted them to get ready for the fight in the arena.
At this suggestion, the boy said, "Well, why don't you fight with us?"
and Thorax reluctantly agreed that maybe he should.
On their way there, they experienced Gal Gadot in more of its grandeur,
experiencing the kind of speciesism that hurts someone like Evil Stevel being a dwarf.
Which he got full on from the shaman, Giggy, who was a member of Thorax's gang.
Upon arriving at the arena, the boys fought Ola, the orc, to get her on their side so that they can get the deal.
A confusing fight where much was espoused about love, who was in love with whom,
Who is a better DM, patches or scratches, some body horror, dark sexual behavior, the things you expect from the show at this point.
Almost, I think all of it.
We're gonna have to run that back.
Can we bring Scratches back to talk about this?
However, the gang easily bested Ola and agreed to her offer over the walrus, which wasn't
so much an offer as much as a guarantee of two fish being a part of the equation at some
point.
However, once the boys left the arena, the strange, surreal, and frankly overwritten
feeling swept over them, as they realized that the nasty shaman Gigi and the prince,
whom they've neglected for some time, vanished during the fight.
What will they do?
Who knows?
that's for sure all right so that's basically what happened so you guys are
sort of the first to recognize that the Prince Prince Jumanji is missing right
and was and so was the shaman those are the two facts you know everyone else is
kind of still like cheering you guys on is like so happy you made the deal it's
a big deal yada yada yada guys guys I'd all over here
Come here. I think the prince kidnapped the shaman. I thought they went separate ways. I thought they weren't even together. I don't
Did you guys want me in the huddle? Get that get out of here guys?
I think you get your wires crossed. I'm there's something. Oh god. What happened last night? My my brain is
is ruined
Last night was a... Oh God!
Last night was a...
a scroll for real. I think the shop...
Real shit. Last night was a
scroll for real for real.
Alright. Uh...
Okay, so I'm gonna stand
just by everybody else. Yeah, we're just kidding. Get in the
huddle. Okay. Alright, get out of the
huddle. Alright, hold on. Here, you can get in the
huddle, but you gotta get in the middle.
Mm-hmm. Yeah. Uh, alright.
He does that.
We're gonna do something.
guys let's link arms and spin around him why cuz it'll scare him
I can hear all of these things
would you be scared if we spun?
if you spun around?
yeah you that is
I was in the tea tub
let's just go
I think I'll be alright
start spinning Sullivan
are you guys talking about everything
that'll show you Sullivan
I'm sorry
I think so we got to find the shaman or we got to find the boy. We have to rescue the shaman
We got to rescue the shaman from the boy. Cuz that is it. Here's the thing. We've been hanging out with him
He's a monster. We've been hanging out here for like two weeks most annoying kid in the world. He didn't really talk much
No, he didn't talk Sullivan
Weird though, I don't think he was like he's five
He's strong cuz he's a Nard, but I don't think he was you know, I mean
Better the situation he could be like 80 and Nard years. We don't really know. It's also not well
He was it was never like one of the guys
No
Me oh, yeah, I'm thinking of you. Okay. Yeah, just checking. Yeah
He should have been more careful. All right, here's my thing just gain a bunch of weight. No, we gonna pick you up
If you're big and fat and huge it's actually a good idea. Yes. All right. So once we get the kid
We're gonna feed him full of food. This will never happen again. Yeah, we're gonna that's a good plan. It's basically anchor him
Yeah, I don't know. All right. I'm not gonna say no to anything
All right, we got to figure out where this kid took this shaman though. Okay. Well, I was a kid
Probably the playground. Yeah, let's go candy store right now. I'm gonna go to a candy store
I mean, where would you go if you was a kid? Is there any we have a wizard?
We could ask him should I roll investigation or something?
Yeah, he's at the candy store
Yeah, it's totally at the candy store you like and like I think with your I think your intelligence is I'll double check I have
your
Shit up here, too
Yeah, so you're yeah, you got like well actually I should say cuz you chose the um
the
intelligence is the inquisitive feet
So I was really just for perception checks. Okay, so yeah, it's just a it's a five so with that I mean
You can see that they're not there. It's you can't really even make out. I can actually see well
Well you could just see that they're not there.
You could just see that they're not there.
I thought the candy store was far away.
I didn't know.
No, no, no, no, you could see that the two, the shaman and the nephew, that's what I'm
calling him, the nard, Prince Jumadjirn out there, that's really it though.
Like you can't really tell if there was a struggle or like where they would have went
or whatever.
Should I roll again?
I'm gonna roll.
Okay.
Investigation here.
That's a 16.
Okay.
Plus what?
It's at 17 minus 1.
Okay cool.
So, yeah, I mean with a 16, yeah, so you, Patrick, Yodar, sort of walk in a small circle around
the group and you just sort of expand the circle and start to notice more things.
You see that, you can see, because it's an arena, it's sort of like a dusty floor, you
can see like, that there was like, some sort of like dust displacement, dust, dirt displacement,
like which you would be not happy about.
Yeah, I'm not happy about seeing that.
You're unhappy that this is up your alley.
I'm putting all the dirt back into the hole.
Yeah, and you could see that there was like, obviously, at some point there was dragging,
and then you see the tracks like stop suddenly towards like further down towards where the
exit is from this part of the arena.
But you see like a struggle at first and then it's just gone.
Okay, yeah.
What'd you see?
I don't know.
You've been investigating again.
I think they went out the exit.
Yeah, I didn't even think to look there.
They might have teleported though.
Can he do that?
Who?
What, the shaman? I mean, I have to imagine he's got some sort of magic, you know.
Oh, so now we're imagining stuff, is that it?
No, wait, no.
Why don't we use our actual brain?
Oh, no, I know, let's play pretend, that'll solve the problem.
That's a lot to solve.
Okay, Orc-Lock-Horns, go ahead, do your thing.
Alright, first of all, I only- I just finished- don't spoil anything, 'cause I just finished reading the fifth book in that series.
I mean, it is incredible.
It is phenomenal.
The twists, that orc lock.
He finds so much stuff.
Don't tell him, because I only got- I'm only a little bit behind.
And when they find out that it was the butler-
Oh my god- WAIT, WHAT THE HELL?!
Don't tell him which room or which weapon he used.
No.
Use the butterfly knife.
How did you-
In the butterfly room.
You all read the book in the book. I'm yeah, that's what we did last night. All we did was sit up and we found it in your backpack
We only read the last chapter oil it you guys made me keep the eye patches on I couldn't see the whole night
We thought you would make a funny sleeping pirate
Okay, was that funny fuck no you know funny
all right, so
Yeah, I mean like you can obviously
Yeah, I'll go up to fuck you. Fuck you. There's other other people who were there too obviously like you know tip for tat
We're back here of the other
Enterprise guy was here. You know there were there was people here. You can talk to and see if they saw anything
All right, mm-hmm Garth see Enterprise mm-hmm Garth see Enterprise. I walk up to him, okay
Hi
Never mind. I'm sorry, okay
I'm about this can I spit game to fuck you?
You can can you spit game to him? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I think so. Yeah
Go for it. Hey, fuck you
How you living
I'm good. I mean, this is fantastic news, right? You guys got money got the deal
I think some things right have to be finalized, but it's fantastic. Yeah, I mean, it's alright, but you know, we got a problem, right?
No, I you're basically your brother
basically like
Took my son and shit
What remember that little ass kid with me? Yeah. Yes. Yes. Yes my son. That's your son. Yeah
I don't your son. It was not that your son guys. I'm trying to confuse him look
I mean the kid I talked to the kid he he he wasn't that bright
He kind of just told me he was the prince. I didn't tell my son stupid to my face. Is that it's not your son
I'm just trying to jigs up. He's not my son
Yeah, he's my son. He's somebody's son. We that's the whole thing
Which one of us we're daddy gone he's dog
say
Any we found out he was Dogen's son - and his son and he was my son the fucking sky man took him
the scam
Took him
Okay, all right, I'm starting to see how this happened maybe okay, um, oh
Oh fuck, um, who knows? Who knows?
You do now.
Should we tell everybody?
No, now I'm implicated.
My son has been kidnapped!
You see everyone's like-
Andy's my son too!
Andy's Dogen's son also!
And that's okay!
Everyone's like, nodding, like,
"Okay, yeah, okay, okay."
You see Thorax kinda like,
like, hears that and is like, "Alright."
And looks around and like, looks away.
Thorax did it. Thorax doesn't really know what that means. Thorax definitely did it. He was the only one who acted differently.
So he's suspect number one. Not a bad point. I just thought you would be concerned if Thorax could tell or not, but
could tell whether we knew that he took the kid. And Thorax is his son,
too, and he's his son and my son. And we thank you for being here, Thorax. And we love you,
like, you're, we love you the most.
Alright, get over here, man. I gotta tell you a secret and shit.
Is this code what do you guys do? Yeah, we're talking basically, you remember that little ass that little they're like really short guy
We lose with the prince. He really how did you know that? He just told me damn it. I didn't tell anybody lose lips
Yeah, his lips. God damn it. Well, I did tell my I did tell my shit. Who did you tell?
Well, I told my I told a few though a few of the guys in the gang. You tell the shaman
Giggy, yeah, he's like
Get him back here, what the hell?
What do you mean get him back here?
Call him on your scroll phone.
He's like looking around.
What did we have here?
We didn't really have anything but I'm scrolling through my contacts.
I don't know where he is.
God damn it.
What do you mean?
What about Giggy?
He stole my kid!
Do you have whatsapp or something?
You see fuck you comes up and goes
The shaman took the boy.
Oh. Fuck.
Yeah.
It's what we said, like, a hundred times.
Oh. Okay. Uh...
A wizard says that you get it.
Fucking piece of shit.
No.
Okay. Uh...
Okay, we gotta, we gotta, we gotta...
Don't tell anybody else.
Let's just try to figure this out.
Sullivan, come over here.
He already knows.
I'm right next to you, man.
What?
Can you get Tit and Tet?
Yeah, sure. Okay.
He's he's the rex like puts his hand on Sullivan's head and stop him from walking
He's like we're not gonna tell anybody else. Hey, Ted. Come here. Yeah, what do you want? Fuck you?
Fuck you, too
Kids missing
What?
Your son is missing. We took your son. We kidnapped your son. We're gonna eat him. Okay
Hold an insight check. Oh
It's got text my mom's getting chick-fil-a that's huge 17. Yeah, dude. I'm so hype. Whoa 17. Yeah, okay
Hold on let me finish this let me make sure that I get the chick-fil-a I want
Sorry, he's getting paid in chick-fil-a, okay, okay
um it's with a 17 you can tell that saying the words like kidnapped and like
son and like the word kidnap kind of made it like perk a bit you don't know why
but like a 17 is high enough that like why did you why did your eyebrow nice
- Where are you guys going, Patrish?
Now we have to kill them.
- What do my eyebrows do, what?
- Your eyebrow did a thing when I said the word kidnap.
- Come on, Tid, let's go.
- Hey, Ted. - No, no, no.
- I already beat the fuck out of you, I think.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, yeah, you did, actually.
I don't really wanna deal with you anymore.
- Yeah, what do you know about the wizard, or the shaman?
Or, and do you know anything about this wizard
that's standing next to me? - Look, I don't know
anything about any of this shit.
You see, Ted-- - Do you know anything
about this guy?
- Who are you pointing at?
- The wizard. - Sorry, I didn't mean
you that um I mean we we sort of exchange pleasantries backstage but um why are you
that's what they're calling it these days okay that's pretty good come on it's not bad though
it's not bad at all actually it's pretty fun um you see tickle what's it to you what happened
to the stupid kid oh shit you're getting an attitude yeah you're coming with us
I'm not going anywhere!
I flick his nose again.
You have-
No!
You have to tell-
I'm gonna bar his nose.
You have to-
You better-
If you don't take that dancing sponge idea off the table-
Alright, fine.
It already got sold.
We already sold it, man.
Yeah, we don't give a cramp about that.
I flick his nose again.
You're not-
Stop flicking my nose!
You know, we-
You're not gonna do anything-
You're not gonna do anything with it!
Stop flicking my nose!
You're not gonna do anything with the dancing sponge idea!
Here.
I'm gonna do it.
- I'm not gonna do anything with the dancing sponge idea.
- Here, what if we gave you a different idea
that's 25 million times better?
- Yeah, we'll come up with an idea
that's way better than the dancing sponge right now.
- No!
- Dancing water.
- Give me my dancing sponge idea.
- How about a hot wing restaurant
where all the women working there got big ass boobs?
- All right, wait, hold on, that's my idea.
- You did not come up with that, I came up with that.
- You see him like, have like a
special moment alone in his heart
as the greatest business idea that's ever existed
just infected his mind.
- It's so smart.
- Comes raw from evil Sievel's brain like,
oh yeah, this would be a tight thing to have.
And he's like, you'll give me that idea?
- Consider it done.
- Okay.
You can flick my nose again at this point.
- No.
(laughing)
Enough flicking.
All I wanna flick is the truth.
- The shaman, he was getting a little antsy backstage.
He started talking about the terrifier this, that, he seemed like one of those, you know,
offshoots of the main church, kind of fanatic types.
Anyway, he started to grab the boy and...
Ah, he's a pedophile, goddammit.
Fortat and I tried to do something, but he pushed us away.
I was so pissed at you guys I didn't even want to tell you this.
And then he, I don't know, he must have cast something and sort of vanished away, and I
saw him a little bit down the ways, and I don't know where he went.
Which way down the ways? Did he cast a specific spell that lets you know where he was going?
Based on his description of like him
Teleporting basically like a short distance you would assume. It's like misty step or something
So some sort of like short distance teleportation spell that he's able to do quickly to just get him away from people
You wouldn't know what else he used but like like if you kept investigating down the way you would see like another
yeah so it's like and but but tip would be able to say um well um I mean I I
tried to go out and see where he was heading it looked like he was heading a
bit a bit further north in town okay all right I mean you gave me an amazing idea
I'm not gonna lie is that is that everything you need it's not even what a
flick sounds like yeah that's what it sounds like on his nose cuz he's like a
- Like a pig or something?
- I'm a goblin.
What the fuck?
- Yeah, there's like pig guy.
- He's a goblin.
- Oink, oink.
- We look the same.
- You guys here just oink, oink over and over again?
- Okay, well I told you what I know.
- All right.
- All right, I'm gonna just walk away.
- Now go, now go, listen. - Thank you for the idea.
- I do get to come on my table when I go to the restaurant.
- Horrible, but if this goes as well
I think it does of course you'll get to do that hold on and you got to clean it up like a
bartender's clothes and shop
Rubbing a rag into my cum
And that's all you know and that's the rule. I haven't okay fine. I had it's a really good idea
I have another idea. I can give you if you can tell me anything else
He's all out of June. I don't really know anything else, and I am all juice - the other guy tat when somebody juice this
Ted what did you do you see the same thing pretty much?
Yeah, I mean, I guess the only thing that I can maybe add if I could add anything to this would be that um
From my time in this in this city there are only
Okay, you're flicking my nose now. You know you I think I don't you you really hurt me last time so okay
There are there are
three main churches in this town
and the only one that goes north is St. Anthony's Parish. The other two are
much bigger operations so if I had to guess where a fanatical terrifier type of
guy would be going he might be going to one of the smaller churches for the
terrifier. And for that I give you an idea half-price Tuesdays, half-price
wings on Tuesday happy hour I mean happy hour I mean whatever it was a wings are
half the kids the wings are half priced as well as the drinks I mean you guys
are assholes but the kid doesn't need to suffer I guess so it's great idea though
half price on happy hour I'll keep that in mind you think that was a good idea
I thought it was a really good idea.
Bitch.
So yeah, I mean you guys got some
information here.
All right, so to the candy store we go.
Yeah, you guys want to head to the church or do you want to verify the information or do you want to like check with
Fuck You spells? I believe him. I think we should go to the church. Yeah.
You think you want to head there? Yeah. Can we talk to Fuck You?
Mm-hmm. Does he have like a clairvoyant type thing? Yeah, he has some divination magic that you could use if you want to do that
Yeah, I'm thinking maybe
Talk to him. Hey, bitch. I mean fuck you. Yeah, well
What's up?
You have any type of
So there's like three churches in town. I just want to make sure we're going to the right one
Sarah any kind of fucking thing that you can do you have like maybe a spell where you know everything
No, right
They like a pill that you can take where you can use more than 10% of your brain that you take right now. Why?
Why which why to which one which question you better answer my question you got three seconds why?
If you can't answer the why it's not you're not very good at divination magic. Okay. Well because no wait
I don't have to answer that question. Okay, look, I can walk.
I can travel with you for a bit.
And then I have some spells that if I'm within the range, am I boring you?
Yawning? Am I boring you?
Nah, I don't know.
I just don't want to.
He puts yawning in front of me.
I mean, I don't give a crap about this wizard stuff. I just want to.
Okay, fine. Just let me travel with you and then I'll cast a spell.
I just want to find this kid so I can get. What do we get? Money or something?
You're going to get something from him.
Return the prince to the king is gonna be something probably some sort of reward, right?
Maybe he'll chop Sullivan's head off in a guillotine. Now that would be something and he gives us four seats
Now it suck for me. I didn't say I said it would be something. We could eat Sullivan's legs fried.
No!
No, that's also-
That hurt me in a specific way. Didn't you two used to be really nice to him?
This is how I'll change something so after that's that night when we partied and couldn't remember anything that happened for some reason
I hate him now. Yeah, I don't know why
To be in the same room. Yeah, it's just like I
Second of every day and maybe that'll change
After two more days, hopefully I'm I'm a superstar now so I get to treat people like shit. That's fair
I'm a musical super life. Well, hmm. Okay. Do we want to go to the church then?
Yeah, it's all of it. Okay. Yes, you guys walk to the church walk a bit north in the city
I
Would say that if you want like fuck you could cast
Clairvoyance
There's locate creature, but that's within a thousand feet which is like kind of a gamble
I'm gonna give him like one opportunity to a divination spell. Okay, so that's a bit of a gamble
So, can we use it to locate the boy?
Yeah, that's the thing. You can do it to locate the boy or the shaman, but it's only within a thousand feet.
So if you're not, you can go right next to the church and do it, and if you're wrong, then that's like your divination spell.
But, um, you could also, like, um, you know, cast clairvoyance, that's a mile long radiance.
Yeah.
And that'll just give you, it'll basically just give you, like, a sensor that remains in the place of this area.
So like you can you can sort of know what's going on in the area, but I'm trying to think
of what other.
Do you think if I ask my God for guidance would he know anything?
Yes, and that's something he could also do.
He could give you guidance too.
Fuck you where he gives you like an extra d4 on that roll.
So if you want to do that.
I would say we can make that into a because you're a paladin we can make that like a straight
charisma check for getting guidance from your God.
I want to do something like that.
Should I do that?
I think like you'll get, I think like, you know, I'm being a little, being a little metagamey
here, but I would say like, let's say like you get to, consulting with your God is one
of the things that, that fuck you can like help you with.
And then if that works out, it works out.
If it doesn't, it doesn't.
But that doesn't cost the divination spell.
No, but that would cost, that would be like him giving you the divination spell.
Oh, okay.
All right.
- Yeah.
- Okay, I don't know.
- You can also like go to the church and investigate
and then get a divination spell too.
- Yeah, let's just go and investigate
and then figure out what to do from there.
- Yeah, I would say you could do that too.
So yeah, you guys can go to the St. Anthony's Parish.
The north end of town is a little--
- That's just a normal church name.
- Yeah, the north end of town,
well, there's three churches in the city.
There's, where is my,
Yeah, there's the Church of Horror, the Blood and Guts Cathedral, and then St. Anthony's Parish is the third.
[laughter]
So...
It's in the north end of town. It's a part of the larger collection of terrifier denominations.
It's a more mild one, but it's also the one that's least sort of like overseen.
So either weird stuff can happen there or too nice stuff can happen there, which is frowned upon by the church at large.
The north end of town is a little less developed than the south end.
Where the south end has a lot of high highs and low lows.
So you guys, where you are, you're sort of in the town center in the hotel, which happens to be the south end of town.
You know how sometimes towns are like the hub is in the south end.
That's sort of where you guys are, near those main churches.
And there's a lot of like really really rich members of the town and really really poor.
Here it's a little bit more like lower middle class, working class, kind of like solidly across.
It's developed around a few like-minded Terrafire-born who were careful to align themselves with the actual trading necessary to keep a city thriving.
So other people were just like killing and looting and fucking each other and this was a town that was like,
"What if we like grew plants and traded with other towns?" and that's how this got on the map more.
more. If it weren't for people like Kevin Ritterfin and some of the greedier officials, a place
like this would be thriving. For now, it's merely quaint with minimal bloodshed and even
fewer slaves. St. Anthony's Parish is the largest church in the area. So there's, you know,
there's smaller ones, but that's like the major church. So yeah, you guys approach the
church and you see like a, a, a doddering old, a, a yuan-tee. So they're like a snake people.
And you see them, you see them, you see him just sort of like raking the leaves out front
kind of like a jump in the leaf pile yeah yeah I woke up to my go what can I do to
help you boys you know that's not all we say I'm doing a leaf angel okay welcome
to St. Anthony's parish. How can I help you boys? Are you Anthony? No. My name is Satsu.
Your name is Tattoo? Satsu. Oh, Satsu. Satsu. Say not so. Satsu. Satsu. Satsu? It's not
so bad. Satsu? Susu? Oh, you must be that famous rock star. Yeah, that's my son. Patrick
And me you may have recognized me already so
He's he's old
May have something about a hostel or
You more high-end a
Big hostel
So basically we're looking for a child.
Two local celebrities.
Yeah, we're two celebrity men looking for a young boy.
And he looks at Sullivan and he's like, "A meal."
(laughing)
You can't eat him.
I'm just kidding.
Yeah, we're gonna eat him.
At the end of our adventure.
Oh, good, good.
He's like, "Oh, finders keepers, I see."
Yeah.
Yeah, this is him marinating.
We basically, we let him walk around with us
to like, so is his, you know, to get his meat ready.
Like so he gets lots of exercise.
Yeah, in a couple days we're gonna...
We're gonna make it team jack.
Extremely free range.
We're gonna break his legs and keep him in a cage so he gets real fat.
Yeah.
We're basically gonna hold him upside down and tear him down the middle like a bone tomahawk.
And I'm gonna make an amazing sauce to go with this.
Yeah.
We're gonna let him marinate in our spit.
This is the...
Oh!
Don't, don't you dare wipe that off.
One second, I'll baste him.
It's all the flavors in there.
And I scoop the spit up.
Okay.
Wait, why did I agree to that?
I scooped the spit up that dripped off him and I put it back on top of them like I'm basically
We'll do that every 10 minutes. Yeah
that's
cool
Thank You snake listen yeah, you're invited to the to the big dinner if you if you listen have you seen a
Freaky little fucker and maybe a bigger
Fucker yeah like a shaman
That's the word. I'm looking for
The prodigal son Gigi he returned today. Yes, his name's Gigi
Gigi Giggity Giggity. No
Not like quagmire. Hey, you know squagmire. Yes, his name's Sato family or
It's not as good as the orcs
You know, they have three
Orc manatees?
Did you guys ever-
They write all their jokes!
Did you guys ever see that- that- that spin-off, Cleave Realm?
*snort*
The Cleave Realm show?
Nah, I didn't.
Yeah. I- I actually- but I- I haven't seen that one, but I did watch Orc American Dead.
*laughter*
So anyway...
That was fun.
Well...
Yes, he came back today.
He...
He did have, um...
A sack with him, but uh...
I got a sack on me check these out. He does have a humongous sack. Was the sack
saying... Was the sack saying little ass kid shit? It was wriggling around. Like a
little ass kid did? There's a chance there was... He... How long ago was this?
It was about an hour or so maybe. He he's always been weird. Is he gone or? He left
our parish to travel with Thorax. He said he was on a mission from from the
Terrifyer but I think he just wanted to loot. Who doesn't? Did he leave the... is he
still here? No he came in and he grabbed something and he left. What'd he grab?
A child. I don't know. I mean... Oh wait he had the child. Why don't you just look at
everything that's in the church and see whatever's not there.
- I guess I could check.
I haven't been, I haven't.
And you see he's like particularly just like rattled
by any form of questioning.
Like he's like getting a little, right?
And you see--
- You're not gonna die, right?
- You see sort of, I'm peeking out from like the church door
you see a very obviously human male wearing an orc mask
And you see him peek out and say,
"Psst, over here.
"What's that orc want?
"Psst, you guys wanna know what happened to Giggy?
"Come here, he doesn't know."
- Okay, so before we go over,
I get on all fours, like a table,
and I look up at one of them,
and I'm motioning to push the old man over.
(laughing)
- Now this guy's my friend.
C.
See? You guys would never do that with me.
Yeah, I would.
7.
It's not even it. It's not even close.
I don't remember how. How do you do it again?
He just reacts to anyone doing C.
He gets very excited.
I can't roll my S's. My bad.
C.
Senior.
Okay.
Guido Ir Elbaño.
in the church all right I'm talking that orc yo orc I'm headed your way and I'm
walking towards you now okay thanks
good we couldn't add those in post and now I'm here what's up okay um I'm glad
you guys are here um my name is Gil um I'm what's it short for just it's just
Gil. What's your last name? Or first name? Is Gil your last name? Gil's my first
name and my only name. Gilbert Arenas? I mean I was raised here. That's your new
name. They tell me I have to wear the mask. You're Gilbert Arenas now.
Gilbert Arenas. I'll take it. Um, Giggy is a bad dude. Thank you for saying that
Gilbert Arenas? I can try to I think I know where he went. There's a small
temple about an hour north of here that's a a Kaiju Manji baby skeleton and
it's a place of worship and I've been seeing a lot of the weirder members of
our church go in and out of there a lot but I just don't want to be implicated in
this and you won't be Gilbert arenas I mean okay I can try to I have a I mean
he goes over to his he's like he starts walking away towards his like yeah it's
like a room like I have like a map as he's walking away I grab his mask off I
say wave check please please please please put it back please put it back
okay this guy's weird. You don't understand, they make me wear it or they say they'll eat me.
Okay, you weird. The people who work here are gonna eat you. Not the people who work, just the people, just a lot of a lot of
people a lot of people in Gal Gadot do not like that I'm human but I was raised
here and I just have to wear this mask forever. If someone would say it's like I
I put my fingers like under the mask.
(gagging)
- That hurt my mouth.
(laughing)
- I think wearing masks is like a prison.
I think people who, I think if you force people to do it.
- Right, yeah.
No, people should not be forced to wear masks.
- Absolutely not. - Absolutely not.
No, it's a form of oppression.
- I think so too.
- And it's disgusting.
- Yes. - I've been saying that.
- And you get sick if you put it on
because it circulates micro bacteria.
- Yeah, and when you take it off, it's healthy.
- I had a funny idea when I came up with it,
I'm seeing the synergy and I'm very excited.
Um, oh here, let me just go get my map.
Plus you can't eat with him on.
Yeah. You see him, as he's walking away he's like,
"That too?" He's like wiggling his finger.
He comes back with a map.
I make a mask.
You make a mask? Out of some
cloth from my shirt.
Let's just do an
intelligence check.
And then I guess a dexterity check.
I like to combine my checks.
Intelligence is an 11.
Dexterity you said?
8.
8?
Okay, it's not a good mask.
It covers for some reason just one of your cheekbones and part of your eye.
So it's just kind of a cloth in the way.
You like my mask?
Take that thing off man.
I just wanted to see if Gilbert or Venus...
Bend the knee.
Ah, cramp.
All these people want you to wear masks here.
Look, okay, here.
I don't want to see you with a diaper on your face ever again.
It wasn't supposed to be, it was supposed to look like him.
Take that diaper off.
We get it, you pooped your mouth.
It was supposed to look like him, I wanted to impress him.
Speaking of him pooping his mouth, he has to roll to see if his bronze butthole kills him.
We're keeping that, that's true.
no i don't know if it's a little reacts that it really is that we thought we did
ok
you can roll just just to see what would have happened
and if he dies in the you've got to get it doesn't know you would have been
fine okay
yeah
okay anyway
you would have been fine but you're always fine
so yeah he's like i i think it's a nice mask uh... uh...
you're flipping us off of the camera for the for the so anyway
You like my mask?
Uh, yeah, yeah, that's fine.
I mean, you could roll an inside check.
You don't even have to, but you certainly could.
Four.
Yeah, you think he likes the mask, I guess.
Yeah, you believe him.
Yeah.
I'm just, I'm like putting my fist in the air, like end of Breakfast Club style.
Yeah, just like, look, look, just, just please, please don't mention me if you run into him
or see him there or see his-
What was your name again?
Gilbert Arenas.
Right, okay.
Okay.
Gilbert Arenas to any of those people.
We won't go up to them and say, "Gilbert Arenas."
- We gotta let them know his new name.
- That's true, okay.
We'll go up to them and we'll say,
just so you know-- - You remember--
- Why do you have to let them know anything about--
- No, no, no, we'll say,
well, listen, listen, listen, hey, calm down, calm down.
We're gonna go up there, we're gonna say--
- We need to know what name not to say.
- Yeah, well, there's a guy you know named--
- Gil, Gilbert. - You guys,
there's a guy named Gil.
- Gilliam. - He's not involved with this.
- Anything-- - Plus, his name is--
His name is Gilbert Arenas now, so...
Mm-hmm.
Just so you know when you go back.
Yeah, we're not gonna, and we're letting you know that we're not gonna say that name.
We didn't see him. We actually saw it on a bulletin board, so we don't even know who he is.
Yeah, he's changed his name and he needs to be on the bulletin board for at least two weeks.
Yeah, we saw it on some kind of wanted poster.
For helping us.
Yeah.
I'm so fucked.
We're just kidding, man.
So you guys can, like, go talk to Fuck You if you want, and want to do a divination thing too.
to just, oh sorry, talk to fuck you if you want to do a divination thing to just to check for
something else or double check things and make sure you know what's going on or you can start
your trek up north outside of Gal Gadot to this baby kaiju manji skeleton temple.
So yeah, you guys can talk to fuck you, see if you want to do that, scry.
Yeah, do we want to scry?
Do we want to wait and save our spell until we get to the other temple?
I think we wait and save our spell.
That's what I was thinking too.
I'm not going to blow my load on this first fucking place dude.
Yeah, true. Come on, bro. That's right. All right, cool. So you guys walk
About an hour's north further north. You're kind of outside the Gal Gadot city limits
You start to see some of the more agrarian settlements that have you know kind of cropped up around there
and
You as you're following the map, you know, it's it's it's kind of going around like a cliffside to like sort of a
little bit more of a like a
wet or darker part of the like near like sort of a long river. Can I spit in it to see how tall the cliff is?
Yeah, okay
I
Took another step 100 200 feet. Okay between 100 and 200 between 100 feet and 200
You can that's as much as you can tell you can buy. I that's like the worst guess ever
between a hundred and two hundred
Could be 150 feet. Mm-hmm. Yeah, I know. Yeah, that's pretty apparent
And as you guys around that you see
Sort of like you haven't seen many of the kaiju manji
Skeletons or skeletal body parts and sent a lot of them seem to have been at some point either
Magically through Ola or just like by happenstance because it's like built on a gravesite of these things all in the city
Constraint the city, but you start to see a few more of these bones and then you see
Further along now, it's sort of it's kind of plateaued as you walk around this cliff
a like full like baby kaiju manji skeleton sitting like cross-legged and
it's holding its head and its head its mouth is like open you could see that
like rock and stone have been built around this and within this thing to
make it into a center of some kind long long abandoned again kaiju manji have
not really been worshipped properly for a long time I guess it's abandoned so
probably should head back yeah I figure I think we've reached the end of town and
we got to go home yeah I think we should cry I think I think we maybe should cry
yeah what is that what do we
joke you know it's real stuff
i'll get this loser frog crying is i'm
well you believe that old time i can't
believe that worked
yeah me too i was kidding haha yeah yeah
all i said was playing
oh yeah none of us good job i said any
tears or frowns on her face or anything
we were just going and you did yeah
we've never cried we don't know we just
doing impression of how i turn around
Yeah, me too! I was doing impression of me also!
Um, you see, uh, fuck you's just like
watching this happen.
Just like, all of you just like, "Okay, um, do you guys want to, uh,
go in there, or... I'm gonna..."
Can you, can we, like, do the spell now to see how many people are in there?
Yeah, I mean, we could try to do...
Okay, they might...
If they're...
They might sense my magic.
You didn't tell us that shit!
Oh come on.
Do a secret spell.
Screw on a different silence spell.
Yeah, that's on your staff.
If I do silence, they would notice that too.
Have you seen John Wick? You know the scene when the two guys are going through the subway and they're shooting at each other?
Yeah, it's a cool scene.
Is that common in Keanu in the second one?
I don't remember. That might be in the third one.
Is it in the third one when Common and Keanu fight?
I don't know.
see them do a song together. So in America I think. Um, what does that have to do with
this? Well do that with a spell so that nobody can tell. Do that with a spell so nobody can
tell. That seems sick. Or you will go to hell. Oh my god. And that will be so swell. I know
some people with record labels, I think we gotta get you. The point of that is that the
other person notice that knows what's going on not the way I remember I just
cast a spell I don't care if they know we're here all right fine one way out of
this place okay so surely wait wait you're right there is one way out of
that place we could maybe set something up we could set a trap or something you
could put a bunch of oil and lighter we could fill I guess the kids in there
never mind watch this I got a great idea do you have a pencil or a piece of
a charcoal? Um, let's just check your inventory. Do you have some painting supplies? Me? I
think you have, you have a flask of oil. Oil paint. Oil paint, yeah, that's a thing. You
just make some paint out of the oil. Oh, you're trying to do a Looney Tunes? I'm trying to,
what's that? But yeah. Oh, what's that? He says John Wick, I can't say Looney Tunes? I
in a hypnotic to frozen state John wick exists in this because it's John wick
exists in this because it's fantasy to them it's like you know you got no
deterrents though that shit yeah well yeah we're all loony toots here
la la la I wasn't talking in game - well you clocked me and I'm giving up on my
I dream of Looney Tune-ins, so hmm.
Cast a spell.
Okay, so which one, do you want to do locate creature,
or do you want to do the one where he has like the
sort of sight for the area?
Can, is there like, for the sight for the area,
would be, we'd be able to see like how many people
are inside and get like a idea of what's going on inside.
Also, could we identify that the boy is one of the
people that we see?
Yeah, I mean, that's, let me see something, so.
Yeah, because I feel like, well I feel like, yeah, I also, I want to know what the boys
there but I also want to know if there's going to be like a hundred people in there before
we go in.
That's what I'm kind of worried about.
So let me, because there are ways to like, to do that.
I want to make sure that I'm like getting the right spell.
Trying to think, because if it's not divination that would have this, there's definitely something
where you can see like within something and see like a group of like see who's in there.
I mean I guess.
Kind of Scry right?
Yeah it's kind of like Scry.
I mean I guess Scry kind of takes care of that.
Let me make sure that it does though.
I want to I haven't like I feel like I very rarely deal in divination so you can see in
here a particular creature you choose that is on the same plane of existence as you.
Target must make a wisdom saving throw yada yada yada yada yada yada yada.
If a target knows you're casting the spell, it could fail.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Oh, so we could scry the... we can scry Jumanji.
Yeah, exactly.
Okay, yeah.
Why don't we just do that to begin with?
Won't we just be able to see wherever he is, then?
Yeah.
Do you want to just do scry?
I think, like, I think, um...
Yeah, I guess I was trying to avoid giving you that ability, but we could do it now.
Well, we went through a whole thing.
You guys went through a whole thing.
We went through hell.
Yeah.
That's right.
I feel like there's got to be a lighter version of Skry. DM me on Discord, please, if you know that.
Let's have him... I mean, he's not going to resist. So, we can have him Skry. He's crying.
He's crying. He's crying. And you see, fuck you, his eyes turn sort of gray.
And he's seeing something. Stop the spell!
And he's like, "Oh, oh, oh.
Okay."
He's scared by me now, because he's like, "What's...
I know now that someone else is watching me."
Um, he's surrounded by many shaman.
Um...
Many shuns?
Shaman.
Ah, I thought you said shuns.
I mean they could I how many we talking
six shans
shaman
seven
ten ten shaman Jesus
They're all in a circle
There's some
They're not doing a ritual are they? Oh, that's a ritual
I'm dude. I've seen a lot of ritual
They didn't draw nothing on the floor, right
If you look me in the eyes
Trying there. I can't really see you right now blink if they got a candle
We should just go home
Are they are they in there? Can you see what I?
I mean, I can't get the sense of their location, but um...
Well, what does it look like where they are?
Does it look like the inside of a skull?
It's very dark.
And horrible.
Can you tell them to put the candle brighter?
Um...
No.
That kind of sounded like he can do that.
Yeah.
You can make the candle brighter with that?
You better not be holding out on us.
I'm not holding out on you. I can't...
If you don't feel like doing it, that's fine, but it would be very helpful.
Yeah, just say you don't feel like doing it.
Let me just try to get a better look and I don't know how much...
I don't want the boy to freak out and then freak them out.
So just give me...
Okay.
So what I'm going to do is I'm actually going to roll for him.
Wait, does Scry...
So Scry...
Does Scry include sound?
Yes, it does.
Okay, somebody make a really loud noise that doesn't sound suspicious.
Oh wait, I can use...
Can I use...
Thaumaturgy can make thunder, right?
I use Thaumaturgy to make thunder.
if you were there the sensor moves with the target the creature can see
invisible objects sees the sensors luminous orbits okay so actually here's
the thing he can and you can't use a spell against okay so what do you
actually can do is you're my awesome solution you can move it around sorry
what was your awesome solution if I can hear what scribe that I can use
thaumaturgy to make thunder where we are and then if you can hear it then I'll
know there well I don't know if you can you it's not like a conduit like pretty
clever though it's really cool I wish I was idea yeah but so what he can do is
- It should happen.
- It's existing like other divination spells,
similar to clairvoyance, where it's like,
you're like an orb that is like floating around,
and if somebody has like true sight, they could see it,
but if they don't, which none of these shaman
would have any reason to have true sight on, to be honest.
So he can move it around.
So he's moving it around the space, and he's like,
okay, okay, go get the matchbook.
All right, what I'm seeing here is, I can't get anything.
Oh God.
There's a lot of blood here.
And there's...
people's...
private parts? Faces. Oh.
Rolled out like rolling pins and plastered on the walls.
That's kinda cool. Wow, yeah. And that's downstairs of this building? Wait, I think I know that bar.
Let me try to get out of this room.
Okay, a darker room.
I see myself! Okay, it's here! I see myself too!
Okay, and you see he snaps back in.
There's one room, a much larger chamber, very dark, very hard to see.
Beyond that is that room.
Where they have the boy.
And there's ten shaman in there.
Now can you, you can, can you scry the candy store just to see if he's there?
I don't, I don't know. So I mean, I could try to scry the candy man.
who works there he's gonna be able to you can have a plus five of resistance i
think uh...
you gotta do you are getting a guy who is our own issue i don't think that's kind
of fun so i guess i'll give it a shot let's see
was a candy man's
d_c_ who's that's
okay i have a number my head i hope not
uh...
plus for those wisdom okay yeah
well yeah
so it's mine
DC probably that okay yeah he probably is I would guess he saved
I am and now I can't use his help for 24 hours
me so I was worth a track
the candy man's like pocket no I just like
now back to my evil things
I'll yeah he just he's a face time request is hung it up yeah
Yeah, he goes back to singing Candyman. Yeah, who can take the sun?
Much better world candy shop. He's just doing that to himself
Okay, well now I can't use it for 24 hours so I will wait go home then
You can't make fun of me, I'm not the frog.
You literally, you like dirt.
I don't like dirt anymore.
I like Oreos now.
You just got exposed, put you on blast, you used to like dirt.
I'm being defeated before my eyes.
I'm just walking into the...
Walking in? Okay, yeah.
Yeah, you're just walking towards it.
So you guys are going towards it, I mean...
So you guys are walking towards it, I mean you're doing it stealthily, I imagine?
Yes.
Everyone roll stealth checks.
Including Mr. Sullivan.
My first roll is fucking useless.
I know, it's a very talky talky one.
Yeah.
Okay, Sullivan.
Alright. Okay.
Got a...
I got a 7.
I got a dirty 20.
Nice. Sullivan's is not too good.
Sullivan got a 5.
Okay, nice.
Plus or minus anything?
It's none of your business, I got 13.
Yeah, and I am ignoring armor modifiers.
Nobody's gonna care about that.
Goddamnit, 7, that's supposed to be my strong suit.
Goddamnit.
Okay, so you guys walk in, some of you a little bit more loudly than the others.
We'll resolve that, though.
I'm singing the Candyman song.
Like, humming it under your breath, but like, too loud.
'Cause you want other people to hear how well you sing, kind of thing?
kind of thing yeah it's a vast chamber it's like very very dark um actually
Patrick Jodar because you lack dark vision you are like virtually blind in
here - I didn't know I lacked that yeah it's a weird thing that Verdans don't
have it but they don't I think I have dark yeah you both do have dark vision
and I think so does mr. I think mr. the frog does mr. the frog have it I don't
He's wearing eye patches so he doesn't have any vision.
He's got no vision.
He's got no vision. Yeah, he I don't think has it either.
So you're both, maybe that's why you're both did so poorly.
You both don't have dark vision.
That makes sense.
For those of you who can see a bit in front of you, so you too.
You can tell by the way your armor is clinking and your footsteps echo that you're in an atrium of some kind.
Beneath your feet is like tile flooring.
You can feel the crunch of debris below your feet.
See the occasional scurrying of rats between discarded pews, stone, and disfigured statues.
As you get closer to some of the statues, you see that they resemble some of the kaiju manji that you saw within like different, you know
You know symbols and just other like paraphernalia or whatever in Gal Gadot, right?
Just the general vibe there, except that they were free. They retain their flesh, right? They're not just bones
They look like full kaiju manji, like kaiju, but they're also like made anthropomorphized and like wearing like aristocratic
Garb so it's um basically like
Mimicking the style probably of the time of like higher ups. So it's like playing dress-up with your gods, basically
You could see a faint light ahead and hear some mild humming and chanting as well
But it's you know much further down passing that other room
with those
lower things
With those lower sneak rolls, so you humming the Candyman and Sullivan just now I'm just fully testing the acoustics of the
And so it's it's all it's like try to sing harmony like
shutting him up like
This boy needs a mouth patch - and you hear
what sounds like
flames.
Yeah, me singing.
Fuck, what's up?
Damn.
That, all the way down in that
room where you hear the chanting,
you see a much
brighter light kind of
coming in from the right,
down that long hallway.
And you see like.
And then you see the
profile of a giant
flaming skeleton head,
and then you see it facing
forward and then you
see it rushing down the hallway and you hear it go as it comes towards you sorry
for everyone hearing that and you guys gonna have to roll initiative as it's
rushing into this giant oh my god
nice job so 16 6 that's a 9 yes good the dot on the bottom I'm having terrible
- The dot on the bottom is a six.
- What?
- 18.
- If it's a bottom by bottom, you mean the circle?
- No, that's a nine.
- What do I--
- Oh, is it?
- Yeah, that's how it works.
The dot means that it's--
- Oh, shit.
- Have you been doing this wrong forever?
- Oh, wait, it's not even a nine, then it's a--
- I thought the dot on the bottom meant
that's where the bottom--
- It's a 12.
- Yeah, that's where the bottom is.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, this is a nine.
- Oh, no, when he said bottom, my first thought was circle.
- Oh.
- That's not the bottom of a nine.
- I was--
- It's the bottom of a six though.
- I was thinking it's the bottom of that shape.
This is what I was thinking.
- Now that is a very good point.
- I apologize.
- It is very dependent on which one
you would consider the bottom.
- Yeah, this was like, just like a needless conversation.
- You have to know which number it is
to know which number it is.
- Yeah, okay cool.
So.
- So it's a 12.
'Cause I forgot to add my.
- You got a 12?
Okay cool.
- Forgot to add my initiative.
- So we got a 12 from Patridge.
- 18 over here.
- 18 from you.
- 16.
- That's very good.
- Even number?
16 that's good too.
Wow.
16.
17.
Dogen.
16.
18.
Evil got 16.
At the mall?
Mr. the Frog.
Oh it's called 17.
16.
Mr. the Frog.
Life begins after school.
Mr. the Frog got.
That's when we bend all the rules.
Mr. the Frog got a dirty 20.
Wow.
I don't know how he does it.
16.
Okay cool.
Alright.
So.
cool all right so mr. the frog is gonna go first with the light of the skull sort
of rushing in he can see a little bit better he's gonna like just immediately
cast a fairy fire on this guy as he's freaking out out of his mind so this guy
just has to resist which again is pretty easy to is a wizard with us - no why me
he was outside. Okay. Yeah. Um, uh,
where is this? It's a coward. He's a bit of a coward.
That's why he's hiding in the cave all the time. Oh God.
Oh God. Is that really his? Oh, well, I'll solve it.
I guess I did make you weak cause I thought it was funny. Um, okay.
I see others. Oh shit. He got a crit. He got a natural one. The skull.
He does not resist fairy fire.
Fuck yeah.
So the flames around this flaming skull.
It's gonna be embarrassing.
His badass skull.
Yeah, change into like a purplish bisexual lighting color.
[Mimics burning skull]
And uh, and the skull's like,
He's like very, very ashamed.
Um, he feels very weird and embarrassed.
Um, but yeah, you guys now all have advantage on attacks against him.
Let's go.
Sick.
and now though it is that's my boy right there it is on the right
let's go your turn dogan
okay
uh...
have actually always like we have arrested since the last no okay that's
what i thought
uh... i'm gonna go up to the skull and i'm gonna attack with my my sh my
shovel
uh... and
so who create
yet correct yeah
all baby okay uh...
uh... which is a little bit of a spoon
right here which is what you decided to get rightful
so for credit you're gonna do double damage obviously still if divine smite
you can do to
yes i mean that is that double as well as it does add a lot of it on to the
area
uh... i'm not going to use it if it doesn't also don't pretty sure that i
might double me double check
i'd i'd need to look at how divine smite works
i don't think that's true though uh...
swindy ten
yet this is a common question i feel like it's been around
uh... to get his your crew will happen in an opportunity
that's why even divides made us double weapon damage and divine smite damage
for your behalf work
rake it's a criticism on spells as a total
all shit
that is fucking nuts it does so that works
so because basically and i bet this is an undead or fiend right
you bet it all my god yeah okay i'm i'm not a little bit you double all damaged
ice associated with the attack yet the whole world is a little like that so it's
a little bit to plus plus sixty eight
if i if i'd cuz it's yes yeah
hold on here and
just like
grand slam this book
scottie all-round and i don't really need to know if you have
so sick
well in a case is five ten
thirteen
twenty twenty seven
plus
of god
uh...
thirty four
thirty seven thirty nine damage
the whole issue
of my god
i want to tell you this 'cause it's so funny is one h_p_
please give it to me
come on
i want to see a bit of the small
what does that do that i think it is a bit larger than me i can add three damage
notion yeah
well
i don't see this once per short rest of the used to get
by god he did it yet describe i mean it is a just a small i i i i i i i i i i
don't back
down the hallway like a business has a bit more this is great to have a swing
and it is good like all the way back in the world
who was like she had a you with you know i got a big these guys are
uh... we and i don't i don't even like react i just do that also i think also
let's make it so that
the other three of us
for the other four we didn't even notice that i was there
i mean he just starts running at dogan
dogan punches him
we just hear like a
(laughter)
- What the, you hear something?
- It got bright in here for a second.
- Yeah, what was that?
You light a match?
- I don't know, it was pretty much nothing.
- You could solve it, it didn't even.
- Good job, Togan.
(snorting)
- Alright, shit, okay.
- Yeah, I mean, that was so cool.
That was like solving, like putting a T on a T-ball.
And then you just fucking crushed it.
That rocked.
Yeah, I mean, that's that mattress, man.
that's he's just dead you guys can keep going into the for the chamber. Hey let's just keep
walking into this I mean there's no one bad here yet yeah yeah um so yeah as you guys walk in
um you see uh the swirls swirls of like magic and light sort of grow in size way down in the hallway
um the main chamber of this temple is like adorned with blood and hanging ornaments of skulls and
bones and cooked flesh and masks of death faces frozen in horror unfrozen
re-frozen made to decay and smell and then blown up and plastered on the walls
like why me saw or fuck you saw you hear laughter too like a magical laughter
similar to the jesters to other dark creatures or critters within the world
other villainy just echoing off of the walls ears are ringing you guys are like
Like, inside- when you guys walk in here, you guys are like, kind of brought to your knees
by just the sheer, like, weight of like, awfulness here.
You see this circle of- of- of shaman, um, sitting and chanting.
Their eyes are like blood red, they're like, filled with like, rage or like- or like, uh,
lust.
It's horrible.
Um, and- and- and for the faintest moment, it's like the end of dreams, the end of joy.
the total annihilation of ease, you feel the terrifier for the first time in generations,
very faintly.
And the second you have that feeling, you see Giggy, his face painted, he disrobes.
"Aww, what?"
"Hey, put that back on, what the hell?"
"Oh my god."
"There's a child in the room and you're showing, you are a freak, you're one of the worst guys."
I wonder what the what the kind of guy would come up with something like this
What kind of horrible pedophile God would invent this situation
It's just not right it's just
It's it's one of the worst things I've ever heard
I'm so sad.
Giggy screeches, "BLOODLETTING!"
And all of these shamans start tearing into each other's flesh, attacking each other.
They're trying to scare each other too, for some reason. It's like the terrifier. They're trying to make each other scared.
The glyph in the center starts to turn multiple colors, shifting in and out until it settles on a vanta black
That absorbs all the flying particles flesh wet blood you feel like a epic dryness sort of like seep into the room
Fuck you guys. Fuck you guys
Seems an epic dryness has appeared
Epic dryness dry dry right? It was super
Feeling wet before but now I'm dry epic style. Yeah, you felt wet when that guy disrobed
No, let's keep doing that instead. Yeah.
No.
Okay.
If the kid wasn't here, I'd say something very bad to you.
Um, the glyph itself begins to swirl and warp until it swallows up this, like, crying, sad form in the middle that is young Prince Jumanji.
And he sees you guys, and he goes, "Guys!"
And then, like, the fucking glyph, like, swallows him up, sinks him down.
And in the midst of all this only one shaman remains alive after all the
bloodshed. It's Giggy. He's lying on the ground near death because someone took
it just a huge chunk out of his jugular and he is just like holding it and
almost dying. And the kid's gone. I turned to them and I went, "That was not good.
That was not a good thing to happen." That was pretty much, that was that too. I feel
like that's that's it really.
- Kid's gone.
- That must just be it.
- Yeah.
- Damn, oh well.
- All right, time to go home.
- Do you see, Giggy's like looking at you all
as he's like dying and he's like,
he's like, I've done it, I've done it.
There's nothing you--
- What, you showed your penis to a boy?
What have you done?
- Yeah, you showed your dick to a kid, you're weird.
- What do you think you've done?
- Now the kid's in a, you put him in a black hole
or something?
with spirits I smelt it on you you rid the woods of the wonderful jester you
stink of equity of the dreaded police the wicked God of fairness once I saw you
had the boy it was only a matter of time can we get him back no he's monologuing
Patrick shut up I'm basic I mean you can ask questions too let's keep going
keep going man you got like 20 seconds of fucking live okay going with you might
as well finish strong he's not he's not dead he's just been sent to his father
they'll be reunited so your mission's complete I guess what wait what what you
wanted well how does that make any sense that's what we were trying to do why'd
you do it yourself and fucking kill your friends? I'm so glad you asked. So, um, in the absence
of his son, the king has been despondent. We have attendants in the kingdom. Now that's
just cover your mouth. Look that back up. You've coaxed the king into performing a ceremony.
The same one to make his boy into a man. He'll be returned with what he thinks is the corpse
of his son and when he performs a ceremony that our attendants have persuaded him
to do the boy will be reborn as the terrifier himself the terrifier shall
return you should be happy and he's looking to you for the Verdan Patrick
Yodar and you Doga the dirt gom or is worked your terrifier born then I
I should be happy about this?
Well, you're a terrifier, boy.
All right, I guess I... yeah, pretty good.
Yeah, that's a good point.
And how should I feel about this news?
You...
should be very, very concerned.
Well, I'm...
Well, now I kind of feel bad. I'm starting to like this guy.
I don't really care, but if you could elaborate what's gonna happen to me, am I gonna lose my job or something?
[laughter]
Uh, something like that.
And as he's fading away at this point and he's looking to you guys, he has like a
moment where he's like, it's like his last thought. He is looking at you again,
Evil Stevel, and he says, "You were not supposed to be there." And then he dies.
Which if you remember, that was the thing that the fire creature in that volcano
or in Mount Honestoodle said to you. Of course I remember. Way back in the first episode.
Oh yeah. That was only six months ago. Yeah. Of course I fucking remember. Of course. And you would remember
probably. Oh you weren't supposed to be in the hotel. That's what you were saying. Oh my god. He's right.
Yeah. It was 12 days in-game time. You probably remember. And you see, you also see when he dies finally,
you you hear the rattling of a cage you look up above for the first time and you
see a long-haired woman black you want to work at a hot wing restaurant my friend
on it measure you she has no tits so no dice so and she she speaks to you and she
says I'm sorry I couldn't stop them I'm the spirit the white woman of the caves
I'm sorry I couldn't stop them. I heard-
You know my uncle?
You don't remember us?
I heard what you did for my sister, the white woman of the woods.
Yeah, that's you.
No.
Yeah, wait, you were at that party too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You were in the lake. You were that lady in the lake.
I was watching my uncle stoop the white lady of the river.
The woods.
The woods. In her river.
Goddammit.
She was in a pond.
She lives in a pond.
And I was watching-
Yeah, I was at that party too.
I was drinking root beer or something.
What?
What was the...
I forgot you were drinking juice.
I was drinking juice.
And the root beer made me go crazy.
They used my power to make him disappear and to turn him into the form of a corpse.
Can you make him not a corpse?
I've been drained too much of it.
I can't teleport you.
You saw my uncle draining his thing into your sister.
I didn't see that.
I heard about it after.
I saw it. I watched the whole thing.
[laughter]
I...
can...
help you get back to Trebuchet Village.
I can't teleport you there.
I can only...
make you go...
really, really, really...
really, really, really, really...
really really really really really really really really fast.
Wait.
Can we go really really really really fast?
Just one less fast.
Listen.
I don't want to know.
Listen to me.
Me.
Alright, I'm hearing you, but how fast are we talking?
I'm talking really really really really really really really really.
I think times that by about two and a half times fast.
So, you want to do it?
Yeah!
Speed me up!
Okay.
And me too!
Oh, okay.
He's actually already really fast.
Yeah, he doesn't need any magic.
He's actually like crazy fast already.
Just imagining and solving, trying to catch up.
So yeah, she casts whatever little magical ability she has left.
And you see it sort of is reflected within the like the glyph like whatever like splattered from that because the thing it like picked him
Up as a hand and dropped him down, but there's still some residue of the paint there and she's sort of like weaving that
This cave paint and she is
Warping it around you guys and you
suddenly like
Take off like lightning
like Kool-Aid man through countless people's houses.
You crash through things. You, at one point over the curvature of the planet, you sort of like
overshoot and like crash through the curvature like you fuck up and crash through and
you like smash through so many walls and you go down down down down down and you explode
in none other
Then sticky fingers joint and you see sticky fingers there. You see the pleasure men there and you see some brave lions
And you see trunchbull as well
Yeah, there you are you old bitch. How you doing? What the why it was were you guys like expecting us or something?
Did you hear that? We were fast now we weren't
but uh, this is good timing cuz that we're about to
We're about to kill the king
[Music]
Now them cops...