[Music]
Last time on Trebuchet Village, the gang finally left the Whippet Woods and made their way
northeast towards Trebuchet Village.
They ran into some brave lions on the way who our heroes dispatched quickly, further making
themselves an enemy to this rebellious troop.
They settled in at the strange Penis Inn where they traded barbs with the bartender, stole
some drinks, and consorted with a moron named Timothy.
After agreeing to help Timothy's home town of Idiot Village where the townsfolk were
suffering from a variety of calamities, including a missing village idiot, the crew slept in
the inn and headed out the next morning.
Idiot Village was as destitute, plague ridden, and starving as Timothy had lamented.
While meeting with the mayor of Idiot Village to discuss how the gang would help, Patrick
Jodar insisted there was an election and that he was running against the mayor.
The mayor, about as smart as he looked, agreed that there was an election and rushed off to
prepare for a debate.
In the interim, Patrick snooped around the mayor's desk and found a resignation letter
signed by the village idiot, detailing how he was tired of being unappreciated for his
efforts helping the morons of Idiot Village and was leaving for good.
After an awesome debate, Patrick Jodard declared he was the mayor, made the former mayor, Ted,
into a sheriff.
Dogen had a tense but helpful conversation with Dogen the Dirt God and the heroes decided
to go to one of the caves the village idiot may be in.
In this case it would be headed north.
Who knows what may lie in wait?
I do.
Um, so, I do.
You.
Wait, why'd you say it like that?
What?
Really?
Wait, do you know what's gonna happen in these before we...
No, I only know...
I don't really know.
I know some of the...
How about you tell us the whole story?
I know it could happen.
Yeah, wait, if you know the story, just say it.
We've been going through all this trouble, rolling all these dice.
No, no, no, no.
The play it and shit?
I'll...
I dress up for every episode.
I was exaggerating.
I want to do that.
First of all, I think you do want to do that.
I do want to do that.
Second of all, I was exaggerating.
I only know, you know, the immediate things that can happen and some potential things
that can happen.
Okay, so what happens right now?
Right now, you guys are in Idiot Village and you're having a meal in whatever is left of
their mess hall where Patrick Yodar, who is now the mayor of Idiot Village, is sitting
at the head of the table with his double serving of gruel and you're all sort of getting ready
to leave on your journey north towards the cave.
So the idiots are around you and you know sort of asking you to solve their problems
while you're trying to eat.
I'm solving them all easily.
What kind of problems you got?
Oh well I'm pretty sure I have two left feet.
Now I'm still figuring out my left from my right,
but don't these two look too similar to not be like that?
Get those feet out.
Let me see them.
Those are two right feet.
Okay, let's take a look.
Hold on. Those are two right feet
you got there.
I have to redo the Velcro and then undo it.
You gotta undo it.
Just undo it.
Oh, okay, I'm undoing it.
All right, now put your feet on the table.
He puts it on the table and they are two right feet.
All right, now just sit like that.
Okay.
For quite a while.
You got it.
Is this gonna, are they gonna just sort of slowly reverse?
Can you shut up?
Just shut up.
Yep.
Alright.
Well, we solved, we solved Stiebel's problem pretty quickly.
Yeah, I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
You mind if I take the gruel with me?
Uh, no.
What are you gonna do with the gruel in the bathroom?
I'm gonna, I'm gonna come out, it's gonna be damn near full.
Alright.
Yeah.
the
fifth
You, not this kid!
No!
Excuse me Mr. Mayor, could I have a little bit more?
I'm all British, everyone else is from the South.
Well this guy, this guy is telling me I can't give you any.
No!
No, you don't want this.
Okay.
Yeah, I'll just eat it myself.
Yeah.
I just eat the whole bowl of...
Yeah, roll it.
Why didn't you, you ate that in front, he was so hungry.
Constitution, Constitution saving throw.
Constitution saving throw.
100%.
Okay, I'm scared.
Hold on.
Actually, wait, sorry, not constitution saving throw.
Do a wisdom saving throw.
I knew you were going to say wisdom.
It's really a mental thing.
15.
Yeah, you've done this before.
It also just tastes the same as it did before I fucking did it.
Yeah, right.
It doesn't have any really flavor.
It doesn't change its flavor profile.
Tastes great.
Mm-hmm.
"Oh, alright, well, I guess I'll go back to eatin'...
sand!"
And, uh, he sort of waddles off.
Sand.
You see the mayor, the former mayor, aka Ted, Sheriff Ted, come up to you guys and go, "Well,
I hope you do a better job at mayor than I did.
I mean, look at this place.
Everybody's all fucked up.
That guy's feet are out on the table.
That's rude.
And that child's British.
So I think you could probably do a better job than me, but I hope I can also protect the
town from things like, well, there's that nasty gang that comes around here always asking
us for money.
But other than that, I don't really know what else I could protect us from.
I guess the village idiot used to handle that.
I didn't really realize how little I appreciated him.
Hmm.
He's the stupidest sheriff I ever met.
Yeah, he was saying that all that stuff facing away from us.
That's 100% he's facing away from you and like undressing
and like crawling into what he thinks is his bed and going to sleep.
And then we can sleep.
That's stupid and more just like in the nonsense it seems.
He's kind of a yeah, he's a guy's a weird guy more than a kind of just random.
I guess he's not the village idiot.
He stands up.
He's got no clothes on.
He says yeah, frankly, I just ran out of like ideas for ways that people can be stupid
Everybody is just gonna be insane
We'll fix this up. What's one plus one?
Fish
But I realized I just kind of fucked it all up
Try like a different number try like
Okay, number 11.
Stupid.
Ah, see that?
That's, that's, man, it's still a little close, man.
I don't know if I'm gonna give you a pass here.
You're in the stupid town, you know what I'm saying?
Yeah, I feel you.
Yeah, I feel you, that's how you talk now?
Alright, just making sure.
So yeah, you guys wanna fucking leave here as soon as possible before I run out of characters?
No, let's solve more problems.
All right, I'm going to I'm going to pack another bag of gruel.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Filling my backpack with gruel.
Yeah, and yeah, sure.
You guys can definitely do that.
And then I'm going to leave.
Yeah, yeah.
All of them are wave to you goodbye facing the other direction.
And you guys start to head on your journey north.
And yeah, the the planes that are above.
Idiot village are like arid, awful, just shitty like grass,
like the worst fucking like dirt grass, just the least arable soil,
like nothing grows there.
And I didn't know they had such good soil out here.
It's definitely an interesting dirt,
probably a composite that you could sort of play around with and feel and and partake in if you
wanted to do again because that's your character. Yeah, I'm I'm pretty right now. Yeah. Yeah. What
do you do with the dirt that you're that you're walking on? I'm swimming in it. Yeah, I'm like
like breaststroke McDuck with I grab his legs and start like lawn mowing him with his mouth on the
the
again. No, I understand. That's about what I thought. Yeah,
Sullivan who you're still married to technically. so you
still get an AC buff. You guys have uh I believe that spell
lasts a week and it's been 4 days. so I think you have I
like that the uh this is a marriage permanent or is the
marriage only West? What's the distinction? I think that I
don't know. Well, marriage is I think marriage is forever. I
I don't think the wedding ceremony, uh, like lasts like the buff from that.
It's like a honeymoon.
It's like a thing to prevent like players metagaming and just all marrying each other to get a
free AC buff.
Yeah, I think it's, yeah, I think, uh, yeah, let me see for the next seven days.
Yeah, yeah, you're, next seven days you get a plus two AC buff if you're in 30 feet of
each other.
That's a crazy thing to choose for, for the wedding effect.
Yeah, I don't really.
Well, it's like you're making harder stronger with them.
Yeah, makes you harder to hit.
Yeah, but yeah, so yeah, you guys can like, you know, you guys travel for a little bit North.
You can see the cave pretty clearly again, because it's like kind of flat.
It's pretty flat.
It's a plane, right?
And as you start to travel and it starts to approach from, you know, it was probably mid-morning when you guys left and now it's kind of closer
to the afternoon.
You see a wandering merchant come by and he's a a cobalt
merchant.
So a little like a drill dragon guy with and he has no teeth
and as he comes to see you all and he has it looks like behind
him a tall humanoid human pleasure man.
So one of the pleasure men from the first episode and you see
him and he goes, he goes, oh, well, it's nice to see fellow
travelers on the plane.
My name's Larry, the plane walker.
You guys interested in my wares?
What happened to your teeth?
You put your teeth in.
I think a child using them as a binder clip right now.
I don't know where they could be.
We just said a binder.
Well, I mean, I just I just don't know where I belong in that stupid city back there.
Oh, idiot, Valash.
No, actually, hold on. Hold on.
What do you what do you have in your let's see your wares?
Oh, sure. And he's I'll send you this link.
And he sends you a link to a shop.
And it's Larry the Plainwalker Shop.
Oh, my God.
So he has moving into the next century.
There's money in D&D.
Yeah, you have some of it.
Holy shit.
Yeah.
So there's some he has some really cool stuff.
He's sort of a weird kind of guy.
So you guys can sort of browse and peruse his wares.
He's got you guys been keeping track of how much gold you've been getting?
I think so.
This says that I have 10 SP gold.
I think I have a bunch of gold.
Yeah, you have a lot of gold, Patrick.
Yoda are I don't I have I think you have 175 last I checked on
your sheet. If you go to your inventory, click inventory,
you'll see it in DND beyond. I don't know if you two I think
I have check your gold pieces. Yeah. I think I think Patrick
has just more or less been like holding any gold you've gotten
part of it is because you guys haven't really done a quest
where you got gold at the end of it and then Patrick has been
stealing from places a lot, which has been I guess helpful.
How much do you have, Patrick?
How much do you have?
175.
Okay, and yeah, while you guys are browsing the wares, the
pleasure man goes over to you evil Stiebel and he sort of
like whispers to you like like he goes, we heard what you
did at Mount Honest do amazing work.
The discharge will be pleased with what you've done.
You're welcome.
Roll a deception.
Fuck, I'm going to get in trouble with this guy.
Five.
He sort of looks at you skeptically.
He says, Do I?
Yeah, I actually say, You're welcome.
Do you do I have the right?
Are you not evil, Stievel?
Did you not go into the volcano?
Yeah, you got the wrong guy.
Oh, I see.
Well, uh huh.
Hmm.
OK, well, sorry you roll roll deception again with disadvantage.
No. OK, nine. Yeah.
He's like, hmm.
He's just sort of skeptical from what you can tell.
He's like, well, either way, I will let discharge
know that we saw what appeared to be an evil Stievel.
No, evil Stievel is my twin brother and it's his birthday.
Let's sing happy birthday for him right now.
Yeah, let's all get in a circle.
Happy birthday.
Evil Stievel, my twin brother.
Look, if you don't want to be associated with the Legend Men,
and I understand.
Look at me.
He looks awful.
I get it.
But just I will.
It's OK.
Don't worry.
He sort of like kind of pedantically taps you, pats you on the shoulder.
All right. Bye.
Yeah. And sort of continue standing guard.
And you see a
Larry, the Larry, the plane walker.
Go, uh, oh, that's my pleasure man guard. He's so fucking weird. He sort of scares off the usual thieves
Was I southern or not us
Rob your ass. Oh
No, just kidding. No, we're just playing king. We're not gonna not not not
not
Not not cuz we're fucking around again
Village, but I do I'm not gonna be able to keep up with all those knots. Okay, not not not
Yeah, let's not make sure that the last knot is the final not. Yeah, we're going to rob you not
Not no, oh, hold on. Oh
We're not gonna rob you. We're not gonna rob you not I'm now trying to keep track. I
See you right
We're not gonna not
You not if two of you say it
Plus it's actually opposite day. I know this my twin's birthday
not not
Yeah, he's uh, he just starts foaming at the mouth, um, I'm gonna level with you I have no money not
Well, if there's anything you want here, please they're pretty rare items. I've got them from okay
Yeah, I'd like to barter with you
I'd like to make a deal for it to where I can get the staff of swarming insects for 15 gold pieces. Oh
That is a just a far too steep a discount
It's a
1500 gold piece item
What is it?
swarming. Yeah, fifteen. He's talking you down to 1%. Cam,
what is the staff of swarming insects? Staff rare. Mm hmm.
You can click. You can click. You can click. It has ten
charges. It can you can cast giant insect or insect plague or
you can make a cloud of insects. Yeah, it's uh insanely
good staff. basically just like mastery over most insect magics
that you would wanna use in DND and it is expensive. Oh, but I
can't use it if it says requires attunement by a bard
cleric druid sorcerer warlock or wizard. That means I can't
use it. Yeah. So yeah, you can't can't attune to it. Hey,
evil Steve. Uh huh. You should steal the staff and then use it
to kill these guys.
All right.
Well, hold on, hold on.
Why?
Why did you steal it?
I'm the.
Yeah, but you can't use it.
I have a feeling that this will be a particularly hard item to steal.
Why?
It's it's the same as any it's because it's the only item with a link for that.
We're gonna we're gonna steal anything.
We might as well steal the one that costs the most.
you want to steal something that's smaller instead that doesn't make any sense.
I do travel the planes from time to time so if you ever wanted to come back when you have
more money I...
I don't know if we'd be able to find you though I feel like we wouldn't be able to so you
know it's kind of a one and done thing here.
Oh well I see.
I kind of blend in with all the other idiots around here.
Oh
Okay, I'm not bad babe. No. No, I'm not like that town those people who ever since why me left
They got really fucked up
Whoo. Yeah, why me?
Yeah, why me? Yeah
He's always going why me why me as me if I gotta talk to you another goddamn second get out of my way
Oh, I mean, you know, that's doing a little guys crazy. Look at this guy. He likes this
He likes getting he likes getting called this stuff you like in you like getting roast like this you get off on stuff like this
I get that
All right. Yeah, you you funky ass look at you badass. What are you a merchant?
I look like she won't even stealth
That's very good
But let's see how the pleasure man guard does. Oh, this is gonna be bad
This is a bad idea. Okay
Okay, he the pleasure men guard is not able to catch you where you're going
And not able to sort of sense that like you're kind of sidling up to where his wares are now
The real trick is of course the slight of handshake 15. Yeah, steal a whole ass staff from an old man
That's not gonna cut it. So here's what happened. I play this up. I want you to try for sure for your sake
Yeah, so he's so - oh, hey
Hey, hey, whoa, you're not calling me fat or gay or something.
He's trying to tickle you.
I didn't say either of those.
I'm doing a different kind, I'm doing a physical roast.
Yeah, point at his big nose and no teeth.
I'm going to point at your thing and I'm going to call it small.
Physical roast is just like beating someone up.
Okay, yeah, roll deception, I guess.
13.
Okay, let's give his insight.
He's, he's, he's shrewd.
Physical roast is so genius.
How's that not with advantage?
Yeah, yeah, come on now.
It's funny.
It's not genius, though.
It's genius, dude. It's genius. That's by the book.
Yeah, no, you know what? He didn't really,
he sort of, he started game for that.
He's like, "Oh, okay, what you doing?
What you doing?
Where you poke?
Boy, did you get a point?
Pinch his cheeks like a fat baby.
I'm gonna point at your thing.
Go.
You're gonna point at my thing?
Yeah.
Pinch his butt.
Pinch his bottom.
And it's small, too.
And see this?
I'm making it look like it's smaller by pointing at it.
No!
Ah!
Play his thingy like the world's smallest violin.
Yeah, I'm gonna try to do that.
Oh, well, you know, you don't have to touch my- Oh, hell, just touch my penis.
No, I'm not- Well, I'm not gonna- Holy crap.
I'm not gonna touch it.
Oh, okay.
Oh my god.
Whoa.
That's weird.
I thought you were bringing it there.
You know what, you better give us an item on the house for that one.
That was weird as hell.
I was trying, I thought we were joking around.
You took it way too far.
Yeah, you made it weird.
I made it weird?
Alright.
So you better give us an item.
I thought we were fooling around from a British boarding school where they do things like that. So
Like not not in like that way. Uh
so
item
Here he had you guys a potion of healing. That's right. That'll do for now
the off-color humor and
Hey, man, it's okay not yeah
Truck on out of here you penis freak. Yeah, you got it
Sayonara, he really likes that
He's really he's really weird. He's really messed up in the head. I'm glad he's gone
It is one of the weirdest guys I've ever seen we've met a lot of weird guys. I think he was maybe the weirdest
Yeah, I uh, yeah shit. I didn't even say anything
Yeah
Clown I there was like a heat emanating off of his penis. We already killed the clown Steve. Oh, that was the last quest
Oh, I mean, let's find the stupid. What is he a dumb?
Idiot. Yeah, let's kill this clown
Yeah
Okay. Yeah, you guys keep wandering and sort of evening approaches
as you wander through the plains and
You start to come across the cave and
and the northern cave. It's a big fucking cave. It's a big mouth of the cave. It's a sort
of a darkish, bluish, grayish rock kind of sticks out in the rock face compared to a lot
of the other sort of the more brownish, you know, more arid looking sort of a geological
outcroppings here. And as you guys wander in, you don't, it's a pretty, it's a, it seems
like a mostly a pretty shallow cave. It looks like a small Creek sort of running through
it like not even like a real substantial like not like a stream, but like a stream of like
a creek of little tiny thin line of water and you don't really see anybody inside.
Remember there were there were two caves obviously and you don't seem to see anyone inside though
right now.
Hello.
Oh, echo, echo, echo, echo.
Can be put in after.
Echo, echo.
No, that's what I'm saying.
the
the other guy. Well, yes, I'm ostensibly the village idiot.
My name is why me? Why me?
Ah, that's this guy.
Well, I got it from earlier.
It's not saying your name over and over again.
It's annoying. You're not a Pokemon.
Yeah. Even evil, evil, evil, evil.
So annoying. That is Petruch Petruch Yarder.
Hi, I'm a way.
I had my hand out and I try to shake his hand.
Yeah, he extends out a frail, wizardly hand and he shakes it.
He says, "Oh, wait, hold on.
And I need to..."
"Can I have your head?"
"I need to test one more thing, maybe."
And he makes everything...
He basically waves his hands around and everything around you goes dark in a way that is magical.
Some sort of magical darkness.
And he says, "Peek-a-boo."
Ah!
Yeah, you're still there.
I don't--
Oh, okay, good.
Just double-checking you're not from that town.
Okay.
'Cause they forget right away.
They just go home.
We are from that town.
Oh, fuck!
Okay.
He's the mayor.
What?
Oh, yeah.
No!
I don't want any part of this town anymore!
I'm done with you fools!
I'm done helping you!
Well, how about--
Well, how about you listen to us first, you asshole?
Ooh, this one's got a mouth on him. They elected a mayor with yeah
Head. Well, I've got I got I got power now
He'll physically roast you man. You want him you better watch out
This guy's wiener on the way here. Yeah, that's right. That guy's a fucking freak. I got so much power now. I don't even know
Also, okay. We're not I guess we're not from the town. Okay, like rain yourselves quick
Yes we are. I'm from a, I'm probably from a bush, but there are, we, we, that is the
last location we were at. I'm just, uh, I'm from around.
Okay. Dirt, dirt guy. How do you know? You're covered in dirt. You got the mark of
Dogan you look like him. Yeah. Yeah, I came from a dirt farm if I remember correctly
Hmm yes you
Hey, do you?
Do you chew dirt?
You look like you're a paladin, right?
No
And dirt is falling out of the corners of my mouth. You know, you don't have to chew dirt to talk to him, right?
he just
he
He's an asshole. He thinks you he makes you think you have to chew dirt. You really don't I don't have to chew dirt
Not to talk to him. No, you could just ask for him
I don't know why he tells all his disciples that they have to chew dirt. I think I funny he does
Yeah, I think it's a good bit, but it's pretty rude
it
but
Anyway, so what do you guys? What do you guys want to say? I think he likes it
So basically this idiot or this normal guy is the idiot mayor of stupid town and
He needs the dumbass which is you right come back and fix
the town
Yeah, pretty much that do you know how much I've done for that town? Anyway, no, we just got here
He waves his hand and
Like chair appears beneath him and three cushions appear and he sort of motions if you'd like to slide we don't get chairs
No, it's my fucking cave. I get the chair
All right, I said in the chair before he does oh yeah, you're gonna roll for that. Yeah, I am
Can I see your head real quick roll suck my dick? I'm sitting in this
No, you could sit in the chair. It's fine. That was fun
Wait, what'd you get? That's 12
On what on dexterity? That's fair. That's probably what I was gonna make it do. Yeah, I'm like pretty much right by the chair, but I summoned
So you just look like an asshole
What's up Patrick, that's your name
Can I put on your head?
Yeah, she could put on my hat. All right
Well, what about the rest of your clothes? No, I need to keep the robot
Could I put those clothes on I have a spare robe if you'd like to wear one
Open let him wear that
Rob, I could go for the host here. You're supposed to show hospitality. You want me to go change out of this room?
Yeah, so get stand up from the chair and just go get the spare
You know what? You've bested me this time. He's actually doing it. He's
He's so stupid.
Oh my god, what a...
I don't even want those clothes.
He really is a village idiot.
He gets up and he walks towards the back of the cave.
You hear him like...
I sit on the chair.
Yeah, so it's between robes.
He comes back and sees you're in the chair.
He's like, "Damn it, dude!
You got my ass!"
And then they call fives.
Yeah, and he gives you a robe, Steve-o.
He gives you one, Patrick.
And Doga just goes, "Did you want one?"
"Duh, go back and get another one."
"You're in the chair!"
All right, I'll go back. What about the frog and and the you he's fine. You brought a child here, too
Okay
Hi, sorry, we don't know that kid and don't know his name or whose son he is, but he's just gonna hang out
and he goes back and he grabs a robe and he comes back and he gives you a robe and
He summons a a bigger chair and sits in it and looks at you don't
Like I use thaumaturgy to cause tremors in the ground and knock over his chair. Oh
fuck
All right, pretty good I'll stand
Look, I've done a lot for that town. Here we go
Do you know what it's like to be a wizard without a tower?
All wizards are supposed to have towers, but why me? No, I don't get a tower
I have a fucking cave you seen this place. Do you know where that Creek leads?
Nowhere good
It sucks. There's just a bunch of bats fucking
You know what this ooze is. It's bat ooze. It sucks
This is my cave. This is my home and one day I got tired of it
And so I wandered around and I found this town where everyone was dying of the plague
And I figured out that they were just sort of poisoning themselves by accident eating their own shit thinking
Well, it came out that end. So why not this end -
Well, you know I helped them with that and they decided I was stupid because I wear
what they called a
Blanket for your body, which I guess is what they think a robe is so and a hat that reaches the stars and
Kind of like what I'm wearing right now. Yeah, it sounds similar to what we have going on
Yeah, just make it up a story about Patrick's hat right now. Oh, I knew it looked good
He says uh, well anyway, so that town is is fucked
Okay, I I tried to integrate there
I thought I was gonna maybe find some people who I could even like but of course
Why me? Oh, why me?
No one likes why me dug in the dirt cobbler?
You know Steve
Hey guys, do you want to
You should I think your biggest problem is you need a better wizard name. Yeah, and I think
Not good. I think maybe
That's a good one.
What?
Maybe.
Or like, what about like, I'm cool.
Yeah. What about like, fuck you?
Oh, fuck you.
Fuck you isn't good.
That would be good.
How does that sound?
Yeah, say it.
Fuck you.
Yeah.
That's pretty good.
You know what?
You know what your problem is, is you let those people walk all over you after you help them.
That's right. You need to help them.
You need to stand up for yourself.
You needed you needed.
Yeah.
You know.
You know what? How did you become mayor?
Me?
Yeah.
I told them I was the mayor.
Holy shit.
Yeah, it's that simple.
You know, I never thought maybe that could just be my fucking town.
Yeah, what if I just bring you back there and I tell them
that I gave that you're me
and
What?
I'm the mayor.
Oh, so fuck me wait, hold on Patrick. You should change your name to fuck me and then you could be fuck you
me. Could we wear backpacks or something? I mean I guess you could yeah. That'd be pretty nice.
You already have matching outfits on. This is really unfolding. See now that uh now that we
got the matching outfits on it's uh not like they're gonna be able to tell that you're not me.
Is there another do you want to try out another voice? I think we're good with the voices. I think
I think that'll be alright.
I think there's another voice we could try out.
Okay.
Whatever.
Look, I'm not opposed to that.
Maybe, I mean, I can't really explain to you how fucked those guys are.
Do you guys know what Gal Gadot is?
Yeah, that is a Mediterranean dish that I've had.
It's egg roasted eggplant and a lot of like as a tar and other things. Yeah, that's true
It was named after the city of Gal Gadot that lies
Further east of here. Anyway, there's a band of
Orcs from there that sort of frequent this area
they're gonna absolutely fuck up that city because they can't pay the fines that that the Gal Gadot collects, so
That city's doomed unless we go back there or unless we go to Gal Gadot or we go to oh we go to idiot
Village, I don't want to go to Gal Gadot. Okay, then we got to go to
I'm a human they make me they'll make me a slave there
Crazy, right? Well, we so so what's gonna happen is we go to idiot village and okay protect idiot village from the Gal
Gadot people we could basically tell them I mean you just tell the idiot village people
They take what if we just get them to move their town
They barely have anything. I mean actually I haven't been there in about a month. This is still just all well scaffolding
Well, there's I mean, I remember we went to a really nice in right a strange penis. Yeah strange penis in you know
I feel like maybe we could get the entire population of the town to move to that in and just live there instead and then maybe
They you know leave this the town there
The orcs will think that they
left
Yeah, what if we scrap all this and we have a big barbecue yeah, we could
We invite all those people
We and the orcs and we can make it like Thanksgiving oh
Yeah, if we bring if we bring enough people to that end then the Bart that stupid-ass bartender won't be able to say anything about
it more of us than there are of him I still got a bone to pick with him he was
very rude to me when I froze him in place magically oh you you froze him in
place and did you steal liquor the little one here with the big balls did
you steal the liquor I might have done that and he was a dick about it he was
so rude so I think we should bring every it might have been my little thieving
ass oh I know that face you're you gotta be you gotta be his nephew right oh yeah
Trunchbull you know oh you know trunch oh oh doesn't know trunchbull legend oh god
total legend that is you had it what a great guy what a great I mean hey look at
you man you look great we're wearing the same thing we look amazing we look
amazing right now me we're gonna we're gonna solve all these problems okay
amazing I'm a little good I don't remember the plan anymore what was the
plan I think we're doing a barbecue town I'm smoking this pipe oh fuck yeah give
want to hit this fucking shit absolutely okay kind of a different direction here
you go he has you guys his Gandalf asspipe oh yeah you got to be careful
this is some wizard shit okay oh yeah you you can't handle this oh yeah he
does it oh look at him he's got a stomachache already I'm already
sweating oh god he's gonna grow up I turned red cuz I'm a goblin yeah I get
so high that I completely like disconnect from reality and I go into a I like close my eyes
and open them and I'm in Fallout 3 in the Megaton mission deciding whether or not to
blow up the town.
I'm back.
You are you alright?
Yeah, I'm alright.
I'm my brain is kind of become a whirlpool of Bob culture.
Like a real 2006 Braid going on here.
Yeah, I gotta fuck you.
You know what Steval needs is a bag of chips.
I don't need no chips, man.
You need some chips.
I don't eat chips.
Come on, eat some chips.
I eat this.
What is that?
I pull out my homemade flashlight that I made with the gruel and a sock and I start slurping
it.
Oh God.
Oh, he nasty.
Oh, I'm nasty.
Look at his little nasty ass.
Oh man, I'm so small and disgusting.
This is awful.
There's a child still here.
I think I I I mean I'm standing there like completely still just
staring into space and I'm like, you know, dragons really be
crazy as hell when you think about it for real.
Get it.
Oh, man.
Look at this guy.
Look at this guy's eyes.
There is red.
There is red is my balls.
You do have red balls.
They're they're really red on the bottom.
They are dragged around.
Actually.
Yeah, they're really I look at it.
Patches balls and I go yo.
Damn, I'm so high and so hungry.
Oh my God stupid little town and try to get some food.
We should go back to high school.
You know what I let's go back to that.
Well, hold on.
Hold on.
It's kind of if you guys want to travel at night, we can't just I don't want to.
We might run into a little bit of trouble.
We can wait here for the night.
Teleport us.
I can't. I'm not just going to burn.
I just make me lie.
You magic bitch.
I could make you like levitate.
Whoa. OK, I'm not levitating yet.
Oh, it's pretty tight.
What? Yeah.
What did you just say?
I said that's pretty tight. He's levitating.
Oh, yeah. Well, I don't think he was, but, you know,
he's I guess there was some forced perspective.
Yeah, yeah.
That's what you think about it.
It's like
they're all kind of levitating.
And you think like the brain is like not touching the ground.
Oh, man, this guy needs some chips so bad.
We got to go.
Okay. Yeah, I think we should probably just
He's all of it is Sullivan is fully decked out the wizard outfit. It's too big for him. I think we should probably
Probably should either stay here the night or if we're gonna move out
We should probably just make a plan in case we run into some not night monsters
And you know what I could stand to go to sleep
Yeah, me too. I'm pretty sure yeah
You guys know
Mr. Mr. What fook you
Yeah, yeah, that's good. Yeah, fuck you. Uh, I don't think I've said I don't know if I've cussed like that in this voice
It's not a cuss word. It's his name. Hey
We don't cuss. Oh, sorry. You don't cuss
When do you think those orcs will come by they gonna come by tonight? I don't know
Oh, oh, uh, all right.
I guess be quiet.
We're trying to sleep over here.
I guess it's sort of talking to talk all night.
Yeah, fuck me.
You guys go to bed.
So yeah, you guys wake up next morning.
You're all snuggled in your wizard outfits.
And it's daybreak is arrived.
and uh, uh, why me or fuck you wakes up, um, and uh, not a sort of a nudges you, uh, uh,
Patrick.
He says, Hey, fuck me.
You ready?
Yeah.
What for what?
We're going to eat.
I remember.
I think I might've greened out last night.
I don't, that's funny.
Yeah.
I don't remember.
You don't.
Uh, well we were gonna go to the town and, um, oh, we were going to the barbecue.
Oh, well, I think that was part of it, but it was also
That was the only thing we planned
Well, we were gonna go there and try to evacuate the town
Fuck that why not just have a big barbecue
And you want to try the bar? Okay, we could just try the barbecue angle. We could just see how that okay
I'm okay with that. You know, you don't sound okay with that. I'm just worried about how it could turn out but
Orcs love barbecue and they're drawn to the smell like a shark to blood
This is true. Yeah, but I thought we were inviting the orcs to the barbecue
Yeah, I think we're trying to reframe the situation where it's like wait wait or take barbecue. What are we thinking about?
Right. I don't even know. The only problem is how we're gonna get any meat
We eat you we could yeah, we could kill some of the villagers. We just kill you eat you
Well, the orcs would like the villager meat.
Yeah, why don't we do why don't we just move all the villagers into the inn so the bartender gets mad and then we can cook
the bartender
Wait, I have an idea. Okay, so here's a problem
We need to get the orcs and the villagers in the same room right to let them chop it up, right?
But the orcs love eating the villagers and we don't have any meat
So what if we go to the town we kill everybody in it and turn them into delicious
Barbecue meat right and then we invite the orcs and then they can eat the barbecue
So we want us to kill the whole town and
As long as I get to eat some ribs, I don't care
Okay, shit. You guys want to go let's do it. You guys want to eat people
We're doing it. Well, I didn't you seem a little excited. I never said anything about us eating the people. Yeah
For the orcs. Oh, all right. You scrapped that plan. You're a man. No, I'm just trying to figure out what the vibe is here
We're let's go. Let's hide the villagers in your cave. Okay, good idea. So yeah, you guys want to get back?
Yeah, idiot village. Hey you guys wander back
It takes, you know, like a good few hours to get there.
You get back and yeah, the idiot villagers are sort of just
doing what they were doing, you know, clipping through the
environment and you know, whatever it is stupid NPCs do and
they see all of you come back dressed in wizard robes and
the mayor or I guess the sheriff mayor Sheriff Ted goes you
see him and he look everybody four five six ten village idiots and everyone
starts to gather around and they're like oh wow hey hey no I'm the mayor wait
you're the mayor yeah I'm the mayor but you're dressed like a village idiot well
a village idiot can be a mayor. And they see them all go, "Oh, I feel
shit being mayor." And as the mayor, I decree that a law.
Oh, well, I guess there's no stopping that with the mayor saying it.
Okay. That's right.
Yeah. Well, if, okay, but then, then are you all the mayor?
Yeah, we're all there.
It's not only him.
He's mostly the mayor.
This guy.
Fuck you.
Yeah, I'm a girl.
My name is fuck you and I'm the mayor of this town and some
things are going to start changing around here.
The first thing that has to change is we need to leave here
or we're going to die.
So let's go to my cave where the bats fuck but there's no orcs
that are going to kill us.
How does that sound?
And you see them all go like, we'll follow you wherever you
go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, and you're all going to throw us a
barbecue after.
Yeah.
Wow.
That sounds like a great idea with human meat.
Well, I don't oh shit.
Oh, we'll figure that out.
Christ.
All right.
But yeah, let's go to the let's go to the cave.
Okay, yeah. So you guys are marching with like, I guess like 50 to 60 people towards a cave
and you're marching through the plains. So at this point, you're kind of a...
I turned all the idiots on. I'm like, "You don't have to march. You can just walk.
marching the entire time just because we're in a group just wanted to clarify but i thought this
was an rts oh [ __ ] i could just walk okay we're gonna walk now guys all right but just walk
in a group don't let anybody leave the group okay so and lift your knees up when you're walking and
You know, do it all in time.
All right.
Yeah, do it all in the same motion, but don't.
No marching.
No marching and don't get lost.
Yeah. Buddy system. Everyone is your buddy.
All right. We're going to do some rolls to see how they know across the play.
So it's not them.
It's just it's just that they are really stupid.
And they're going to go so much.
Yeah. Let's see how they do.
So we're going to do a collective intelligence role.
So I'm going to average out to pretty low.
Wow, a solid.
Okay, so only 25% of them get lost on the way.
It was it could have been a lot worse.
I'm telling you it was very impressive.
Yeah, so 25% of them are just gone.
You guys look turn around and they're just like they just
peel off and you just don't know where they go.
As you're walking.
It is just walk in the wrong direction.
Yeah, just walk in the wrong direction fall down a hole.
Gone and you see you all right arrive at the cave and it's
it's a closer to like sort of mid-afternoon like dusk now
and you see the, uh, you see, uh, Fook you, uh, look at all,
everybody who's in, oh, wow, this is actually a lot better than
the last time we tried to do this. Um, okay.
Well now we'll just sort of wait here for a little while and then,
you know, if the Orcs come here for some, whatever reason, you know,
you all hurry into the cave and keep yourselves hidden and
we will protect you
but i don't have them going to cave now
i guess
yet
witty
white why add up in the cave yet i'll make it complicated to snow and you know
everyone in the bills get a decade
uh... okay like all that
the bad news is food
just getting not him
you lose four of them as they walk towards
uh...
uh... homes
and uh...
Yes, they're hiding in the cave and is the night the night is
coming.
You all start to hear you all start guys are like hanging out
outside the cave.
You guys light in a fire.
I'm hanging out.
We're just doing out to the cave and I'm just I'm repeatedly
just going boo at every time every single.
Yeah, it was screaming.
Times in a row.
Boo-boo-boo.
I think it's a new ghost.
Yeah.
Oh wait, watch this one, watch this one.
Alright, everybody cover your eyes!
They all do.
I DON'T EXIST!
*laughter*
Oh man, that one used to fucking get me
every time.
Shit. You guys wanna try another one?
Yeah, let's try, uh...
How about this?
Uh...
I just throw like a flaming lock.
*laughter*
Yeah, just like
fucking hits one of them there's like oh yeah that's like a funny prank they're
so stupid what the hell yeah dude you're evil what I mean I mean that was cool
but that's evil that was that evil that was just a funny prank you just burned
the
I forgot I forgot about that.
Yeah, they're people for sure.
Yeah.
You know, they kind of just have been like, kind of like fodder this whole time.
Oh, absolutely.
I'm trying to humanize them as much as possible.
It's it's kind of easy to forget at times.
Oh,
yeah.
All right, hold on.
Let me try that again.
Then.
the
guys fuck around and fuck with the townsfolk. You hear like a horse footsteps or something,
some horse like thing. I bet it's a horse. You see in the distance, oh, it's a horse
alright. It's like a, it's a big horse though. You see like six or seven strong looking fucking
orcs, orcs, a couple of them are half orcs riding up to the mouth of the cave.
And you see them, they sort of stand in front of you guys are about like 30 feet
away and they're looking at you all and they say, why me?
And this is, ah, hello, Thorax.
And you guys are no, no, fuck you.
Not why me?
Fuck you.
What?
Tell him, tell him your name.
Fuck you.
Fuck you, not why me, fuck you.
- Fuck you.
- Exactly.
- That's his name.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Oh, oh, okay.
Oh shit.
Why me?
You didn't tell, fuck you.
You didn't tell me you were changing your name.
All right, well.
- You actually got it pretty fast, honestly.
That usually takes people a lot longer,
especially when you add fuck me into the equation.
- Oh yeah.
No, I mean, wizards always do shit like this.
They're just trying to find themselves.
They're very annoying.
- Yeah, I get it.
Look, it's been a while.
We went to the village, we were looking for payment.
Nobody was there.
We found about 25 or so other guys
just sort of wandering around
and the kind of a trail of them led us here.
- Did they pay you?
- No, they had dick on them, if anything at all.
- Why have you looked there?
- I'm sure a few of them had penises.
- What? - Did they pay you?
All of them had penises, regardless of gender,
and none of them paid me.
And they led to here.
And I could see now we have four
who are clipping the sides of the cave right now, so.
- All right.
How much do they owe? - What's going on?
Oh, it's how much that they owe Gal Gadot.
Not me, Thorax.
(all talking over each other)
- You guys, you guys tell me,
just give me a number, bitch.
And you guys look at them,
And you realize that you recognize him actually from the Strange Penis Inn.
He was he was part of that group of guys who were leaning against the
the wall on the bench on the side there.
Wait a second.
You're the guy from the wall.
Oh, oh, you've been to the Strange Penis Inn then.
Yeah. Yeah, it's a cool place.
That bartender sucks, right?
Otto? Yeah, he's a bit of a prick.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to freeze him magically.
Oh, damn.
All right.
You guys are tough.
That's pretty cool.
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
And now he as he hears you guys like rapping about like how you guys would fuck with a
human bartender.
He's like, oh, shit.
Yo, yo, Doug.
What?
These are the guys I was fucking telling you about.
Oh, oh, these are the guys at the Brave Lion.
Yeah.
Fuck with the brave lions, right? Is that bad? It's fucking awesome, man. All right, cool suck
Well, yeah fucking losers. God damn. Okay. Yeah, I knew I recognized your faces
You guys are by the way much better looking in those drawings if you guys. Oh, thanks
Like I remember you on that wall like it was yesterday. Yeah
I might have been I'm a beautiful man. You rode that wall. Oh, so well, okay
There's a line and I'm here for it. So
Okay, yeah, maybe we could what's let's try to work something out here, okay you guys
Okay. Wow, this is great. I'm so excited to meet you guys. It's just man those guys those guys fucking suck-ass
They just been trying to fuck with we have we have these great slaves and they just want to fucking ruin it
They fucking pricks. Oh, they're trying to take away your slaves, man
It's awful man, it should be illegal. I
Have been saying that and then meanwhile that stupid fucking King Nardwuar now wants to make it all nice and hunky-dory
the fucking asshole anyway, so
Appreciate that
But yeah, they definitely owe us some money. So who's in charge then? Are you guys you guys in charge of these basically a council?
Yeah, we're pretty much all in charge. All right, but I guess technically but fuck is the man. Fuck you. Yeah
So if you're about to say anything that has to do with a money amount, it does.
It's OK. All right.
Loud and clear, fellas. OK.
Thorax. Look, man, you know, these guys aren't good for it.
Yeah, of course I know that.
So what do you want? What do you want?
Well, they could be our slaves.
That's kind of always one of the good solutions.
We could eat them.
Who is talking right now?
Hold on, let me try to find a way to delineate the voices.
So this is how about this is thorax, right?
He sounds a little bit more like this.
I'll put him in this register.
He sounds more like my way to hold.
How about that? Yeah, there we go. I found it.
I found that sounds about right.
Yeah, I found that is a good voice.
Isn't that a better voice there? Yeah, it took me a little bit,
but I had to I had to sort of search in my throat to find it.
But I sound like a John Benjamin with a cold.
the
this
I got back to the H. John Benjamin cold voices.
Was this it?
I'm trying to.
Yeah, that's that's about it.
All right, good.
Look, you can make them my slaves or, you know.
Look, if you guys want, you could come with me to Galgado
and you could try to work something out with the with the fellas over there.
So that or they're my slaves or I mean, we're going to eat them.
Well, here's here's my here's my thinking.
Okay.
So how about we turn
their land
into a part of Gal Gadot?
Amusement park.
Oh.
No, really.
A part of Gal Gadot that is an amusement park.
And all of them will be the walk-around characters.
And it's called--
And it is called--
Idiot Land. Stupid Bill.
Yeah.
Idiot Land, Stupid Bill.
It could be like an Idiot Land
and then there could be like an Epcot.
Well, it's like there's an Epcot and it has like a fork in a microwave.
So basically they would kind of be your slaves, but they would entertain you for you.
But also the best part is they're so stupid they wouldn't even realize they were slaves.
Not just be living their life.
It'll be the first amusement park in the realm.
So you're going to be making a lot of money off that way more than you'd get from.
it say, uh, thorax presents.
Yeah.
That's great.
All you guys need a couple of, a couple of one way mirrors so that they, and
it actually better cause they get confused by their reflection.
Oh yeah.
So it'll be like, you ever tried, you ever tried throwing a
flaming log at one of them?
Uh, this guy, this guy knows me.
All right.
Uh, roll a, uh, let's roll a persuasion check guys.
It's pretty, uh, all three.
24.
Yeah, all three and we'll sort of average it out.
1214.
I mean, that's pretty good.
Honestly, you also got that.
God, Patrick, your fucking charisma is crazy.
Oh God. OK, cool.
Yeah, you see he goes, he looks his guys, you see them.
You see also that one of them, not Doug, but one of the other ones
who's carrying like a staff is sort of squinting his eyes at you guys.
You guys clock that he doesn't look like he's going to like do anything or say
anything, but you guys clock that somebody in his group is a
little bit more skeptical of you guys. But yeah, he turns to
you all and says, alright, I mean, be honest. I **** like it.
I think it's a good idea. I think the people of Gal could
do could use some sort of a distraction from the woes of
living but yeah, I mean they're barely living. Oh, it's not
It's not. It's no way to live.
No.
And, but here's the thing.
If we want to pull this off,
you guys then have to come with me to Gal Gadot and be,
you know, I need to prove that I have sort of like investors
or businessmen or wherever you guys are.
Yeah, we can do business.
That's easy.
So you're telling me you have like a room in Gal Gadot,
right?
With maybe like a long hallway walking up to it.
And you got say like, I don't know,
five very powerful people who might be willing to invest in our idea.
Something like that.
Exactly that, please.
Yeah, pretty much for the next one.
Exactly that.
Basically, exactly that.
But then we do it for the next thing.
Please, please, please, please.
Oh, I guess it's happening.
And maybe there's a voiceover that explains our idea as we walk up to the door.
Oh, I guess it's a hundred percent happening.
I cannot, I cannot wait for this.
Let me tell you what, I'm gonna say we'll do it.
Yeah, this is happening.
This is happening.
This is a hundred percent happening.
And, uh, oh yeah.
And, uh, are we done?
Is that?
I think an hour and five minutes.
Okay.
I was gonna say, was that fair?
[laughter]
And uh, are we done?
Is that...
[music]
Okay, I was gonna say...