Yarrrgh! Last time on Trebuchet Village, Tales from the Seabob, Sinbad, Virtue Good, Lady
Better. These three salty sea dogs defeated their nemesis Weirdbeard, and had a massive
beast cloaked in white mist that varnished into the ocean. Then, upon receiving confusing
Following orders from Governor Gracias Mi Amigo of Port Virtue Good, they hunted high
and low for the bandits of Isle de Cou, and found themselves face to face with a sandwich
worshipping cove of were-dolphin, the erg.
But the three captains of the Caribbean Royale kept their Isle de Cou, and rescued these fiends
from a life of thievery, to instead become a hearty crew of old-fashioned sea slaves.
Soon however, they were trying to make each other walk the plank, and were unable to figure
out why until it hit them. Their toilet looked a lot like a guy they used to bully and figured
they should try to recover him from his untimely demise. But how? Well first they returned to
Governor Gracias Mi Amigo to tell him of their intent and their success in routing the bandit
issue discreetly. So yeah, you guys kind of had this revelation last time that there was
something missing. And first you have to go report to Gracias Mi Amigo that your
mission was a success and he's very pleased to see you and he says, "Ah, hola!
It's good to see all of you." Hola. Hola. Hola, mi amigo. Yes, that is my name.
Si, gracias. Gracias. Do you think this could hold up for another episode? It has to.
I
Have met very appreciative of all the work you've done for us
What's your middle name have we done that before I don't think we hit that yet me me me gracias me
I thought mi amigo was your last name.
No, no, no, amigo is my last name.
Mi is my middle name.
Are you related to Casamigos?
But I'm mi.
I don't think so.
Who's Casamigo?
Yeah, wait, what?
But he's me.
I'm me.
Yeah, he's me.
And you're my amigo.
Okay, so anyway, that's what you get for trying to sneak Spanish into this damn game.
Honestly, it was my fault.
Speak American.
Yeah, I'm trying.
I'm trying, actually.
But, uh, I hear tell that you wish to leave Port of Virtue Good just when I was going to make you privateers, officially, part of the army.
You're gonna look at my- what?
What?
You're gonna-
Oh, no, no, no, no. Privateers.
Private-
Private ears?
What?
Is it-
I-
Look, I don't have any private ears. Ladies have private ears downstairs.
Mm-hmm. They have ears-
I've heard that too. It's an ear down there.
Yeah.
Yep. That's why it's got flaps.
Yeah, it's all the different-
Those are the lobes.
Yeah.
It's all cartilage.
Right. I mean, look, I don't know where the women you come from, they could be all...
I come from space.
We don't know what that is yet.
But why do you wish to leave? Tell me.
I think we need to shit in a different toilet.
Ah, yes.
I can't remember.
The hunt for the golden toilet, of course.
- Many have tried. - No, it's different.
- It was a different one. - It was a green toilet.
- It's a different quest. - Yeah.
- The Emerald Toilet. - It's like a frog.
- No, no, he's like meat. - The Hunt for the Amphibian Toilet.
You're going to kiss a toilet so it turns into a prince?
No, we're not gonna kiss a toilet. What's wrong with you?
- Well, if I have to. - I'm just trying to see.
Nah, I wouldn't kiss this toilet if he was a man.
Which toilet?
- The toilet. - The toilet.
- You wanna come see it? - Wait, hold on, hold on.
- It'll be easier if we just show you the toilet. - The banyo.
I guess I could go...
Oh!
No, that's the bathroom.
Ah, yes, the bathroom!
No!
(laughter)
Oh, you get it.
Well, I guess I could go...
Bueno ir el baño.
Yes, let me see your toilet.
That's not what that means.
Can we take him to the ship?
Is that what that means?
I thought that means I have to go to the bathroom.
I'll take him to the ship.
I don't speak Spanish.
(laughter)
And I'll show him to the Sullivan toilet.
okay he looks at he says it this looks like a guy yeah that's what we're saying
did you know this guy I think so yeah might have been my I think he maybe was
married to him I don't know about that part but we know I think he was a slave
No, I think wait. I think you married this
Married a slave you married a toilet slave. Yeah, I don't think that or a slave
No, regardless slave to the toilet. Mm-hmm whether the toilet was free or enslaved
I think I need to bring you all to the court wizard. I think that's the only way the basketball court wizard
Yeah, he is quite tall. I'd like to go to the food court wizard. I'm hungry as hell. We had to get rid of him
What? I'll bring you to our wizard. His name is Fook-Me. We're standing right in front of the wizard.
What? We're standing right in front of the wizard. Oh, the wizard. I see. That's pretty funny.
Gracias, amigo. Say the name again. Wizard. No. The name of the court wizard. Oh, Fook-Me.
(Gasp)
If I have to.
I'm about to wash your damn mouth out.
The soap's over there.
Okay, come here.
Okay, I have the soap and I stick it in his mouth.
Now show me that wizard.
Okay, we gotta go back to the...
Let me see your wizard.
Okay, wait.
I've got lots of trouble...
We don't have time to go to his bathroom.
Can I spit out the soap?
Are you gonna keep saying naughty things?
And cussing?
No.
We can spit it out. Okay I'll take you to the wizard. And he brings you to his
bathroom and he says there it is and then he takes you. Why did we end it? And then he
takes you to a wizard who looks very familiar. You guys know Fook Yu. This
is his brother Fook Mi. Who unlike his brother. Wait isn't is Fook Yu still
named Fook you or did we change his name? You changed his name from Why Me to Fook
you. Why is his brother's name Fook Me? Well they both had the last name Me
until we changed it. Yeah you changed him to Fook you. He's Fook Me. So I guess we gave him
his brother's name. So his brother's name was Fook? No no no they're both
called... his name was Why and his brother's name was Fook. You changed his
name to Fook you. This is his brother Fook Me. Okay it's starting to make sense. You got rid of
his last name. Yeah, we changed his last name. Sounds awesome. We changed his whole name.
We changed both his first and last name. To his brother's first name and a new last name
that we might encounter later. Yes. To my last name. Dogen U. That's a huge lore reveal
for this episode. I did say there'd be lore in this episode. Yeah, you're Dogen U? Yeah.
I love that I'm dogan you buddy. Oh, I'm dogan you're a dogan me. That's I'm a
middle name guy. My first name is
Rod dogan you
canon immediately cannon, not even a question
rod dogan you
so anyway yeah. Yeah, you see this wizard. He looks similar to to fuk you
obviously, but he's
he's cleaned up. He doesn't look like Gandalf. He looks like a like normal
looking person who is a scholar. He is much more confident than his brother, as
you'll soon see,
and and just in generally a more accomplished wizard and
gracias. Me me goes as ah fuck me and he's
just the who's on first campaign. I pull his shirt off
(laughter)
- It'll stop, I promise, it'll stop soon.
Please put my shirt back on.
- Nope.
- Okay, I put it on myself.
- Oh no, should've been more specific.
- Hi Fookme, I'm Rod Dogan, you?
- Evil Steve, all in a little shirt.
- Ah, we have three, oh, these are your three privateers
you've told me so much about.
It's good to meet you all, I'm Fookme.
- I take his shirt off too.
- Oh, now, now, now, his shirt magically pops back on
as you take it off.
- He's a wizard, you're gonna have to do better than that.
- Yeah, you're gonna have to do better than that.
I am a wizard.
- Challenge accepted.
- Well, that's okay.
What seems to be the issue?
These three, they--
- I have an issue, your shirt's still on.
- Well, now look, maybe another time, pal.
- I'm gonna roll deception.
- Okay, go for it.
You're gonna try to deceive him to get him naked?
- Actually, I'm gonna roll persuasion.
- Deceive him, get me naked?
- You're gonna persuade him to get him naked?
- Get Fook me naked?
Wow, okay.
It's not getting naked, he's just taking his shirt off.
You're gonna attack him?
Yeah.
Persuasively sexual?
Okay, alright.
I mean, yeah, you laid it out for me.
It's a 19.
Okay, he says, "Is it customary where you're from?"
Yes, it's a customary where he's from and I'm trying to help him.
Alright, I guess I'm from sexo- sexo-land.
Sexo-land.
I've never heard of that in my studies.
It's real look regardless. I can take my shirt off. It's all all well
He takes his shirt off and he's very I got him to do it bitch now
They seem to be they look at the toilet and they try to member a remember a slave is this right
No
Well, yeah, I guess that is right. Yeah, see it was a wife slave a wife slave
The toilet used to be his wife and I think our slave.
No.
And he was a green frog.
A green frog wife slave.
And then I don't remember what happened after that.
Also we knew your brother.
Oh, why me?
We still knew your brother.
No.
No, his new name.
Fook you.
I pointed at him.
I'm Rock, don't get you.
Fook me.
[laughter]
What's your name again?
So stupid.
It's all my fault.
What's your name again?
Fook me!
Yeah, I'm RoeDog and you're Fook You.
Yeah Fook You.
Fook You.
That's your brother, your brother is Fook, we changed his name.
No, my brother's Why Me.
No, no listen, we changed his name, I don't remember how, and he's Fook You now.
Ah, he was always, well, rather.
Your brother's gonna Fook You.
Yeah.
Your brother will fuck your butt.
I think is his name now.
Well, you know, I'm glad he seems to have found his way.
He was always a bit of, you know, a little bit different, I guess.
So - What's that supposed to mean?
Ah, it's just, you know, he was smaller - You mean different.
He was shorter.
Well, he wasn't - I don't think that's what he meant.
Maybe, I don't know.
He always sort of was crying about things and -
Oh yeah, yep.
I tried to.
Oh, I know what you're talking about now.
Yep, crying about things.
Little bit of this.
Oh, oh, oh.
played basketball and he hurt his legs. He's doing a swish. Yep. A little bit of this.
Perfect three-point shot. Yep. Now I remember this guy. He looks, he's
looking in his his drawers. Ah, here it is. He pulls out. What's he doing in them damn
drawers? I'm sorry, I'm miming it. He's opening up drawers. Not his drawers. Oh, okay. And he
pulls out a sort of like, it looks like a piece of like metal that's been like
jagged and been ripped off of something else and it has a bit of a ethereal glow
to it and he says, "Okay, all of you put your hands on this. We're gonna try to
see what you are grasping at here." It's not okay. It's very rare to have a
a collective sort of coincidental memory of can I do a joke before you do that if
you need to do a joke of course can he can does he does does it can fuk me give
me a piece of food you guys just ask this way I think it's just just wait get
ready do you have any food that I could eat really quick I'm just hungry before
we do this diabetes oh well diabetes in that well I don't know is he a sorcerer
- Who's that?
- I have a--
- He has dirt-a-beeties.
- Just get me a piece of meat or something.
Just a piece of meat.
Just say it's a piece of meat or something.
- How do you have a piece of meat?
- I mean, I could give you--
- I don't know.
He was eating earlier.
I can see the plate.
I can see the plate with the meat.
Can I just have it?
- Oh, there's crumbs on his face.
He obviously eats meat.
- Okay, sure.
- Meat crumbs.
- Yes, here's the flank steak I was having.
- I have a fork and knife and I cut into it and I take a bite and I go, "Fook me, it's
practically raw."
(laughter)
- We can go back.
- Oh, the bathroom, I get it, that's funny.
Okay, so if you all put your,
this is a piece from another world.
This metal here, I'll explain, but first--
- Yeah, piece of crap.
What am I supposed to do with this?
Eat it, okay.
- No, no, don't eat it.
try to eat it? He could try to eat it. He's gonna do a strength check against you.
Okay. Try to stop you from doing that. Do I need to do a strength check? Yeah, yeah. It's gonna be a
strength, a little strength contest here. Okay, yeah. 15. He got, he got, I mean he got 18. Yeah,
I see that. Plus three. Dude, that would, I could have changed everything about this damn campaign.
It just would have been very confusing, but uh, he says. I could have become the thing.
But when you grab it, I have to say, because you, you did grab it in that,
You briefly have flashes of what had happened prior,
the events that led up to you guys becoming
famous privateers.
You know, you see flying into the,
you see somebody getting stabbed in a ritual,
but you can't make out who it is.
You see yourselves flying in the air
and landing into a forest with,
you think it's four people,
but it feels like there's a fifth person there.
Like you experience that briefly.
And can I remember it as four people and a toilet?
Yeah, okay. That's fine. All right. I think that's still good. You haven't got through the full
ritual yet. He says, and Fook-mee obviously senses that too. And he's like, "Okay,
there is somebody in your past. This is, please, all of you, I need all of you to put your hand
on this. Don't try to eat it this time." At least not yet. I'll try to eat it.
You're going to try to eat it? Okay. Yeah.
Let's try that.
You're really good.
Okay.
Okay, that's a six plus.
Where's my...
It's right there.
It's right here, bud.
I really should have him cast a spell, but it's...
You really should take off your indoor sunglasses, I would say.
I can't.
Oh, he got a crit 20.
Oh.
Dude, what the f...
He's the strongest guy ever.
Yeah, you're a wizard.
You should be weak.
I guess I don't need these anymore, because I don't need to read this.
I will eventually, though.
You're going to also try to eat it, Matt?
Okay.
That is for the people who are watching.
I'm going to try to eat it.
eventually though. You're gonna also try to eat it, Matt? Okay.
That is for the people at home. He's just shaking it tight.
Oh boy.
What'd you get? It's a strength. Yeah, I got 12. What'd you get?
What'd you get? I got a 13. No way.
Okay, you grab it, you eat it.
Yes! Say the thing.
No, oh my god, folk folk me. It's practically wrong. It's practically wrong. Yep
There we go. Pretty good
And you like that eat or and my eyes light up. Yeah, you are having a sort of a real episode you were remembering
You're not just remember so God if you think about what this the implications of this would be
So you're not just I touch my belly to remember it - you're not just remembering
these lakes
Shades of memory you remembering like moment by moment everything that happened to you leading up to this
it is like an excruciating amount of like
Information that is being funneled into your frontal lobe right now, so roll a wisdom saving throw
What'd you get?
Nice I
Think you will lose your mind soon. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I have a pretty strong feeling about that oh
Oh
Feels like you're just rolling these for no reason no it's gonna be it's it's 3d 12 that one is a weird
for any sort of
Feedback from this thing
Okay
So you take 15 damage, like psychic damage from this, but you also remember Sullivan perfectly.
Not as a toilet.
As a frog.
He does.
The toilet was a frog that we knew?
Huh?
What's a frog?
Frog and his name was, it's a green amphibian and it hops.
What's an amphibian?
Kinda like a reptile.
What's a reptile?
Kinda like a Komodo dragon.
Oh!
Okay.
So basically, it's a few steps away from a Komodo dragon.
What happened to this toilet, Frog?
Wait, I think I remember that.
We were in a...
I think I remember what was happening to him.
Touch his tummy.
Wait.
touch his tummy. I can't think right now I'm like there was mm-hmm there was a
white woman in the water and my uncle fucked her. You remember her nose is
bleeding. Yeah yeah you guys touch his tummy and it comes where you guys
remember he basically in this sense it's sort of like he has all of the the
concrete details you two remember specifically going into the terrifier
realm and you two being the ones who convinced the prince to stab solvent 500
times and that is what you remember I don't remember a thing either wait
actually I think the toilet somebody took a doo-doo and put it into the into the
toilet a knife-shaped poop a very sharp doo-doo that is what I'm remembering put
it in and out of the toilet remembering a poop that looks like a knife you guys
he's going to roll deception on this wizard. He's trying to help you okay. I
was lying. It's okay. You can't it's fun.
I admit I'm lying and yeah still
to do. I got a twenty. It's open three different apps. He's going to roll
inside on that yeah. No he's like he thinks you still think it's poop. He
You said you're lying.
Yep.
So what do you actually remember?
I think I am...
Knife-shaped like poop?
I think I am remembering a knife-shaped like poop.
And you?
There was a frog named Skon.
I don't really know what you're going into more.
Do any of you know a knife-shaped like poop?
Do you know what the frog's name is?
Brelebin.
Su...
Son of a...
Scrub-a-ding.
Scrotum in little hold on and he goes rub-a-dub he goes to your time I think it
was poop or something he goes to your tummy and we name the crap that was a
different world and he goes to your tummy and he tries to he's like
searching and trying to remember he goes ah he died outside this realm your
friend or slave. You seem to have all confusing psychosexual feelings about this.
Friend, slave, wife. I don't know. I'm pretty, now that I have touched his stomach, I
remember that you guys were married. I don't remember it. We worked at his
general store. Oh he was our boss. He was our, that's what it was. It was like a
work, it was a work relationship. What no he would, you remember and that he would
boss you around because he was your wife? No, I think because it...
Yeah, I'm remembering the wedding perfectly now. Oh my god.
We went to the ladies thing and then he got... we all woke up and he was
married and there was a... and they were... the ring that they had, they
each... Oh, you guys are remembering that prank we played that didn't...
was a there was a ceremony in frog culture you got the ring I remember that do you
remember it perfectly or do you guys remember that we were playing a prank on
you to make you think we're getting married because we would never do
something like that I don't think either of you are there wasn't that no I start
I start rubbing my belly really hard it was not a prank
remember it not be a practice you were never you never know I mean we planned it
actually I remember roll wisdom saving throw I remember feeling emotional at
your wedding because it was so you're so in love you fell for the prank that's
pretty pathetic you felt emotional cuz I felt absolutely nothing you married it
till a night tears rolling down my cheek I got a 21 okay cool you're yeah you're
safe you're safe anytime you try to remember this it's gonna hurt you cuz
you ate it but you will remember it like perfectly every time he says
Um, well, there are legends of those who die outside our realm to not be...
Can I poop this out now?
It's gonna take some time, I'm afraid.
Ah, crap.
They're not dead, in our sense.
If he truly died in the Terrifier Realm like your tummy told me...
Well think of it like this.
Sullivan died in the Terrifier Realm, so while it erased him from other realms, it was a cessation
of life outside of the realm he originated in, but not to the other realms. Does that
make sense?
Say it, what?
He's dead here, but he technically exists beyond it, because he didn't die in the realm he
was properly established in.
All right. Okay.
Regardless, you'll need to sail. If you really-
I'm rubbing my belly right now, and I'm remembering the night I watched my uncle fuck the white
lady of the water of the woods.
All right, you gotta roll again. You keep doing this to yourself.
just have perfect memory. I'm going, "Oh yeah. Oh yeah." You're gonna get hurt. Nine. That's
like the fifth time you've checked what your wisdom is. Well, let me roll that. Uh-oh. You're
dead. Yeah, I'm dead. You're probably dead. I'm dead because I have... Wait, wait, wait.
'cause I started with 19 HP. You're dead. Yeah. But I was maxed out at 27. You were passed
out. You were passed out remembering your uncle fucking that woman. That's a good last
memory. Oh yeah! Does he need to hear this too? Nah, he's pretty much just there to fuck
shit up. We can tell. We'll have Grassius, me amigo, who's gonna try to stabilize you.
Okay, he's able to stabilize you.
We would have had to enter initiative and did death-saving throws, but gracias mi amigo is able to stabilize you.
Either way, if the legend is true, you'll have to sail to realms deep.
You see, every realm has a gate, or so it's said, that connects us to other realms.
Or rather, could connect us to other realms.
This hasn't been done in anything except legend, until of course, those fools over at St. Anthony's
Parish.
I thought we were in legend.
Well, you're a legend.
Isn't that what fantasy is?
No, it's different.
Oh, okay.
That's fantasy different than legend.
St. Anthony's Parish contacted the Terrifier Realm, hence the situation we're in.
To go around the proper channels to call forth a vengeful god would have caused great unrest,
So it's good you stopped that, but it seems in your efforts to stop that, you've lost
a comrade who seems near and dear to you.
More like a commode!
Now Realm's Gate cannot be reached by normal means.
Frankly, it's never been reached at all, except in legend.
The pirate king Virtuegood, whose port and this archipelago is his namesake, he's said
to have sailed with his fearsome crew to Realm's Deep, never to be seen again.
It was his final adventure.
And daring means to escape death.
Many believed he did, many believed he didn't.
They are like equally likely in my eye, but actually it's more likely he's dead.
But don't let that dissuade you.
If you really want to find your friend, you're going to have to sail west, deeper into the archipelago.
You must sail beyond the reach of the Terrafire's kingdom as well.
Now the governor and I can't sanction this, so we can turn a blind eye.
So you're gonna sanction it?
We're gonna turn a blind eye.
Okay, I do this.
I have a letter.
I do the two fingers into the eyes.
Either way, I did write this monologue, so I'll continue.
If you are found out, you will not be welcomed here.
You may be heroes, but journeying to realms deep, even if it seems to be mere legend or
fantasy will not please some who've joined the Council of Late.
So I'm alive right now?
Yeah.
I can speak no no you're you're passed out you would have to get a health
potion I just wanted to ask if we can what if we do it by accident what if we
do it by accident well I mean there's gonna be no difference for the
pleasure men who are on the council now Oh God look God because of the recent
events in the kingdom the pleasure men are now on the council they likely don't
want anything at all to lessen the power of discharge their God who's raised in
standing since the King Nardwuar has now fallen out of favor. You'll have to head
to Cape Shit and sail until-- Oh I get it. Oh yeah, took me a second. Very well
written yes thank you not like Cape Cod no get it Cape shit shit what it's like
doo-doo but also like Cape Cape Cod chips oh actually I misread what I wrote here
Cape spit is what I meant because spit is a type of okay yeah that's why I did
that spit is a type of a land formation anyway you have to sail it to the port
City of Angelfire. I don't get it at all. It doesn't make any fucking sense. I thought it was poop.
That's why I need my glasses. My cool sunglasses. Because then I actually can't read what I wrote.
You'll have to sail into the port city of Angelfire. Angelfire is the last city in
the Terrafire's kingdom. Beyond that is unknown. We only have some knowledge as
to what goes beyond. Perhaps you'll gain a better sense of what lies beyond once
you reach Angel Fire. This is you're taking a picture of me with the sunglasses.
Fucking asshole. Patrick just took a creep shot.
Yeah. He's wearing sunglasses.
He has a little, he has a skirt on. I don't have.
And he's sitting on a glass chair. No, I don't have my, my, my regular prescription
glasses broke. And so I only have my prescription sunglasses. And it's very hard for me to read
the text I wrote. I don't like zooming in because then I have to zoom out and then
I have other notes. Anyway, so he continues. He says to you all, "If you want to go on this
journey to realms deep and find your friend Sullivan at the end of this realm,
it's not going to be an easy one and you'll not receive much from anyone who
catches wind of it. I would be discreet about your journey, but..." You say catch
wind and my past out body just goes.
It's past wind I think right?
Well you're going to catch it in a second.
No I just caught the wind.
Yeah I grabbed it in my hand.
I put it back into his mouth.
I put it into his mouth.
I crack up the fart in my hands.
Can that work as a smelling salt?
In what way?
I just don't want him to lose any of his life essence and die.
It brings you your conscious.
Look, if you all wish to go on this journey,
we can give you ample supplies and enough gold
to be able to go to the correct port towns.
If, of course--
- Ample, you say?
- The governor wishes to sanction this.
These three have been amazing, wonderful privateers.
I would happily do this for them.
- Gracias.
- Gracias. - Mi amigo.
- Gracias, mi amigo.
- They are all my friends.
(laughing)
- Thank you, my friend.
- Thank you, my friends.
Thank you my friend.
Your name is Thank You My Friend now.
Oh no! We're pretty much the name changers.
One of us is a notary.
Yeah.
You guys gonna do this? You guys gonna go to
realms deep? No. No. That would be fine. You guys could just fuck around and be pirates.
Damn.
What do you guys want to do?
Should we go on an amazing quest to save
Sullivan the frog or should we hang out?
From my from my my inventory I pull out a scroll that's a map to babe island
So we'll make our way there
Yeah, we have a map to realms deep right here and it's an island
It's like an aisle that looks like two boobs. So I have okay. I'll add that so I have a map
I'm not I haven't finalized it yet
But I do have a map of the archipelago that I'm working on and I will I will add Bay by Lynn to it
But don't don't look don't look I have to finish it you guys will sell West
During this session so you shouldn't barring anything
Magical on my table of pirate events so wait which way is you should run?
You shouldn't run into the rest of my map. Hopefully. Yes, well, which way is Rome steep the east it's West
Okay, East is back towards the Terrifier Kingdom
what's north and what's south I mean north there's some scant islands south
similarly there's no game like there's generally clan islands this is generally
clan island there's nothing of note I mean like it's okay so our the options
you're giving us or you go back to the first you could just say I could go west
you could keep going north I guess and like there will you said there's nothing
there's no islands. There's no settlements that at least that here's
the what's a that I know of as a so can we even if we're on there could be
other nations. If you guys choose to go north, I can I can try to I can like
figure out a little bit more of the geography. I'm being very transparent
about my what if we do I feel I think we did this exact same thing last time
when you gave us a place that we clearly had to go. What if we go like
northwest or southwest, just me look at where you are on the map and we can
goof off more. Let me see what's north west of you guys, because I do I mean
the maps not
whichever has a cool, whichever direction as a cool thing. That's not
the main quest. Can you just tell us where to go and we'll go there, but you
want to go. It needs to be a little bit annoying to you. So if you go, you want
to go not want us to go right now. This is how I think we need to head south
south to Mexico. South is there is an island. There's a few things there that
Wait.
Very much not a part of the bank.
Where is Gracias...
I'll invite this to me.
Wait, where is Gracias mi amigo from?
Gracias mi amigo?
Uh, I mean he's from Port Virtue Good.
He was born and raised there.
Port Virtue Good's been established for a long time.
Like, like relatively.
Like, like, like a hundred, hundred fifty years.
So he, he was governor based on sort of like, like,
"Oh, I've been here for a while, yadda yadda yadda."
So he's really old?
Mm-mm.
Let's, hmm.
I think we gotta head south.
We can head south.
You head south, it will... it's not gonna... I won't like it, so if you want to do something I don't like, you can do that.
Will it make it a shitty...
No.
No, I've got stuff ready for it, it's just then I'm...
I am going to treat the map I made seriously, which means I'll have to deal with the fact that you go south.
So I've got stuff prepared for this session.
Wait, will you not move your head at all?
Are you trying to look at the map?
You trying to look at the map?
Guys, I don't think we should go south.
He's looking at the McDonald's logo now.
There's seriously a bunch of pictures of hamburgers south.
is there doesn't that mean we should go south let's go south okay cool
yes you guys want to leave you guys wait I gotta get a health potion or some shit
first you can long rest again I mean you can just you can yeah I mean you guys
can go to the tavern and long rest in the you thought there's gonna be a way you
could do it that wasn't in the app
- You haven't used any of your hit die
or any of your resources that would,
I mean hit die, I don't think you have any spells.
So hit die, you probably have--
- I used a long rest.
- Yeah, so if you just do long rest, you're good there.
Yeah, you guys sleep in the tavern.
- I'm long resting too.
- Or the inn rather.
It's called Inn Thank You Very Much.
- What's up?
- It's called Inn Thank You Very Much.
- Not this again.
- So what, I made it before I knew you guys
were going to the innkeeper.
So what's the name of this inn?
Thank you very much.
Gracias mi amigo.
No, that's the governor.
I'm thank you very much.
De nada.
Of course.
Wait, who's that?
Why did I say that?
I'm the chef, of course!
Oh, it's de nada.
De nada!
See voo play.
Yes, it is I, the baker.
I'll see voo play.
I'll create as many characters as you need me to.
I'm rondo-ing you.
there was only thank you very much and a chef whose name was dug which you've
changed how to I guess whatever the fuck did not a dunk is sharing whatever
whatever the fuck
but there's no whatever the fuck I'm not gonna do I mean like I'll make it
happened
here's the thing we could do we can you know we can play this game I could just
make a whole world based on your stupid shit
let's do it who you like to keep going you said I'm gonna be a movie like that
but that's about no it's about emojis emojis. You idiot I went again. Are
there
any
there any emojis in the in
yes or no,
I have been doing D and D for a really long time. It's some magic somebody
asking me. Are there any of those
never occurred to me emoji. I just saw the B emoji in the in here. I'm chasing
down we're chasing the BMO yeah but I'm trying to introduce myself to him but
I'm walking up to them really fast ago hi I'm Rod Ogun you slow down I'm Rod
Ogun you this is the B emoji trying to fuck the B emoji you guys could just
actually sail instead yeah I think we should I think we can do okay all right
we will sail okay East or West I think we just do West let's just give let's
just give this guy's there an island or magical item where no where I mean it's
further out you're not gonna probably find it this this session I'm gonna be
you
okay you can go back okay just go back to terrifying okay what are you going on in
the terrifying kingdom I have I want to pay I want to go west coast in West okay
what are you voting for I don't even know anymore just pick a direction what
are you voting for I'm gonna let's go north okay I pick south so we need a
tiebreaker what if we just say what about the 30 guys on the ship that are
all controlled by badges no I mean you can ask them yeah we just asked them yes
the rubbers yeah oh we'll we'll we will you told us you would make us your
slaves at the amusement park so you guys could bring them to the amusement park
you know what actually that's a pretty good idea yeah we can't bring them but
we were gonna open a SeaWorld types like spit separate locations
so the amusement park so Gal Gadot is a part of the eastern part of the kingdom
okay so you'd have to go like you have to go through is is Islam I think we
have to go no I think we go what I think we should go west is a little bit we
know that's a new brave lion's need to be on the coast yeah yeah yeah we don't
want to put it in the same place I think wait you could do that - how rich are we
really um really rich are you really I mean like could we do we have enough
capital to just start this thing by ourselves or do we need to go back to
Shark Tank start which thing the SeaWorld thing yeah yeah second part well
Well so to get the, I mean you could do like, promissory notes, and you could get, you could
pull, you'd have to talk with, you'd have to talk with Ola, she, who is your, sort of
your patron for everything.
Yeah, yeah, I remember her.
You'd have to talk with her about like, getting additional capital.
Ola?
Or what if we just go around her and give like, you know.
We could just get a treasure chest.
Do like, futures, contracts kind of thing, and like, then just beg her after the fact,
too.
We could also treasure chest it would probably be enough money. We probably have a treasure chest.
No, we could get we could also just get one probably. Remember earlier when I said we should get that treasure chest?
No. The game before? That was a good point. Yeah, you're right. What treasure? I don't know what you're talking about.
This is tight. On Weird Beard's ship, I said we should get his treasure chest. I said there was probably not.
There was treasure there! There was treasure there!
No, there was treasure there!
No, you were asking about a magic sword. Mm-hmm. I remember I edited that this morning.
Here's the thing, I kind of like this. I think this is breaking new ground in the actual play
world. We can really like, I think your shared hatred of Sullivan is creating new kinds of
play where we can right now, if you guys don't want to go on like the critical path because
Sullivan's annoying and you guys want to play around.
I don't even know that yet. I just think, I mean, I don't want to hang out with a toilet
all that bad. What if we just roll a d4 and that's the direction we go?
good idea so it's yeah one is one is no or him come up with which okay yeah
which is which I'll roll it um let's do like one is north that's what I said
copying we're gonna do you want to do clockwise no copy to two is easier to
is east three is is is South Forge West Forest West do it okay ready yep that's
what was that East all right this is so fun roll again no no let's do it let's do
it no I've got I have the one that I don't it has so here's the thing I mean
like next session you can change direction we could do it like that
spending 15 minutes on where to go let's just hit the yeah okay we're going east
back to where we were before. We all just decided to go east for no reason. Let's go.
All right, cool. Let me roll. I have to roll. Where's my d10? There it is. Okay.
Sorry, I have some stuff. Thank you for apologizing.
Pat is stacking dice. Yeah. Okay. I can't look. He physically can't stop making dice towers.
Okay, cool. That's fun. Okay. I have no idea where it went. So it's a
it's pretty good weather for sailing. Um, you guys are able to head east. I shoot a gun at the bow.
What? At the forward mast. You don't have a gun? The bow. There's no such thing as a gun yet.
I shoot a bazooka at the sails. You had to get a derailment in so fast.
You said, "I shoot a gun at the bow." I shoot a bazooka at the sails.
You just had a primal urge, "I need to interrupt you right now."
I need to interrupt you right now. I shoot a gun at the bow.
Alright. So he shoots a gun at the bow, and then what happens?
shoots his um yeah i guess he shoots uh just a cross boy pirates have guns
yep not wait a second we haven't we didn't see
do we have is there guns there are cannons there was a can there are
flintlock pistols in this world yo you haven't have way okay before we
still can we all just go to the store and each buy a flintlock pistol please
can we all do that yeah i buy a flintlock bazooka can we all only use
guns this game i'm down there are all the all the yes
My crossbow turns into a musket. My dagger turns... no that stays.
And then...
No, it's a cutlass.
My cutlass...
You're gonna change your rapier into a cutlass.
I think that's probably pretty good.
And then my dagger is a pistol.
This is fun. We didn't do really a session zero.
This is kind of like a session zero. Impromptu session zero.
This is like a negative one.
[Laughter]
I'm very down for you guys to go to like a general store and like...
So, okay, we don't have to go that I'll just I'll just do a Patrick it
I know I said it was a war or I'm changing it to a war gun and I just hit people with it doesn't
I I think what we can do then is try and think of like I would rather you guys have
Let me make a note of that for next time and I can make you guys like some of my own
Becomes an arm strike
There are some pretty good
There's some interesting gun mechanics out there and I would want to like make sure I do a little bit more research
- Can I just change my crossbow to a gun?
- Of course you can.
- Sick.
- You have an Uzi?
- I'd say right now.
- He's just like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Next session, next session, we can do,
I can update your whole outfit.
We can make you guys pirates way more.
But yeah, sailing--
- With the hat.
- With the hat, and you know I gotta have the hat.
- Yes.
- So you guys, very funny,
you guys all have this sudden urge,
you remember to think about Sullivan you remember him how important he was to you
and you immediately sail in the complete opposite direction. Well no we realized
how much we fucking hated it. Yeah and so you sail in the opposite direction and
we're trying to prove that the world is round we're gonna end up in the same place.
So your guys like I don't know if I described you guys your ship that much so
there's like four levels to your galleon the Caribbean Royale or the Royal
Caribbean there's the main deck right there's a quarter deck the quarter deck
is on top of the main deck it's sort of like the main deck is like the middle of
it I'm making sure you guys a picture or two that I have that's very useful that's
you so like the quarter deck is on top of the big ass that's like the raised
front and back part. Yes, exactly. Yeah. So where the helm is right and and the the foremast and
the uh I wish I used to have the I think I have this written yeah yeah the mizzenmast and foremaster
in the back and the front of this respectively. You have the lower deck uh the lower deck has
basically where the crew sleeps um you guys sleep in the main in the in the captain's quarters.
Sick. Which is towards the hull uh towards the back the uh the stern um the crew sleeps towards
the bow in the main deck there's a lower deck and then there's a bow yeah the bow
yeah there's the hold the hold has we have a brig in the hold yes you do you
have a makeshift brig I mean you have like is there bilge down there bilge I
actually don't know more ballast ballast oh I actually like bilge Oh interesting
somebody doesn't know as much about boats as he's trying to hey patches well
where the grog at the grog is in the lower deck I go to the lower day do and
in the hold is that where Davey Jones well the grog I should say the grog that
is accessible for the weak supplies is in the lower deck the the hold has like the
majority of your like food stuffs like our guys what's our what's our figure
head what was it what was on galax Q pack cuz it was this ship belonged to what's
her name what's his name French ball mm-hmm what was his figurehead his
figurehead was a picture of me and what are you doing in the picture it's my
presidential portrait okay he wanted his favorite nephew to be his ship that's
adorable that's so he couldn't get you so he just gave the sculptor a picture
made a picture frame. I'm not paying anymore. It has like a fold in the back. Patridge I tried to do my best here I think I think this is
pretty good though right it's it's sort of a kind of a postmodern take on is
this trunchable before he became before he died before he yeah yeah before he
- You came too old to speak before he died.
'Cause he had a brief moment of lucidity
right before his death where he slow danced with you
and you went through puberty.
- Oh yeah.
- Yeah.
Look, I tried my best here.
I kinda think it ended up being
a more of a post-modern sort of thing.
- So how old, this is a flashback.
- Yeah, you're like a teenager or like a--
- Yeah, that is, that is, that is, that looks pretty good.
- One day this ship will be yours, kid, I'm telling you.
- Oh, I can't wait.
Oh yeah, you're my-
Oh, that's gonna be awesome!
You're my favorite-
Hold on.
What's that? The call of adventure.
You see, I'm a very famous hero.
I need to go.
Oh, I can't wait to be a famous hero like you!
That's right.
You're gonna have sorta issues because I abandon you all the time for adventure.
But you're gonna live up to those issues.
Yeah, you're my favorite uncle since my mom and dad died.
That's right.
I was here too!
*laughter*
Right.
Yeah, your dirt friend is here.
And flashback!
Okay, yeah. So yeah, and you guys hear...
[snort]
I thought that was cozy!
You guys hear the... sound. You guys hear a sound. It sounds like a...
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
You guys...
You shouted so fast I'm like, "Is that a fucking ghost?"
You guys hear a sound. Your crew on deck, your... your... your butt, your... you guys have your...
My what?
Your butt.
Pardon me?
If you guys remember, it's your butt.
Your butt's on the poop deck.
You take that back.
Your face is about to be on my poop deck.
Oh snap.
I'm raw dogging you.
Gracias.
Oh snap. Oh no he didn't.
I've never heard that before.
Talk to the hook.
No.
Talk to the hook, or you're gonna get a peg in the ass.
(laughing)
Yep, I'm gonna peg you.
- That doesn't, I don't know what that means.
- I'm raw dogging you with my peg.
- No.
(laughing)
I think I want to quit being a pirate.
- That's how I introduce myself to people.
Is I say my name and then I point to my peg leg
and say, "With my peg."
(laughing)
- I'm raw dogging you with my...
Everyone everyone listening the I'm a hooker the future
future episodes are going to be have more direction. I promise yeah East
East and East and East is forever. Yeah, that's that's our thing. Now we're
trying to prove the world's round. That's a we're going to have to go all
the way around from the other side at the at this time. Do people believe that
earth is round no okay yeah we're gonna prove it yeah that's what we're gonna go
fucking that's the you guys didn't go Magellan on this yeah that's the campaign
yeah we go all the way we prove the earth is round well it's actually a
plan a bomb yes we are planet ebon yeah we've we've way is plenty we're trying
to get as far away as you're a man from Sullivan we accidentally prove that the
Yeah, we think we're going...
We're getting this far away from Sullivan.
[Laughter]
And we accidentally become the greatest
explorers ever. We found the angle.
Wait, that is so funny.
Yeah, that's perfect.
You guys are listening
live to
us figuring out maybe the greatest D&D
campaign of all time. You guys realize
that Sullivan is west
and you decide we need to
go as far away as possible
East and you end up going around yeah okay I like that adventure here's a
thing okay I guess I gotta figure that out because I have in my mind your map
the geography yeah well the geography of the planet is it's a planet so the length
of time it would take you to go all the way around what would that 180 days it's
- It's not around the planet in 180 days?
- A year and a half?
Sailing?
How big is planet E-bomb in comparison to Earth?
- How long did Greta Thunberg do it?
- How big is planet E-bomb?
- Planet E-bomb?
I mean, it's not as big as Earth.
It's sort of--
- So it's smaller.
- That's correct.
- Maybe the size of Mercury?
- It's closer to--
- Or the moon?
- The moon is actually--
- So a sixth of the size.
- So it's pretty small, yes.
- Would it take the amount of time
for Mercury to go around the sun?
we're gonna do science right now and i can't have a longer i think i love
science
would also have around the place a little around the world it takes three years
okay so a sixth of that is half a year yeah so it's six months
no shit so bad
six months yeah we need six six months eighty eight days
uh... here we go with the everybody listening to the other ninety days
whenever everybody listening
A little behind the scenes thing here.
It is 180 days.
Around Ebaums world in 180 days.
Yeah, that's what I knew it.
The guys are about to go on tour and so we wanted to make sure that we got a couple episodes
in because we were excited about that.
If that's okay, is that okay?
Oh no, I just almost fell out of my chair.
He does that every single day.
Everyone needs to know.
No, no, so what I want, what I like about this is this is going to, so for everyone
at home, this is going to give me enough time to sort of rework this campaign around the
idea of you guys going around the world the other way. I'm going to figure out
the map of E-bomb, the pre-gun city map of E-bomb. I'll figure out, to
the best of my ability, I'll leave some blanks, strategic blanks as a DM. I
really, I think this is extremely fun. Okay, I like this. 180 days.
180 days, so it'll be a six-month journey. 180 sessions. 180 sessions. 180 episodes.
God willing, right?
But, okay.
Meanwhile,
your first
moment in this adventure.
You guys hear a song.
Everybody roll a charisma saving throw.
Oh dear God.
Oh, crit one.
Okay.
It literally was on 15 and I saw it just tip over.
I got a nine.
Nine, what about you Pat?
You've got pretty great charisma. Yeah
Thank you. Damn it. I opened up the wrong. Hold on
Actually, you have excellent charisma too because you're your pal 17 Dogen. I rolled a 17
Okay
Dogen
Mm-hmm evil. I rolled a nine. Oh, yeah
You guys hear the most beautiful song you've ever heard. Oh
Something in a thing I'm hearing how to sing it by the same Pablo sing it I'm gonna sing it yeah, okay?
Whatever we're hearing or else. I can't find the words to describe this girl without being disrespectful
oh
My god, uh do you hear that bullshit? Yeah?
I'm going crazy. Oh my god. The same sound is him just for a different reason you're passing the
the shard from another realm through your ass right now.
(laughing)
- Oh.
Oh, oh my God.
- You see, your, your, your, your,
sorry, my words are failing me here.
Your quartermaster, Wayne, the half-orc,
he says, he's, oh shit, actually I need him to roll.
- Quartermaster, half-orc.
- Uh-oh.
He's like, we're gonna have to sail towards that sound.
We need to figure out what it is.
No, it's a, it's a, uh, don't do that.
You're in the bathroom.
It's a, I, don't do that.
It's a siren of some sort.
Weeeeee, that kind of siren?
What do you mean?
It's, I, well, I mean, I got like a 17, right?
Yeah, you know what it is.
You guys have been sailing for a while.
Yeah, I know it's a siren.
And then we're going to roll one more charisma saving throw.
All of us?
No, no, I'm rolling.
Just me.
Okay.
Good, because I got a three.
So it is sirens singing on the rocks.
There's also a ship in a bikini that is singing, and your ship hears that and it fails and
it screws the sailing throat.
And it is sailing towards these rocks, and you see these sirens there.
You two are completely enamored.
You are the only one who is not enamored, Patrick.
Can I move the ship?
You can try to grab the helm from Wayne right now.
I'm going to try and do that.
What are you doing?
Get away from here!
I'm being random.
What do you want to do to do it?
Do you want to just like wrestle him forward?
Do you have like a...
Because you've got more tools than a toolkit.
I do Cosby Show intro face.
I do the...
I put my hands over my face and I go like...
I don't know what that does.
It just made me laugh.
Does that make Wayne laugh?
Yes.
Roll performance check.
Did you get a crit 20?
A nat 20?
He goes like...
And he's supposed to be a doctor?
(laughter)
- He's so silly.
- Okay, yeah, you can take control of the wheel.
- I guess I just steer it away from wherever the siren is.
- Okay, the siren--
- Why don't you wanna hear this song?
- 'Cause I don't wanna have sex with these women.
It's not gonna, they're gonna lead us into rocks
and they're gonna break the ship.
- Okay. - Huh?
- Huh? - Huh?
- Huh? - My hand keeps--
- She's not my girl. - I keep like--
you've ever seen before. I keep involuntarily putting my hook hand down my pants and going
OW! OW! It's over and over. And in my pants too. Yeah. And in his pants too. The way that
body moving. You hear all this, this is rolling off your shoulders though. You've heard this,
you know, you got Acon's number. I know, yeah. You got this man. Can I call Acon on my pirate
phone? No, but that's a pretty good lie. They did have phones in pirate times. I've actually
wait wait wait can I call can I call a con on my soul stone why do you think a
comet have a soul stone he definitely soul stones in Wind Waker he definitely
got a pirate a cons of a con is definitely a pirate my bad yes sorry
I'm the DIC a pirate captain a con sounds sick that does sound cool sounds cool
yeah I think a con as a person doesn't make any sense but as a pirate sounds
pretty cool. I like your hat actually. Yeah, I could be wrong though. I'm gonna
roll to see if Akon's a pirate. I got a 12, he's a pirate.
It's a genius DM move. Yeah, the genius DM move is just do what you want.
I'll roll for it, fine. Okay, so you can try to steer the ship out of this
situation, Patrick. So for that I'm gonna have you, I mean this, this you
I'm trying to think of what the,
this should really be a strength check
because the ship itself has a will,
but it's moving towards.
You don't have to contend with Wayne anymore,
but you do have to contend with the ship's own will
as it is very attracted to the ship with the bikini
that is on the rocks.
- Okay.
- So roll a strength check,
and you can try other things too.
You can try to fuck with the sails,
if with throwing knives,
or you know, be playful with this.
- I look down, I stomp on the ship,
I say, "Hey, check this out." And I do Gangnam Style. You're going to try to out-charisma
the sirens? Yeah. Oh, I don't think it's going to work, man. You don't know that. Do a performance
check. If you get higher than 18. Wait, I wouldn't roll a charisma saving throw? No,
this is a performance check to try to charm the ship. It's really a persuasion check.
If you get higher than a natural 18, I'll let it go.
'Cause these are sign-wise.
- Higher than a natural 18?
- Yeah. - At or above an 18?
- Yes, at or above.
- Okay. - 'Cause these are sign.
- And it's a persuasion check?
- Disroll the die. - Performance.
- Yes, but it's nothing to do with your own natural charisma.
It's just the roll itself.
20! - Oh my God!
- No way! - Oh!
(laughing)
Holy shit, dude.
- Wait, two Nat 20s in like four rolls?
- No, I hope you guys have a good tour.
- In a row.
- I hope you guys have a good...
(laughing)
- We're done, we're done.
I hope you guys have a good tour.
(laughing)
You ship a voice of siren.
I'll see you guys next month.
- Wow.
- I just started enjoying the song, man.
(laughing)
- I'm sirening to "Gangnam Style."
- Gravitating to "Gangnam Style."
(laughing)
Perfect rendition of "Oh My God"
Sexy ladies
We all know the lyrics now
We're hoping
Sexy ladies
*imitates the beat*
Alright, perfect
Happy Halloween
[Music]