[MUSIC PLAYING]
All right, now we're rolling.
Last time on Trebuchet Village, end of ZEbomb's world.
We're going to take that again.
Yeah, let's go.
We're taking that one again.
OK, sorry about that.
We're not letting that one slide.
People pay for this.
Yep, you're right.
I'm sorry.
Wake up.
i think that a cool and we're really any more on trial to another in more time
yet and we're
last time on
refugee village
and c_d_ bombs world
after two-hour time
yeah
if you forget of thinking about it
so all of stuff that happened before that was
the gang decided they were going to take the ship
uh... and sailed down to beriberi to revive
quadro mud marks
uh...
and
there was a cat on board
they had a little interaction with that, there was a snake guy
that was such bullshit
there was other, i mean
well because other stuff happened
yeah i'm remembering it all now
i just think it's so funny that you couldn't hold yourself back
from showing us that the cat was a snake man instead of letting us just
forget about it we already forgot about it.
Just show this little...
The cat actually was a snake man but it's dead now.
You couldn't even let it be a snake man and like
escape or something and like come back to haunt us later.
Yeah you just realized...
Shut up! That's a good idea.
That's a really good idea.
But he was also a snake man.
It would have been such a better
move as a DM.
He turned to a snake and he slithered.
Remember me, I'm the cat from before.
Your stupidity with the ship he would have...
even have a voice for him yeah just what a way to write on that maybe now we're
already know because well I can well we'll see what I do with that we'll see
if there's a zombie cat we'll see what it does with that you see a very wet cat
now does anytime we see a cat or a snake man we're just gonna come in excuse me
are you the cat from before oh all right continue your little intro then there
Sorry to belittle it.
No, detritus and debris also.
I forgot about that.
No, I'm just trying to get it out of the way.
I forgot about detritus.
That was my fault.
Yeah.
So I've heard all of these.
I was really like not, I was really reaching with some of those.
Why are you not holding your microphone?
I'm not alive yet.
Then don't talk.
You either hold your microphone or you don't talk.
I'm weighing down the law right now.
okay I whiffed I should have just named my character detritus debris but I have a
new I have a whole thing that would have been so mad if you just changed it last
minute yeah yeah yeah yeah I would be mad about that and it was a whirlpool and
you could have sailed around it and would have risked capsizing or sailed in it
and done something really cool. Yeah. You sailed in it and...
A hundred, not on me at all. Patrick rolled a one on being able to help sort of steady the ship,
which led to me trying to figure out exactly what kind of DC you needed to not completely crash,
and you failed it. And you rolled another one on a death save. Yeah, and he died. And you ended up
in the underground or undercove layer of one Flint Lateralis. One mass
murderer. Yeah, yeah. Sort of a bemused scientist or inventor. Essentially a
Hitler. Who did not realize that he was Hitler. Basically a Sea Hitler. Yeah, a
A whirlpool Hitler. Yeah, see Hitler. And yeah and then you guys woke up and
pretty much immediately tried to kill him which is totally fair and then he
said I'm sorry I did not realize. You know I never asked if I should. Mm-hmm.
You know that whole thing. Yeah Jurassic Park. Right that's the one. Yeah and this
Jurassic Park would be in the future because of how far back in time this
fantasy world is. Right. And he looked at you guys, he says, "Anything I can
make it up to you?" and you guys were like, "Pretty much no." And he said, "What if I
gave you this submarine?" and you kind of like forgot about this. Oh yeah. All of our
friends died, hundreds of our... And he was about to tell you about the submarine and
just that, "If you're going to use it to leave, I have these for you."
Here, and he gives you guys two vials.
And he says, "Inside these are the temporary gill salves."
So you rub them on your ribs and you'll grow gills for about an hour.
And once you do, you'll be able to swim underwater if you need to.
Leave the submarine. And otherwise, the submarine, well, it's a very particular...
Just be careful with it if you're going to use it.
But I also, you also welcome to rest up.
You're telling people to be careful with stuff.
You also should probably rest up.
You guys look pretty battered.
Basically, you guys should probably take a long rest before you do anything else.
Okay, what kind of accommodations do we have over here at Mr. Laderalus' cave?
He has, I mean he has a cot for himself.
And then he has just sort of like...
Not a guest cot?
No, I mean he doesn't get guests usually.
Okay, so I'm in his cot.
Yeah, he probably kills all of them.
He will let you guys.
Sick son of a bitch.
He'll let you have his cots.
Yeah, I'm in his cot.
Okay, I sleep on him.
Okay.
I'd like to lay him down.
On Ladder Alice?
I'll sleep on him like he's my shadow.
It pretty much works.
He accepts it.
I deserve this.
I deserve it.
Yes, you do.
Mm-hmm.
Now make your nose shorter.
Okay.
I'm wetting his bed.
One second.
There we go.
It was hitting the back of my neck.
Okay.
He made his nose shorter.
Something gnomes can do.
You guys have a full rest.
You guys are healed up.
You have your spell slots back.
You're in a better place now.
You're ready to take the submarine out for a spin.
Okay.
Alright. I'm ready.
I see Patrick making a face.
He's gearing up for something.
Actually, on second thought,
I don't want to go in the submarine.
Yeah, actually, I think I will take yet another long rest.
at another long rest.
(laughter)
Okay, yeah, you guys sleep for another
eight hours.
(yawn)
I don't think you get the benefits of it if you do it in a row.
I think you double your health.
You triple your health?
You said triple.
Or we'll triple it. I know a way to triple it.
Yeah, of course, you can stay as long as you like.
I really fucked up.
I'm bored.
Oh man, I'm getting hungry.
What you got to eat in your digs?
Mostly fish and kelp.
I like kelp.
I like fish.
Always, always likes kelp.
Okay, I can make you guys a sort of kelp and fish bowl.
Do you have Krabby Patties?
No.
That's where it seems like this is going.
Maybe.
Alright, make me a fish bowl.
Why don't you roll to see if I have Krabby Patties?
Is this submarine red?
I rolled a 17.
Looks like I have Krabby Patties!
Yeah, Krabby Patties!
Alright, I'll eat a Krabby Patty.
Okay, so what is it? So, tell me the ingredients of a Krabby Patty, Patches.
Including?
Including just everything.
Yeah, just everything.
Well, there's some things that I can't say. You guys both know that.
You guys both know I can't say it.
I really thought that would work.
I'll get you one day, Patches.
Okay, I finished my Krabby Patty.
Okay.
Why is Krabby Patties making me tired?
[Laughter]
I don't know.
Alright, okay. What now? I think next you want to jump on the bed. Let's do it
Let's invent soccer and play it
I
Mean you guys do notice that like his lair is filled with with toys, but like oh my god
He has like a pogo stick a pro toys proto
I've never even heard of that like he has like primitive Legos. They're like wooden
almost
What are you doing?
I'm filming a video.
You have to pick up your mic.
I'm not alive, I can't do anything.
Why don't you listen?
It's so quiet.
You're not even pointing the speaker at the mic.
Okay, just because he's being annoying I'm getting into the submarine.
Okay, cool.
Alright, so you guys try to get into the submarine and suddenly, you hear a loud noise.
You hear a loud noise.
yellowing the way i'm getting into the summer okay cool
all right so you guys try to get into the submarine and suck suddenly
who
who are getting out of the site
i think i was in the book but i don't know what you know don't touch that
the submarine is net is not
an invention per se
well no
Oh no, no, no, no.
Oh no, oh no.
Oh no.
Who do we have here?
Hey, there it's me.
The chuggy singing submarine.
Yes I am a boat,
but I am your friend.
And I'll take you to the world's end.
Yes I am a giant
changeling.
but i am a hundred times of for
well so i have many spirits in one of them is me
the
the i_d_a_'s like a dot
what
uh... it's all i got the singing suffering
uh...
Hello everybody!
Chuggy.
I didn't even know.
Chugging.
I'd never even heard of a submarine until...
Oh my god.
I took a lot of Percocet, now I'm like this.
Percocet's an herb we invented.
Do you have eyes?
Yeah, I have like my window, the two front windows.
Okay, so it's full Cars logic.
So, most changelings, when they transform, can only stay within...
I used to be a human form, and then I took a bunch of Percocet.
Which is a thing that he invented.
It is me. It is me.
Or what's the...
We co-invented. We world-built it together.
What's the Flint Lateratus...
Lateratus...
Lateratles.
It's so fucking hot in here.
He did take a bunch of Percocet.
So the lore we've come up with...
Yeah, I thought that the doctor invented it.
Well, a lot of... Percocet is a very rare herb.
yeah that
uh... come from the art that she's changed the way things can take
and if they do uh...
uh... it can potentially unlock
uh...
rare forms of changing change links technically
can only change within their size so
chuggy
here has other
i mean you can see like a normal changes are used to be a normal guy named chuggy
yeah
and he's checking the changeling
yeah so and i think it's a good idea
i have a lot of other than i want to
do it i am so i hear this in character
this is why so wait you know i took a
bunch of percocet and then one day
molecules in my body started changing
what's a molecule what the hell are you
talking about word i learned it from
science well could be i mean oh that i'm
familiar yeah yeah yeah popular are
taking that in middle school now yeah
Alchemy class, god damn.
Oh my god, my lab partner, Mr. Frederick,
My alchemy teacher had the fattest ass!
Oh my god, he's sexual.
My alchemy teacher in middle school was a veteran
and we all laughed when he saw him crying on Veterans Day.
[laughter]
I'm uh, so I'm just a-
My alchemy teacher had a thyroid problem
and that's why her ass was so big.
That's not a joke.
[laughter]
Mine wasn't a joke either.
I guess I'm just a little confused as to, I mean do you, so will you always be just a ship?
No!
Okay, so...
Please explain.
I have four separate personalities!
I'm just, uh, great.
So here's the thing, a changeling can technically turn into any form and mimic any voice that
they've met before.
Now, for our purposes, we've narrowed down, obviously you can still turn into any form
that you've seen, but we've narrowed down the voices for everyone's...
Well I have, I have, I can change into anything but it's like the...
He has three that he's used around when he's like wants to not be a submarine and be a normal person.
But he mostly likes being a submarine.
That's what he is.
Oh you are just a submarine that can do, that can do a little bit of disguise work.
Yeah.
Alright.
So you're a submarine.
We'll meet, we'll, I mean we could, do we want to talk about the forms now?
I guess I can just do...
Or we wanna, or we wanna...
No, I wanna see them in action.
Yes, we'll meet them in action.
We know who they are.
Let's see them in action.
Alright, well, I've known you for about 30 seconds and I'm ready to jump in your body.
I hate when a new submarine trauma dumps to me about their forms.
I'm glad this one didn't do that.
Yeah, me too.
Okay, I'm opening up a hole in your body and walking in it.
I'm opening up the door at the back.
That's my penis hole!
Which one?
The back or the side?
Which side are you getting in?
The right side.
That's my armpit!
We do need to roll for stats. I wanted to roll live so we can see here. Hold on, hold on, hold on.
I'll show them how we do it.
I know. I'm so excited.
I know. I'm praying to God that this is just the worst stats of all time.
We're going to do the very friendly method that we do for everybody.
A 4d6, drop the lowest.
For each of them.
So, also to give you some information, Chuggie is a level 5 bard.
College of Glamour, much like Sullivan.
I was.
College of Glamour.
Uh, but Glamour is really useful for, um, doing disguise work and the ability to also
sort of like charm people into making them sleep.
So you went to Glamour College?
Mmhmm.
And things like that, and uh, to escape captors, cause of potentially we can get into Chuggie's
past.
Can you put a weave on Steeble?
Um.
A weave?
Mmhmm.
Uh, I mean he has a disguise kit and he has proficiency in it, so potentially.
Oh my fucking god.
If you're asking character.
We'll get to that.
And so he's got -- he'll be a very useful party member probably.
So let's start rolling for stats though to find out.
I believe you already have a +4.
You have a +4 starting in Charisma because we have 3 from your race and +1 because of
a feat you took which is Actor.
It's going to give you advantages when you're doing --
He and Rachel chat rooms are showing feat.
He said race and feat.
I got 3 twos.
So I can say that.
that's an 8. Yo! Alright, we're one roll. Oh my god. Let's get it. 6, 2, 3. What's that?
That is an 11. Alright. It's low so far. 6, 6, 2. Nice. It's a 14, that's not bad. For
it
Oh my god, I can't wait to riff on you doing that dude. I'm over here itching to riff. We're gonna win five four two
You guys can talk you just won't rip you know
I said it before I moved it that was a five five and a four or five five and a two five
I'm gonna which one did I said five four two on your so is a five four two okay five four two it's an 11
Okay, he's getting a little
It's this one three four three five two it's a ten. It's pretty good. You're getting decent decent, okay?
There's a nice six four three ten is plus zero is a 13. Okay. Wait, we're at we're at we're done. We're at six
We're done. So we've got 8 11 14 11 10. I'm gonna put a oh my god
Finally, he's he's power level is is is the same as ours now. Yeah, you're nerfed relatively speaking
I would put I would just put the 14 in charisma because you're gonna be a caster
Yeah, and then you'll have 18 and you'll have a plus 4 there which is gonna be holy crap. It's gonna be important
Shit man, but yeah, I would say a dex is pretty important for
You guys yeah, a dex is pretty important for ash ketchup as well. Yeah, this riffing over here
Don't mind and uncles nationwide. I guess I guess when I said riff. I just meant talk no let me in my riffs
No, I'm super sorry
How much longer
I have like a huge amount of stats to get done here.
That's just a riff I came up with.
Get a riff off of that one.
That's pretty cool.
I got another riff guys.
Let's hear it.
Here's mine.
That's actually fucking terrible.
I don't recommend...
Holy fucking shit man.
Holy fuck dude.
I think we need to get bongos.
Wow. Wow wow wow.
Wow wow wow.
*singing along to the riff*
I heard that riff.
I cannot wait to hear that riff used in a song.
*singing along to the riff*
Alright, let's move over to more...
Is there something for us to riff on?
What stat are you working on right now?
Right now I'm working on his skills.
So, bards have...
Ain't got none.
Bards actually have quite a bit of skills.
He's killing my boner when I see this ugly guy.
So they have proficiency.
And you get half proficiency.
You let him swim underwater with no breath.
On things they're not proficient with.
And they have expertise on certain ones.
Expertise.
That sounds like a name.
What about in character?
What's an expert?
You guys are meeting for the first time?
You guys want to talk about something?
So do we have...
I'm basically...
I'm buying a ticket on you.
What's your decks?
My deck?
Well, I have two decks.
The poop deck and the...
The pee deck.
There's a riff for you, Patrick.
There you go.
The diarrhea deck.
I'll never ask for anything.
What the hell?
Wait.
Listen, I'm just kidding about that.
Wait, so if you...
How do you get the diarrhea deck?
I don't know.
Where, how do you poop? What happens if you're a submarine?
It comes out as exhaust!
Exhaust?
Yeah, I'm getting pretty exhausted by this fucking character.
What are you saying?
I poop all over his stuff.
Completely all over his stuff.
Like you dust the room?
I completely crop dust him when I leave.
How do you eat while you're a submarine?
I eat the water.
You eat water?
You eat water, what do you drink?
I eat the krill that's inside of it.
a big whale. So you're just a whale that we can get inside. But I'm a submarine. And I
love to sing. Wait, what makes you a submarine? I hope that this doesn't get misconstrued
in Gay Boy. I'm doing an impression of the guy from Mary Poppins. Which guy? Edwin. Oh
yeah, we talked about this. He also played the Mad Hatter. Yeah, I think that's the more
Yeah, like iconic version of his voice than Edwin from Harry Potter.
Well his name was Edwin.
It was Edwin.
But the Mad Hatter was gay though.
Oh shit!
People aren't gonna like this voice.
I think they're gonna be fine with it.
I hope they are.
Can I...
You bunch of...
What is the inside of you look like before I open this damn thing?
Blood and guts!
Okay, so it's fully...
It's fully blood and guts so you are shaped like a control that you are just a whale
I'm pretty much just the whale who's shaped like a submarine. I think most submarines already say like whales
From a whale what my control deck and the steering wheel of my intestine
But you can also you can decide where we're going as well. Yes, we don't have to steer you from we have no
Basically no point for you to go inside of me
Well, if the thing is let you're like that he will move
He moves way faster than you guys
So you guys want to travel like swim at the actual speed of like a boat you were using I'm a part unless I'm in human
Form how faster than our ship what happens is about the same speed as your ship
I'm gonna transform back into a person when we're inside you late it
You will die. I think I'm
Probably take who is taller me you if he transforms while you're inside him you will die
Yeah, cuz you will sort of try to
Write up my organs will go around them. Yeah. Yeah, okay. Yeah, well, I mean we'll probably just get hurt
But then you have to come up with another spells. I gave you I also gave him
I gave him the tiny hut spell so if you guys I
Wow, I thought it was a periscope but it's clearly a hat
The water from my blowhole shoots up. You have a blow your submarine with a blowhole
Oh, you're literally a whale.
What are you talking about?
How else am I going to breathe?
So let me just lay this out.
So now I'm trying to--
The only way for me to function as a submarine
is if I'm technically a whale.
Right.
So you're a whale.
Because I'm a living, breathing thing.
But we're going to call you a submarine.
And this guy--
But I go by Chuggie the Submarine.
How do you feel about this fucking guy fucking claiming
he made you?
Yeah, why did he say he invented you yeah?
Well I I don't he is my latest invention in that I've I'm his slave no don't don't
I'm going over it roll for insight see if he's a slave not you you know you're a slave I
got a
16 I mean he's not got a
I'm gonna crit 1.
Okay, you probably won't really understand it, but...
Yeah, no. You know he's a slave.
He makes me go out to faraway lands!
That sounds horrible! Who would want to do that?
And I have to eat other people!
[Laughter]
What?
When he captains me, I have to eat people.
Wait, he captains you? Is that like a sex thing?
I gotta crit 1, I feel like.
It's a complete sex thing for him!
[Laughter]
but he lets me talk here.
He darts with you here?
He darts with me!
It's not a sex thing!
My penis is the size of him!
Look at him, he's 5'2".
Well, he fits the package.
He's all for it, though.
Well, proportionally I'm not packing.
That's true.
Because I'm 30 feet long.
Currently.
I got enough numbers on here that we'll be safe for now.
We'll be safe for now.
a sixth of your body.
Yeah.
It's like if you had a one foot dick.
I won't be able to speak after recording anymore
because of this voice.
See, that's why you gotta be smart like me and pick a voice like this
after doing a bunch of voices like this.
I wanted to show off my talents.
I mean, you could definitely, if you need to,
because you are a changeling,
you can just swap out to one of your other voices if...
I have full schizophrenia!
That's not really what a changeling is.
No, he's a whale.
I'm a singing submarine!
Okay, you know, you guys are both by the way...
I'm not gonna do much singing unless I need to introduce myself to other people!
But that was kinda singing right there, guys.
I don't know if that was singing!
That was definitely singing.
That was singing.
What are you talking about?
*laughter*
I was on the line.
He constantly sings.
Alright.
*sings* Now I don't!
That one was singing.
*sings* That was that singing I stubbed my toe!
That one was actually not singing.
A lovely Barry Tenner, but it's time for him to go.
*sings* Who's Barry Tenner?
*laughter*
*sings* Is that what you said? I couldn't hear you.
That's a pretty good idea. Barry Tender.
Like a chicken.
chicken me get a little bit
i guess i really i think now that uh... that now that
patrick you know there is dead
uh... that i know right at me the same here that's great
while i'm looking at the fact that i don't know what you are big
uh... this is a spot
is that this uh... this this mud body here
officially holds no value besides being quadra mud marks
and whatever plotline we're falling before is officially severed and doesn't
matter we can completely a hundred percent focus.
Which by the way, Chuggy, our whole thing right now is we're gonna
Vive this. I know a guy! Oh my god. Well technically, one of my personalities does.
Wait, oh my god this makes things very easy. Can you Vive this? We would still
have to go and get him Vived. Yeah so he still has to go to Beriberi but he knows a guy
I
that
put him on quadro.
- Yeah, and his leg. - So his leg.
- And his wing, on quadro double A.
- And I can eat his head and his legs and his arm.
Not his arm.
- And we'll feed him, we'll feed the rest of him.
- Yeah, I feel like I have a submarine.
- I can eat the torso.
- You guys always do like a Frankenstein thing.
- He did just claim that he only eats krill.
- But I said that my captor makes me eat people.
- We'll feed you a dead guy.
- Okay, so my friend. - I did.
- So like, take to me.
- Okay, so Patrick eats Patrich.
- I was gonna do Barney's voice for this.
- Yeah, we do like a--
- And I kind of wish I did.
We do like a forged in fire style montage of us and there's guitar music.
[imitates guitar]
And we're hitting his arms and legs on a forge, chopping them up, breaking them.
Mudding them.
And then soldering his arms and legs to a quadruped mark.
You get help from Flint.
He gives you access to his...
We try dipping his arms and legs into a forge.
- He's like, "Don't do that."
- Yeah.
- Okay, perfect.
- And then we toss his head and his torso.
- Yeah, and you like -- yeah.
I like the idea of you sort of like coat the arms and legs.
- It tastes just like chicken.
- So it's like they're sturdy as rock, just like the hardened mud.
It's like now it's all one, like, statue.
And then the head, where you -- guys, put the patridge's head.
- Oh, that's in his mouth.
He needs that.
- Yeah.
- Put it in his mouth.
with that the patridge's oh that's in his mouth
it's not that the idea that you are going to fight dot that personality after a
unit
maybe i can see how it will be you have met him so it's how change things work
yeah which was like a priority stretching that i don't think you've met
a subnet change the windows and alright
i try to keep some stuff
sort of above board me you let him make a submarine
i did what you're doing a magic school bus thank you
He's doing a Magic School bus thing, I'm allowing it.
I'm doing a song!
Whoa!
So yeah, you guys want to go out to the deep blue sea?
Yeah.
With Chuggie the singing submarine?
Listen, I've never seen anybody I want to spend more time with than Chuggie.
I'm getting in there.
Hell yeah.
Okay, yeah, you guys get into Chuggie.
It's sort of fleshy and red.
What is it inside of you?
It's like, if...
So you guys are inside of me?
Yeah.
If you turn on a light, you can see every single thing.
There's a light in there?
You have a light in your body?
Lights aren't even invented.
What the fuck is going on?
That must be, he was pointing past Chuggie into the middle of his body.
Must have meant the light bulb.
This bulb shaped light thing.
What the hell is it? This is the weirdest candle I've ever seen.
I guess we could call it a bulb light.
It's a kidney stone! And it's interacting with the electrons in my body.
Alright, well.
Alright, well, whatever.
I'm gonna flip it on.
dimmer oh my god let's set the mood yeah if you if you turn the light if you turn
the uh the kidney stone on inside of my body you it's just like completely
translucent you can see all my veins all my bones and guts and stuff i'm gonna
can i lick the his wall his inner wall hey you gotta buy me dinner first
i'm hitting his back wall i just gave you dinner i fed you my dead friend's body
i guess you can lick me yes i'm gonna do this all i want
Only for the duration of this trip. If you keep feeding me you can keep doing it. It'll take two weeks to get there.
Alright.
This is how we do it. You can only do that for two weeks. I don't even, this time I'm getting electrolytes and
My electrolytes if you keep doing that. No, you're meeting krill. I'm jumping up and down in the back.
I'm like a parasite.
I'm bouncing off. I'm bouncing off his back walls like sky zone if I jump back if he
Specifically back walls if he jumps inside me is fine. I've I have 30 feet long
I am 30 rubbing myself against your walls, and I'm
So you're - I guess
I guess I'm two years old.
In submarine years.
How many normal years are in a submarine year?
I don't remember.
I took too many Percocets.
He's an adult.
Who thinks he's two.
Moving on.
Please.
on. Please.
Sue.
I'm two years old.
Oh, okay.
Alright, so you guys go underwater, right?
So you guys, you can chart the same path
towards
We're going to Berry Berry, right?
I know a shortcut to Berry Berry.
Does he know a shortcut?
Can I roll to see
if I know a shortcut?
No!
[Laughter]
Can we-
It's a submarine, we go in a straight line.
You just go in a straight-
I mean, yeah, there's a huge amount of benefits in riding in a submarine as opposed to a ship.
There's a secret ocean between you.
There's a secret way-
Well, I'm faster, right?
You are faster.
So, it was two weeks-
It'll be less than two weeks.
It was two on a ship, so it could be- is it one week on a submarine?
It's like one and a half, basically.
Okay.
Based on like, one and a third.
But it's not a- it's on- no.
It's like, it's one and a half.
One and a quarter.
No, no, no, this is based on I I did in 3/8. This is not I mean I let you be a submarine
All right, so it's true. Let me be
I've I've an idea how close are we to the vortex?
To the the fake whirlpool. Yeah the whirlpool. I mean you're like, right
Survivors or anybody? Yeah, sure a ladder out. Can you turn that whirlpool off?
We want to do a sweep because I might as well go to bed
also
like three days down there.
Oh yeah.
So, I don't think there's a single survivor.
Alright, is there a snake man that's swimming around here anywhere?
Yeah.
Alright, well hey, if you-
Oh, he's gone! He's gone!
Who knows where he went?
Oh, look at this!
Or, the tiny cat in the water!
Okay, alright. Well, let's just head to Berry Berry then.
I wanna get this- I wanna get Quad Double M, like, up.
Yeah.
I wanna get him up and running.
You guys are-
Okay, you guys are beelining for Berry Berry.
So, in the uninhabitable sea bomb, that's the uncharted zone.
Phil Thomas Kent.
But yeah, you guys are in the sea bomb.
Not many people have ever been able to, I mean, unless you're a merfolk, you just usually
don't get to be underwater.
Don't get me started on merfolk!
I don't want to get you started.
So this is like, you're seeing through the translucent skin, I guess.
a
with my eyes but i have like like little port holes on the side that i know that i
had yet you are a submarine yeah so that i look like that you don't see as
extends
what that is a little
c_n_n_ number of the american a bunch of blood and bone and grossness party
losses and you have like a
you look at it as a call to like i was like the bus i have a business and that
and that's a little bit body is that
periscope yeah
my hair picture
you have one here
like a cartoon baby
I have a bunch of different
hairs but they form a periscope
the transformation
it makes more sense when you see it
I'll look up in that
and I'll watch
let me open my porthole
and I'll watch as the ships go by
and the portholes are just my pores
just pores that I had black heads in
and they formed a lens
Like because he's a submarine like when he's in this form he can withstand
The kind of pressure that most like you know usually like oh that also makes me susceptible to like
cannonballs
Underwater what are you talking about? Yeah? Well? I don't know if there's gonna be any kind of underwater combat that I'm gonna have to cannibals cannonballs
Cannibals you are a giant you are yeah
Exactly yeah cannibals you'd only have to worry about about well train we know like submarine whales
Yeah, I guess I'll also change into a person
Yeah, and so well here's the thing lateralis did give you guys the gill rub so if you run into any
Encounters where you need to fight and in a different form which you know for combat you would have to change out of chuggy chuggy
Doesn't do combat okay
That one is gay what he is gay. Yeah, so
So you would have to move so you'd have to change it
But you have the gills thing so the way those skills work is when you're out of combat
They let you breathe underwater for an hour when you're in combat
They let you breathe underwater for a minute, and then you have to use a bonus action to reapply it okay
Because it's just more intense yeah, and shit
We use a 60 times more oxygen. Yes exactly
Fuck so I have to do that too as chuggy
Chuggy is your only form that lets you breathe underwater.
Okay.
Also, you said you had a blowhole.
Alright, that's a good point.
Which would mean that you don't breathe underwater.
You just can't hold your breath for a long time and then I guess you have to come up
for air sometimes.
He's nodding.
Do I have to go up for air?
Yeah, I guess I do have to go up for air.
If you have a blowhole, that is what that is.
I'm pretty sure.
Alright, that is what a blowhole is.
Okay.
Okay, cool.
So, you guys, but you can go a couple hundred feet underwater.
A blowhole.
you can't go much further underwater or the pressure will actually start to
rupture you which I have rules for that too. You have the Benz rules? Yeah I mean I made my
own version of it. Well not the Benz, the Benz is when you come back. Yeah. I thought that's what he was saying.
I wasn't listening. No I don't have like Benz rules but I mean I mean we could figure that out.
Are you listening to me talking Chuggy? Hello Chuggy. What is this voice right here? Oh no it's another character.
But yeah, no, it's what it is is if you go
Below the threshold and I'll let you know when you are below the threshold where like certain amount of pressure is being applied
You can stay at that pressure level for like, you know below that level for like I think I put a minute or two minutes
A minute and then once you're at that you have to roll a constitution saving throw
Every minute after that to see if you take damage from like just pressure compounding on your mm-hmm
self
Also when you swim you guys have a swimming speed of 10 feet
Okay, so just you know, your walking speed is like like yours
Yeah is I think both of yours is 25 feet cuz you're shorter
But like you're just gonna have you're just gonna swim slower than you walk. Okay - 30 feet. So oh, yours is 30 feet
Oh, maybe give you - 1 million feet. It's not what I wrote there. So what it says, yeah as you guys
travel along in the submarine
You chuggy are approached
by getting me a group of
What looks to be dolphins and they start to talk to you rappers
Rappers, hey
You yeah whale guy
You all I'm not that big have you seen?
That's cute
Have you seen?
That was pretty a dwarf of her Dan and a goblin
What the hell are you talking about?
All right. Well, what is the dwarf? They tried to sell us to a make us into put us in a sex factory
Wait, he survivors. Well, they're robbers. They're robbers, but they survived
They got out of the sex factory. They survived our sex
factory they tried to turn you into what then they tried to we didn't really
understand what the sex factory was when we were in it but it wasn't good you
know what a sex factory is on there what kind of to explain what a sex factory
red-blooded man wouldn't kill to work in a sex factory hot babe why are you
retroactively turning our sex factory into something evil and yeah and I was
under the impression that these people were gainfully employed at the sex factory and
having as much fun as possible. We found a gap in the economy. We found a spot, a market.
We cornered the market here. We didn't ask anybody involved what they wanted to do. Because
it's a meat of, would you want to work in a sex factory? No, I'm married and I'm happy.
But if you were a dolphin named a rubber? Hold on. Yeah. Now I'm getting, I'm putting,
I guess maybe on okay and and and there is an important detail kills of you out
here the sex factory is on hot babe Island that is a good point
these ones were gay there's gay guys in pop babe Island I don't think people can
have hot babe sex I guess gay guys guys can be hot babes or maybe maybe they
were trying to maybe they were trying to I mean maybe they were just
experimenting. These guys were upset that you sent them to a sex factory. See, they
sound like a bunch of complainers. I reject this premise. Yeah, I think this isn't happening.
You can keep going, I just mean, this is honestly, this is
like, you know, this is a cornerstone that's being removed and it feels like
everything's toppling down your house of cards. You think I'm
really unsettling sort of the logic and world we built together. That's how I
I feel right is that you're almost like we've been doing this how long two years
and I kind of feel like you're like a disc like I'm like taking it apart now
pretty much yeah like you're dismantling it before my very eyes
because I feel like we've we've established such a nice sex factory
positive kind of like work here you know and it's a work it's okay and it is work
and no and it's not that I this text I feel like it's very
the show. You're one to talk, I don't want to hear it from you.
Well anyway, he asks you and you don't seem to know, and so he says, so the
the group of were-dolphins. I've got an idea.
There's a man.
I don't know how far we are, but he controls whirlpools
and he's always looking for new clients.
I guess we'll ask him where they are.
And he loves it when when uh, what are what are you?
Porpoise why did you send him to the person who will tell us tell him where they are?
Oh, Chuckie doesn't know I was trying to make them become slaves again
All right, well, I guess we'll be on the lookout for that. Thanks actually never mind what?
What if you went to the zoo
*laughter*
Alright, role deception, which you are excellent at.
Oh, just a sea creature
saying to a fellow sea creature.
*laughter*
How is it deceiving to say "go to the zoo"?
I mean, at this point he's just trying to
get them off his tail. Let me make sure
you have a tail. And I have a tail!
Asked and answered.
Is there nothing?
'Cause I thought there was maybe something you had.
You have.
That maybe allows you to roll again.
Shit.
I don't remember if I gave him something.
No, because you're not passing yourself off as a different person.
You're passing yourself off as yourself.
So you don't get advantage.
Oh.
So you just get a one.
You gotta stop rolling that way, for your sake.
They go, "You know something.
What aren't you telling us?"
"Yeah, what aren't you telling us?"
Me too, what do you tell them?
That man I'm sending you to had me as his slave.
Why would you send us to him?
Because I'm rude.
We appreciate you owning up to that.
And I'm working on it.
Look, if you haven't seen those three guys, then we're gonna just go.
Well, I've got a great idea for where you could go.
I mean, honestly, we're not gonna buy it.
because you just read this and let's go
every to go but it's not a good way
uh... so you guys can keep uh... going along uh...
and uh... let's do some random encounters
yes under water and the meekness
okay throughout a so i thought she could achieve skim out of the shadows
i've got a random encounter
okay so i didn't
So I think I saw a waffle mm-hmm
Okay, it's random. So yeah, are you still no wall bacon that midnight? Are you still in random?
I know exactly what that means. He's doing the Paris. Hell. Yeah, brother. Yeah, I've been chillin on the Periscope this whole time
Yeah, so you're looking in the Periscope and honestly, I'll be real. I'm licking it. You're looking in the Periscope. Also, is it hair?
And I'm hands-free
the white trail behind it. Yeah. My exhaust. That's the exhaust. You say sea exhaust? The
exhaust. Oh, I like sea exhaust. I like that term. So yeah, you're looking in the periscope
and... Licking in the periscope, yes. Licking in the periscope and you see about like, oh,
about like a couple hundred feet ahead of you, you start to see, you see a glowing,
It looks like it looks like a stick and as you get a little bit closer you realize it's it's a trident
stuck
Inside of some kind of like like rock formation. It's it's kind of bulbous and it's in the underwater
This is a water. We've seen that this is an underwater version of the first thing that ever happened to us
Didn't we bore there was a sword and uh and uh the first thing that happened us to a gather where there was a sword
And a rock was no sword. Oh, yes, there was a sword in the room
I don't know.
- And then we tried to pull-- - The first thing I remember
happening to me--
- I guess I'm just talking to you at this point, yeah.
- The first thing I remember happening to me
is waking up in a laboratory
and being made to eat a human.
(laughing)
- Oh yeah.
- That's, that's right.
- Okay.
- And the second thing I remember
is shitting it all out.
- Wow.
- That fat immediately? - I don't remember my life
before I turned into Chuggie, the singing submarine.
- All right, well Chuggie,
we're actually kind of having a conversation back here.
- Well, I can hear everything you're saying
'cause you're inside of me.
- I don't think that's how that works,
but I guess it is 'cause you do hear us.
- The vibrations are rubbing off my wall.
- Also, I'm not really sure how you--
- My front wall, not my back wall.
- If I have to, I'll decide that he can hear you.
- Do you have a second mouth that kind of goes inward
that lets us hear you?
'cause otherwise you're just going,
"Gloves, gloves, gloves."
All right, I don't know.
I wish I'd never said anything.
(laughing)
Anyway, so.
- Yeah, but yeah, there was a sword in the rock monster
and this seems to be exactly the same
based on my memory that I have of my life.
- Is that what you said?
Rock lobster?
I'm gonna be honest, I can't hear you that well.
(laughing)
- Oh, can Chuggie see this thing out there?
- Yeah, Chuggie, you can see this.
By the way, there's a trident in a stone.
- I see that.
Now, Chuggie, will you go and try to maybe bite that?
- I'm gonna ram into it at full force.
- All right, well, let's go.
- And then bite it.
And then try and go backwards at the same force.
- Try your dental.
I get tri-dental.
- I have teeth like a whale.
- What Chuggie would know is that the trident
works kind of well. What Chuggie would know is that the trident is far enough down, you
know, it's sort of like a diagonal from you, but it's far enough down that it would start
to apply pressure on you if you did it. So you can go down there and ram it, but if you
don't, you know, if you're there for longer than a minute, it could start to...
This is exactly a trap we have seen before, and we're gonna go into, we're gonna go get
crushed while we fall for the same trap.
These are all opportunities.
I want Chuggie to die so badly that I have so much to do with Chuggie you can't kill him.
I mean you're about to kill him ramming into this thing Chugster.
Do whatever you want to do.
What would Chuggie do?
Yeah Chuggie's in control here.
Yeah Chuggie.
If Chuggie would just ram into it he should.
So it's going to apply pressure.
How much pressure?
So you'll be fine.
I says here 100 points of pressure.
You'll be fine for a minute down there.
100% pressure.
there okay so I mean like running into it you know that's gonna be you look can I
swim down normally at it I'll be fine no I mean you'll still have the pressure
applying to you it's a matter of the level goes down like like 10 feet every
month then he'll get his body yes yes if you go down 10 feet every month you'll
I'm gonna go down 10 feet every bumps all right
I'm sure I'm trapped in his body
Nothing they can do I shall kill me and I don't know how much rations you guys have I mean I'll fucking eat his spit
I don't care seems like all rationality is departed. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, I guess I'm not gonna go towards that trident
I think it's a mirage. Do you have a big frog tongue where he gets and just grab it no, okay?
well I guess I get trick looks so hopefully it patches for one second
okay do I have
they can go down like one hour right well but the pressure will be even worse
the pressure the pressure it still happens stuff here but you have
abilities I just this is I mean okay here's what I here's what I say right
The the worst possible thing that can happen here is we all die and we have to make new characters
The best thing that could possibly happen is maybe we get a trident
And I feel like that's not a great risk reward
Spread going on there. I'm looking at my well
I will say okay what I will say is the pressure
Damage is not so much that it's gonna just kill you if you take damage from it
Like it'll do it'll do damage, but it won't just kill you outright like and you would be able to swim up also
You know what I mean? It's not like it's not like it's are you gonna light the paper on fire?
I just realized I'm I looked at my later looked at my character sheet. Apparently I'm immune to disease. Did you guys know that?
Yes, you are
Paladins are immune to disease you have resistance to poison also
Not you Steve-o does. Can I use um, what's up? Can I use find traps?
If you have that spell cast that at the second level yes, let's uh wait to you. Where is that on your spell list?
I mean, I have jack of all trades
I have jack of all trades, and I think it says that I can add a proof half my proficiency bonus
Well, that is added to Oh guys ability check it says right here. I don't I have intelligence
I don't have I don't have fine traps on I have it on my child
You haven't asked so you don't have that prepared. That's one of the spells you can prepare though. I have to peeper this
You have to not gonna do that. Yeah, I mean so I mean looking at your spells which I have these are no
Yeah, you have stuff you've prepared and stuff you haven't prepared what you can I mean you can also I forgot you have anime
I guess I'll just
Run an investigation, but yeah, I mean you guys can just get close to close enough to it that you can start to investigate it
Maybe just go around it. All right. Yeah, can we get close enough that I can invest? Yeah, but without
Yeah, I chose you go pull up about just whenever you start
75 feet tall whenever you feel that pressure in your ears, you know pull up on the gas pedal. Yeah, okay
You just know how to do it. All right, you guys get it
I go 99 feet guys get about closer as you get closer to it. Wait 99 feet
Well, I start to feel the pressure at 99 feet
I mean, it's up to I'm not giving exact feet measurement here, but I would say I guess now I'll have to
so
If we're talking like I said, you're about 200 feet away
I'd like to get an exact feet measure on patches and oil those things up and
If you're in six and a half you're approaching
Yeah, I was gonna say
That's how all birds measures
We're talking about here you are you are whoops we rolled a one on our authentication check
We're heading into town to visit the blacksmith for repairs very cool D&D beyond. It was a funny website
Yeah, hilarious, so if you go you're gonna if you're going 75 feet at the diagonal like I'd say you can go about like
No, because then
About a hundred yes, you can go a hundred feet and when you're 50 feet away at the diagonal if you go any further than that
Like lower so I could go 50 feet and then let them go down
But if they go down, they'll know it's gonna be worse for us than it is for you
Let's not to feel the pressure, but you're gonna feel the pressure, but you're close enough at that point and the it's that you can start
To investigate it reasonably. I mean I will adjust because you're not right next to it. Okay, you are also pet
I feel like your body is so much more
For pressure than ours is mm-hmm. You're a big submarine. All right, then. I'll go we're tiny little I will go 75 feet
You can go so you can go a bit closer. I'll say here's here's what I think I think that makes sense
So what we should probably do is
You can go a bit closer than them so we can get you about 25 feet from it
Yeah, and then if you go any closer though, like you will have about two minutes in your submarine form
Yeah, he's rolling away on the rolly. I know I gave him the really rolly chair
But you guys can both investigate too, so I mean it's up to you guys
I'm gonna I want to roll my investigation. Yeah, you roll your investigation. You can have advantage if there if cams helping you
Oh, okay, I'll give you
Yes, okay, wait that was a 19. There's a 10. Oh, and what was that 10 and a 3 so what's my?
12 12 okay cool so from what you can tell with a 12
Is that yeah the faint red glowing you were seeing on the Trident?
Yeah, we're actually just seeing it around the tip which is sticking out of the why did I think you said it was green?
I don't know that it was gold. It's what I thought it was. I thought it was white and gold
All right, well, we're I'm a bad. I'm bad at describing you things I guess so it's a red
Glowing around sort of where I thought it said laurel the spikes
grid the pokers
Tongues one of those calls
And then you can also see with that 12
But the rock is sort of soft on that top part like it's kind of like unstable
Where it's that looks like a crab's head. I do think this might be a creature. Yeah, I think it's up
I think there as there ever
Hmm has there ever been a creature like this yes, really?
Okay, cuz I've seen it. I feel like I said it before a few times
We've already seen a creature like this - yeah, and I'm gonna turn around
You cannot quite tell if it's a creature. I'm gonna turn around I tell
Saw creature that was exactly this I don't feel like I'm going crazy recycling ideas. God is recycling ideas
Making them under water
Schizophrenia right now because I saw a pattern in my life completely turn around and I'm gonna shoot as much as
We got a head that way we got to go to berry berry no, I mean I'm turning back up
up. Okay, you're going up. All right. That's yeah. What is he lives his life
three dimensionally. So avoiding the triangle big whale, you're avoiding the
trident and you guys keep going and we'll roll for another random and can
better not be another trident. This time. It's a it's a it's a spear and a
stone. You this much if that if the next one's a trident, I'm beating it. I
thought that was right now. Now that we will pass it by. Was it a creature and
I'm going to whoop it. No, I'm not going to tell you this. I'll tell you
anymore and the next was a lot of them whooping it
you know who you're gonna want to slide on it i'm not gonna tell you for the
creature
that when you can tell us if it's my it was not it was not a creature
who is a different is the next one our ops
we are you saw our ops
the rubbers
here's a year i see my opto almost slide
right away you know that means
i might open a can you will pass on my own you
is there a shy replacement old-fashioned chin music on my up
My op is going to get a knuckle sandwich.
[laughter]
Fisticuffs with the op again.
How do I introduce this one?
This will be weird.
Kickboxing my op though.
Ten paces at noon, op.
Dude, if I see my op, I'm throwing down my gauntlet.
We're jousting.
We're jousting at dawn.
Okay, that's fair.
So yeah, you guys keep swimming along.
Got my op doing at Charleston with my girl.
Biting my thumb at my op.
at least not swimming along, but sailing along.
It goes by kind of uneventful, it seems like.
- Okay.
- I hate events.
- And like hours go by.
- Okay.
- It's uneventful.
- Time loop, time loop, Groundhog Day.
I killed myself.
- 99 bottles of beer on the wall, 99 bottles of beer.
Take one down, pass them around.
- When you do start to notice.
- No one else is singing with me.
is that it has not changed from night to day.
- Oh my God, oh my God.
- Holy fuck dude, you are readable.
This guy's got you at every turn.
- I deserve a trophy.
- You do deserve a trophy.
- That's two in a row.
That was, okay.
- Well, I mean, you could try--
- I knew it.
- You could try to kill yourself though.
(laughing)
- Wait, so we've noticed that it doesn't go
from day to night.
- Night to day. - Night to day.
- It's been night. - The lonely stoner
seems to free his mind at night.
- And when Chuggy goes up for--
- And that's a song I wrote.
If Chuggy goes up for air, it is still night.
- Okay.
But it's been well over 12 hours, yes.
- Hmm.
- We should go back to the triangle.
- I think we might be in some kind of night world.
- Groundhog's night.
- Hmm.
- Wait, is it groundhog's night tonight?
Now that I think about it.
- What the hell's a groundhog?
- It's an animal. - Groundhog.
- I've heard of a groundworm.
- I only know sea pigs.
- I've heard of a sea pig.
- I've heard of a yardworm.
(laughing)
part of a ground hob. No, okay, so there seriously won't be a creature called
cannot. You know, I mean, this is all I got. I'm just gonna roll
investigation again. Can I can I also roll and get a real investigation? Can I
look up at the night sky and roll an investigation specifically looking up
there? Of course you can. Okay, all right, I'm gonna twist your hair is
getting twisted and now it's kind of a top knot and we're looking directly up.
Okay, I'm gonna help him. Yeah, I'm holding on to his back like I'm riding a
motorcycle with him I got a 21 looks in the periscope looking up at the night
sky what you start to notice is that the stars underneath it are like billowing
out and kind of like it's like the sky is physical so it looks like instead like
the stars are shifting but it's like we got guys we got eaten by a giant creature
and he's got a night belly.
(laughter)
Not again for me!
That's my guess.
Okay, do I notice anything else?
I mean, you've noticed...
you've definitely noticed that there's something organic above you.
Which one of us has the longest range gun again?
I don't even know what weapons I have.
I got the blunderbuss, I think.
Because whoever got the rifle should shoot upwards.
I guess one of us died and doesn't have that gun that we used to have.
I think he had the longest range one too.
My gun isn't on here.
Yeah, and put your guns on there.
I have a disguise kit.
Well, I guess I'll just shoot.
What I will say, I should have the gun info here, I apologize.
It's been a minute since we've done gun stuff.
I have dark vision.
Does that help me at all with seeing anything about the night sky?
No, it just helps you see.
Oh, fuck off.
It just helps you that when it's dark you can see, um, it becomes dim light rather than
total darkness.
Okay, alright.
Fair enough.
Can I use, um, hmm, can I use detect magic?
Oh, uh, yeah, you certainly can.
Yeah.
I will also say, what do I have here for the guys?
There's musket.
I also have.
There's only a 30 foot sphere though.
Right here I have, um.
Oh, I mean, you can still try it.
This one's good. I think I could use this.
Um, detect peppermint.
[laughter]
Um, is one of the
thaumaturgy things making light or am I
like, it doesn't have a list of what the things are.
I can't remember. Uh, thaumaturgy, I think one of them
is light. I mean, he has prestidigitation
too. Yeah, I also have um
Chuggy would have to turn into his, one of his
human forms to use any of his abilities
or combat though. Um, I'm gonna use
detect magic. Okay, cool.
Uh, you don't have to... What does shatter do?
I don't have to roll for that.
Can I make stuff shatter?
Yeah, make stuff go boom boom.
Wait, wait, wait.
What if I try to shatter a star?
You can just detect magic.
You...
don't detect magic.
30 feet above you, below you,
or around you.
You don't detect any type of magic.
What about in my heart?
What about in my heart? You're sitting next to it.
Yeah, you detect magic in him.
him because he's a changer. That makes sense. But I don't ask. I don't feel like you're lying.
I mean you don't really detect any magic. You don't detect any spells being used or any like
magical things being used. Hmm. Detect. I have detect good and evil. Do that. Yeah do
that. We can see if it's good or evil. I'm going to do that. That is divine sense. And
that's within 60 feet. What if it's a bigger whale? You don't detect any evil. Okay what
about good. What does that mean? That's not fair.
Good and evil is a no. Even though we haven't talked about it, we've mostly noticed that
it's a yes or no. Neutral? There's no neutral. It's a yes or no. You don't detect good or
evil. Okay. I detect neutral. You know what he's saying? It's a neutral whether or not
you detect good. I have a new theory. My new theory is that there's actually a different
thing but it's just on top of us and it's just like a basically a giant tarp but
it's I think it's alive though yeah it seems I think it's alive though maybe
okay I use thumb a beauty I'm used thumb I don't even I don't say I'm doing this
but instantly just use thumb and turn you to make the loudest noise possible
Oh did you see if I can try to make a ripple and or startle it if it is alive
okay and I'm not I'm not betraying I'm like in the middle and like yeah I think
think and I think that we and then it's a freak out Chuggie and yeah you see that
thing up there it's a thing up there you see it like fucking quiver for a second
and Chuggie you being a little bit further out with your eyes you know holy
shit you're looking up you can see that it has some kind of head over there whoa
and it looks like there's like a you just said over there like in front of
him
That's too hot for overwear.
Wrong neck and like a human kind of head.
It's got a human head?
Damn.
How big, can we see an end to it or does it just reach to the horizon?
Yeah, can we tell how far up it is?
How far up it is?
I mean, it's like...
Hello?
I mean, it doesn't respond when you say hello.
Bitch!
A human head.
That's scary.
This thing's cool.
This is like the coolest creature you've ever made.
Yeah, it's really cool.
So we're inside of it?
I think we're just under it.
No.
Yeah.
- Yeah, you can now tell-- - It's like a dome.
- You, Chuggy, would be able to--
- It's like a dome with a head on the under inside.
- It's like a--
- Is the head upside down or upside right?
- Well, after the big boom,
Chuggy, you would see the neck crane down
and the head sort of just like look at you.
And then just like dead eye. - It shivers.
- This is honestly just, this is good.
- Thank you. - Yeah.
- Every once in a while.
- You still got it.
- Hey, yeah.
Hell of this thing and you guys could see it inside of the thing it is just like
What if I go backwards
Maybe we get what?
Surface, what do you mean up? We're on the surface. We're gonna try to find we need to go away from you notice
you're like
Chuggy's like confusingly, he's like, "Well, why don't we go?"
That's very funny. As you notice the uh...
I thought we were under something. As that thing notices you and notices you noticing it, you start to see its jaw unhinge
Very slowly and he's getting ready to say something
Maybe he's gonna sing with me
islands in the stream, that is what we hope.
- From the periscope, you can see the stars start to part.
- Yuck.
- And the innards start to be revealed
and you start to feel it, it's starting to descend.
So Chuggie, you have to make a move.
- Go down, go down, go down, go down, go down, go down.
- I'm gonna get eaten by the scary shit.
- I guess I'm going down.
Yeah, okay, you go, you dart down, it starts to chase you.
we're gonna have to do some rolls for this.
- When you say chase, like it like is descending faster now?
- It's descending faster down while Chuggy's,
like Chuggy's going down and this thing is going like,
built like an umbrella right now.
- Yes, okay. - Yeah.
- Like kind of like just charging down
with its mouth head first and then like trying to,
what it's ideally gonna try to do is latch on to Chuggy
and then sort of move its body around and inhale you.
- Damn. - What?
- I got it. - A 20?
- Yep. - I didn't tell you
what to roll for, but that is really good.
That is basically what I was, I was basically gonna ask you to do athletics rolls.
So, I mean this thing's gonna try to keep up.
It has very-
What's a 20?
It has very good athletics. I mean if it also gets a 20-
I'm gonna roll whether or not I pee my pants from fear.
So yeah, you got a crit 20.
I got 13.
Oh, nice.
I don't pee much though.
Yeah, so you, with a crit 20-
I do a, I do a, I'm doing a roll to see if I unleash poop.
For a crit 20, you're able to like just-
I got a 3.
Chuggy has escaped many captors before in Chuggy's life of being experimented on.
And so he is able to just like on instinct, once you realize what's going on,
you're like *pffft* like just start darting down as this thing is like coming closer and closer towards you.
And you're able to get away for the most part until you reach a point where you're almost at your pressure level.
So here's the thing.
If you go, you can go, you can keep going further down and you just have to like maintain your, like you have to just maintain speed to get away from it.
That's just gonna be one of the roll, it's gonna be a lower, a lot lower of a DC because you got a crit 20 on just getting away from it at this point.
'Cause it will be able to follow you lower than you can go.
So you'll have to kinda like hit your pressure level and then just bolt ahead to get away fully.
So again, it's a lower DC to get away at this point.
So yeah, you just gotta roll again. Let's put it that way.
Why don't we just-
Okay, I can't play that as it lies, 'cause it's gone too far.
Yes, let's just get another d20.
Let's roll, let's roll nice this time.
Oh my god, that's pretty bad.
But, what is your athletics?
I mean, you can also do acrobatics.
Will it help even though?
Oh, it's pretty bad.
He died again.
Instantly.
You're not gonna die.
Don't worry. You got a crit 20 on getting away from this thing. So even though he got a three this time
You do you what what really happens here is you manage to get pretty far away, but this thing does
as it's getting closer and closer and
Like it does latch on to you. It's like human head like like bites onto your light
Onto the periscope. So you guys see the head like oh
scared I pin okay wait real quick wait wait the periscope is hair oh yeah so
he's all I need is a haircut
we need people line me up from the inside from the inside I need you to line me up
I can't allow this. It's very funny though. In a better game that would be more possible
So you he bites onto your flesh hair thing yeah you guys see like the face
like like just like grab on and its body now is gonna whip around and it is gonna
make an attack I mean it did very poorly so it so your body is able to sort of
get away and then roll a roll a strength just a strength check so we'll just add
your strength which is not very good five you're not able to get away you're
Thrashing about this thing's gonna try to attack you again try to bite you again
Boy, I need you to get out of me and fight this thing. No. Thank you. It's too scary
I got some why are you rolling it on to that cuz cuz it's full okay? You rolled how many times no no?
This is the only role that counts okay. Well. We got the same role. Yeah, so it still misses the attack
Are you saying unfortunately for me? Well is it do you want that one to kill us? It's fun fuck
What the fuck? Why do we keep getting fives?
You didn't even roll that, you just threw it down.
So here's the thing, you guys do have an opportunity to try to cast something if you want to try something.
I mean, this thing's now been thrashing about.
You guys have to kill this thing.
Now keep in mind, you can see it, it's interesting. I wonder...
I'm using dreadful aspect.
Does it require you to see the target, is my question?
Because you saw it with the periscope.
Technically you can see with the periscope, you see it's like lips and...
it's like it's it's a target creature that can see me so I'm gonna put my face
up to the porthole and okay cool does make a window a scary aspect of every
each creature of my choice that can see me within 30 feet must make a wisdom
saving throw on failure it's frightened and it has to move very cool okay so
we'll roll for that um very good move it's a wisdom saving throw yeah did we
We didn't roll initiative right?
No, not yet. I should have done that for turn order
But I'm basically just basing it off of that was happening back and forth and you can go after I mean it's saved
You saw like seven okay plus its wisdom so damn, but I mean it was a good that was a good idea
Okay, what did you try to do? What you did dreadful aspect? Did you like?
Yeah, cuz it's so scary. I think maybe a funny. Yeah, right out face might be scary - we need a little levity to this
situation. Can I, I would like to cast blindness and deafness on this thing. Oh,
very cool. What does that do? It's a wisdom saving throw, right? I can't read.
There's, it doesn't say anything. It says the spells. Do you have a spell thing for that? No, I didn't get a spell thing. I'm just, I just know that I have
that. Yeah, I rely too much on. None of my spells are actually listed on any of these. Oh man, I'm
pretty sure. Oh, blindness and deafness, it says right here. Con 13. What does it say?
It's constitution? Oh, I guess that makes more sense. Yeah, 13 because of his spell
casting modifier uh... so it has to say that's a thirteen
against its constitution which is fairly high so this would have to be pretty bad
all but it was going to be bad
uh... and by the definition of the probably have to see if you can do the
same thing you go to the portal
the
to do a lot of it so that turns it up
goggles on
yeah i know it's able to say okay i'm taking the portal back in a missing
dreadful aspect again before that happens
will go back to the top of the or established on
and you you already tried to get away to try to attack you now
it's doing very poorly all right
you know i don't get away
it's gonna start that's in between rolling here
you here
what is this
with the same number still act in it
so pretty bad uh... okay like uh... i mean i need to go again to get rid of
last week to get here
here for you for a few months and i was just not a still slow
can trip
or wait well it's gotta be a spell slot
uh... so it's just a thing
and then it has an action each creature of your choices that know it's a channel
divinity. Oh, how many do you have? Wait, do I have another? No, I don't have another. Wait,
where does it say I have one? I thought I had more than one. Isn't it the same as one per
short rest? Yeah. Okay, I take a short rest. No, I'll cast a spell. I forgot I have fucking
spells. I can't do anything. You can't do anything while you're a submarine. I see my
spell. Stop taking my spells away from me. I'm sorry. I guess I will do... Wait, can I?
I have a message.
What's up with Crown of Madness?
It's a wisdom saving throw. It does damage.
I don't think it...
Let me make sure. It's wisdom, right?
Is there anything that can make something scared?
A ghost?
Maybe Zone of Truth might help us.
Nothing's scarier than the truth.
I don't think Count of Madness actually does fear.
I don't think I have anything I can really do here.
The other thing you could do, I mean you would have to, you could...
I'll just use Thaumaturgy again and make a loud noise right at it and see if it can,
if it's, because it seemed to spook it a little bit the first time.
Yeah, you can do that again.
I'm gonna try that.
Yeah, you use Thaumaturgy, you make another loud noise at it,
a little bit off. So, Patrick, why don't you try to get away again.
Not my name. I'm so sorry.
Chuggy. Bro.
I'm sorry. Bro.
Wow. That was really insensitive of me. I'll let you try to get away again before it takes
its turn. With Domitry.
19. There we go.
Yo. You're able to rest free. You're still going
to take some damage. Also the loud noise that made was a fart noise.
Nice. That's funny as fuck.
That's that levity I was talking about earlier.
Okay, you take...
21 damage from the whole encounter.
From basically ripping your...
I only have 7 HP.
No, you have 28 HP.
So you now have 7 now.
Yeah, yeah.
Holy crap.
Yeah, that thing is a very good move.
Very good instincts to be like, "We shouldn't get out and fight this thing."
"We should just do what we can to get away from it."
Yeah, we got away. Yeah, nice. Basically like oh man, I'm beat
And so am I
Wait real real quick. I do I do that did put up build up a bunch of peepee in me
Where do we pee in and poop and chuggy just do it wherever?
All right
Yeah, and there's the and that's all folks close. Yeah, you guys pooping and peeing. Yeah inside of your new friend
I'm taking a shit and you see my asshole and then that's all folks
Comes in it and it is off the the poop like oh, that's really good
Yeah, no sometimes where that were like porky the pig will maybe pull it back open. That's I sticking my penis through
You're peeing next to my asshole open. I pull the hole open and I'd pee
it's your but Chuck Chuck Chuck says Chucky definitely says that's all folks
And that's all, folks!
[Music]
[BLANK_AUDIO]