[Music]
Last time on Trebuchet Village, the gang accepted the quest of the mudmen to go slay the beast.
Patrick Yodar used his survival skills from cosplaying as a poor person to track the beast,
and on their way, they ran into a hunter, Goofus Tiedrich, who attempted to kidnap Prince Jumanji.
But Dogen's magical dirt pouch and Patrick Yodar's keen eyes led to the boy's rescue.
The gang then set upon Goofus, beating him so badly that they forced information out of him,
learning about something called the Brave Lions, a notorious band of scaredy cats, elves, humans,
dwarves, and the like, who have banded together to take down the terrifier kingdom,
claiming that the normalization efforts by King Nardwuar are too little too late.
Goofus was hired as a bounty hunter to kill the young Nardboy, or capture him, and so that our
heroes would spare his life, he led them to the White Woman of the Woods as well, who lives in
the pond further south. Upon meeting the white woman, Dogen jammed a javelin inside of Goof
as far enough that it killed him. The white woman of the woods is a goodly spirit who
wishes to banish the jester and his terrible reign over the whippet woods, especially the
kitsunes who worship him and enslave her precious kugler elves. The jester made all of the creatures
and plants weird and angry, like something out of Nightmare Before Christians.
When the whip it was, it used to be normal, used to not make people laugh uncontrollably
or have fucked up plants that try to kill you.
The White Woman of Wood says that the Yoni Egg of Baskin, an ancient and powerful artifact,
was stolen from her during the Great War long ago between the Terrifier and the police,
which led to the Jester's rise in power.
Now it is possessed by the vile warlock Connoria, who serves the jester in the woods, cursing
its creatures with weirdness and laughter.
The white woman promises to help the boys get out of the woods and more if they are able
to return her yoni egg.
Perhaps they can avenge the mudmen as well and even find the beast captured by the kitsune
people.
Who knows.
After some words were exchanged about Trunchbull Yodar having sex with the white woman in the
woods while Patrick Yodar watched and spilled juicy juice. The gang headed back
out into the night. Whereupon, resting at a campsite and after being attacked by
teleporting monkeys, they were visited by a handsome cowboy who tried to lull them
to sleep. However, steadfast Dogen would not take his dirt nap so easily and
batted away the bastard with his trusty shovel. Now fully on edge, or he
clotheslined him? I'll have to re-listen to that part. Now fully on edge, the group tried their
best to get a good night's sleep and in the morning made their way to Connoria's
disgusting hovel he lives in like the nasty warlock he is. He seemed to be
speaking with the Jester who scared the crap out of everyone and offered them a
chance to serve him in the woods, find their own way out, or continue on their
foolish errand at their own risk. They chose option three and the Jester
seemingly possessed the body of Connoria, held the yoni egg of Baskin Skyward and
beckoned them to fight. Will our heroes be able to beat the Jester and restore
the whip it woods to being normal well Patrick Yodar find a five-star hotel
will Sullivan ever get a good night's sleep is the prince really safe with
these boys I don't know it's improv you stupid bitch so yeah I can tell you're
excited for this yeah it's gonna be sick ass I just fucked up the I spent time on
everything but the intro this time the intro all right then I'm excited let's
go it's gonna be good we already roll initiatives no no I mean also like if
you did unless I wrote them down because we were all together when we did that so
unless I wrote them down doesn't count so everyone roll initiative. I got
an 11. I got a crit one. I got a two. Can we roll it again that doesn't count? What?
No it all counts. What do you have? I'm trying to look out for my two boys here.
No, it can't we've lost already. So my character commits suicide
Well, actually if you want to do that, hey badges all of us commit suicide
I'm gonna pull out my ghost campaign book
for that. I knew I'd make something so bad. Everyone would
quit.
So we got an eleven. It's Patrick we got. Dogen with a two
we got crit one right. So yeah, I count crits for initiative.
Some people don't do that. I like it. It's funny and then
What'd you get, Evil Steeble?
You got a soft two.
- A normal two. - Yeah.
- He's got a soft two.
- Soft two, that's not that unimpressive.
- A hard one. - No.
Doesn't even make sense.
- I know.
- And then, okay. - That's so weird.
- Creepy. - Let's see what happens
with our friend Conneria.
Okay, what is that?
Okay.
Oh boy.
And...
And another friend, Sullivan, the frog.
All right, Sullivan, how you living?
How you doing, man?
How you gonna do on this initiative roll?
You gonna slay it?
He got a 20. He's the best.
Damn, he's good.
Okay.
Sullivan goes first, believe it or not.
So, Connery is this warlock, and I mean, from what you can tell,
It seems like he's either possessed by the power of the jester or it's hard to gather
that right away.
But he's holding a Yoni Egiloft.
Looks like he's ready to cast something.
But before that, Sulvin gets a jump on him and thankfully with that long rest, he's going
to be able to cast Faerie Fire.
So he's going to try to cast Faerie Fire on this bastard jester.
So let's see.
Dex saving throw and the dexterity of our friend here is
not not terrible. Unfortunately for Sullivan. So let's see how
it goes. Oh boy. Holy **** he **** up so Sullivan the frog
gets a jump on this guy and this guy Connery. He's like
sort of like saying his whatever thing he said at the
very end of the episode. I don't remember exactly what I
said but and as he's saying it's all then it was a ha ha and holds aloft his loot
and strums a terrible chord but it shoots out this like bluish amber like
translucent fire that wraps itself around Connery a who is now as long as
Sullivan maintains concentration you know all now have advantage on any attack
against him. Dude, yes. Yeah. Keep concentrating. Alright, here I go. He's just like scrunching
his eyes a little harder. I can tell you're faking. Can you try harder than that? I really
don't believe that you're... Stick your tongue out like Michael Jordan. Yeah, stick your tongue
out Sullivan. You look so stupid now. You do look kind of stupid. You do look like a fool.
Do I put the tongue back in? Hey, you do whatever you want. I'm not. Okay, I'm gonna put the
tongue back in. Yeah, all right. Well, if you're gonna do that, that's fine. My forehead
hurts.
I don't understand why you're doing that.
That's good.
Keep concentrating.
And so, out of the, let's see now.
So yeah, evil Steve, as you're shouting, keep concentrating.
I'm going to need you to roll a dexterity saving throw.
All right.
It's too easy.
It's a six.
That's gotta be pretty bad, right?
Yeah, it's not good. So what happens is, is rustling in the trees above, you hear the
familiar gentle voice of the, of a singing voice of a cowboy. And you hear him as he's
like saying, "I'm gonna get you." And he just jumps out of the trees, grabs onto your head,
evil Steve-o and he turns into some sort of like awful looking ugly changeling
and he is just like grabbing at your head so this is the changeling that
belongs to Conneria. Get off my damn head! And he does... oh no. Get off! Yeah so he goes
in there he's just like he like like jumps down and just like starts grabbing
and
the
a
name is Impy? I named it Impy, yes. That's the best you can come up with. Is that short
for something? I don't know. It's short for impressive hair on Stevel's head. I really
named it that ahead of time. That's really impressive. I knew. I had a crystal ball.
He's got a crystal ball now. That's good news. So now we know when we kill him and loot him
we'll find a crystal ball.
- No, no, no.
- You won't be getting added to our inventory.
- No.
- That is exactly, that is exactly what happened.
- Am I not allowed to riff in character?
(laughing)
Is that just what it is?
You'll take advantage?
- Not unless, uh...
- I'm using details that have been established?
- Not unless, okay, that's right.
- Look, I'm a...
- That'll show him.
Not unless.
- I need to go get a glass of water.
I'm very thirsty.
(laughing)
very warm in my room in the game.
Do you want to get a glass of water Pat?
I'm fine, I'll wait.
Just looking out for you buddy.
NEMO!
(laughter)
Okay.
So,
Conneria,
I think he said stop.
I don't know.
I would say that too
if you did that to me every time you recorded.
you recorded. Alright, I want to kill this Conneria bastard. And I want to take his crystal
ball. I want to see the future. If we look into it and we see something that doesn't
eventually happen, we're cancelling the campaign. Can you guys believe these players? Fine,
I kill myself Pat these players are you done drive me crazy as the DM don't kill yourself
Please that will be hard to deal with I will think I think this
It is it is such a good
Such a good thing. You can always use on me
You can quote patches on that it's such a suicide such a good no, I saw the Bo Burnham special
Tell the kids at home it works on your parents too.
So he, Conneria, who's been frozen in time, unfreezes and shoots out a like, like it looks
like almost like a heavy bolt of electricity like it has this weight to it and it shoots
out towards you Patrick Jodar since you're sort of the most conspicuous right now because
of your giant balls and he's going to try to attack you.
You better not touch these.
I'm going to say that right now.
I can see your line of sight is looking straight at my balls.
My eyes are up here.
What's your AC?
My AC is
All right
so
the bolt you feel alike
He's gonna torment you for the rest of the episode
*laughing*
You deserve it!
He dropped all my skateboards!
*laughing*
He walked in and he opened the door and hit all my skateboards!
That's what you deserve.
*laughing*
Okay, what was happening?
Your balls are getting electrocuted, Pat.
That sucks, I hate that so much.
Uh, so...
You'd scream.
Ouch.
Well, you're about to take some serious frickin' damage.
So you're gonna start.
Hopefully not serious, we'll see.
How much?
Twelve.
I'm dead.
Yeah.
You fucking got one hit on your balls, dude.
They're a blessing and a curse.
Dude, kill yourself before it hits.
*sneeze*
It does 12 damage, does the max amount of damage it can do at this level.
And it just, yeah, it just fucking like, electrocutes you.
And you're just out cold.
Dude.
This sucks. I don't like this.
Yeah, you're out cold.
Ouch.
That is probably how Al-Analda's gonna go.
I hurt so bad.
And it is now Evil Stevel's turn because Patrick Yodar is out cold.
Okay, so I still have the hair on my head, yeah?
Mm-hmm.
Um, Cam, what do you think? Should I attack the Imp or should I fight Knoria?
Knoria!
Yeah.
I'm Knoria, from the Knoria tribe.
I tried to be medieval sounding.
I don't know.
I uh, I guess.
Well with some help you turned out to be, I'm gonna use Ray of Sickness on Konoria.
You had Ray of Sickness this whole time?
You held off on that for three episodes?
That sounds so cool.
It does a lot of damage if it hits.
It's a good spell.
It's a solid spell.
Alright, go for it, Doug.
Alright, here I go.
Ray of Sickness.
Eleven.
11. Alright, and that is on Connoria.
Or Connoria. And, uh...
Where's his AC? Ah, it's not quite enough to hit him. I'm gonna fucking die, dude.
We're all dead. Fucking three episodes in. He just shoots...
Yeah, we could just try again. We're always better than ten episodes in.
That's a good point, I guess. Just start again.
Hell yeah.
So you shoot this ray of sickness, which I like to imagine is sort of just a green
- It's poop. - Cosmoses Jones. Poop.
I was gonna say it's some poop guy, but yeah, it's just poop.
You just basically, yeah, you throw a ray of sickness.
- It's a long poop that I... - It's a long poop that's sling from your...
Flies out of my hand, but like, it looks like magic at first,
but then you think, "Maybe I had a poop in my sleeve this entire time."
You see Cotterill like, "Oh, that looks like magic."
And as it gets closer, that's not that's
Anybody he's able to pretty deftly dodge out of the way it is now your turn Dogen
Okay
Well, I'm not gonna try to attack. Oh, I'm sorry. You have advantage because he has fairy fire on him. Oh
Dude I'm really sorry
Well, fuck this guy!
[Laughter]
The exact same rule.
Alright.
Okay, it's not my day.
It's the same rule.
Okay, sorry.
Alright, Togan, you're up.
Oh man, I was so happy for one second there.
[Laughter]
I'm not gonna attack
the guy on your head because
I think I might kill you by accident if I miss.
miss. So I'm gonna attack Conneria I think with my war hammer. Or my war shovel I should
say. Okay that's 8 but I have advantage. Hold on. It keeps popping up a sidebar so I can't
click it again. Yeah it's annoying. 11. The evil number. The most evil number. You made
strong. He's it's a that's just he's his AC is not that high. I'm telling you now you could do it.
You could do it. We clearly can't do it. Yeah, you swing and a miss. He dodges the poop. You
charge at him like after the poop comes out, you know, sort of like in his blind spot with your
shovel and he's able to dodge that again pretty deftly. So we're back to the top of the order.
It is Mr. Sullivan the Frog's turn.
You better do work, Sullivan.
Okay.
And he looks up top to you.
He looks up to, sorry, he looks at Conneria and he gets his dagger out and he flings it towards the guy.
And let's see how he does.
That is just the damage.
Whoops.
That is... Why is that...
Why would that be crit?
He rolled a 12 crit.
But it looks like a crit.
What is this?
What happened to the UI here?
The user interface of Roll20 thinks that a 9 for Sullivan is crit.
Well let's just count it a crit then.
Yeah, that's a crit.
It's green.
There we go. Well don't worry, he got advantage anyway, so...
He did better. I guess Sullivan only does crits.
only
what is happening?
How is this?
What did I?
What did I roll?
20 could tell you were abusing us.
It has the mic detected too many suicide threats in a city.
I had some crits.
All right, Sullivan does.
Sullivan does not create, but Sullivan does do for damage on Connery.
So Sullivan pulling his goddamn weight sort of closes his eyes and throws the knife.
And after Connery, those two deaf dodges that knife just like gets in his thigh.
He's like, and yeah.
and
poofing it like a 50s bob haircut.
Okay.
Click on the side.
What's your AC?
Let me check.
I think it's not so bad, right?
It's like a hundred.
Yeah, he tries to claw at you again.
Um, uh,
and you're able to just like, uh,
deflect it with your shield, um,
or with your armor, whatever you use to
deflect. How do you deflect things?
Don't say you're like your ass or something.
My ass.
Ah, so he's...
(laughing)
- Yeah, you just-- - Oh, no, my shield!
Oh, fuck, come on.
(laughing)
Oh, not my ass.
- Yeah, you use your butt, you just deflect him.
So, yeah, that's kinda it for his turn,
but now it's our, it's our, the villain--
- When do I get to do, like, death saves or whatever?
- After Konariya's turn, you will.
- I hate this fucking guy.
I hate him so fucking much. - Oh, actually,
you know what I realized?
I should've already let you do one.
So you wanna do one now? - Yeah.
- Yes. - Yeah, go for it.
What do I roll?
D20.
You actually, in your sheet, you should have a way to just click it.
In the D&D Beyond sheet.
Alright, where?
Up top.
If you lower your health to like zero on D&D Beyond, it'll show you death saves.
It says I got a, I did a custom roll.
Yeah, it's got an alert that you did a custom roll on my...
Yeah, well it was a 20.
Whoa, it was a 20.
Oh, it was a crit? Alright, so you get two successes.
Oh, sick.
So only one more on your turn and you'll be back stabilized.
So, now it's Konaria's turn and he's going to shoot a blast of Eldritch Energy at you, Dogen, after you went after him.
So, let's see how he does
Choke
What's your AC?
18. Yeah
Don't you don't do don't do that choker I started doing a Reggie Miller like this
Don't know don't don't tell me to choke
Yeah, and it's now Patrick Yodar roll for death save do a custom roll yeah
I got another 20. Is that how high it's custom? Is it custom so you only get 20?
You got a 16 and a 20. What are you doing?
I rolled again while I was waiting.
That's great. I mean, you're doing great.
They're both successful.
Yeah, you're stabilized. So you're just like chilling at zero HP.
That was horrible. I don't want to do that again.
Yeah, so as soon as somebody heals you, you can get up and get back in the game.
Can one of you guys they just give me like a potion?
I mean I have a you have guys have the cookies you have the I have healing potions and cookies in my pocket
But apparently I'm not allowed to touch them. Well, no
Yeah, you're just talking
State I'm just gonna be sitting here
You're gonna be sitting here. I'm gonna be sitting here
Why'd you drop your accent for that one letter that time? I have a speech impediment
(laughing)
- That makes me sound like Alan Alda.
- You're up,
Evil Steeble.
- Okay, I'm going to use
Ray of Sickness on this dastardly imp.
- Okay, docky.
- Twint, crit, dude.
- Oh, wow.
- Please tell me that hits.
- Yeah, that definitely hits.
- Oh, nice.
- You got a crit, dog.
shooting it at your own head too?
yeah and i- oh yeah i do shoot it at my own head
alright so now roll for damage yeah?
mhm
fuck yeah um oh and it makes a con save
right it also will make a con save
um
cause uh if it if it on a failed save
it'll also be poisoned so
let's see how it does on constitution
it fails the con save! it's fricken poisoned
Poisoned as well. You badass bitch. Yeah, so you just like put your hands up wearing on on top of your head
It just blast this guy off. He's like and
It is now poisoned
which in 5e is not like
damage over time
Which is what you would expect from like poison, but they have disadvantage on attack rolls and ability checks, which is still pretty good
so
Yeah, so yeah, he's also not looking good by the way
This imp he's just he's not that strong
So he's sort of like wobbling and like vomiting because you hit him with this ray of sickness. So he's just vomiting up poop
That's fucking disgusting go to the bathroom if you're gonna do that bullshit you see him like he's like a changeling
He's like kind of changing between different forms as he's like sit falling ill like he looks like the cowboy again
He looks like Marie Curie. He looks like
He's just like shifting between all these different people Tony the tiger
And now it is your turn Dogen
Okay, do I still have advantage on on a test Sullivan's maintained? Yeah, I'm just gonna I'm just gonna swing again
Anybody gonna gonna help me down here and the ground my face you have a cookie dude
Oh again over this to see if you get not allowed to touch it a
18 so yeah, I will heal you when I when I finish doing the thing that you couldn't do you also have what you should know
my man
Dogen the dirt goblin you have um, oh, do you have divine smite yet or not yet? No, not yet
Oh, yeah, you'll get it. But I am gonna use fury of the small on this I think fuck. Yeah, I assume he's bigger than me
Yes. Yeah, Connery is a human. Okay. Yeah, so I do
Nine damage fuck. Yeah, so you um, yeah, how do you hit him? What do you do?
this shovel
God
I don't know dude. I'd sit him with the shovel. Damn. All right, so you hit him with the shovel
He's like, oh that wasn't that didn't feel very descriptive
But yeah, he's he's he got pretty brutalized there he's still up but
Yeah, so now we're back to the top of the order
which means it is Sullivan's turn and Sullivan oh yeah also Connery I will
say is bloodied between you and you and Sullivan's attacks so he's got yeah
just 13 HP left or Sullivan Sullivan is going to throw another dagger at this
guy see how he does he has advantage obviously so that's beautiful okay let's
see if he gets a crit he doesn't but respectable mr. the frog oh wait
actually does he yes okay cool all right oh no wait maybe he doesn't hit I just
realize oh he's so bad top toying with my emotions I'm sorry he's so bad patches
does this when he's sitting on the bus too he just talks with you oh very
respectable mr. frog oh yes yes he's getting so excited too everybody on the
bus is like in a circle that's how good of a storyteller you are oh you guys he
missed the dagger he missed so he just throws it and just sails over his head
And you see you see immediately you you could look at Sullivan the fries crest fallen
He's had such a string of successes the moment he failed
It's just like he's back to where he always is just the second. It's over
And it is now the imps turn impy impy the changeling
Who is
Poisoned so he's gonna try to attack you evil steve-o, but you know, he's got this advantage
So, let's see how he do
Okay.
Uh huh.
What's your AC?
It's 14, right?
Wait, no.
What is it?
Evil Stevel?
Oh, yeah, 14.
All right.
Fortunately for you, he does hit.
He got very lucky.
And he does, you have 4 HP left, right?
Yes, sir.
He does 3 damage.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
So he just runs in and just like, in frustration, he's like vomiting up doo doo and he's like,
"I'm gonna go get my AC."
And he's like, "I'm gonna go get my AC."
three damage.
Oh man.
Yeah, so he just runs in and just like like in frustration.
He's like vomiting up doo doo and he just like fucking headbutts you in the gut, which
is just like enough to like make you like kind of like, oh shit, like this is not this
might not end well.
I gotta keep up appearances.
Make sure you keep intimidating them.
Yeah, you like?
Yeah, I pretty much got like a million HP points left.
Like whatever.
And pussy roll deception, all right
14 yeah, he's like man. He's probably has a lot of HP. He's like
Like a million or something you're like eyes a little bit out of your socket
Okay, cool it is now Connery is turn who he is going to
Strike back at you
Dogen after you you let landed that hefty blow on him
The way he's gonna do it though. He's going to cast a spell
so he
holds his arms aloft and
You see these like large like ghostly arms
Sort of a coming towards you
Dogen I dance and for hey, we're about to find out
And yeah, roll a wisdom saving throw.
10.
No.
So these arms come towards you
and you try to like mentally like bat them away
and they grab you and they hold you completely still.
And what, you guys don't see these arms.
They're a mental sort of thing.
He's cast hold person on you and you are paralyzed like five seconds too late. I go choke
Say not this time and so you're
paralyzed
we'll see if that's gonna be of any use to him though because
But first it's gonna be
Mr. Yud yud yud ours turn you're just sort of chilling. Sorry Patrick
We're going to evil Steve. Oh
My turn again. My arms are at my side like
I'm on the ground just like yeah kind of like a weeble yeah you see the prince is
like the prince is like trying to shake you awake the prince should hand him the
cookie come on this guy's useless if the prince is shaking him away you know what
I'm the cookie you know what doing absolutely nothing for me right now can
you know what me like a I'm actually I'm a hundred percent okay that makes total
sense to me that's a good call I'm very okay with that did you convince me um so
So the prince is panicking a little bit and he goes into your pocket.
He remembers you saying, "Never go into my pocket."
That is what a five-year-old kid would do too.
He's like, "This guy's dead.
I should put a cookie in his mouth."
And he's panicking and he's sort of sniffling.
He's worried about you.
And he just shoves the cookie in your mouth.
So that's a healing potion.
I believe we said right each cookie.
So that's 2d 4 plus 2 is a healing potion in D&D.
If I'm correct.
Yes, I'm am.
So that is 7 plus 2.
That's 9.
Oh, baby.
So you got 9 HP back and so yeah, you just shoot awake.
You've got like these delicious cookies.
Cooper.
Cooper elf cookies.
And that was it.
What was it like a lemon poppy seed cookie?
That was a it really hit the spot. I'm gonna I'm just gonna sit this one out. I'm gonna sit the rest of this
I got one health point. I mean I got a million
No, why don't you try one of these? Why don't you try one of these cookies? I
Don't have a sweet tooth like that. I have maybe like a hamburger. That's I
Don't have a hamburger or anything like that
All right, well if it's gonna be the case then I'm definitely gonna sit this one out
Yeah, so you want to skip your turn? No, can I get attacked?
I get attacked so I can like block it or something
Yeah, I'll make try to make that happen one HP fucking bash
Fuck you. So I it's is it my turn right now. It's your turn. Yeah, it's sort of going back
Yeah, I'm gonna shit this one out and I sit down I go
Uh, what the hell? And I just turn, I'm sitting down and I take my bow and arrow out and I use uh, Conneria.
Go for it.
Okay, me. Fuck.
Let me fuck.
No. What?
[Laughter]
Uh, alright, I'm gonna use my arrow of "You're about to crap your pants."
Oh yeah.
God, you have that arrow?
[Laughter]
Wait, what does that fucking do exactly?
uh... yes
and i did a d_-day mature that you're all damages that of a attack try the attack
role i know i can get out of the
uh... i think the plus other got a great
good fucking god i guess role for damage
okay role for damage again
yeah is accurate nine
uh... yen dogan is in range so i will use this time is not as a military uh...
let me read with the error of your but the crap your pants does
I mean, here's, I'll tell you right now.
When this arrow strikes a humanoid target, the target must immediately use its reaction
to attempt to find an out of sight area as its bowels clench and roil.
On the target's next turn, it must succeed a D16 Con Saving Throw or spend its action,
bonus action, free action, and movement speed crapping itself, then hastily try to clean
itself up.
Uh, you killed him, though.
So he's gonna shit anyway.
So do you want to describe what happens?
I want you to describe what happens as the arrow enters his heart.
Well, I'm sitting down and I'm like, "Eh, what the hell?"
And I just point it, just really quick.
Just like, arrow in my hand, boom, yeah.
And then I guess it hits his heart or something and then he dies immediately.
And then just shits.
I think, Dogen, you might be close enough and perceptive enough to see that as the arrow
enters his heart, you watch his eyes flicker a couple moments, scanning for a place to
go to the bathroom, and then you watch them just go completely glazed over.
And so his last moments were just trying to find a place to take a shit as he just falls
to the ground.
at this moment was no no no no and just vanishes hey uh hey dogan can you grab that arrow for me
that's uh am i unparalyzed yeah okay i go to pick up the arrow and i accidentally touch the arrowhead
and i go oh you idiot here let me do it and i do this oh hey hey sullivan can you grab that for me
I don't feel like getting up. I just yeah, okay. I'll go and he he press touches the arrow on the tip and he just feels fine
I have a bowel problem. I think actually so this is making me pretty nervous
Okay. Now I have to go
Yes, you guys
Whoop their ass
It was pretty close though. Like I said to you guys over in our secret group chat
You guys you guys level up
Is this is this the time this is the level up time if you guys want to do that
Okay. All right. Let's do it. So
in
D&D beyond
Go to your character
Go to edit
Like there's like a little gear and you can click on like edit your character. Yeah
and you can just you can raise the level up one and
Some of you will get new stuff. I don't remember. I don't think most of you will though. I don't think I get anything
I get to pick my fighting style. Oh, yeah, you get you get some stuff
I think you're the only one who gets real stuff. I think level three is when so many options I have to read about
Oh, no. Mm-hmm
So I'm gonna go to your oh, I have higher hit points, that's good. Yes. Oh, yeah
If I level up, do I get max, do I get highest HP again? No.
I guess we have to wait for a long wait for that.
Or you could use a short rest and shift.
But yeah, so you're going to get more HP.
Now, Blessed Warrior, I could learn some spells, which would be cool.
Ooh, yeah. That is cool.
Can you just, what's the deal with cantrips?
So cantrips, cantrips you can cast at will whenever.
You never run out of them.
I'm probably going to pick that.
Let me look at what the cantrips are.
Yeah.
Light?
Light gives you, you can do light.
You can make light.
Mending, I can fix things.
Yeah.
What would, what would Dogen pick?
Is kind of, you know.
That's a good question.
A Dungeons and Dragons type question.
Yes it is.
This is the way of the world.
I'm choosing Thaumaturgy and Word of Radiance, I think.
- Woo! - Unless...
Is Sacred Flame AoE? No.
- No, it's not. - I'm picking Word of...
- Thaumaturgy and Word of Radiance... - Okay.
...are my two...
- Yeah. - ...cantrips that I'm learning.
Yeah. So, yeah, that's from Xanathar's Guide to Everything.
So, it's a very... it's a cool, cool spell.
Wait, is Word of Radiance AoE?
Yes.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It wraps you in each creature, which is right, right, right,
because everyone around you.
So basically, like, you're surrounded.
Everyone I can see that I can choose, yeah.
Hell yeah.
So, yeah.
So, yeah, you, in this moment of leveling up,
you commune with Dogen, the dirt god,
and he sees that you are, you know...
You know, oh, also you're going to get divine smite too.
So basically it's like you're recommitting yourself to Dogen the Dirt God.
You get divine smite which means you can spend a spell slot.
After you land an attack, you can spend a spell slot to add an extra d8 of damage.
Oh, okay, that's cool.
So it's very, very strong.
Do I get spells or is that just for cantrips?
You'll get spells, you can get some spells later because your paladins are basically a gish class.
So it's pretty cool.
They're just, they're like very much the typical spellblade class, I would say, actually.
Some people would maybe say, I mean there's obviously like Hexblade for Warlock and stuff, but like as far as straight, nobody cares.
So yeah, yeah, you commune with Dogen, and you know, divine from him what you're meant, how you're meant to fight.
And he you know, you determine that you're supposed to use magic.
You're supposed to become more of a magical fighter a silly little
magic fighter man and you guys leveled up which is pretty cool.
And now yeah, the hovel is yours for the taking.
There's no sign of the jester around whatever the jester wherever
he was or they were whatever doesn't seem to be around anymore,
But you see, you know, Connor is holding, you know, or he just dropped
Connery has just dropped the Yoni egg of Baskin.
So you see it.
It looks like a sort of typical Jade Yoni egg, except it is
has tiger print around it instead of like Jade.
Is that the crystal ball there?
Was that?
Yeah, I'm looking for the crystal ball.
I don't care about this Yoni egg thing.
I care about the crystal ball.
You can go and you can actually just throw that Yoni egg away.
i really don't care about it at all you know that
undertake that put in my my pocket of throat after a very funny trash barrel
and litter
and so yeah you guys to go into his hovel and see what he has their uh...
in connery is hovel
yeah is also is anyone damaged
and one h_p_
okay give me all the all kill you five h_p_
yeah
the you've got dirt into his wounds
which is how you describe it.
And I get my fingernails in there too.
So you describe lay on hands.
Yeah, it's a deep cleanse or more like rub on hands when I'm
fine.
Whoa, giving it.
Yeah, come on.
Come on.
It's just true.
So yeah, you go into his hovel.
It's pretty modest modestly sized.
Got some wood furniture.
It's got a some posters up of the jester.
He's obviously a big fan of the Jester.
[laughter]
Uh, yeah, uh...
That's environmental storytelling right there.
Oh yeah, you know me. I'm brilliant.
And, uh, yeah.
Yeah, I mean, you can obviously rummage around, see if you find anything
else that he has. Um, you know.
You could do an investigation check.
Do a little bit of digging. I'm gonna investigate.
See what you can find.
can obviously loot him as well. Yeah, I'm gonna investigate
too. Okay. I got it and I will I will also investigate. Oh
yeah. Oh, you got 21. You got a crit. Patrick Yodar got a crit
Patrick Yodar. You really dive into this place. You know,
there are other things I could have described other sort of
clues I could have given you as to where to look, but you
you didn't need them. You just sort of divine right away what
this place was my second use of define that way I gotta find some new words and
so a couple of the things that you find as you look first under his sort of cot
that he has there you find that he was storing some sort of viscous substance in
a bunch of vials I'm not gonna open these and I'm not gonna taste test them
Yeah, you're not sure exactly what they're made of but they are there.
They're in these vials.
You don't know what he was making you also find in a little box
a wooden box that has a picture of has like a like a jester hat
on it and it's like a little lock box when you open it up.
It's got like a hundred gold pieces in there.
So you find that I just weld.
Yeah, and then yeah, as you sort of rummage around through you find you find just some notes that have been left from
Well, I like notes of his own writing of him
Experimenting and it's a lot about the goo. He was messing with this goo. That's in this
Jar talks about that. He was putting in his his excrement his perspiration
All this stuff and like trial runs with it and the goo says it can make him very very slippery so
Slippery that he can't be he can't be reached
He can't be grabbed or grappled or anything. And so it's just like about what he's been doing with the good Sullivan
I made you a love potion
I'm okay. Like I don't
What do you what do you mean? You made me a love for what? Am I gonna fall? No, I think you're gonna want to drink
this I think it's a yeah it's called it's called the love
potion, but it's actually a potion that will make you
taller. Yeah. It's called that because you're going to love
it. It's specifically says in the in the great writings that
you've read like you you you douse yourself with the goo.
You do not drink it like it's not at all. So I didn't read
those. So oh yeah. Okay. So you don't even know so you if you
want to you can definitely roll a deception check Patrick
to
6 deception.
You're getting crits though.
See, not getting a crit there.
Oh my god, this is not a good switch dude.
What the fuck.
Oh my god, yeah I mean.
Okay, there's a crit again.
What the fuck.
You get 4 and fuck.
I think my items just really, I have really good stats.
Not how the crits work.
I'm taking you to Vegas dude.
Okay, I got 11.
So, SolvinTheFrog 100% believes you, that it's something you should drink, and so he starts
to drink it, and it's- he vomits immediately.
He's like, "BLEGH!"
And also, he's- "My insides feel weird."
"That's not my problem."
"Ugh, this doesn't feel good.
Oh, oh, he sees walking all weird now like he's doing like a little dance like he's like
he's all fucked up like he's like, you know, in Ghostbusters 2 when they put the ooze in
the toaster and it's like, I see I see Sullivan's having a bad reaction. I go quickly Sullivan
Get it out of your system.
And I try to grab Patrick's magic arrow to touch him with it,
but I accidentally touch the arrowhead and I go, oh,
Yeah, and then you also of course find a crystal ball.
I don't know if it works, but you do find a crystal ball in
there. I would like to use it.
Okay, you can try to roll like an Arcana check to see if you
can figure out how this thing works.
that's really would be like a there are a lot of you could do
yet seems like it's me iraq
could be iraq instead
could be a glassy rock
uh...
here but i don't know if you're correct
he's he's he's he's he's
okay uh...
and uh... it's hard to find exactly how this would work god again
uh... so
a smash it
it breaks
So like magical spirit comes out of it or anything. What about a genie spongebob comes out? Oh
Bob hi guys. Hi guys. Oh shit. Oh
It's football punch him out of the window the hovel
I don't like crystal balls
That was so fucked up. Let's get out of here.
So yeah, I mean you guys have the Yoni egg now.
You can bring that back to the white woman of the woods.
Or you can do whatever you want.
Let's do that and then let's also get the beast. I want 100% the woods.
Yeah. Okay. Alright. So you guys
start to make your way back
the white woman of the woods. If you recall it was kind of earlier in the
morning when you guys arrived because you slept the evening when you're
attacked by the changeling cowboy and you make it through the woods you kind
of know the way back at this point you know how to avoid the monkey and you
arrive at the park. Talk about the monkey I was thinking for a second what is he talking about?
Yeah, there is a monkey. It was very brief, but I had the monkey there.
And, yeah, you guys arrive at the pond.
And as you're walking towards the pond, it's not...
Once it's in view and you keep walking, you walk for about a minute and he's just not getting any closer.
And once you all sort of collectively realize this, that's when the jester appears again.
I
Fucking guy I
I'd like to make a deal with you three. Hey, check this out. No, fuck you clown
Laughing like that like that funny you like
Oh, you think this is funny?
I show my ass.
That's my ass!
Oh, now you laughing at my ass, huh?
That's two middle fingers that I'm pointing at.
Looks like this guy thinks we're real comedians, huh?
Sullivan, fuck this kid up!
Oh, no way!
Fuck him up, Sully!
I'm so, he's so weird.
I'm really nervous.
You know what?
He is pretty weird.
Thanks, man!
bet and the jester after he's done laughing I was like I would like to make
a deal with you all give me the yoni egg I can't hold it on my own it needs to be
given to me by a proper vessel a person and vessel what I if you well that's
what what did you think Connery a was think it was as natural talent as a
the
a
So you were enhancing- so I think- okay you-
Give me the egg.
You're excused from the conversation.
Give me the-
So you were- you were enhancing the- the warlock.
Give me the egg.
Were you-
I wasn't enhancing him.
You did male enhancement to that man.
Natural male enhancement?
Come on.
You- wait, hold on, hold on.
We beat him so you must be pretty weak.
Yeah, are you saying you have the secret to natural male enhancement?
Is that what this is about?
I'm not weak and no.
No, okay, that was gonna say definite deal.
If you're so not weak, why don't you just kill us right now to prove it?
100% would have been a deal if you would have given me a pill or something that would make my penis stay hard.
I'm gonna punch you in the gut if you get too close to me.
I can only control creatures and send them to do my bidding like the kitsune's.
I am coming to you now before you give the yoni egg to that stupid woman.
Hey, she had sex with my uncle one time.
Alright, she's technically my aunt.
That's not... Are you sure?
I call her I called her auntie once and she told me not to do that because it was during that I'm not gonna get into
that but
Give me the egg. I'll show you how to leave these woods and
To top it off. I'll give you this and he produces a
scepter that looks like it's made of
Tragedy and comedy masks kind of all like stacked up on one another
And on top of it has like a jester crown
It's a very very powerful artifact
Can curse those you wish to?
because with uncontrollable laughter
All right, so you can like it you could sell it. I like these smiling guys, but what are you frowning faces all about?
How much care for that
Well, do you have an all comedy scepter?
well, some would say that the other side of of comedy is is a
Tragedy and so they could they're inseparable
What what are you talking about? Thanks must be funny. Shut up. Tell it
Yeah, you know what fuck I'ma kill your ass I'm gonna say this right now shut up. All right, we're gonna do the talking
Yeah
See we do the talk.
If you don't want to take this deal, fine.
What did I just say?
Okay, I'm waiting.
I'm going to count to three.
And I'm going to count to fifteen.
A big feat for both of you.
Because fifteen is higher than three.
Yeah, that's five threes
All right nerd
One
Two one three
Four one sink fuck. Yeah, fuck it. I'm killing you. I attack him. Okay
when you wait I have
I killed myself
I'm messing up. I can't I can't fight you
You can't fight me we exist in different
Realms. All right. I'm going to the funny realm in and I'm killing you. No, don't come to the funny
I'm going someone tell me a joke
Quick, is that no good? No good. Tell me a joke. I think this is gonna work neck-neck. All right
Sorry, who's there it was interrupting Sullivan who's there
*laughter*
Oh I think I'm going somewhere!
You see the world around you
spin as you finally
succumb to the seizure.
*laughter*
Yeah I'm just on the ground.
That is not what I thought was gonna
happen.
Here I have these, I think I have smelling salts
or something.
I don't know what you do for a season.
If you don't want the scepter, you don't want a way out, you will...
I won't be the last spirit that will hunt you down.
God damn it.
When I get up, I'm killing you.
I'll send my kitsune's for you.
I'll admit we'll be a bit weaker without the yoni egg, but they will still come down on
you.
So you'll be weak.
You're already weak.
You'll be weaker.
I won't.
I mean that scepter looks like crap anyway.
CONNORIA SUCKED!
Okay, if I had a better warlock in my employ...
I think your whole squad's trash.
Yeah, he's stupid.
He'd be like, "What if I cast a spell like this?" and he'd try to use his toes.
I had to tell him not to do that.
Didn't make any sense.
He sucked.
I mean, that reflects on you.
You keep bad company.
I don't have anything else to say to you.
Yeah, I you know, you've you've been here for way too long in this deal.
We've already made it very clear this deal is not happening.
You've made that somewhat clear.
All right. Cool. Yes.
You guys, I don't think I think threats of violence are pretty clear indication
that there's going to be no deal.
Yeah. So is there no no deal?
I don't want to stick.
I jump up for my seizure.
Cool. Wow. First of all, the funny realm, really not that funny.
Second of all, we ain't taking your deal, you stinker.
So be it.
Well, actually, let's talk it over for 10 more minutes.
Yeah. And as you walk towards the pond, it now starts to get closer to you
and you get closer. And so as you do, you see the white woman of the woods
just come out of the water without you having to holler at her.
She's she's like, my egg, I can sense it.
It's near. Please.
Oh, I don't need to know that.
I watch your time of the month as nasty bullshit.
I spit the spit the egg out of my mouth.
My eyes is near.
This is is there any this is the worst way it's ever
ever have this delivered to me this is okay just just just hand it here and you
see her like holding her hands out for you to put the egg in do you give her
the egg give me like first I spit it out of my mouth and I said you're it was in
your what you better like that egg I had to go to the funny realm yeah that egg
You see her slowly dip below the water and you see her like going
Yeah, it's in there, yeah
That's what that guess that's what that feels like
It's been a while. Okay, and you see
Around her and around the pond
all the weird
plants that are like snapping at things and doing like weird little like
Goofy things and spitting seeds start to turn into normal plants like flowers and daffodils
trees with leaves that aren't
that don't
Like make you sneeze and all this weird bullshit
You see the thing that was like the egg that would
The bird that would hatch into an egg becomes an egg that can hatch into a bird this time
Everything is starting to look normal around her again
and you see she says I've
Restored so much of my power
Thank you. I cannot thank you enough
The the five of you even the little boy. Thank you
now if you wish to defeat the kitsune's I
Can have my I controlled the woods now they will be on your side in the coming fight. So that guy's a liar. I
I knew he was full of crap. He was laughing all the time.
He's probably just kidding about the whole thing now that I think about it.
That's a really strong point.
He could have just been joking about that.
Well, without the Yoni egg, he can't control the woods the same way that I could.
So, now he just has these kitsune eggs.
Do you have like a magical item you were going to give us? Or is it just that you can control the woods?
Like I mean it would be really cool if we could have like a like some kind of staff that like yeah
No, maybe maybe a staff. That's all laughter. Yeah, the snow after the funny stand. Oh, it's
Yeah, no, it's sort of like when you make the choice, oh, I'll do the good thing, you know
So we did a good thing. I'm on it
Well, I don't know what it's too early in the campaign to say whether
One thing is good or bad, but you know, you rejected the staff. I have nothing to give you yet
perhaps perhaps if you fight the kitsune's and
Kill the beast or whatever you want to do the mud men can give you I don't know
There's all right. Can we have like some of your water at least? Yes
Did you see what she did in that water?
That's her house I've been
I've been in the house. She does a lot of things in there. She had sex with my uncle in there
Can you at least let me sit in the water and make a make a Shrek farting hot tub?
Before I leave it's a dream of mine
I I
Unfortunately, I'm in your debt
Nice, I do it
Yeah, it's and it's awesome. Yeah
Yep.
Um, yeah, so she does what she did with the with the fucking warlock where she sort of
implants in your mind, like the knowledge of where the kitsune are located.
So you guys can kind of know where to go to get there.
It's it's definitely like, probably like, you know, it's a big woods and you have to
to
to sleep in the pond. Is it alright if we sleep in your house?
Um, I don't, I don't... We're in your debt.
Yeah, right. Last thing I remember, you said we were in your debt.
And I know that, I know that, uh, that whatever his character's name is that I forgot, Evil
Steve will, uh, you know, pay for it. What the hell? I thought you were my best
friend
Yeah, you know I think one of us is gonna have to sleep on it on a couch or somewhere right side
Yeah, and I'm thinking is dogan. No, I'm
See, I know your name. You already farted it all up in there
So I think that you know, you should have to stay outside. You didn't know my name. I've been with you for days
You have a confusing name. It's very long
rhymes
Goblins goblins don't have rhymes
You fucker.
Alright.
Yeah, she sort of watches this sad play between two friends losing touch with one another.
And she relents, if you want to sleep in my sort of makeshift home, I reserve for when I am entertaining guests, I can at least owe you that.
You're gonna be entertaining us too?
No, that's not- I'm not.
That is amazing! I can't wait to see what you do.
You would not want- actually, Evil Stevel, you should come down too.
If there's gonna be entertainment, I want to squash this.
'Cause I want to enjoy this fully with my friends.
The woods have just been restored. I have a lot of work to do.
Yeah, you're damn right! You gotta learn to juggle, bitch!
[laughter]
I- I'll- I will-
Okay, I'll get something together.
And, uh, you see she like claps her hands.
hands and out from the pond comes this like giant like conch shell that's like
a conch shell home. She's like I know it's sea but it's water and I just thematic
it just worked and so you see there's like a little swirly sort of big thing
on the top you see inside if you go inside there's sort of like it has a
beaded curtain and when you go in you see like live love laugh signs and it's wine
o'clock somewhere you see a lot of like just boyfriend sweaters just laying
around on the floor. I put them all on over my armor. Hey that last one was my
uncle's sweater yeah he says it says it says Trudgepole did it.
Trudgepole did it.
Yeah that's his calling card after he has sex.
He turns a sweater inside out.
He pins it up on the wall.
It's written in paint.
He's like, he gets, he leaves the room, he like looks at her and goes, "Now this is happening."
And just like, you know.
Cause he's also, he has the sweater on the whole time.
He doesn't take it off until he leaves.
He's inside, he's inside her and you see those bledders start to slowly appear, like by magic.
He's like, "Check it out."
There's like a carpet and shit like a carpet like a carpet that is a
Babe, I'm like on the wall like one of those things that girls do if it's like it's like are you sure you can put?
This on the wall. It seems a little offensive, but they do it anyway
and
Yeah, it's a nice nice cozy place got some beanbag chairs and also
She's gonna bring in some entertainment. So some critters from the woods are gonna come by
What critters you guys want to come from the three chipmunks
That's how I get in that's good
They sing that whole song
Wow
I use I use my new I use my new
Thaumaturgy to make a window fly open and the house floats
Just to test it out to see if it works yeah, it fills up with water
You see her just like just like roll her eyes and like wave her hand the water trades out and but you but she doesn't notice
a chipmunks are just like caught in between the window pane
screen. Yeah. Yeah. It's you guys hang out with the chipmunks
for a little bit. Enjoy that Sullivan tries to play you guys
a song. You see Sullivan with his loot and he's like I said
maybe hold on. I said maybe he's playing like the wrong playing
like a chord that's like also like a chord everyone knows but it's not the right one.
I said my- hold on.
God damn it can you fucking play this song?
I just I just I just looked up the tabs just.
On what?
On uh ye olde guitar tabs.
Oh okay yeah.
Yeah thanks man.
Yeah.
Um hey Sullivan can you play the axis of awesome four chords?
one's easy. Oh it's like 16 minutes long. I don't know if I can do it. We have a whole
night of entertainment ahead of us. Okay. Promise to us. Alright I'll do my best. What
is it what is it what is the first song in that? I don't know but I know it has
four chords. You know just play the chords you don't have to you don't have
to sing anything. Yeah he just tries to play the chords. You see Prince Jumanji is
is
the mall too many NPCs sort of went over this last session too.
Um, I just want to say thanks.
Yeah, good talk kid. Alright, bedtime.
Alright, well. You shouldn't have stayed up this late. You're gonna be cranky tomorrow.
I used thaumaturgy again to make my voice three times as loud and go
"BEDTIME!"
See you later.
Okay, okay
Well, good. Good night guys. And yeah, you see he
Climbs up on the ceiling and uses the towns at Nards have to hang upside down and start to fall asleep
Yeah, you guys can just sort of rest there for the night and just chill
Yeah, you all you all go to sleep nice full health, yeah, yeah full health all your spell slots are back nice
abilities used
So yeah, it's the morning you guys are waking up rubbing sleep from your eyes and it's time to head out and go
See the go go take down the kitsune. So, you know, I 100% this forest. I'm hungry
Yeah, I knock on the wall this to try and summon the the white woman of the woods. Yeah, she comes in. Yes
What is it? Yeah, what's breakfast breakfast time?
Do you know how to make egg steve-o
What's egg stevel - raw eggs hot sauce
Raw I could make raw eggs. Yeah, I'll take some dirt stevel
Is that the same but it's - eggs are dirt yeah, okay got it
I'll try to I'll get you some raw eggs
Get me some raw eggs. You're making breakfast. I
Will I have to get the raw eggs just they're just no go
I'm just I'm just throwing up before did you want anything Patrick okay this is
this is all a big flashback now oh man you vomit in my house oh man I had too
much juicy juice again yeah no I remember I'm glad you do that every time
you go somewhere okay and I'll get I guess I'll fix something up for the frog
the
evil
laughter it's people to out there so have to receive all just
honestly would be better than the rations we've been eating
uh... and in our it says just a bird
all you know bird and uh... so she goes out comes back with
six raw eggs
a couple of dirt
uh... so that's us some hot sauce
a bottle of blood red wine a_k_a_a_ juicy juice
uh...
and uh... all of her
alive bird
and she uh... fixes it all up
on uh... couple of these complaints
uh... uh... was very nice backseat chef i'm yelling at her
he's not she's not pouring the dirt right this too much of a head on it
well what should i do that should i tip the bowl while important that there is
i don't know if you figure it out
who's saying is too much head what do you mean i'm not seeing any head on the
dirt
stop
of what it's not doing what do you want
okay we go out to find the beast
but i can't kill myself
you guys kill yourselves uh... legacy breakfast it's delicious it's good
uh...
you guys say your goodbyes and you want to head out
or do you wanna
We can get lunch too.
I'll take PB and Steeble for lunch.
Raw peanut butter.
Hot eggs.
Yeah, I'm gonna take some Dee Steeble.
Do you have Steeble sauce?
I always keep
What kind of Steve we think I am
Evil's a clan
I think it's time for dinner
All right now that I've had three square meals I believe that I'm ready to destroy the beast
Thing maybe actually some dessert might get me on my feet
Yes, you brings you guys a gun
Loaded gun for dessert. Come on. Do you care we're gonna do it that oh no
Say you guys head out to the M
to towards the the kitsune's and as you sort of start to approach the place
you have to get a better look at what it looks like.
So it's you still hear the faint laughter here, you know, when most of the woods now sort of seem kind of normal, but at least where the kitsune's are things are still kind of weird.
You're still here laughter seeks on sort of weird weird googly
eye looking critters like, you know, crawling around and shit
and and and the laughter is sort of like echoing.
It's now like more real right where before it was sort of
needling at your subconscious.
Now, it's like a real laughter and it's like a horrible
shrieking one like like a hyena except a mad.
It's instead.
It's it's it's a kitsune.
It's not a gestures trick.
It's very real.
You see them now the kitsune's you see that they're dressed
in these cartoonish array of garments that are patched
together.
They look like sort of clownish comedians and you see they're
seven feet tall.
They're massive long Fox creatures and you see that their
foxhole home is this giant Technicolor tent that sits above
like a giant foxhole.
It looks like a circus tent, but its colors are both like sort of richer and reddier.
And you can see that it's like it's textured with like weight.
It's stained with berry juice, dog shit, blood, and then like some natural dyes.
Like it looks like a circus tent, but it looks like a fucking horrible like mockery of a circus tent.
And you hear them like going, "AHHHHH!"
Like just laughing and just fucking skipping around and doing dumb shit.
And you also see the White Woman of the Woods pressure
Kubler elves tending to their every whim.
Their little hands chained, giving them their food
and rubbing their feet and tending to their whim.
You see one of them taunt the Kubler elf with a cookie
and then turns it into a carrot and gives it to him.
And you also see in the tent a giant beast,
the Sasquatchian type of beast that the Mudmen were talking about.
And when you see it though, it looks like a Sasquatch from the back.
And when you see its face though, it just looks like a human clown.
And it seems to be having a pretty good time.
And it's like sort of dancing around and performing for the Kitsunes who are
laughing and enjoying it. You're all kind of watching this from the bushes.
And you also see that the clown is attending, that the clownish Sasquatch is
is
the
I'm gonna miss
You miss you might still you know alarm I'm gonna yeah, what we don't want to do what are they doing does
Okay, then I'm gonna shoot at the beast
Good thing don't do anything. Let's talk to them
Wait, hold on hold on. Can y'all hear me?
Yeah, so you pop right stop wait, oh don't my friends about to shoot you with an arrow please dodge it
I got an 11.
You shoot the arrow into the air and it crests by the beast.
And what it does, you see the laughter kind of stops and these massive foxes sort of like
stop cackling.
Like, "Ahh!"
And they start looking around to see where that arrow came from.
Who did that?
You're just standing in full view.
There is an evil guy out here.
is
and
I was going to ask you to try it's going to be a very hard to 23.
Oh my God.
Wow.
They are looking at you and they're like I have the arrow that
have the bow in my hand still you see this one kitsune come up
to you and and they're smaller than the other ones actually.
They're not like a seven foot beast, but you see they're also
dressed in a jester hat sort of similar to the jester you saw
the sea look at you
and uh... it goes uh... uh...
mining is
i think it's in a
say that it had a weird
named by c_n_n_ soon a bussy keats in a
in
okay there's a bad guy outs out in the woods somewhere in the shooting bow and
arrows and you shot an arrow at us
that is not what he what he talking about man that is not that is for i'm going to
and
radiance yeah okay so uh you guys want to roll for initiative yeah let's do it
nine five I'm getting bad initiative man why are my rolls bad now so the second
you guys roll for initiative the you see you hear like almost in like
in your mind's eye like now from like the white woman in the woods and you see
other animals now appearing from the woods bears and lions and tigers and all
these critters oh my yeah oh yeah jumping out and like attacking many of
the other kitsune you still have a group of them and Bussie in front of you but
you see now why she wanted the yoni egg because a full frontal assault is
actually plausible maybe for you guys now. And so yeah, you have some distance from
them. You're about 60 feet from this like crowd of them and you see the beast is
batting away these like bears and tigers and shit fighting among the other
kitsune and you see the Dean and Luca Vegas brothers are like cowering as
they're tied to the pole. You see the Kubler elves are like running away
trying to hide, trying not to get hurt. But yeah, so it's gonna be Bussy Kitsune's turn
first. And they're gonna take a blow dart and shoot it at you, Patrick G. O'Dar. Don't do
Don't do that. Let's see how that goes.
Okay, what is your AC?
14.
Okay, it misses you.
You see it.
You see it like sail past you and then you see two other
kitsune's now are going to sort of run up run up on you guys.
One of them is going to go for you Dogen.
The other one's going to go for you evil Stevel and they have
these very colorful looking bo staves that they're sort of spinning around and going
after you with them.
So first Dogen, that misses you, and now you.
Evil Steevel, that's a hit.
Oh yeah.
How much?
It does 4 damage.
He just sort of spins it at you and just whaps you on the side of the head.
That's nothing to me.
And now it is your turn, Dogen.
Okay, how many are nearby?
You have two that are near you, near you guys.
One that's in range of you with your melee weapon.
You have Bussi Kitsune who's in the back.
You have one more behind Bussi that hasn't gone yet.
And you have another one that's on Evil Steeble.
And then obviously whatever happens at the carnage in the back, you know, there could be more.
be more.
Yeah.
Okay.
Um, well, since there's one right next to me, I don't want to, I would like to help Steve,
but I don't want to get an attack of opportunity on me.
So I'm just going to hit that guy with my, my shovel.
Um, that's six.
Yeah.
You just like, it's just, he's just too fast.
And it's like, like, just like happily dodging your attacks.
Um, uh, and uh, yeah, it's now your turn.
Patrick, Patrick Yodar.
is
the
Adam
sword in a circle. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Like link. Yeah, it's
like it's like Kermit the Frog's arms like you know when
he's excited, he goes like yeah. Alright, I'm doing that
with my sword. Yeah, it's just doesn't really have to move too
much. Yeah. And now it is actually mister the frog's turn
So he's going to try to do fairy fire on Basakitsune, who's going to try to avoid it.
What is happening?
Yeah, I don't know what's going on.
So to give people at home context, Solven's spell save is like a nine.
So it's very easy to get out of the way, but people keep not getting out of the way.
So yeah, yeah, Busty Kitsune is like covered in the fairy fire.
You have advantage on attacks against them.
And now is Evil Stevels turn.
I'm just going to use my mace.
I think go for it on the one who's close to me.
Yeah, do it do it up.
Fuck.
Yeah, 17.
Yeah, it's okay.
Roll for the damage.
One.
that's a
down on a heater tonight
yeah i'm not sure how to scratch it with the
like the way that it is
and that's just a sample of what's going to happen
to you if we keep fighting
but
the
uh...
okay cool
uh... or date at the top of the order
uh...
and uh...
uh... yes of the fight is on you know the sort of already kind of you guys are
already going at each other
and you see way in the back by the tents where the clown sort of beast is.
You see it is fighting off these other beasts and stuff and you see it picking up
Dean and Luca Vegas and just using them as like swords as it's whacking things around.
and you see it sort of look to the three of you and hold one of them out towards you like
a blade like you're next and I kind of want to end it there.
So I'll end in the middle of the spread.
I don't know if that's...
I'm scared.
All time, within the past, present and future
Man has sought to destroy
All that's giving away
[Music]