Last time on Trebuchet Village, end of the E-Bomb's world, Raw Dogen and Evil Steevel
joined the epic Hot Babe pillow fight on Hot Babe Island, while Patrick stayed in his old
room in the Hot Babe Beehive Palace and started coloring.
Raw Dogen entered crazy demon mode and became a deaf and blind monster that scared all the
beautiful women while Stiebel tried to mitigate the situation by almost dying.
Patrick meanwhile was finally no finally met his birth mother and learned the
truth about Trunchbull who he thought was a good uncle but was actually a bad
father. Right when she seemed like she was going to tell an even darker truth a
A rune on her body activated and killed her.
Patrick was inconsolable.
After consulting with the Queen, they learned of the witch Albert, a hot babe who refuses
the moniker and lives deep in a cove on the island, but who just may be able to tell the
boys more about this rune.
Evil also harassed a nurse very badly.
And that's that.
Very badly.
Mm-hmm. I don't think it was that bad. Hmm
Bruh for you know
So we're yeah you guys are in the palace
Patrick's mother has passed away death by rune
And I take my sword and I cut my arm oh
How how deeply never mind?
so and the
the the Queen has addressed you all and has told you about the witch Albert you
could go to her she lives in the cove in the in hot babe Island you can also just
stop investigating this and go back to trying to sail to the end of the world I
want to meet this witch I feel like I feel like maybe we can kill her yeah
yeah yeah yeah maybe has some cool stuff to take yeah yeah maybe maybe she has a
wand maybe a staff or wand or cauldron but does she have a she have a tall
pointy hat oh does she fly in a broomstick that's a good question
confirm or deny these things. Is she green or a warted nose? I don't I don't know.
Does she have... I can't say this. I can't answer this. You can ask you can ask. Does she have buck teeth?
Does she sound a little bit like this? Does she laugh a lot?
Ask the queen. Nah. I'm asking all of this to the queen. Does she have pubes that are greener than her
actual green skin so there's some contrast? I haven't seen her- Like a darker green? I
haven't seen her her pubes in a long time but- So she does have- I don't remember them being green. So she has
clothes on. Is her robe dirty or clean? Does she know how to use uh- I don't care
anymore I didn't even know what I'm asking does she know Joe Joe who all
right let's go find a living a Halloween castle okay we could go no to the
Halloween castle that she lives in so Halloween Cove well what you should know
is that she lives... Halloween Cove on Hot Babe Island would be choice! Oh my god, so many
cats and nurses. Well her name is Albert so she lives in Albert's Cove she's the
only one who lives there. I didn't say that I didn't say that in character voice.
Okay, Albert who? She just goes by Albert. She goes by Albert? Albert one.
Interesting name for a hot babe. Albert Finney. Albert your hand with a
a match. Albert Einstein. Now Albert Einstein is a guy I used to know. She was one of the
fairer babes but she's decided that she didn't want to have anything to do with us and off
she went to the cove. You say fair babe like a bearded lady? Yeah she's got a full beard
right? I don't remember. She's a geek. You see at the fair. Not that I remember. Holy
I don't I don't fuck with geeks.
She's more of a freak or a geek?
If we mean geek by
Circus terms I guess freak then just cuz she uses a she's a freak, but she has all her faculties, you know
Oh, she's and what direction did you think she was?
So she works at the school from freaks and geeks. Okay. She's faculty
She's the therapist in this guidance counselor. Oh the one with the long hair. Yeah, who's in that?
I always knew that was a girl because of the long hair.
Yeah, that makes sense.
It makes sense that it's a girl.
What is it a long time?
Because he has long hair or she has look.
I don't even know anymore.
Let's go to the Halloween Cove.
So it's she'll tell you how to get there.
So on the woods on the far side of the island is a sharp cliff
that drops off and from below their inland is Albert's Cove.
Okay, so sort of around that cliff and then inland and towards the island.
The best way would be to take your ship around the island from where you've docked.
I have to take a ship.
You have your own?
Yeah, I just shipped my pants.
I want a bag of ships.
Around the island towards the cove until the waterway will narrow and then you'll anchor
it and then take your dinghy through the rest of the way.
Yeah, I took a ship on my dinghy.
*laughter*
No, your dinghy is on your ship.
That's how I got a dinghy off of your ship.
*laughter*
No, I got ship on my dinghy.
Get that ship off of your dinghy.
What you must know...
*laughter*
It's already the worst episode we've ever done of TNT, bro.
is that the
the the co so there are women on this island who
Are not born hot
These are average looking women as we know they become feral
So oftentimes we try to take care of them
Some of them though they don't want to be taken care of and they
They run from us and they end up towards the cove and you should you should
Know that they are there and they are dangerous the legacy sorority girl the hot girls childhood best friend
The loud girl who could be hot, but she's really loud. So when you try to remember her face, she's always fatter than you think she is
or worst of all
The horse girl whose eyes are too close together
So she sort of looks like the horses she rides and you're thinking why would you pick this as the thing you do?
It's like sort of increasing the association
They're all here though on the island and so you should just be wary of that.
Do they have a bathroom on the island?
Because I gotta take a ship on my dinghy.
Mm-hmm.
You guys like that?
Did you guys like that?
She tuned you out.
What'd you say?
No, I'm not talking to you.
I'm talking to my boys.
I, you know, I feel like we were so far gone past the ship and dinghy thing that I honestly
tuned that out completely.
Alright that makes sense.
I'm going.
I will give you.
It's gonna be funny again in a little bit.
I do actually believe that.
I think it's already pretty funny.
I think it's already pretty funny, yeah.
I'm going to give you.
Get that ship off your dingy.
Oh my god.
Patrick your dingy.
It's covered in ship.
Put your dingy.
First of all, I'm not going to put my dingy on the ship.
I'm not going to put my dingy on the ship.
Patrick, your dinghy! It's covered in chip!
First of all, put your dinghy away.
Nobody wants to see your dinghy.
Second of all, it's covered in chip!
Ain't nobody got time for that.
The hot babes who've been endlessly tolerant with you all, their eyes are glazing over.
They're just trying to focus.
You see one of their nose starts bleeding as you keep rambling about dinghies and chips.
Okay, I would like to go capture these ugly women this very instant. I'm ready
to go to the witch. They're not ugly, they're average. Oh that's, you know what, it's it's
all on a, you gotta, it's a curve on the island. It's like you're trying to keep us in this room. Yeah, stop, just
just don't correct me, but here's what I'm gonna do. I'm gonna, I'm gonna attack
every last one of these ugly women and I will put them all over the dinghy and
and put shit all over them.
(laughing)
- Yeah, and I'll do that too.
- Yeah.
So I'm gonna go find them right now
and you will give me a dog that I can give their scent to.
I can give the dog things that ugly women like.
- I can be the dog.
When I was deaf and blind,
my sense of smell got super powered like daredevil
so I'm like a dog now for women.
Okay, here, smell this cammy.
It smells like shit.
(laughing)
Woo!
I'm gonna put it on my dingy.
(laughing)
Yeah.
Okay, now point with your entire--
Now it smells like dingy.
Okay, yeah, so let's, I guess I have to.
So yeah, you guys are sent out of the palace.
Since you won't walk out.
you're sent out of the palace.
This heat's cooking me.
Woo!
I am so tired.
I can't function at all.
It's okay, we're gonna power through this.
My brain is literally only shipping
patches.
You need to right the ship, ship diggy.
I've got stuff.
I've got stuff for you.
I'll right the ship.
I think I got it.
I'm gonna be honest with you.
the I don't remember what we're talking about yeah so which yeah so here's a
rune on the room I'll give you a little no there's nothing like that going on
there was so the rune on your mother my mom yeah the character yeah when it
activated disbelief yeah you were your mom died yeah yeah your mom died and
when she died there's one you can't say shippy dinger yeah she said shippy
dinger and she said chippy dinger and then she died. And after she died you guys were like well we
don't know the actual origins of the rune all that stuff and so the Queen Bee
suggested you could go to see Albert she's the one on the island who might
have something to say about that and that's sort of what this is is you trying
figure out why did your mom die when she said what she said how can you figure
out what happened there do we have the room with us I mean so you can request
that you can try to get either you can make a copy of it or you can do
something more and we're gonna draw on my flesh no I'm gonna Patrick yeah so we
both that we agree you didn't know that was your mother right I don't remember
Yeah, you didn't know. So you're not exactly attached to the idea of her body
being completely intact at this point in time. Look, honestly, I got real into that
ship and dinghy thing. That's all I care about right now. Okay, cool. Can I put, is
there maybe a big blanket in the room that I could just throw over, over
Patrick? Um, was there a big blanket in the room? I mean, so some of the guards have
like cloaks that they're okay I'd like to take that off of one of the guards and
throw that over Patrick's head and then I'd like to go and I'm gonna try to cut
out the rune from his mom's body okay yeah I mean you start to start to do
that and she's like what are you what are you doing one of the guards what are
you doing yeah I have a different voice for her I got ship on my dinghy look at
that guy he's he doesn't know what he's yeah he stole your cloak I stole a cloak
okay well stop doing okay this is cut it off cut it off from the mom's body yeah
I cut it off yeah dude nice roll roll medicine check actually let's have you
roll but I can see how well you cut it off I would say very well but we'll see
we'll play your little game through five you've been playing it for years uh-huh
Uh, a five?
Yeah, you kind of like cut a little bit through it as you're cutting it off so you can I can I can I accidentally just cut her head off?
Yeah, i'll allow it yeah
And where on her body is the rune?
The rune was on her
Neck if I remember correctly, okay, so so either way
I got the rune right?
Yeah, it's kind of mangled.
So I just have her head in my hand? Yeah.
Guys I got the rune! Let's take it to Albert.
Okay, let's go. Alright, it's fine.
So you got Patrick's mom's head in your
I guess inventory. You guys get on the ship.
I guess I need to hide that so that Patrick doesn't see it. I don't think he saw it.
I have my hand inside it.
I'm doing it.
I don't give a crap.
I'm doing its mouth like a sock puppet.
I'm going like...
What are you making her say?
Really don't give a shit at all.
There's shit on the TV.
That's about what I thought it was.
That's what I like.
I like that.
It's so heavy that I don't really want to...
Oh, I'm dead.
Yeah.
I'm doing that to Patrick.
That's my mom's head.
- That's my mom's head and she died.
- Hey Patrick, check this out.
- I died, my head came off, look at me.
- My mom's head came off and she died.
- And look Patrick, I'm completely making out with her now.
- Yeah, he's making out with her now, look at that.
That's crazy.
That's crazy, that is crazy stuff happening.
- And because the head is kind of heavy,
if I'm just gonna put it in my backpack,
- She's a heavy, she was a, let's be real,
she was a bit of a heavy set, big ass set.
- She was a hot babe.
- She had a big head, okay.
- Yeah, she was a hot babe.
- If she was Patrick's mom, she had a big head.
So I'm gonna take the head and it's a little heavy.
So instead of just carrying it--
- We're playing a fantasy game, you didn't have to say that.
- I'm gonna throw, just every couple of--
- It's a complete fantasy game,
you did not have to say that at all.
- Every 20 feet or so, I'm just gonna throw it ahead of us
to just, so I don't have to carry it
and then just keep picking it up.
- I'm running to catch it.
And maybe as it hits the ground,
it's like picking up leaves.
- Yeah, roll athletics.
- There's pine cones getting stuck in her head and stuff.
- Both of you roll athletics.
- I'm instinctively trying to fetch it
because I'm a dog now for winning.
- I got an eight.
- You roll two.
- Dogen, raw Dogen.
- What am I rolling?
- Athletics.
- So an eight, it's a pretty bad toss.
It's kind of low.
It's kind of like when you're playing catch with somebody
and they kind of throw it like.
I got a nine.
Around your like gut and you're like, "Oh, okay, I guess I'll have to catch it there."
A nine?
Okay.
Yeah, he just kind of like, you overshoot it and he just throws the head at like the
back of your like calves as you're running.
It's like it's caught.
Ow.
Yeah, he's holding his arms close to his body like he's about to catch like a perfect football
throw.
Yeah, yeah.
And I do spiral the head, by the way.
Yeah.
Awesome.
That's awesome.
And you end up on the ship.
And you guys take the ship around
Hape Bay Island. It takes a little bit of time.
It's not like an insignificant island.
You know, it takes a few...
It takes probably like an hour to get around.
I spent the hour
building
a new body for
Patrick's mom out of mud.
[Laughter]
You see some of your
rubbers coming and you're like commanding
them to help you build the...
Didn't we leave them in our sex factory?
Did you leave all of them in the sex factory?
I thought that was the whole thing.
While he's doing that, I...
I cut off a rubber's head and I put my mom's head on it.
No, you don't kill one of the rubbers, man.
Why?
We need them for our sex sperm woman factory.
Because we're sperming, we're using them for sperm.
Our women in spermulators.
I'm turning a rubber into a woman.
I'm turning a rubber into my mom. That's not they're both
Made a perfectly good. Yeah, mom. Yeah
All right. I guess I have a mud mom now
But she can't talk unless I stick my hand in her mouth
It's cool, they got like a mud
Mom, you got solvent toilet. You need to sort of populate your whole
World you're right. You're right. That's a really good point patches. We start using her head as the toilet instead
Let's just consolidate it all yeah
Yeah, I don't want it. We don't need a mutt. We don't have room for a mud statue. There's already too many
We need another toilet. There's
Are you gonna use the rune then or no? Yeah, we're bringing a bomb with us. Yeah
Okay, bring it all the mud bomb comes wherever we go. I guess we don't want shit in her when we
we'll wait until yeah we'll wait until after but yeah so we're just so I guess
we'll just hold her head with the mud body on it yeah with a it's a more of a
mud case it's a mud mom yeah mom body it's like a pillar for a bust yeah it's
like a moth full bomb bomb body would be a with big front and back yeah gathered
around the crew to try to explain what you're doing.
- Yeah.
- They're all like standing there.
- I need no mind, this is, this is,
- Looking on.
- This woman's not alive.
- Okay.
- It's a mud mom body.
- A mud body, a mud back and mud front.
And I assure you, she's not feeling any pain right now.
- Where'd you get her head from then?
- We don't really remember.
- All right, that's no problem then.
But where'd you get the mud from then?
- The ground.
That's really none of your business.
Sorry, sorry, Captain.
My apologies. Mom, me, my apologies.
Plank. Plank.
Oh, no. Not the plank.
I see one other. A bigger crew member
takes out a plank.
I'm making a new plank.
I take a picture with my
iPhone. Oh, this is so
humiliating.
You like it. It's the new trend.
I don't like it.
Because this world is so old, it takes place
so long ago the plank was still viral yep holy shit and that's how far back in
time we went I didn't realize that we were so ancient that it was set in a
fucking time when the plank was still viral. The plank was still viral. Holy fucking shit are you for real?
you're not just kidding right Cam? It was still viral the post planking. The plank? Oh my god so alright so that means
Is the plank viral right now? The plank in this world it's so far back in time
that planking is still viral to do.
- Oh my God!
- That's really fucking crazy.
- And Gangnam Style just cracked 1,000 views.
- Whoa.
- It's over a billion now, how's that fucking possible?
- It's 'cause it's so far back
that even planking took off.
- All right, if we're gonna exist
in this weird, fucked up, old ass world,
then let's just continue on with it.
- I guess so, if this is how it's gonna have to be.
- Yeah.
- All right, we're at the, we got--
- You get to the cove.
And you guys get to the cove, and it is like,
much like everything else on Hot Bay Bayon,
it's beautiful.
Like it just sort of is immediately like arresting visually,
has this like, kind of beautiful dark rock
that makes up the cove,
with like sort of a, you know,
crag, craggy sort of sidling that you can walk along,
and this sort of like, you're rushing waves
that are like colliding in the center of it.
but is getting narrower now and see certain for the ship and you have your
dingy
you take your dingy out in the three of you i guess in the mud mom before view
together
they finally got a replacement for sold and
and it's a patrick's mom
uh... with uh... with a full mud mom body from a fronted mud breath back in
and a a guys can take the uh... the small boat through the cove
uh... uh...
and uh... uh...
it's it's it's such a good obviously if you're cool
as you're selling through search to get darker
and uh...
uh... kisses co has no natural light
uh... you should take here sort of like
they like you like whispering in like
humming in these
and he said he was sort of like creeping and crawling in
the crinkling of uh... older
uh... certain our flesh
and uh... i need you uh... who's actually actually what's your orientation on the
thingy right now
where's everybody's it's really on the day you
you know i'm not a buddy i don't know about these guys i am not sitting on a
biggie
i don't know what i ship all over that day he i sit my sweet fucking
pussy right on that day
mhm
okay if i'm gonna sit on the big yet just the tip i'm sitting right at the tip of
the day he of the front of the back to it
of the front tip
on all the way down
I got the whole dinghy.
Count has got the whole dinghy.
He's taken the entire dinghy.
I'm teasing the tip of the dinghy.
Where is...
It's just the front end of a boat
with the tip of it just going slightly
in your asshole.
Being like, yeah.
Nuh uh. That's all you get.
I can take it all.
Ladies, if I wanted to...
My feet are in the water.
Yeah, so that's your position.
Yeah.
Uh, wait, but Pat, when you say "all the way down," where is that in the boat?
Is it like in the front of the boat?
The bow?
The stern?
All the way down.
That should be it.
Where's the mud mom?
She's on my lap.
What?
Bro.
So you're...
Don't.
You didn't say anything.
So are you getting...
you say you're getting are you like getting like sort of like penetrated by
the tip of the boat no I got a little bit yeah a little bit okay and so the mud
mom is like there's a tease yeah how are you guys balancing that so that the boat
doesn't tip over I guess okay then I guess I have the back end of the boat
the big flat part in my ass because I would say weight wise Dogen is the
lightest probably so it's not an issue yeah so then I'm sitting at the back of
it okay okay that's probably fine and I guess yeah Patrick is all the way down
so which is at the back so Dogen I need you to roll dexterity saving throw with
disadvantage because you have a mud mom on your lap and I have a tip in my ting
it doesn't affect your dexterity oh it affects mine you know my legs are shaking
I can't react properly.
Uh, what do I need to roll?
Dexterity save?
[Groan]
With disadvantage?
Oh yeah, yeah Jerry.
Well that was good.
Thank you.
I have to get out moments of peace.
Wow, they're both 20.
No shit, really?
Gorgeous.
I rolled two 19s in a row.
So a, like, a, um,
perfectly average arm reaches out from the rock on the side of you. As you're
getting into this cove, the sides of it are sort of narrowing in. You could see
areas where you could walk, but you guys are taking your boat, which is probably
safer. The walking area starts to slope. But from the walls on the side, an arm
reaches out and grabs you, and you're able to pretty deftly dodge it. And you
start to see a sort of a like, not a great haircut, but like she's doing her
best pop its head out of the wall and we need you all to roll initiative.
Holy crap. Finally a little bit of fucking action. Yeah we haven't had action for
like I mean pretty much two episodes because the pillow fight kind of became
more of a psychological standoff. Yeah. So I got an 18 and then a 22 because it says
virtual tabletop not found. I got an 11. 18, 12. You got an 11? Yeah. Charlie Brown reference.
I got an 11. He would be pretty, I mean that's a pretty good roll though. I got, well it's
really. It's more the phrasing that's the reference rather than. Charlie Brown, he got
rock yeah dice is kind of like a rock so the actually the the the the average
women go first despite that 18 which is very good just they were 22 when you're
saying average do you can you maybe name like a real-life women woman that like
all four of us know as like a like kind of a jumping-off point but not a
of celebrity like someone we personally know? Let me think for a little bit. Let
me see like let me look at some of our group chats. Hold on. Yeah. Oh they
changed the name of that one. One of the girls in here for sure. Oh that one okay.
Say no more.
Okay, yeah.
Yeah.
So yeah, the woman who reached out to grab you,
she's going to try to swipe again.
This time she's trying to reach out with one arm and then her other arm is now
like bursting out of the wall and coming out for another swipe.
And it's like a pretty ferocious swipe.
It's like kind of like almost shocking, but she's not able to get you.
you're able to dodge it, even with the mud mom on your lap.
You're able to dodge it.
- I have the brick in my thick.
- And then you, Patrick, you spot
at the peripheral of your eye,
one of the women who burst out of the wall,
and she's holding in her hand two glowing rocks,
that are two glowing rocks,
and she's hurling them at you and going, "Nyah, nyah!"
And she rolls them.
- Two glowing rocks, rocks, dude's rock.
And, uh, oh, she got a natural 20.
Uh, yeah.
Okay.
You take, uh, uh, 15 damage as she hurls this rock square between your,
uh, your eyes, Patrick.
Oh, I don't care anymore.
It's, it's not letting me hold on.
Yeah.
All good.
It's all fine.
I'll also take a look.
Meanwhile, the last one who is currently fighting you all, who popped down from
below the ceiling, and she's falling onto the boat right now. And I think for
cinematic's sake, I'm gonna give you all a chance to sort of use a reaction as
this woman who looks like she like has to splurge at Ambercrombie and
fish is sort of falling onto the boat.
Is there anything you guys want to do?
Are you going to let her sort of like pounce?
She'll probably land on patridge.
There might be things you can do that like you have a reaction for.
So you can dodge, you can definitely like try to like shove her off.
Can I like swing the mud mom by her ankles and like try and hit her out of the way?
I swung my cutlass at Cortez and got a 23.
Okay, so you could do either of those things.
I would say that like in this scenario, which is very much me breaking
a bunch of rules, but you can pick one sort of action
that I think like will sort of determine like...
One action for all of us or each of us?
That's a bad idea. I think here's the thing, if each of you do an action, I think like
either, because I'm being very playful right now, you can either each like
pick an action that all works together and then like kind of resolve it together
or if you're all doing like like if you're swinging your cutlass and you're
swinging your mud woman we're gonna have to kind of resolve both those things
happening as this person is coming guys hear me out what if we all got on the
back of the boat so the pointy and that used to be up Dogen's asshole that he
was teasing with his little asshole if we if we got all on the back of the boat
straight up like this and then she landed on the tip and like just yeah just got
like sliced in half by the shark oh my god Dogen was that thing that was in
your ass would you describe it as razor-sharp it's covered in ship well
that's perfect cuz I think that we might be able to kill this this woman who must
be on her period we can kill her with the shippy dinger all right let's do it
all right I run to the back of the boat okay so you hear is just coming with you
okay let's do a couple rolls in the resolve this y'all thought I was teasing
teasing. I think to make this work, let's have you guys do a
let's have a straight decks checks. And then I'm trying to
think Yeah, I think I think athletics really is honestly
what this is. I say either acrobatics or athletics, sort of
make the call of like, sort of maneuvering to the back. And
then we're gonna have to figure out a couple other like probably
one or two other checks just for balancing the boat. I think this is like a fun idea.
So athletics?
We're rolling athletics.
Yeah, all of you guys pick either athletics or acrobatics.
Oh, either? Well then I'm choosing acrobatics. Well, never mind, I'm choosing my athletics.
I got a 10 on both so it doesn't matter.
I got a 19.
Okay, and you, Patrick?
22.
Okay, Caleb, you're fine, or sorry, evil I should really be saying. You're already in
the back of the boat, so it's sort of like-
Yeah, I didn't know who you were talking about at first.
I should say that because that's, I think, I feel that's proper etiquette.
I agree.
Oh, heavens.
You two, very nice rolls.
You're able to make, to maneuver to the back.
Now, and this is, I want you to both roll, all three of you to roll.
I would say, oh, this is fun.
I kind of want to do like, I think if this is, I think this is just straight, no, this
is either athletics or acrobatics again just to make sure you're balancing
correctly so you all made it to the back pretty quickly while this thing is this
thing is like popped its head out falling down you immediately all new to like
strategize and go to the back but to balance the boat I think correctly all of
you should roll acrobats and athletics again okay acrobatics or athletics or
both again or or just about you know knowing your I got a weight okay 16 okay
Patrick?
Hey Pat.
Eighteen.
Eighteen?
Okay.
Very helpful to offset that eight.
Pretty good.
Yeah, I would say you're like, this woman is falling down and as she is, you can hear the
tip of the boat, like, because you guys can barely even like see it.
You kind of just all like, it's actually new just from fighting together for all these years.
So just like sort of like, you know, you can hear the tip of the boat.
You can barely even like see it.
You kind of just all like, it's actually new just from fighting together for all these years.
So just like sort of like, you know, you can hear the tip of the boat.
You can barely even like, you can barely even like, you can barely even like, you can barely
and as she is, you can hear the tip of the boat,
like, 'cause you guys can barely even see it,
you kinda just all, it's actually new,
just from fighting together for all these years,
to just like, sort of, for these six months, really,
in game, but you guys have been fighting together
a while, pretty closely, to just go like,
oh, let's fuck her up, and you guys run to the back
of the boat, sort of like, adjust your weight,
and boom, boom, and this just gets the small of her back
she's falling like here and she just like knocks her fucking she smashes her
head like on the front of the boat as the boat sort of like gets back down and
she's she's not looking good she's still alive what the dinghy went right I don't
think that it I don't know if that impales her in a pair impaled Ogins
fucking get it little man okay if it injured her at all she's gonna
get like sepsis or something cuz there's there's shit all over that yeah I start
tapping my wrist and now we wait I couldn't give you I couldn't give you a
full a full impaling based on the rolls but you did very well she's not it must
be so hard to DM us because we're so fucking like creative and it come up
with ideas like no other person has ever come up with and in Dungeons & Dragons
history. Basically, but also though you don't argue with anything I say when it
comes to rules so it's easier because I'd have people going well actually
that's not how you would do that move. Oh. So it's be like hmm it's both easier and
harder. I'm gonna start doing that. Please. Yeah I'm gonna learn. Stay tuned. I'm gonna do it. I don't have to worry. I'm gonna finally learn the first thing about D&D. I don't have to worry about that. But now it is
actually who got the 18? Patrick you did. It's your turn. Okay. So you have one of them
coming out of the side well I got that 22 with the cutlass of Cortez do I have to
roll again no you said you got oh yes you do have to roll why'd you say that
like such a bitch I got the 22 with the cutlass of Cortez.
I got a 21.
Wow.
My cutlass is a Cortez.
And I got 9 damage.
Okay, who are you attacking?
So uh.
Whoever.
I'm attacking everybody.
Oh my god.
What about the lady who we impaled?
Will she live if we don't attack her?
You get 9 damage.
able to then slide nine damage for a total damage of 27 no that's what it
says right here so this is 10 plus a long because my slashing damage is 10 I have
to slashing damage I'm I what have I done it says slashing my hand slashing
damage eight and then well there's a sneak attack roll here but I don't think
that I got a sneak attack. - Oh yeah.
Ooh, do you have a sneak attack here?
- We're flanking them. - How do I know?
- The mud bomb is flanking them.
- I don't think you're flanking.
- All right, I guess we'll just take away the--
- The mud bomb just stayed in the bow of the boat.
- Yeah. - So you're flanking her.
The sneak attack rules, I always like,
they're very annoying.
You don't have advantage. - I don't know how
I got a sneak attack though. - Oh, you know what though?
You are within, yes.
That has a hostile creature within 5 feet of it.
But you're thinking, "An enemy has a hostile creature within 5 feet of it."
And it does, because you're all within 5 feet of her.
That's true.
So it's not quite flanking, but it is, um...
Yeah, you do get sneak attack also.
Okay, so...
God, I figure how easy it is to get sneak attack.
Um...
So I got a 27 damage.
No, hold on.
That's what it says.
You might be right, I'm just, um...
You may be crazy.
Might just be a lunatic I'm looking for.
I just want to read.
Okay, that's 1d6, 5+5, right you got 5 on that I forgot.
Because it gave you the bonus.
Because you have the charisma of a conquistador.
And 3d6.
And another 2d6.
Who is that?
What is the origin of that?
2d6?
That sounds like sneak attack to me.
Well it is, but there's like an additional 2d6 I'm trying to...
Double sneak attack.
No, it's not.
You can't just say stuff.
Only I can do that.
It's a double sneak attack.
I mean, you know what?
If it's resolving that, I'll look up the origins later or somebody will correct me and DM me.
Oh my god.
What is that?
27 damage?
I'll have to figure that out.
I'm going to have to figure that out later.
I mean, describe your kill, obviously, on this sort of firm 6 out of 10 type of broad.
Well...
A 6 out of 10 New York.
I cut her head off and then I put it on the mud mom's body.
Whoa, what do you do with mud mom's head?
You chillock it.
It's two-headed.
Oh my god, a two-headed mud mom.
- Oh my god. - We got a two-headed mud mom.
- And I turn to the other guys.
- We got a two-headed mud mom.
- I turn to the other guys and I say,
yeah, just aim for their heads
and then we're just gonna keep putting them
on top of the mud mom's body.
- Mud mom totem pole.
- Mud mom. - Mud mom.
- Totem pole. - Mud mom.
- Mud mom, totem pole.
- This is great.
So it is now,
who got the 12 again?
- Cha-cha-cha-cha.
I talk like that sometimes. I think I got the initiative roll. An 11 or something. I think
it was... Okay, so it's you. Me? What did you get Caleb? I don't remember. I think I got
the 12. I think you got the 12. So wait, did you kill the... So is the one who hit the
tip of the dinghy, they're dead right? The ship tip. The ship who shipped all over the
- The dinghy, there's a shippy tip.
- Yeah, she already took--
- The shippy dinghy tip.
- Which one's closest to me?
- She already took a significant amount of damage
when you killed her.
- Okay.
- So the one that's closest to you is,
the one that's flinging rocks at you,
I mean, she's all the way up there.
Like, you gotta do ranged attacks on her.
There's one that is within reach
and is like grabbing at you.
That one, you can try to take her out.
- Hmm, interesting.
Okay, so maybe I will use...
(whining)
Maybe I will use Guiding Bolt.
- Okay, but aim for the head.
- Oh yeah, I guess I need to cut her head off.
- But not the brain.
- Wait, hmm.
- What kind of-- - Get it at her neck.
- Can I-- - Her head is quite strong.
Do you wanna aim for a specific body part?
- Yeah, can I aim for her fucking neck right now?
You don't mind. I'm gonna see if I feel like there's something either buried in the yes
Yeah in the Dungeon Master guide about
body parts and if not
Yeah, I don't think there is. All right
Okay, cool
You can definitely aim for the neck what we'll do
Trying to think of what we'll do
Has a hundred and twenty foot range on that one
Yeah
You'll roll for an attack roll and then we'll roll a we'll just roll a
D20 again just to see if you're able to approach the head
and
We'll I'll average it out from there. I'll come up with a better system for body part attacking
I feel like somebody has one out there. So yeah roll an attack roll just on the guiding bull
So I click cast on God and Volt, right?
Yep.
Nothing happens on my screen when I do that.
That's so strange.
Except it takes one of my spell slots, that's it.
You should be able to press on the damage.
Oh, I think it thinks you're dead.
Why would I be fucking dead?
You might have played so damn badly.
No.
It's just not true, so...
Let me just make you back to life.
Alright.
I'm gonna take my spell slot back then.
I think that my neighbor got a bird.
What kind of bird?
One that goes "wow wow wow wow wow".
That's just a sparrow.
I think it actually might be a sparrow.
I think I might have a pirate in my fucking building.
A sparrow.
My God, my neighbor's pet sparrow is so loud.
I'm sick of all the sparrows in my neighborhood.
Am I alive again?
Yeah.
Just click on the damage thing.
But that, I have to hit if I do that.
I have to hit before I go.
So hit the plus four, oh no, not the plus four.
Yeah, plus four and guiding bolt.
Oh, there we go.
Okay, so I got a 20.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Beautiful, that hits for sure.
All right, and now I'm gonna roll for damage and I got a 22 with my damage nice
You're aiming which one again the the one that was throwing rocks at me. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, so you you
Sling your guiding bolt at her and it like
Roll another d20 just do a nice. You just do that. That's the only thing that this doesn't is this doesn't does
19 nice. Yeah, you got it fucking right on the neck. Oh
you get her neck and
You start to see tearing there
Starting to show and is there blood just fucking everywhere. Of course. Oh my fucking god
Yeah, there's blood and guts everywhere
Yes
Just gushing
From her neck. She's still alive, but she's not looking too
She's hot nor was she ever
And you're up
Dogen, Rod Dogen, me.
Okay.
Um...
What's...
Is there one close to me that I can just swing at the neck?
Yes.
I'm just gonna go ahead and swing at the neck real quick.
Yes, just the one I was reaching out at you before.
Yes.
With my war oar?
Go for it.
I'm not gonna do anything fancy with it.
Let's see here.
Mm-hmm.
My attack is a 14.
Okay.
If it does not hit, she's able to sort of swiftly dodge out of the way of it.
for you. Okay. Okay. No bonus actions. I don't think you have anything really worth doing.
No. Yeah. And I'm not going to do anything. I'm just going to chill. Meeep! Okay. No.
It's their turn. So the woman you just swung at, she's going to pop back inside the wall.
And so she's gone from inside, she went back inside the wall. The other one who you like,
who, Steve-o, you like-
A wall woman?
seared her neck
um
she's gonna, uh, take her-
she's gonna reach back inside the wall, both her arms
and just sort of
*weird noise*
and yank out a giant fucking rock
and toss it directly at your-
PUT THAT BACK!
um
so I need all of you to roll a
uh, dexterity saving throw
ok
this one
I got a-
you're gonna roll something like that?
I got a six
which is
I think it's out of six or seven. Mega yikes, dude. I got a 13. Okay.
Patridge.
Seven. So the rock fucking crashes onto the the uh the dinghy and um uh it traps your leg,
Stievel and your arm Patridge. Both of you take... Traps it in a good way?
Both of you take 11 damage. Fuck. Dogen you're gonna take half damage. I'm at 1 HP.
Yeah. It's half of 11 so 5.5. No no no no you take you take you take 6. I'm gonna go
ahead and take five thanks mmm yeah thanks for your input but yeah I'm gonna
go ahead with 5.5 probably gonna take oh everyone says it rounds down and I don't
believe in that I think you should always round up that creates more tension yeah
I'm gonna go ahead I just took 5.5 I'm fine you can take five damage do you know
that's the wrong number do you know where to find your health top right
corner. Oh yeah okay so it it thought that I was at zero HP the entire time so what
should I be at? Should I just be at max HP?
From your max HP is 35 so you took 11 so you should be at 24. Yeah okay so now
yeah but in D&D Beyond I was for some reason I was at zero HP so now I'm at 24
Okay, I'm ready to go.
Alright, fine. I like rounding.
I'm back.
Plus he's at Wizards of the Coast.
Who I love, also.
And I love Hasbro.
I already rounded up. You can drop it.
Drop it!
Drop it.
Change the subject.
Ummm...
And the other...
Yeah, she missed already, right?
other one? No, she went in the hole. Yes, oh yeah, that's gonna be fun. Your turn,
Patrick.
Who am I close to? Right now... Do I have like potions that I can take to heal
myself? I don't know if you have healing abilities. Your friends, you, I think
Stevel should have a cure wounds spell maybe okay then I'm gonna take my sword
and just hit anyone in my vicinity so before you do that the only people in
your vicinity are your friends and your mud mother okay please don't hit me bro
do you have other abilities you have a gun too by the way I have a gun yes okay
then I will shoot my gun. You can shoot it at the one who's who's far away. Yeah. Okay
roll d20. I had a whole gun system but I'm abandoning it right now. All right.
I just don't want to deal with that.
I mean it's seven. So yeah that that way. So you shoot your gun. 20 plus anything? I mean it's
gonna be adding your your dex and your proficiency which is which is plus five
which is still not enough. Okay. So you shoot it and sort of just like clinks off the
side of the rock and you're not able to hit her. I mean you have you know you have
bonus actions, not really though. I mean I guess you can you can use a eye for
detail. So you can use a bonus action to make a perception check to spot a hidden
creature object. Okay I'm gonna do that. Make an investigation because one of them did just
disappear. I just did that. Okay so roll, you rolled perception. Ten. Cool. You don't
know exactly where she went but you start to listen and you go to hear kind of
like scurrying along the walls so if somebody else maybe tried listening
they'd maybe be able to find where this thing is gonna pop out next
next I put my gun in my mouth and I say
I roll intimidation 10 that's not enough all right and we're gonna go to Steve
it's your turn. Alright, um, hmm. I'm gonna cast a level fucking nothing chill touch
I think, because she's pretty much dead right? That the bitch all the way over on
the other end. Make sure to get her head though. Yeah, so don't worry I got an idea
here. She's pretty close yeah? Yeah, she's not doing the hottest of all time. Alright, well
she was never the hottest of all time right?
You used to have a shit head, come on.
All right, so I'm gonna roll chill touch.
- Maybe the hottest dog of all time.
- All right, I got it.
- Canine creature.
- Yeah, you're the hottest of all time.
Yeah, the hottest dog of all time.
That's pretty good.
- Yeah, I am.
- I'm gonna have to remember that, write that down.
- I got an eight.
- On your attack?
- On my attack, is that considered good?
- No way that's that hit.
- Okay, down a notch.
All right, no, no.
- It's not either.
- I got an eight.
- You're out, Dogen.
can you guy on your attack you know so it's a she is his lawyers uh...
resents
so you have a sleeve a gun
yeah but i wanted i wanted to swing and hit her head off
i know but she is like uh... on
like uh...
there's nobody down
uh... no or or or and you can also try to find the one who's down
I'm just, I'll shoot my gun. I roll a d20.
You're...
Okay.
And add what?
Add your dex plus your proficiency for you.
Okay, I don't know what that is.
So your dex is...
My dex is one. Okay, then that's a... Your proficiency is two.
So that's supposed to be...
Oh, where did it go? Oh my god. I think it's a thirteen.
You should be able to see it.
I can't find it.
No, it'll be a 15.
That hits.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Okay, a 15.
Then what do I roll?
That's not so bad, bro.
Now roll 1d10.
Okay.
That is a 3.
Okay, plus 3.
Alright, so you shoot her...
In the neck.
In the neck also.
Adding to the gushing blood, but it doesn't quite kill her.
uh... he's shooting her neck
he's like please stop
pretty impressive
stop it
uh... no i will continue
now you uh... uh...
uh... the evil stevel
uh...
roll a dexterity saving throw with disadvantage
shh
no
I'm not making any more rolls for the rest of the game.
I got a five.
Okay.
Um...
Two cold, bony hands grab your shoulders.
Roll a strength check.
Oh, fuck.
Um...
Seven.
I got a seven.
You are dragged towards the wall, off the boat.
God damn it, bro.
*Steve laughs*
As you hear *laughs*
Oh my god she does laugh like that!
As a woman drags you off the boat.
It's not necessarily the witch.
I think it might be necessarily the witch!
*laughs*
And the other one who's looking really bad with her neck.
She takes out a rock and she's throwing it at you, Steve-le.
And she's going to have advantage on the throw because one of the other women is holding him.
Holding you. Him.
You.
holding you him you so let me roll for that excuse me pardon me yeah pardon you
is right hey there ain't gonna be a pardon for you you're going straight to
jail she throws two rocks at you and somehow even with a disadvantage I mean
even with you, even with her having advantage on it,
she misses all four, just like somehow,
just like whiffing it, like probably her neck
hanging barely on her head, her body rather,
just sort of fucking with her aim.
And then you are gonna be up now, Patrick.
Steve-O right now is being held back,
not too far from where you guys were,
all within the same, it's all within six seconds but he is now being held against
his will by a average-looking woman. I rolled my my d20 on my gun and it was a
13. Okay so we're gonna add your deck. That hits! With your decks that hits. Who are
you aiming at? Stevel. You're aiming at Stivel. Why me man? No I'm aiming at whoever is holding
nice okay roll for the shot roll roll roll 2d6 that was close guys I almost died
there wouldn't have been paid snake eyes no I got an 8 nice okay cool so you
shoot at her at her and she lets go Steve will see well you're now sort of
wading in this, wading in the water, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, with your armor on.
So you're probably having a little bit of trouble swimming.
Um, uh, you are now up the Stevel.
Um, I mean, you can use your turn to just get back on the boat.
That's probably what you'll have or, or you can just hang out.
In the water.
I think, I guess I will, I guess I will freeze my foot.
Yeah.
I'll, I'll swim over to the dinghy.
This is moving pretty fast.
So you huff and you puff and you get over to the dinghy.
- Can I flop up onto the dinghy on my back
and then cough and I spit up like a goldfish?
- You spit up a really beautiful, weird looking fish.
- Okay, and then I, does it look like
it's gonna be worth something?
- Whoa, can I collect it?
- You spit it up.
- I wanna collect it from him.
- And when it hits the boat, it sort of dissolves
splinters into like these weird like fragments of color and goes back into
the water it's very strange that was quite strange you're up to again okay is
there anyone in reach of me yet no okay gun again neck okay cool which one the
the one with the neck problems already yes let's see okay that's a seven plus
whatever okay three okay doesn't hit okay can it hit can it hit somebody like
really far away that we aren't aware of like on the island it hits and kills
somebody it killed that old man who was on the island okay all right they're up
now the one woman who was who got hit she's like trying to claw her way over
to the boat. She's gonna swipe at you, Patrick. And she do... oh. She do hit you.
I'm dead. Yeah, she won't be able to kill you. But yeah, you are past it. I mean, not...
She won't be able to, you know, kill you, kill you, like, get all the way to your
negative HP, but yeah, you're knocked out. The other one is gonna try to throw
another two rocks at you steve-o fuck me man and she misses both of them now
we're back to top of the order Patrick's roll death saving throw where is that on
I think it's it next to your HP. Yeah should be where your HP was.
I don't see it. It'll just be a d20 so just roll d20.
I I I about a head out. What? It's not like a meme. Success. The fuck are you talking about?
you're doing okay. So I'm alive. One success. Now, Stievel, you're up. Okay, so that lady,
her head is still on her, yeah? Yeah, she's not looking good. Okay, I'm back on the
boat though, so I'm gonna try this again. I'm gonna do a chill touch. I'm rolling. I
got a 22. Yeah, that hits her. It's gonna kill her. Nice, okay, so I'm
okay, so I hit a three. So I'm gonna use, I cast chill touch, the blue hand comes
out of my out of my wherever my ass and it goes on to I grab her I grab her by
her head she's really shitty like highlights and she got layers done - yeah
yeah yeah so I'm grabbing her she got real she got red highlights from super
coats I grab her by the hair and I rip her head off of that with the blue hand
I rip her head off of her neck and then I and then it's slowly I slowly carry it
back. Okay, that's just unrealistic. She wouldn't scream if her head is off her
body. No, I mean she did and then she she's not screaming now. Okay, okay.
I apologize. Okay, fine. So then I carry her head and I put it on top of the
other heads that are on the mom. That was cool. Okay, so Mud Mom is now three
heads high, yes? Yes, yes, yes, yes. All right. Okay, cool. It is now your turn,
Dogen I would say okay you you can also take a use a bonus action try to suss
out where this one is okay I'll do that it's a roll
please section boy section okay and I'm using my nose sense smelling yes yes
your new no sense I'm a dog now for women that's right a dog okay that's a
nine okay plus your wisdom though what his perception yeah I think my wisdom
is zero is it not oh is it zero it is zero I'm sorry I didn't see okay yeah
so you're not quite able to smell out what you assume is the smell of an
average woman yeah but you can try with your ore to dig through the rock to try
Okay, can I dig with my hands? Yeah, go for it. Roll strength check. I love my hands.
Okay, let's see. Strength. Okay, that's a 14. Okay, cool. You're able to dig out and
you're able to hear the rustling a little bit with a little bit more
precision at this point. So now we're back to top of the order.
She's gonna try to pop out and grab you, Dogen. So roll
dexterity saving throw. Okay dexterity that is oh 11 Wow. Okay she's able to grab you
roll strength check. Okay another roll let's see here a strength check that is
12. Okay yeah she's able to pull you off the boat and grab you off the boat you
are now up Patrick roll a death saving throw okay oh my god I got a B a crit
you are back you're stabilized Oh that crit you're immediately stabilized so
I'm at 27 no you're back you're back at like zero but you're breathing yeah
you're not gonna die you're just not gonna die you're just like uh and now
you're up Steve-o fuck yes hmm these bitches are holding
Dogen and she's holding Dogen back as he is sort of hanging loosely along
on
inflict wounds right now yeah I go for it and that's a 23 hell yeah I mean come on
oh my god ah and with the 18 this was a Steve's fight
describe your kill I'm just so fucking good us on the head wounds I think if I
remember correctly it rips their head off it instantly so once the head but
it's gonna do it with such force that her head just pops off her body and the head
is actually gonna do three or four somersaults in the air on the way to the
mud mom sit directly on top and now we got a fucking quattro mud mommy.
Quattro mud mommy. Yeah. Okay. And then I just start poking all it just put
my hand in every single one of their mouths just back and forth like I'm like
I'm playing some kind of instrument. That is awesome. Yeah. Yeah you guys won that
fight and I'm gonna tie all their tongues together okay at one they're
kissing and I actually like time my tongue in well I do it on purpose but I
pretend it was an accident so after you guys defeated the the uggo ass women or
sorry average you once you've made it past the gauntlet you see a faint sort of
things start to go like really black. Before it was already pretty dim and
hard to see but now that you're much further in it's kind of like that inky
darkness. You see a faint prismatic glow in the immediate distance, sort of like a
pulsing light and then another and then another. Varying shades and hues and a
sort of like a nascent constellation of dolapolescence and it fixes like a
pockmarked glints to the expanding sea of blackness. So you start to see this kind
of like almost like it's like almost musical the way it looks and then you
look up you see these winding fissures in the rock which were imperceptible until
now and they cut through with like a glow and that's like sort of the origin of
this light and it's giving shape to your journey. It's giving shape sis. You can see
murky shimmering shapes that rise in concert with the stream and meet the air
and they flicker fly and spill back into the sea these are the fish that you were
in your mouth earlier. Steeble. And when they hit the surface they leave trails
of sort of squirming weird color create little sort of gossamer puddles.
I'm gonna leave you squirming. It's giving puddles. These filmy things atop the surface of the water.
and then there's this sort of a rolling light that is forming from all these
different sources of light that are kind of these bizarre sort of like spectacles of
light and the interstice, like these cracks, are growing larger and
larger and the light is brighter and brighter. And from deep below this fish
in the sea you start to see vegetation as well that's like pulsing and shimmying
and pushing smoke and heat. It starts to feel kind of like Primordial where you're going
into. It's not quite the same kind of like regular cove now. There's something magical
and a weird low rumbling too. And then you start to hear a chittering sound too. So we're
hearing the sort of grumbles of average women. Now you're starting to hear these sort of
chittering on the lengthening side wing. It's flanking your vessel, right? So it seems more
like a walkway on the side of you is forming.
And as it reaches its peak, you can make out three glowing eyes.
Like, one for one eye, one for another eye, one on the forehead.
And you start to see like a snout pop out from that, and a reptilian frame and a poodle
tail.
And then this creature sort of like squeaks at you and squeezes in between the glowing
cracks.
As the crevices themselves now start to resemble more like latticework, it's more intentional
in their design, they're not just cracks through.
Somebody made this happen,
somebody carved this whole sort of scenery.
You start to see within sort of that darkness
a small opening and this sort of like painterly,
striking scene of like a large cavern before you, right?
Sort of this like perfect symmetrical shot, right?
And you see a woman sitting there
and she's one of the most,
if not the most beautiful woman you've seen so far.
And she's sitting on a porch that's sort of fungal in shape.
And on top of a domicile, like a part of a domicile that's made of stone and metal and some sort of organic matter meshed together.
And her head whips towards you before you can even really register her frame.
And a grim smile sort of cuts through her face, her aquiline face.
And this is Albert.
And as you approach the cavern, I'll describe that next time.
Lesbian.
What did you just say?
I called her a lesbian.
Okay, we need to see her head on the mud, mom.
I need to see her.
She's the piece de resistance.
Yeah.
Okay, everybody can stop recording.
Must be the season of the rich Must be the season of the rich
When I grew up
(upbeat music)