(dramatic music)
- Cam's penis smells like chips and fries.
- It's getting completely cut out.
It's gonna start with the thing.
- No it's not, you're gonna leave it in.
- Oh, I'm not gonna leave it in.
- Yes you will because people will like that.
- It's gonna be completely cut out
and it's gonna be put in its own episode.
- I'm gonna tell Patrick to do it in the next episode.
- I won't do it.
- Okay, you can start now, Patches.
- Okay.
- Last time on--
- Cam's penis.
I was not going to cut it out, you'd have to do it again.
Last time on Tribuche Village, the gang ventured deep into Albert the Witch's cove with Patrick's
mom's head.
After the witch, oh no, Albert the Witch was one of the hot babes on Hot Babe Island who
refused a moniker of hot babe, choosing to nest in the strange cove beneath the island.
As they traveled through the waterway into the cove, our heroes were attacked by average
average looking women
first with feral
filming fury from being not that attractive
after passing them by using their dingy
the gang found themselves in the which is
fantasmic or
and uh...
want to mention more than a little bit of a lot of them
and hold your mic you are you're the way you are how many heads to have on the
mud mom
oh yeah for
damn
you got mom you got the three
what are you doing you did the joke four times already
i'm trying to know if i didn't see what's the joke
he's got a new dance
oh ok
it was a new one he did a good new one earlier
what was a good new one?
that i said you could slow it down and it would be really good
yeah but i like it fast too
i mean that's not a really good dance
see when we start filming these it's gonna be awesome
Yeah, we're not gonna do that though ever.
Yeah, that's right. Yeah, definitely not. So, um...
So yeah, you guys are in your dinghy.
You're approaching now the witch,
Albert, and she's...
There's ship on my dinghy!
Yeah!
He's ruined every episode for like two years of this is my fault
This is a was a dingy said dingy, and I shouldn't have called it a dingy
I should have just called it a my dingy smells like shit
Dropped a bunch of chum out of my dingy. That's not as funny. No, that's all that
You say my dingy my dingy shooting chum
No, you see you're missing a really crucial day. I'm coming maybe what I'm coming
I'm coming to you with my on my dinghy. Yeah, my dinghy and I'm coming right for you
My nigga, my dinghy is coming for your ship
No, you're coming for you. I'm coming for your ass with my dinghy
My dinghy is coming in your ass pretty soon. The cavern is filled with the the sort of full splendor
I'm coming in that hole with my dinghy. This cavern is filled with ship.
Wait, just a question. Does the dinghy have bowels?
It has a bow?
Yeah, a bow. Does it have a bow? Yeah, I mean it's a ship.
My dinghy's bows are full of chum.
This is crap. This is complete crap. What if I said "chum"?
Okay, that might, yeah. Like you did a bore at?
All right.
So like a sort of like a multicolored sort of a muscular beam, you know, like sun beams
kind of like are coming down.
They're splattering kind of like everywhere.
There's all these creatures that you saw before.
There's got to be some prisms in there then, huh?
Oh, yeah.
There's some prismatic light for sure.
Grotesque creatures crane their necks and munch on transparent fruits that vent gas.
It's sort of this like strange sort of otherworldly garden that's sort of flanking on the edges
of the cavern as you approach her her hovel and there's some flowers that are
like spitting and spinning and like they're shivering it's it's really
pretty and an interesting. So our dinghy's going into her hovel. I'll just I'll read
this to myself later. No, no, I thought you were done. Don't give me a second cuz I
I will jump on it.
- Any opportunity.
- I will jump on your dinghy.
- I didn't know that.
Okay, it's fine.
I mean, there's just more descriptions
of what it looks like. - Keep describing.
Keep going. - I'm listening.
- And use funny words that we can say
in between the paragraphs.
- All right, I'll try to replace some of these then.
There's a persistent din,
sort of a chorus of psychic sounds
that whisper and soothe,
sort of like this,
there's like kind of constant whispering around you.
And those fish that you saw,
like fish that would leap and sort of hit the water and then like splatter into like other
colors. There's more of those and then the snouted sort of reptilian thing that you saw
earlier, you see them now and what they fully look like. They kind of have like a sort of
like a dog's face but mixed with kind of like a crocodile and then this like sort of reptile
body and the sort of like poodley kind of like, you know, curly tail. I'll be putting
my dinghy in there poodley.
They have reptile bodies. Does that mean they're cold-blooded?
I mean um... So the room is really hot?
No, I mean it's a fantasy world.
The room is regularly temperate.
Just wanted to know something about the reptiles.
And then the uh... the crone now speaks, the witch.
And she says um... What does she look like?
She's... I mean she's... she's
quite beautiful. Does she have cold blood like a reptile? I don't know.
I actually cannot answer that. She is, I mean, you'll learn more about her, but she's quite
beautiful. She has gigantic boobs. She has, I don't know her boob size. Regular? Good.
If you don't know it, then they're small. What's regular to you, Patches? Just like
a... Double D. Double D's. Interesting. It's actually most women have, most women don't
buy the correct bras. That's something I have to hear about sometimes. You hear about that
At your work?
Just from friends or women.
At Victoria's Secret? Or I forgot you don't work there.
You just hang out there.
Just hang out.
Something I hear a lot.
You know, you have female friends
and they talk about that stuff.
Yeah, I wouldn't call them your friends.
The people in Victoria's Secret, they kind of try to ignore you.
They harass.
You're smelling patients.
It's funny you say friends now because usually you call them targets but yeah
okay well you know let's let's keep let's try to keep the the you know all that
down low. My thingy has shit on it. Yeah Patches is Victoria's Secret. He's like a phantom of the opera.
Yeah he's got the pains on the air duck. The phantom of the opera under these Victoria's Secrets.
Now it's gonna hold on so anyway you get up and approach her and she looks she's like
she's she no she's she's very beautiful you know you could see that she was a hot
babe but she's just doesn't she sort of I
pull my balls she has like she's hot she
used to be hobbit that she grew armpit
hair and stuff yeah she's like that kind
of bullshit yeah yeah so I pull my balls
through my zipper that's completely
assault yeah no that was his first
instinct was to expose himself to this
woman she's not looking as soon as he
was like she has armpit hair I'm pulling
my balls up yeah he's in fact right in
Bush he's glad that she's not looking
he's trying to sneak up on her no do you put your balls back in your shorts are
you in my shorts I changed I pulled them out because I was changing into shorts
okay all right that's fair though yeah fine really fine because it's because it
is hot in there because of the reptile yeah all right we're painting a picture
here and yeah so she says to you well what can I do for you city what the
The fuck is that voice?
It's my voice?
*mimics voice*
It's a language that only the two of us know.
Yes, it's true. I didn't know you spoke that.
Who are you three? Why do you come to Macavar?
I'm Rod Dogan, you!
That's unfortunate. What about you two?
I'm Steevel.
Blank Peter.
Soul Deception.
Black.
That's how I feel.
That's exactly how I feel.
26.
All right, yeah, she thinks you're Black Peter.
There's no consequence really to that.
Okay.
She says, "What do you three doing here?
Oh, I see you've got the mud mom.
What are you doing with your mud mom?"
I lied about my name.
Okay, what's your name?
Did you think that was cool that was my name?
I would have thought it was your name.
That's about it.
Okay, then it's still my name.
Okay, cool.
What are you three doing here?
I have the right mind to cast you out.
We're trying to change our names.
I don't, uh, oh, um,
this, I point to the mud mom.
This one.
She had a, okay, so one of these,
wait which head was it I think I'm off and like just looking at him not this one
oh it's this one that has all my spit in the mouth of it oh my god there's a lot
of so she clean this out I like put my hand in and it's like it's the his spit
consistency is like aloe vera it's like so thick as she as you're pulling the the
spit out of her mouth the Patrick's mom's head's mouth she Albert has a
realization she's like oh no that's Patrick's mom that was her name
do you mean black Peters mom well you changed my name because I thought it
would be funny well you're her son yeah why do you say Patrick's mom that was
her name oh yeah I forgot we didn't give her name and I thought that would be cool
no what happened is this whole situation but that's all right so what happened
was tried to break dance on her head like a grape come come I haven't seen
you since you order we hi Patrick you're gonna have to explain this one cuz all I
know is what happened is that I took her head off and I put it on to this other
I've blocked out the memory completely I just don't even care.
Alright so we don't really know what happened. Don't you have like a magical memory stone?
Yeah but I can choose to block things out if I feel like it. I didn't even know that
I didn't know much. Maybe the death of my mom is very traumatic and I want to block it out.
It seemed very traumatic when it happened.
When I saw that I said oh crap. I didn't know much about her
I didn't even barely know that it was Patricks mom I knew she was kind of a
she's clearly a scumbag because she had this tattoo
And I show her the the room yeah, she looks at the room. She says oh my
Okay, here come come here, and she takes the she takes the head if you're giving it to her
I kick it. I like punt it across the dinghy to her. Okay. I'm gonna roll an athletics check for her
Oh my god getting some head across your dinghy though
I'm getting head from Patrick's mom on the dinghy.
And then you start...
Will you be giving it to her?
Aren't you giving head on the dinghy?
I'm gonna use her...
He's giving head on a dinghy.
Yeah, to your mom, who's dead.
She's able to catch it pretty easily.
It's giving head to me on the dinghy.
And she sort of sees and she's like, "Ugh."
And she puts it down on a table.
Oh my god, on a table.
How disrespectful can you be?
I didn't know we had a table on our dinghy.
So, it's on your dinghy. Well, you're on - at this point, she has sort of like a little island.
I think it's - I think it's all on the dinghy.
Yeah.
I think we're still on it.
You guys can either stay on - you can stay on the dinghy.
No, I'll get off.
You don't have to.
Yeah, get off my dinghy.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, you're on the island. You start to see some of those flowers that are kind of like
weirdly alive and then they sort of like curve their heads towards you guys and sort of look
around and take note of your presence and note of her not being sort of hostile to you guys.
like there's sort of like a welcoming to it and she takes the the head and she
she she looks at the the hideous tattoo on it she says this alright this is a
Quinta rune. Do you guys know much about runes? La Quinta. That's right. La Quinta.
I get a rune at the La Quinta and I got fucked in it. It's pretty good. So in runes
there are typically most ruins are a trace of bedrooms tresor is ruins nope
no no living in in as in yeah yeah yeah the the quinta in no not a quinta in
when you saying you're saying in are you touched yes Barry oh my god what a
breakthrough so most ruins are trace ruins right you have the ruin itself
she sure points at the room she says you could see here it has a pentagram ik
design what that means is that there's five entities associated with it all the
ruins have at least two okay the ruin itself and then the place the extant body
but it's a that it's a attached to right so for example if you get like your
accident buddy that I'm attached to damn and keep going though. I have five
roll a roll persuasion. Okay, one second. I have to see what my persuasion is. I
think your charisma is pretty good because you're a paladin. I don't think
it is. I don't think I have any good ability scores. Let's see here.
Persuasion that roll is a 19. All right yeah. She's not like you know into it, but
but she's like, yeah, I wasn't like trying to do anything either.
I just kind of like charming, like you're being sort of silly. Uh, yeah,
it wasn't silly. I was cool. No, it was really cool. It's cool.
I dug that. And she keeps going and she says, uh,
and uh, so there's the extent body in the room itself.
Most of the rooms are trace rooms because there's also typically the third
entity involved is the effect, right? So for example, in this case,
well, how did she die? This can somebody tell me?
I think that she tried to say a cuss and her head,
she died from cussing.
- So some sort of powered word then, okay.
- Yeah. - Well, I hope it wasn't a,
nothing.
Never mind. - What?
- Huh? - I don't care anymore.
- So in that case-- - I heard the word
was chicken tenders.
- Okay, chicken tenders.
So she said chicken tenders and then she died?
- That's just what I heard.
I was sitting in a line of like 20 people
they were all one by one whispering the word into each other's ears and and yeah
that's what it was the word Patrick do you remember what she was about this what
she said before that bathroom break
fingers okay sticky fingers chicken no I think it was chicken yeah I mean that's
just what I we were playing a way of conveying information called I love when
play away of information. Yeah, it's not a game. If it was a game, maybe the whole
thing would be like to see what funny it, but it's like, you know. But you play it
though. Yeah, you play it. Yeah, and it wasn't called, it wasn't called
telephone. Yeah, it was called talking. It was called yelling from one room to
another. Yeah. So then in that case now, that accounts for the third point here,
but the other two is the part that I'm a little bit confused by. So some of what
we can do here is look at the runes themselves, some of the magical drawings inside of them.
And I'm also going to have to know a little bit more detail from you what happened. She
said "Sticky Fingers" to you. And then her head popped off like a grape. I don't think
it popped, I think we ripped her head off. Who is Sticky Fingers? He was like, I guess
he was like my uncle's buddy. So yeah, Sticky Fingers was the head of the Thieves Guild.
back in Trebuchet Village. He was my uncle's buddy. Your uncle's buddy. He was a part of the group
that you guys knew about which was called The 60 Tricksters Eating Chicky Tenders
and Their Mixing Genders with Their 120 Fingers. Which was Patrick - which is Trunchbull's crew,
is what they were called.
- Yep.
- And so, she says, "Okay."
So when she said sticky fingers,
now that makes some sense,
but the only thing then is,
and if I'm looking at the runes here,
we're seeing some transmutation, some illusion magic,
some of that is usually to obscure a rune, right?
So keep it hidden, which makes sense.
Probably people weren't looking for it on her body,
but what's odd is I'm seeing also abjuration signs.
Abjuration is the suppression of magic.
- Observations?
- Abjuration.
A, B, J, U, R.
- Abjurbation.
- Yes, no, you know, closer, but--
- Absurbations.
- What this means is that there is some sort
of protective magic here,
but obviously there is no protecting going on.
And finally, the power word.
Patrick, when was the last time you saw your mother?
100 years ago.
That's not true, he saw her when she died.
Oh right, I saw her when she died.
Before that.
100 years ago.
So a long time ago.
But that's 700 years if it was in dog years.
Just in case that, I don't know.
I think I saw her seven million years, no.
Six years.
You wouldn't know that you saw her,
you only saw her last when you were a baby
before you were taken from Babe Island.
So--
- So 100 years ago.
- Sure, you can be 100 years old.
- I forget how old I am.
- Oh my God, you're 100 years old?
- Oh my God.
- I'm 19.
- I'm 12.
- I don't know what the Verdan age thing is, but--
- Yeah, when did I hit puberty?
- Yeah, Verdan's--
- I'm canonically 12 and he took his balls out in front of me.
- They live to be about 200.
- So you're middle-aged.
- You being 100 would be middle-aged,
if you're middle-aged. Yeah, but I hit puberty.
Yeah, well, it, yeah. Late bloomer. That did happen. Maybe it's, maybe you're fifty.
Maybe. Puberty at like forty. Yeah, that's basically what happened to you.
You're an extremely late bloomer, maybe.
And she says, uh...
"Now this might be a wee bit upsetting, but I think you're sort of responsible for
your mother's death in that case."
That's fine.
- Well, okay.
- I didn't know her that well.
- Well, she was,
she was a good woman.
- Okay.
- She was pretty stupid, but you know, nobody really minded.
- Can I knock on her head and it sounds empty
like a coconut?
- It absolutely does.
- Yeah.
- Says, "What likely happened here is that
somebody was waiting, or the rune itself was waiting for,"
that's power word, "sticky fingers."
- Wait, it's not doing anything right now.
Well it's only doing something to the person who had the rune on them.
I put it on.
Well did you put the rune on her?
I put the rune on right now.
It's in her body.
No you can't, it's etched into her body, you can't really put it on.
The way the runes work-
I thought it was a necklace.
No no no, the runes are sort of marked onto a body, usually through some kind of magical
application and cotton and stuff.
It's like a letter.
So did the guy who took me put the rune on my mom and wait for her to say it?
That's what I'm wondering. Either somebody did it, could have been the person who took you, could have been somebody else.
It might have been Sticky Fingers because his name was a complete activation phase.
It might have been Sticky Fingers.
Wait, say Sticky Fingers backwards.
Bullshit.
Zrig... Zrig... Zrig... Rr... Neff...
Wait... St... Eekis... St... Eekits...
Stop, you're gonna put the curse on us!
What?
Oh, I'm just kidding.
Oh, don't kid like that.
That actually works.
- Too far.
- Sticky fingers.
Zriffing.
Yes, that.
Ifkists.
Wanna see me do it again?
(laughing)
- Yeah, that doesn't help.
- Give me another one.
- Try poop.
- The only thing here--
- Boob.
Oh no, I flipped it the wrong way.
- It's again that abjuration piece.
- Boob.
- Try race car.
cat race. Try taco cat, say that backwards. Stuck-o cat. Try bob. Bob. Try... I don't know,
I got no more palindromes. I don't know how to do... I go bob, blay bob. That one's too
hard. What's likely happened then, this last piece, the abjuration piece, this was probably
then again, abjuration is usually protection types of magic,
but it also works for alarms.
- I don't do that.
- So, watch.
- Nice.
- Okay, and I got it.
- Up top.
(laughing)
- Pat just got it now.
- She says, if I had to guess, once it's activated,
somebody else or something was alarmed
that it was activated.
- Yeah, I was, my mom's head fell off.
- Besides you, right?
- It sounds alarming.
Somebody or something from a distance.
Oh, so like somebody knew that this happened.
Essentially, yes. Potentially, or it just was an alarm that was set for a
specific amount of time, I don't know. Like an alarm clock?
Well, it could be an alarm. So you're saying she was an alarm clock, which isn't real.
Alarm clocks are real in this world. No, she's the one piece of technology.
I have no idea what that is.
I don't know what a clock is, but I know what an alarm clock is.
An alarm sundial.
I don't know, it wasn't quite like that.
It's more like if somebody walks into a private place and you have a security guard that sees you and they go...
Like if a horse walks into the bar and the bartender says "Why the long face?"
Right, but imagine if the bartender was doing that to warn everybody but the horse was walking in.
He is.
Beginning a cool joke.
bars a couple of times or the bartender says why the long face and I don't even
look I just leave. Well in that case yes it's just like that it's like when
somebody says that and you leave. Somebody somewhere has been notified that
this rune has been activated. I don't like that. Is there any way to find out
who it could be? Could we reverse engineer the rune? Reverse the curse. Well
- Well, could we reverse the curse?
- Reverse the curse? - 'Cause otherwise,
- Srook and Sraver.
- 'Cause if we can't, I'm gonna tell you one thing,
this head's going in the ocean.
- No, well-- - No, we need it
for our mud mom, don't you dare.
- If you're talking about that kind of--
- Yeah, we need that for the mud mom.
- Look, I'll be honest,
runes are not necessarily the thing I'm best at,
but if you're looking to do something
like reversing a curse or a death,
I do know some necromancers in Beriberi you could go to see.
I don't want to bring Patrick's mom back to life.
I'd rather have the mud mom become a totally new life.
But I'm more interested in finding out
where the thing is from.
Also, do you want to buy these other three heads?
I think they might've been your friends.
Oh no, those are not my friends.
Those are just--
So you wouldn't care if we use them as pins
in a bowling game, where we use his mom's head as the ball,
'cause it's the roundest.
Yeah, it's really round.
I did know her, but yeah, I mean, she's your head now.
What if we put makeup on her?
Would that be better?
I would love that.
Do you have any makeup?
No, that's why you rejected the whole hot babe thing.
I would like to do a makeup montage
with just kind of like mud and rocks and stuff
and try to pretty up his mom a little bit.
Role, in that case, God, what would that even be?
I guess is that charisma?
I guess it's performance kind of?
Yeah, it's like disguise.
Yeah, 'cause it's a disguise character.
Charisma check?
Yeah, we'll just do straight charisma
see if you know how to and then yeah I would say that's fair because you can be
the most dexterous motherfucker I got a natural 20 you serious yeah she looks
Wow what she looks 15 years younger and alive what song do I do the montage -
that's a good like walking on sunshine there we go and I'm just like using a
like a rock say it was just run through all the scenes you're doing this okay so
So first of all, I take some gravel, some dark charcoal, I burn something and turn it into
like a black soot and then I put it under her eyes to make her look like a football player.
And then I give her big Groucho Marx eyebrows too.
And you know what?
Okay, scrap the football player thing.
I'm walking on sunshine still playing.
I do Groucho Marx eyebrows, a Groucho Marx mustache, and then I carve I guess an onion
to make it look like a nose.
I put that on her and then I also I'm gonna build up some glasses really
quickly and so she just has a whole groucho thing going on. Yeah she looks
amazing. And I put a piece of poop in her mouth like a cigar. Yeah she's smoking on that poop.
She looks great. Okay yeah. Now what do you want to do with her? So now let's
reverse the curse. Yeah. Well to reverse the curse do you mean like to track
who do we have to bring her back to life or do we just we don't know if anything
coming to life it's mud marks okay
the heads yeah they look completely like like all the marks brothers but but
Groucho, the mom has to be the main.
- Yeah, of course she has to be Groucho.
- Yeah, which one's fucking, yeah, they even do Zeppo.
- Yes, yes, yes.
- Okay, so and then we have them just sitting in a row
and they will be coming to life at some point.
- Yeah, that's like a--
- We need you to show us the Necromancer right now.
- Okay, well, you're gonna have to go to Berry Berry
and go to the academy.
There you can find a Necromancer who can help you.
- Wait a minute, are we still,
is this about the rune?
I don't know.
this is not what we'll give you a train to bring it back to life
and some sort of a
uh... famous comedy
the quadro
quartet or what's wrong with what you're here
then you can do that to a trip but you can't
actually
but we're going to let it work we are going to use it for all of the all of
the heads are are on the same body so they will be a quadro
yeah yeah they don't have a quadro marks
amazing
quadro marks
alright so we have quadro marks
he's not alive yet
but his head is stacked
so what you said we need to go to
he just changed the gender of all the women
on the head
well they don't have bodies they're just heads
no i'm not into it
quadro marks
well they do have a mud body
in a suit. We carved the mud into a suit. I can make an introduction for you at the place
in Betty Betty. Now you guys would know on the map, I'll show you on the map where-
Can you teleport us there? I don't know if she could do that, no that's the old map.
Alright. Hold on let me find the map. Where the fuck is the map? Oh it's here. He deleted
the map. There it is, sorry. Wow, it's gorgeous. Yeah so Berry Berry, you guys are like-
here still. Yeah and Barry Barry's the like okay. It's not like
necessarily the tip it's just like this area. Okay so you just put the words on
in a strange manner. Well just so that it wasn't obscuring the the. Oh right the
little the green dots. Yeah. There's lots of locales. Yeah. Yeah okay. There's the this
is the Academy town. Okay. So is and they can help us with the rune and bringing
this person back or yeah there's there's that is basically the well I want to
Hogwarts of the terror I would like to just completely exit out of this
conversation just press escape a hundred times in a row whatever it takes to
instantly just go there okay yeah I would like I really need to see mud marks
it's gonna take like it's gonna take time to get there okay but I didn't and
and I would like to immediately start that time what you without a single more
word I can't do that this session because of just it literally I mean how far is a
be real with me in miles okay no no I'm not saying we have to skip through the
journey I'm saying let's start the journey immediately I'm I would like the
which does not exist to me anymore we've already started by the way just from the
time that you said that even though you're not describing it we've already
already the clock is ticking. We're already going.
Okay, so I like that. Okay, the adventure is now about creating
quadro marks.
Quadro mud marks.
The second, yeah, the second that she said.
Well, that's, you know, we'll see. We'll reevaluate what happened.
We'll see in the room too, but that's...
That's our immediate focus is on that.
Yes, yes. Any way to get you further from Sullivan and one of them being...
And a new better sidekick.
And a new better sidekick, yes.
Who I can't wait until Pat just has to do four voices.
I mean, I...
Three, three. Harpo doesn't talk.
Harpo doesn't talk.
will they will not the smile the woman who used to be like talk hmm I could do
that that what why why can't he do that maybe a whale in the in the ocean
supposed to be Harpo's horn oh what hack he's a horn he has a horn and a horn and
a which one cuts the tie with scissors I don't know yeah I could do a I could do
Groucho Marx. Oh, save it! Yeah, come on. I don't even want to do it almost anymore. You're teasing me. I do. Sorry, sorry.
But you're spoiling it. Sorry, sorry. I won't. I want the payoff. And plus, I would like to add a note,
which is that you're not doing Groucho Marx, you're doing a mud mom as Groucho Marx. Oh, okay, yeah.
So, well, don't do it now, okay? I want to, I want to, I want to. I see you leaning back like you're about to do it.
I won't. It probably, we'll see how the necromancy goes. I'm sure there'll be some roles involved,
but I can tell you a mud person probably is not going to do a great Groucho Marx.
just keep that in mind. Yeah, even think about that. Well, you have you okay,
okay, I want you to stop massaging different parts of your throat, because
I'm worried you're going to do the voice and I will not do the voice. I'm
saying you have the larynx at least so you have her you have like a real
larynx. Now you don't have like real lungs. So that'll be like no. Oh man,
this will be really fun. So we got a fine body. If you go, yes, that's what
I mean. Literally, you guys would have to go to berry berry find a
necromancer willing to do this that's easy
will we have like an option of like the good yeah like a good like a high-end
like yeah I don't want any spoilers I want to start sailing excited I've ever
been for anything in my I don't okay I just want to say right now I don't want
any Conrad money okay but you have to make a God marks all right I will I'll
I'll make sure that happens. I'm going to do a lot of I don't want to Conrad
Marie type of neck.
I'm answering not to Quadro.
Quadro is a perfect name for a four-headed marks.
Yeah, Quadro marks Quadro.
Yeah.
Don't mention that.
It's made out of mud and women's heads.
Quadra marks Quadro marks is genius.
Yeah on its own and then I add you add the on top of that literally on top of
that you had women's heads and mud.
yes and a genius and I do think that like also I feel like wrong with that like
we've carved ourselves a serious kind of identity as a as a treat as a trio of
entrepreneurs yes so maybe we can make some money off a quadro I have I have
oh man I have oh yeah also I can say anything yeah we are we let we're
leaving our sex factory here to process and I would like to have a second bench
I would like to ask one more I wanted to make sure you didn't forget about our
sex factory I would like to ask one more question about don't forget the sex
I would like to ask one more question in regards to
Quadra the future quadro marks and the world that we're in have leashes like dog leashes been invented yet
Yeah, I mean there's like horses you have to write so there's bridles and stuff like that
Okay, I think we're gonna have quite a lot of fun. Yeah, I don't I don't want to know and I won't ask he's gonna run
away
All three of you roll perception, okay
Perception
Okay guys are in the dinghy you guys already started yeah, we're paddling I'm paddling my dinghy says goodbye
Thanks for visiting people does not does not register with me at all. Okay. Yeah, I got a nine
I got a nine on person wrote this fucking can't it's fancy an ass cavern
And it has just been said she knows not rolling. It was beautiful now
It was I would like to torpedo that cavern do we have torpedoes on a dinger?
It was
Every no one can know every beautiful thing you built you you just it was it was also like oh man it was yeah
What's up, Pat?
Perception
It's taking so long you can use also the d20 and just add with your number you see there
Yeah, I'll give you the thing
Which also all you can have you guys can all have I don't even need it
I don't even need to use my phone for it D&D Beyond style. I think we should go
beyond D&D into Quadro Marks. Yeah. Standalone RPG. Yeah. About
Quadro Mud Marks. What did you get? I got a 9. And you? 12. Jesus Christ.
Okay yeah you guys are sort of paddling through at this point any average women
that would be going after you or they're there yeah they know that we're there
they're out of their league yeah they know not worse leagues away pretty much
yeah yeah and if we kill another one we're gonna have to kill three more on
top of that and then also yeah mud body so we could make it we could make a
quadro marks et and it's like the chipettes to the head but they're
already women's heads yeah well so but yeah I mean guys heads no I think this
should not be touched you cannot touch I'm touching all over quadrants right
now cuz it's not alive yet yes yeah it's a yeah we're looking at like a
place man it's a hot one what a scorcher I'm licking mud marks like it's not cold
but I do like doing this okay so we put our dinghy back in ship yeah you guys
ways of in the dingy goes into the ship paddling a pile of ship yeah and you
notice that the poop deck
you notice that as you're sort of paddling back, you dock your boat.
I putting my dingy in a deck.
I'm docking my dingy with another dingy.
You hear a two tries to
you're not at your ship yet. You're just you're you're at the beach where
you know, your ship is, you carry the ship,
that's like how, part of how that works.
And I need all of you,
'cause you guys didn't fucking sense shit,
to roll a d20.
Just a straight d20.
- Okay.
- Not a problem for me.
- If you want me to, I will, I guess.
- And I basically rolled a very good roll.
- I got a natural 20.
I got a, can I see that?
I'm
say it was a five. Okay. All right, we'll just say that. You two take 16 points of damage.
Jesus. Whoa. You take 8 points of damage. For a nat 20? Come on. Come on. He doesn't get
a single damage. Don't play with me. Don't play with me like that. How much damage I
take? I have one hit point right now. Shit's about to get real. It's already gotten real.
I'm down to 7 damage. We're all gonna die right now.
Bro.
As, before we ever, you're gonna ruin my quadro.
As three beams of just, of fire shoot towards you three, you didn't notice it, but each
of them sort of hitting you, scorching you, you least badly, Radogan you, you two pretty
pretty badly. It gets into you guys see landing in front of
you is this massive massive yet found
real quick. Yes, found real quickly. Can we kind of because
mud marks is also there my marks probably gets hit by some of
the fire right quadro a quadro can it kind of act like a kiln
and kind of harden yeah kind of harden quadro so that when we do
bring him alive he's not just like sopping wet.
Yeah, he's way too wet.
Alright, then I'll take the damage.
I'm not worried about it.
Okay, yeah, I'll allow it.
Okay.
Oh yeah, everyone roll for initiative.
Okay, great.
I can't roll, I'm dead.
You can just roll what you're dead.
You have one HP, you said.
No, I had one HP.
Oh yeah, you're dead.
How much do you have now?
Oh, you're dead.
You should still roll for initiative.
I have seven.
Because we're rolling for death saving throws.
How much negative do you have?
Thirteen.
That doesn't matter.
No, I, my, um.
As long as it's not negative, his first one.
Yeah, I'm going to roll for death saving throws.
13.
That doesn't matter.
No, I, my, um.
As long as it's not negative his full health.
Okay, well that's what I was checking.
Well it's negative 15, but I rolled a 13.
I have, I have initiative 11.
Oh, nat 20.
My second nat 20.
Oh my gosh.
Or as, or a B. I just hit the heal button.
So I guess I'm healed now.
It's seriously fucked up that roll 20 makes a nat roll 20, or, but D&D Beyond makes it
to
first in the initiative order and you got
I think I'm going first.
Okay yes you are going first.
Okay I would like to lay down and die.
I'm gonna lay down and die.
Yes I said what I meant.
Alright I mean you could skip your turn.
Whatever I don't I mean I don't even know what's attacking us.
Wait so what's the thing that's attacking us?
You said a yethound.
So it's this massive feral sort of like dog creature.
Yethounds aren't always massive but this one is pretty massive.
feral so it's a dog in the ocean. Well,
yes, hounds are you'll will talk about
have you have hounds later, but they're
usually later. I'm fine. We're doing
know about what role you can roll
history or what what am I like it's a
dog. Let me roll in the water or it's
floating or what's going on at least
Google a picture of a yes hound. Yeah,
you can do that. What do you do that
to it's why ETH H o und it comes
right up from Pathfinder. He's from a
lot of places. Okay. This thing looks
like a dog with a dog with a man face Jersey devil yeah it looks like a
hairless Chihuahua but it's big Chihuahua and and it's swimming and right now
it's on the beach with you guys it's about like I thought we were no okay my
guys are like on the beach you dock the boat it shot at you you're like sort of
was
- Are you telling me they've been getting intimate with this dog?
- No, I haven't said anything like that.
- But why is there--
- Wait, they copulated with the dog?
I'd like to check out the dog's genitals
to see if it's a boy or a girl dog.
- I guess I'll flip a coin.
- You don't have this--
- You don't even know?
- It doesn't--
- You're the dungeon master.
- It's not important.
- This guy thinks it's not important
whether or not it's a girl or a boy dog.
- Yeah.
- I think it's important.
a weakness point that I could attack. A girl should not have a boy dog. Yeah. Do the coin flip. I want
to know. All right. And tails got to be girls. Okay. Actually no, head got to be girls. Okay.
Tails got to be guys. One, two, three, girls, four, five, six guys. Deal. It's a deal. We got
one, two, three, girls. It's a girl. It's a girl dog. It's a girl dog. Can you re-roll? Yeah, sure.
Okay, it's a guide dog.
Yes!
Yeah, it's a guide dog.
Um, yeah. I mean, in so...
I mean, you can roll a history check to see if you what you remember or know about.
No, I know all I need to know now. It's a guide dog.
Okay, cool.
And how tall is it?
It's like...
Like 10-ish feet high.
Whoa!
That's a tall dog.
10 feet to the shoulder?
Yes.
Holy sh...
Oh my god!
That's my reaction.
Yeah, it's a big beast.
Can I hold up my...
That's gotta be at least...
That's gotta be like 10 feet up to the shoulder.
I'm like oh my God that must be at least seven feet tall as I'm not I wouldn't
know how tall it was. I'm kind of making like an estimate. I'm not so smart yeah.
All right, so I get to attack first. I get to I get first first. Yes, you get
the first I get dibs. You get dibs. Do I have a bone?
I don't know. I don't think I'm almost positive you don't. I could get a bone
out of you. Sure. I guess let's look at your inventory. I do. I have what do
dogs like peanut butter peanut butter peba peba jr. That's oh my God wait my I
would like to declare before my turn that all of my rations my the rations
that I'm carrying chicken are there pb and J. No, no, what this far no that's
what I would eat. No yeah and my favorite food would probably have to be
begging. It's not like I said it's jars of peanut butter. Okay, it's PB and J.
So I'll still have to scrape the jelly off if I want the dog to eat it because
dogs don't like jelly as much as peanut butter. Honestly, I don't have anything
all that good. You use your action to scrape off the jelly. So you admit
they're PB and J's. I don't have roll a sleight of hand. No. You said roll a
sleight of hand, so. No, no. I don't have anything all that good in my inventory
for this. Yeah, no. There's like combat options too, though. Wait a second. I
I feel like we definitely all have rope.
Can I just...
Dogs love to play tug of war with rope.
I'd like to cast blindness and deafness and I want to try to just flee this battle.
I want to try to make him deaf.
So I'm going to try that.
I think that's fair. Let me see.
[Humming]
Oh, that's crazy.
That's crazy.
I would not let that happen.
What?
Nothing. I was just reading about some of its immunities.
about that. That's insane. What's it immune to? COVID-19 and monkey pucks? No, it has some crazy
immunity. It's gonna have resistances but not immunities. So yeah, I mean you can try, let's
see, blindness and deafness, right? So it says for hit slash DCS as constitution 12. Okay,
it's ranged within 30 feet so you have to just move, you have to move close right now it's 60
feet away. So you can use your movement. Okay, I'll use my movement. Cool, yeah. What is a,
What does it look like when you try to blind or deafen something?
It's a...
It's just a plastic bag that just appears over their head.
Okay.
Oh, that's not a good roll.
And it can't be.
I'd just like to remind you I'm completely dead.
It's a black plastic bag.
Yeah, I'm trying to save your fucking dumb ass.
All right.
It is able to resist it.
So the plastic bag starts to go in its head and you're like...
Just like chews it up and throws it around.
Okay, can I use the can I I would like to use the rest of my turn to mope yeah
You wait, that was you should use your
You should use your spell create chocolate. It's your thing. It's create water turn
Create you might trick me
Patrick you're a brawl death saving throw. Yeah, I
Yeah, be so fun. If we just all died to a dog. I think we're honestly about I have low health
I've seven what do I roll it? Yeah, I think 20
I think we are going to die here this guy what's his name has something that 20
nice okay yeah you're up or you're you're stable holy crap my mind I was
playing with a friend and he was doing that wrong I like that better where if
you get a nat 20 on it or natural one you're just either dead or stable so
you're stable now so now somebody just needs to heal you we have a shot here
you're gonna have to heal I don't have any healing you can you were the only
with healing. Have you seen the Karate Kid? What's that? You might be able to rub...
What's that? It's a movie. Okay. It's the Yeth Hound's turn. What's your AC? Have I seen a Karate Kid?
Not a Karate Kid. The movie, the Karate Kid. My AC is 15. Okay, cool. The Yeth Hound comes out to bite you.
Like runs up to you, goes at you, comes out. You gay! I'm gay! And then tries to bite you. Oh, you gay!
That's why it was important that it's a boy dog.
And if it was a girl dog, I'd be drooling.
Yeah.
And he misses trying to bite you.
You so gay, you can't even bite me.
Shut up!
And--
It's a very dog-like voice.
It's a spot on dog.
And you're up now, Cam.
OK, I'm going to play with the rope with it.
You're going to play with the rope?
You're going to tug rope with a hempen rope?
What?
Why don't you try to kill it?
One second.
were uh... like the most important fight is using our
rope
i mean you could we're going to try to do exactly
uh...
like that's what it would do it through
the fifties now
it seems in talent of the only you will react to but it could be to want to put
the magically intent on killing you is there any can i can i fully get this is
loyal to some could i force it to say sticky fingers
no that's not how the power of the uh...
well
Maybe is there any okay? How close to also how close are we to the boat? Is
there a chance we could just run to the boat and like push off? I mean, so you
get away from it. Can we doing I guess also I'd like to roll a check to know
whether it can swim if that's okay. I mean if I would know that you roll
history check you can do that. It's free action. How much you do that
history? I have a minus one history reception because then you see if it
has some trunks on. Okay, that's an eight. I mean from what you can tell
just because it's a dog like it can probably swim but my dog doesn't like to
go on the ocean yeah mine either well you can't quite tell that but I mean you
can tell that it probably could swim not as fast as it could run okay and where
are we close to the dinghy you and Patrick is my diggy close to ship you
and Patrick are about 15 answer him from the dinghy oh my god no the ship is not
not the ships like you know like 200 feet away to a hundred foot ship. This
dog is between you guys and you are I mean you're 45 because you ran up to
attack it and it's about where you are. But yeah you're about now I feel like we
run away right. I think that's our only chance here is that we need to yeah let
me I can can I make a wave on land I have my wave or yeah that's producing it
Magically, okay, you were able to do what you did of course. How could I have sorry yeah, it's magical
Yeah, I guess I'll try to push it back with a wave that's a good move
I don't maybe try and pick up Patrick you should have it into the ocean
Well, okay. He just said it can swim. He said he doesn't know
It can probably swim probably isn't for sure I would like to push it back
So that means you would do this away your big or spell when you isn't it?
But it's between us and the ship though right so then I'll just push it out of the way and yeah
I'll push it wherever is going away push it inland so okay. That's what I meant so
You can um it's it's got it. You're within range now. You don't wouldn't even have to move towards it to try to push it so
I'm gonna roll first
Dexterity saving throw. What is it against? Let me see big or wait. Well, it's an attack roll. I think no, but
Dexterity saving throw. That's what I put it up against. Okay, cool. So first roll an attack roll
Okay
That is a oh wait, no don't make it a girl sorry. Okay good. Yeah
See who that is not good this probably failed
Yeah, if yeah, yeah town failed. Well, you conjure up this 30-foot long 10 feet wide 10 feet tall wave
Just like massive. Yeah, and it deals damage - yes, it does. And where's my d8 I can roll it
I got it right here. Hey cool before but you can roll it to go ahead. No, you should roll
I'm no, I mean I already rolled it but I feel like you might maybe roll it
It's like a four or seven actually, it's plus three. All right, cool. So you do seven damage to it
You knock it back though. Also
Yeah, what else did I say you knocked it back? Oh you knocked it prone right shit, okay?
It's not prone
And okay cool. Yeah, you knocked it. You knocked it prone
So it's on the ground prone. That's that's basically the turn right now. Yeah, and then I'm gonna
Can I I'm gonna break it to the boat? Yeah, can I like just drag?
Patrick behind yeah, you can just read okay cool like you're not it's and I'll do that yeah, okay cool
And that is a free action. I'll go Steve. Oh over here
mm-hmm just in case you didn't see okay cool and so we're back to the top of the
order and it is your turn so I'm gonna so this beast is now knocked prone on
the okay I'm trying to I guess should I heal him or should we just pick him up
and really well I brought him to the boat already oh okay
I mean you can use me like a bat if you use your full movement you'll be able to
get to the boat and you guys will be able to use me I'll use I'm just gonna
run straight to the boat. All right. All right cool. And now it is well actually I
should see here's what I should say. So if you use your full movement you're just
gonna be able to get on the boat. If you use your movement and then heal Patrick
I mean then he can also. I feel like he's gonna last one more. Yeah okay cool.
Yeah. So you get on the boat. I'm just gonna go straight to the boat. Patrick is just alive and just stable and then. I pull out
up my sword and I split my wrist and then the F. I was going to be able to get up.
It's going to try to shoot got a fire ability. Yeah, it's gonna try to shoot at
you guys this time. It's going to be to
or dead or done. Let's see how it does. It might not do to completely over.
Let's see if I'd be fine. We are it did it did half my health left last hit and
that was like I rolled. That was a surprise round on that one. It did extra
damage. It might not do as much as time, but it might still do a lot of
is there. Do we have guardian angels?
Yes. No, that says here we do. I'm looking at the rules.
It says each player gets one guardian angel if they want it.
Let's just do it over here. He saw the role. Wasn't going to kill us.
So he put, he re-rolled it. I know. I actually saw that happen. Wow.
I saw it live. Okay. Well maybe this one I'm seeing most of this stuff live.
- Okay, all right, so only Dogen got hit.
- How much?
- Thatta was a close-ah.
- Let's see.
- Thatta was a close-ah, yes-ah.
- Thatta was a close-ah.
- Yes-ah.
Yes-ah, me understand-ah.
- Where is it?
Where are ya?
- Right here.
- Right here, just joking.
- You see, it's a little less damage, okay, cool.
Take seven damage.
- Okay, only seven.
- Woo, okay, cool.
Yeah, see, it's not gonna be as bad.
I'm at 11.
I'm surprised, like, hitting you guys.
You're at 11?
Yeah.
Bro, you were complaining.
You did half my HP last hit and that was like half damage.
Or something.
And it's also, so it got up, it shot that, so it's still, like, far away from you because
it didn't, like, then.
What's the range on this attack?
Would you know off the top of your head?
I do know it off the top of my head, but I'm not going to say.
You could probably.
Realistically, how far can fire go without being blown completely out by the wind?
In this, I would say this kind of ray, you could guesstimate around 60-ish feet.
All right.
Back to the top of the order?
Yes.
No.
No, I just went.
It's actually Patrick's.
No, Patrick's win.
It's your turn.
Oh, okay.
I'll row the boat.
Yeah.
You can start rowing it.
Cool.
So you guys move out of range.
You guys move a bit further.
You can use your turn also to do that.
Or if you want to heal Patrick, you can.
I'm gonna go ahead and heal Patrick with the healing touch.
Yeah, do it.
Or whatever it's called.
So you can do that and also use some of your movement action to row the ore.
I know that might be like a use item action, whatever, but I don't give a fuck ass shit.
Or spare the dying.
Not your grandma's Dungeons and Dragons.
No, it's not.
She's really strict about the rules.
Or no, false life is what I'm gonna cast.
Yeah, spare the dying just stabilizes him.
- Give him some temporary hit points.
Does false life, if you give somebody temporary hit points,
does that bring them back to life is the question.
- Well, I'm already back to life.
- Well, you know what I meant like--
- I rolled a nat 20.
- So eight, I heal him eight.
- Do you, hold on, let me see, now I'm curious.
- You said he was stabilized, right?
And my spare the dying just stabilizes.
- Yeah, but false hit, or like temporary hit points
are like a different, they're like armor.
- Oh, well that's all I have as far as healing, I think.
I feel like I don't have any healing.
I think I used to and then when I broke my paladin oath I lost all my healing.
That's what I thought.
Temporary doesn't restore consciousness.
I do have an actual healing but I don't have any spell slots to cast it.
So I can't heal.
Alright, so Patrick is just going to be like chilling.
Okay, so I shouldn't roll that.
Wait, is my Lay on Hands damage now?
Yeah, no it heals.
It does HP healing.
You can use Lay on Hands.
Oh, I thought I didn't have that anymore.
No, you have that.
Okay, then I should have done that.
Can we retroactively say that I did lay on hands and Caleb rowed and just switch our
turns?
Yeah, that's totally fine.
Okay, I will lay on hands and do.
And I will row.
Alright, cool.
So Patrick, you're up.
I guess I'll just heal 20.
How much HP?
What's your max HP?
27.
I'll just do 20, yeah.
Cool, do it.
Alright, so Patrick, you're back up and you're rowing and now Patrick, are you going to row
also?
You're also going to row?
I'm going to row.
So you guys have some serious distance now from this thing.
Because we're strong, right?
And I just rolled two D100s.
I got a 27.
It's going to charge to the shore and try one more time shooting at you guys.
God, Jesus.
Okay.
It can still reach us?
Interesting.
It's really...
No, it did not really land.
Fascinating.
All right, yep.
again. Oh my god. Bitch ass. Um. How much? Uh, six damage. Six? Yeah. Alright, I'm at five.
Okay, yeah. And uh, yeah at this point I'll say like you guys are far enough away, you're
approaching your ship. I mean if you start yelling at them now to get shit going, the
dog won't be able to like fucking turn around. Yeah. Along the coast. Put my dinghy in your
ship! What? What captain? Put my dinghy in your ship! I'm radogging you! Put my dinghy
on your shit oh you want to fuck me in the ass sure let's go guys like they all
know they all pick the thingy up they put it on the ship the dog is approaching
again just firing like rays of fire rojo eyes and you guys are able to sort of
approaching is it swimming no it's like running along the shore now trying to
I thought it was just coming out here.
Well I think yethounds can hover but I don't know.
Whoa!
But this one, but this one.
They can hover?
No, this one, I modified this one.
That's so funny to know that I rolled that bad check and you're like yeah it might be
able to swim.
It could swim and you knew it in your brain that it could hover.
I've modified the F-Hound. I specifically didn't want it to be... I wanted it to have spells
because it doesn't have spells usually and I wanted it to like not... I wanted it to
be able to specifically not be able to like hover so that you can do something like this
which is like get away from it in case like this was happening. But also I wanted it to
be bigger and stronger.
Probably you were a ho-guard.
Anyway.
You were a ho-ish ass hound.
So you're able to sort of sail away and next session we'll figure out where you're going
going to go next if you're going to go to berry berry, if you guys want to keep
going towards the end of the earth or if you guys want to go to the dirtlands or
anywhere else on the map and we'll also begin it with leveling up and you guys
will be level five. Actually the the game changer level. Let's go the game
changer level. Oh yeah, yeah, I'll be like bro. I'll be like bro bro. So we
loving laying up at the end of the next session. Next session. We're already
done why'd that vending up is that okay um can I use a little man can we do it
well let's just do something fun yeah can we do let's see mud we got my mom with
us right why don't we why don't we all do like a barbershop court I know I don't
want to do that no we've done enough barbershop quartets over the years I
think yeah um you know let's do a scene and I quit the show okay let's do a
scene that's Patrick quitting the show that's how we'll close it out okay okay
- All right, all right.
Well, just got to the office.
- Wow, man.
- Here, we'll all be ourselves.
Patches, you can be the front door.
- Okay.
- Okay, here I go, opening the front door.
- All right, and I'm closing it behind me.
All right, and now I'm at the office.
- Okay, I'm knocking on the front door.
- Okay, looks like I gotta go open the front door again.
- I'm still knocking.
Nobody, hello, hello?
- Time to open the front door, here I go.
- No, why, who's?
(laughing)
- Something's wrong, wait, hold on.
Wait, let me wiggle this door.
I think hold on. Oh, that's not that I was noticing that too when I was when I was
moving the door. I think we might we might need to put some oil on the hinges.
Yeah, I think we need hey Patrick. Do you have any oil? I'm not here yet. Okay.
Oh, okay. We'll have to go out of the door to get oil. All right. Well, let's
open the door. I'm here, but I'm in the bathroom. Okay. So you also have to play
the bathroom door and the toilet. Okay. Okay. Well, I'm going out. I'm opening
the front door. Okay, I'm walking down the street. Okay, now I'm fine.
Why is the door making noise when you walk down the street?
There's something really wrong with the door. I'm on the phone with you, Caleb.
I can hear over the speaker phone that there's something really wrong with the door.
It's making noise when I walk down the street.
It's making some weird sounds. It stopped for some reason.
I'm opening the door to the...
Are you opening and closing it right now?
Oh my God, the door's talking!
I'm opening the door to the oil store right now.
The oil store?
Yeah.
Okay, so it sounds like the door at the office is making noise when I open the
door to the oil store.
That makes no fucking sense.
Okay, anyway.
I'm buying oil now.
Okay, I don't know what that noise is.
That's actually in the store and not from the door.
Yeah, it's almost like the door is getting confused about his role in the whole story.
Okay, I bought the oil. It was really cheap and now I'm coming back.
Okay, I hope to see you soon.
I'm knocking on the door.
I'm opening the door.
Oh, hey, sorry, I forgot. Yeah, all good. Patrick, are you out of the bathroom yet?
It seems like Patrick might have died in the bathroom. Hey Pat, are you in there?
I'm putting oil on the door. Oh my god! You're squirting everywhere. The door is making a weird noise when I put the oil on it.
The oil is completely noiseless when it comes out of the container, but as soon as it touches the door, the door makes a squelching noise.
noise. Are you doing it now? I can't tell. Okay, I finished putting the oil on. Okay,
Patrick. Patrick, are you out of the bathroom yet? Yeah, you out dude. Okay, I'm
opening the bathroom door. Why is the front door making noise? Oh, there's
something more important. I'm dead and somebody in the office, there's a note
that says it's I'm dead and somebody in the office did this and you it's your
her job to find out who somebody like just between me and camera
there's somebody else in the office. I did it
and it's and it's a door yeah. Well, it wasn't me and it wasn't the intruder.
It must have been Caleb.
It must have been that talking door. Okay, I'm killing the I'm seriously
taking the door out of the office. I don't want it anymore. You're not
screaming door in pain. You're sentient enough to kill Patrick, but you can't
scream in pain when I kill you?
- Ah!
- Oh my God, a screaming door!
We're gonna be famous.
- Okay, now we're on the Ellen show.
- Yep.
- I'm Ellen, I'm Ellen.
- Okay. - Thank God.
- My period!
- That honestly is how you sound a lot of the times,
Ellen, you stupid bitch.
- Yeah. - But check this out.
- But anyway, I'm an angry bitch.
- But we brought something that even--
- We brought an incredible phenomenon.
- Wait, wait, I gotta do Ellen's dance.
- That's very cool.
Now listen, you need to pay attention,
because we brought something that even a lesbian could appreciate.
Look at this door.
Oh my god, that'd be amazing in my vagina.
Okay, you're seriously making everything about your lesbian sex lifestyle.
And my wife.
Stop, okay.
And now, and Ellen, I'm a girl with a wife.
Listen, the choices that you make are none of my business, but I'm going to tell you
that-
Hey!
Ellen, Ellen, I need to show you something incredible about this door.
Listen for the noise that it makes when I open the front door of the oil store, and
I'm going to the oil store right now.
I'm on the phone with Ellen.
Ellen, I'm about to go into the oil store.
Okay? Now watch this.
I open the door to the oil store.
That sounds like my wife when I have sex with her.
Yeah, but we get it dude. You're a complete lesbo
and that's okay these days.
Hey!
Ahhhh!
And every time I say hey ho, we start dancing.
Yes. Okay, and then it's like
that's the end of it. Curtains come down and then it's like
years later. It's like the epilogue and now I have a job at the oil store and
the years later and it's me and the door. We fall in love and we're sitting on
our porch in rural Tennessee right and we're sitting in our rockers just going
back and forth right and maybe maybe you know Mumford and son songs kind of
silently like quietly playing like from the on screen not like in reality right
yeah yeah and we're just sitting there and I and I'm holding the door the door
not the doors knob and I'm saying you know what you know what door after all
All these years, I gotta tell you what, marrying you was truly...
The door is making that noise right now because I'm opening and closing the door at the oil
store where my job is.
I seriously think marrying you is the greatest decision I ever made in my life.
And I have absolutely no regrets about the life we've made.
And then I'm in the hospital with cancer.
And then I quietly, I quietly pass away from old age.
Right there, right there on my porch.
Me as Ellen, I pass away too.
thirty two years
and ellen is in hell and her name is helen
and that's gonna be it probably right?
that's the improv part of the show
i think we should do scenes from now on
i think we pretty much need to do a who's on who anyway briefing
And I will wait, I will wait for you And I will wait, I will wait for you
[MUSIC]