[Music]
Once upon a time, on the planet Ebon,
long before Gun City and the arrival of Earthlings,
before the Tamagotchis and the Crayolas,
Before the void and the cataclysm, there was a great war between the police, the ultimate
good, the light of the universe, the saints of decency, joy, and love, and the terrifier,
an ancient evil, unknowable and untraceable, the thing that goes bump and grind in the
night and bump and grind in the day. The war lasted almost a day, but everyone's tummies
started to hurt, so it really needed to end so people could go home and watch TV. And the
terrifier won. Elves, men, dwarves, gnomes, all manner of mortal creatures of decent disposition
were forced into slavery, or killed, or eaten, or all three.
But just as quickly as the Terrifier won, he vanished, presumably to terrify some other
suckers.
In his stead, he left the Terrifier's kingdom to his Gnars.
Furry monsters with a gnarled underbite, bulging yellow eyes, a bat's nose, six legs like a
mutated tripod with talons on the ends, two arms, and a penis that acts as a scorpion tail
that whispers dark thoughts into their weird little ears.
They did their best to rule over the orcs, goblinoids, and other nasty creatures who could
finally live the brutal, bloodied life of their dreams.
For years, however, these nards battled one another for supremacy as they always did,
killed one another, drank, fought, started wars, enslaved the conquered, and did it all over again.
Eventually, even some of the unruliest of Nards grew tired of the ceaseless fighting.
But it was all they knew. The Terrifyer made all these horrendous monsters to do one thing,
terrify. But without their leader, they were aimless, self-destructive, and soon possessed
by the worst of things, ennui. They began to turn to literature, of how things once were,
but none of them could read. They cautiously approached their learned slaves, and asked
them for guidance. "We want to be normal," said King Nardwaur. "We want to not kill each other.
We want to use soap and be nice. We want to see if plumbing would be good for us. If not, just
Maybe pick a place to shit, rather than just wherever we're standing."
"And I want to sing!" said one Nard. "Shut up!" And King Nardwar swallowed this Nard whole,
and slapped his belly and said, "Ooh, you betcha." Then, possessed by lucidity, he said, "See? That's
not how we should solve problems. I have eaten too many guys. I don't wanna eat guys." And so,
Over time the slaves were freed. Elves, humans, dwarves and the like were able to live amongst
the Nards to help show them how to be regular. This did not sit well with all the Nards or other
denizens of the Terrifier Kingdom, but so the threat of a greater war looms.
One of the cornerstones of this growing trend of teaching Nards how to be regular
was adventuring. Adventurers from far and wide scoured the kingdom for lost treasures of being
normal or a free community still under the tyrannical rule of slavers.
They sought ancient magics, fought dark wizards, and befriended beasts that lurked beneath the
planet and ruled its skies.
Such adventurers were few and far between.
But there were three such intrepid fellows, nestled into the armpit of the kingdom.
A small village that rests outside of King Nardwuar's Claw Castle that's shaped like
a claw.
Trebuchet Village.
Trebuchet Village is a bleak and vile little place filled with nasty peasants and monsters
and evil magic and a remarkable, peerless cruelty extended towards anyone unfortunate enough
to live in the damn place.
The stench of death and shit hung low and heavy, followed by the stench of foot, then the stench
of death, then the stench of shit and death again, rounding it out.
The town has all the trappings of a real place though, including a lovely little general store
run by ye old Sullivan the Frog.
This trebuchet village is first in hundreds of years, and it gets robbed only bi-weekly
by orcs, nards, and the like.
To run such a general store and protect it, ye olde Sullivan hired three expert retail
sales associates, each of whom, unbeknownst to the other, moonlight as adventurers themselves.
Who are these three adventurers?
Well that's enough out of me, at this point I'll let them speak for themselves.
So, who are each of you?
Let's start with you, Dogen.
Hello, everyone.
My name is Dogen the Dirt Goblin.
My whole life I've loved dirt.
I was born as an orphan with no mother or father
and I grew up on my own dirt farm,
tending to my crops and selling dirt at the local farmer's market.
It was a boring but fulfilling life and one filled with dirt.
One day though, I was struck with a vision.
I walked out to my fields and saw a burning dirt bush.
A voice boomed forth from it.
"What's up?" it said.
This was the voice of Dogen the Dirt God, my namesake.
I swore devotion to him immediately and became a paladin,
a bold warrior spreading the gospel of dirt.
I left my dirt farm under the care
of my adoptive little brother, Dogen the Dirt Kobold,
and moved to Trebuchet Village,
where I took the first open room I found on Craigs Scroll.
This room happened to be the cramped basement
of a minotaur hype house,
which has led to a lot of comedic and silly,
almost Animal House-esque situations
that maybe could be explored in the future,
but also could just be left alone.
By day, I work at Ye Olde Sullivan's General Store,
where I sweep dirt onto the floor from outside.
My boss is awesome.
He is so nice, and I respect him deeply
because he has years and years more experience than me.
I can't see that ever changing.
By night, I'm a daring adventurer,
striking the fear of dirt into the hearts of monsters
with my trusty shovel,
which is named Dogen the Dirt Shovel.
By the time between day and night,
I sleep or something, I guess.
Thank you, Dogen.
Yeah, right now, are you just sweeping dirt then in the general store?
Yeah, I'm sweeping dirt, but I'm also not satisfied with how much dirt I'm bringing in.
So I'm also like picking up dirt and putting it in my pockets and sprinkling it around
the floor too.
Yes.
And you are a paladin, a level one paladin for folks who that's important for them.
And it's just some of them, right?
You wield a war hammer.
It's a shovel.
Yeah, it's a shovel.
It's a war shovel.
It's a war shovel. I apologize. Right. You're yeah and you have a one other item. That's pretty interesting, which is a pouch of forever dirt. We don't have to get into that now if you don't want to but it's pretty pretty cool. Yeah. Yeah. It's your secret. I apologize then for even saying anything.
Yeah, it's a now we'll we'll sort of look over in the store in the in general general store.
Maybe hanging out by the dougla burgers deli counter is a Patrick you dark.
Patrick Patrick you dark Patrick you dark.
What's up? Hi, how's it going? My name is Patrick Yodar. I'm the nephew of Trunchbull Yodar, one of the most famous explorers in all of Trebuchet Village.
And I am riding that out until I eventually die. How do people get famous in these times? I actually have no idea.
I have no idea how somebody becomes famous nowadays.
Basically you just walk up to somebody and say something like, "Hey, I'm a famous guy."
And they believe you?
I really have no idea.
I've seen Uncle Trunchbull do that a few times and it's worked.
I mean really there is no way for you to prove whether or not somebody is famous in these
times.
My uncle could just be taking credit for some other verdan, and I would be none the wiser,
honestly.
I live a pretty lavish life in the shadow of my uncle, and it's taught me one very important
life skill, and it's shoplifting.
God damn, god damn do I love shoplifting.
Oh man, you know, I could walk into any shop in Trebuchet Village and just say, "Hey, I'm
Trunchbull Yodar's nephew," and they would at least give me a free fruit or something.
but uh...
no i think it's funny to shoplift
that's my thing it's awesome
uh... you some kind of funny about me i have a
comically large balls
absolutely absolutely huge balls very comical
a lot of people laugh and uh... hey i get it
uh... anyway i've uh...
i've been working at Sullivan's General Store because uh... i think it's funny
i think it's uh... funny to work with poor people
my uncle so rich that i can do that for fun can you believe it
anyway that's enough about me what about you
you can't
that the alda is so good
i mean i think you know dark yeah what the fuck you can't do it and comes
harry patrick you know dark
uh... we have to hear of her dan uh... river ever done actually
don't know that technical media the pronunciation of that here
They are a goblinoid race.
I think they're in Acquisitions Incorporated,
is the source book they're from.
So I don't know if that's, I don't know much about
Acquisitions Incorporated, but it's a cool looking race.
They're sort of like smart, inquisitive goblins.
And yeah, they also have,
What's interesting is they have a weird growth spurt that they go through at some point. So
they start goblin-sized and then grow bigger when they're going through puberty or something.
Yeah. And so you're hanging out by Doug LaBerger's deli counter. Is he serving you up a flesh burger?
Hey, Doug, how about you just slide me one of those burgers right there?
Yeah, no problem, Patrick.
Oh, great. You're one of the best guys that works here. I absolutely love you. You're one of the-
I mean, no, I love you too.
You're one of my favorite employees here.
I believe you every time you say it.
I love you too.
Oh, I love you.
I love you so much.
I would, I would kill somebody for you if I had to.
Hey, you just might.
Play your cards right.
Oh, trust me.
I mean, at times like these, we love violence, don't we?
Yeah, always.
Always love violence in the Terrafires kingdom.
It's absolutely fantastic.
I love, I love, I love just getting my short sword under somebody's neck.
He sort of like laughs to himself and like shuts down the conversation.
Don't you just love it? Don't you just love it when you're playing?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean it's just like a do-it-yourself tracheotomy. It's amazing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right, you gonna give me that burger now?
Yep, here it comes.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
You're beautiful and we sort of move a little bit past the
counter and we see another fella this time a dwarf of some
kind one evil steve.
Evil Stievel
Oh before actually I should mention sorry didn't mean to take the thunder there
Patrick Yodar is a rogue
For whatever that's worth to people
Against first level so not a lot of subclasses or sub anything already decided. But yeah
He's a rogue
Sorry, yes, please evil steeple
Sup, I'm evil Steve. Oh, you know, I'm bad better than a weasel with a needle
Better than a beaver that's a cheater better would then a threesome with a cheetah better than a pizza on a pita
That's why they call me Steve
Or or evil. I'm a hill dwarf cleric. I'll use my magic to deceive you
I'm also a Christian. So I really hate the devil
I'm Steven
Like Steve and evil. I'm wide like a beetle and I'm short like
Like a beetle
Yes, so what I'm legal
But I'm still evil evil Steve
Evil Steve all is a cleric an evil cleric of the death domain. Yep
So death domain is pretty cool. They have sort of take and invert the life domain
Yeah, all right. They do necrotic damage. They don't really do too much healing. It's sort of a
damaged healing cleric type
And yeah, he's a dwarf a hill dwarf. So it's pretty cool
So, what do you what do you what do you do in the store evil Steve? Like what's sort of your I knocked the cans off
the shelves
Yo Sullivan pick these up man
Sullivan I think I think yeah, I think some of them are broken. I think you might have to put that in the inventory
You don't do it now. I'm knocking more cans over
You don't want it. You don't want to see this guy knock any more cans
I mean, it's just one of the only three guys in the town who won't just try to eat me
So there go the fried beans, please stop. Okay. Oh, no. Oh, I think that was the one and I respect so deeply
How you're handling the situation? I there goes the okra. I'm your
the
And I'm out.
There are actually seven aisles in Sullivan's Deli store.
[Laughter]
Produce, flesh, tools, alcohol, alcohol, and knick-knacks, and then Doug LaBurger Deli Fresh.
Which I guess isn't an aisle, but more of a station.
So yeah, you guys are sort of, it's sort of towards the end of the day.
You know, you're kind of eager, all of you are eager to get out for a couple of reasons, which we'll get into.
But one of which is today's a big day in the kingdom of the terrifier.
It is the murder celebration because the prince, Prince Jumanji, is turning five, which is the age of murder.
So you're all eager to get out and there's festivities but also each of you have sort of a job to do with the festivities which will get into but before you can do that and while solving is sort of a.
Try to stack the shelves stack the cans back up but evil steve was just a few inches taller than him so he just able to like sort of like stuff it in his face like that.
he doesn't like it. No. I can tell. I can tell looking over here that he does not like it.
There's something about you, Patrick Yodar, is just just so serving. I have to say.
Thank you. It's probably these big-ass balls. It could be these balls. I mean I'm just sitting on
these things. I have not done a lick of work today. No, I've watched. I know. I'm taking
advantage of well well-being that has distracted talking to those two i'm like shoveling dirt
in like just huge shovels of dirt i'm filling the doorway with dirt and uh sullivan i uh
i know this is probably not a good time i uh i need an advance in my paycheck
oh well i already gave you an advance today yeah i'm gonna need a i'm gonna need like the next uh
you want the next one too okay yeah i'm gonna need the next one advanced so it's just the last
so the events i gave you today was sort of the third advance
so this is now
it's i don't know what will will let me know it's it's going to be five advances
no i i understand because we are all trying our best is already like writing
the check for you
and
uh... you see
pushing through the dirt pile that you made
uh... are
uh... yeah
uh...
the dogan
are three Grimlocks and Grimlocks are just nasty looking fucked up guys.
They have their brow is so deep down sort of a what's his name you know from Highlander
that they are blind and they have stringy long hair and a bald crown and they're kind
of and these are clearly teenage Grimlocks and Sullivan knows them well and so you could
see he's already as he hears them come in and it's a three of them here's
there's there's three and one of them goes like well looks like we're gonna
start messing this place up it's gonna be a good time looks like that way
ahead of you yeah this guy gets it oh maybe we should maybe we should knock
over one of the shelves and the third one goes I know exactly what he was
saying and Sullivan says please no the Grimlocks are back can you guys please
Please take care of it.
Ah, Christ.
Alright, I guess I can get off my balls for a little bit.
Blah blah blah blah blah.
I get it, it's so tempting to sit on them.
Oh man.
I've had thoughts.
It's actually, it is one of the most wonderful feelings.
Sorry, do you have room?
Oh yeah, actually, hop right on.
Wow.
I'll move over to the left one and then you can get on the right one.
Oh my God.
Wait, is that a massage function I feel on my back?
well yeah i had that installed last week and i like that
yet necromancer put that in the exact actually uses the uh... uses the uh...
that the the leg bones of a lot of uh... dead men
magic credible yeah yeah it's amazing what they're doing with that
with magic nowadays mhm
uh... so you guys are just like that we discovered station
and the crib walks are like
looking at you like expecting you to say something good the
the bigger, dumber one goes, "What?"
What do you want?
Do you want to sit on my balls right now?
No. Hey look, there's a little bit more room in the front. I think I can get one or two of you
right here and then I think around the back.
Roll up, roll up.
Are Grimlocks tall or are they goblin size or how big are they?
They're like medium size, a little bigger.
if
Come on now, come on now, why you gotta throw that at me?
Excuse me, gentlemen.
Nasty.
When you guys came in here looking to cause trouble,
it seems you may have already caused a little bit
of trouble with me without even realizing it.
Did you notice that beautiful pile of dirt
that you just knocked out of the way?
I'm gonna need you guys to go back outside,
take some trowels, and put that back to how it was before,
'cause I will not be having this.
You don't wanna mess with that guy's dirt.
Oh yeah, what you gonna do about it?
(mimics babbling)
- Hey, hey, come on, come on now.
Let's not use that language in here.
- What did he say, what did he say?
What did he say to me?
- Look, I'm not gonna repeat what he said, but--
- Okay, can you, all right, well,
write it down and tell me later.
- He says that your dad's fat.
And you see him shaking his head no and going,
(mimics babbling)
(laughing)
- Oh, come on, come on now.
You don't say that about any of our fathers.
- I don't have a dad.
I was born an orphan.
- Yeah, he doesn't have a dad.
- I said that, I said that.
Didn't you guys hear me monologuing that
while you were waiting outside?
No, we weren't listening.
I hit him with my shovel.
All right, roll initiative.
Four.
It's a bad start.
14.
It's a better start.
That's an intelligence saving throw.
Nope, that's wrong.
Initiative doesn't start with an I-N-T, I guess.
It's a walking speed, if you have it, yeah.
Nice, okay, cool.
All right, cool.
So yeah, uh, yeah, the battle, the battle's about to begin.
I'm going to position you guys to probably where you are at this point.
You offered him to sit on your balls.
So probably kind of closer.
I sat on his balls.
You sat on his ball.
So you're still on him and you're still on his balls.
So yes, you'll take three feet of your movement speed to get up.
Deep down are these damn balls.
Dude, I'm four feet tall.
There's no way.
I'm three foot eleven.
You're all really small.
Yeah.
Okay.
So first in the order is actually Patrick Yodar as the
goblin that they
is in front of you.
Look, I don't I don't I don't want to cause any problems, but
it seems like you already have caused some trouble.
So I'm going to have to get involved.
Okay, is that all right with you?
I'm going to take that as a yes.
Okay, cool. What do you want to do?
Um, I'm just gonna... hold on.
Um, yeah. So, you can go to your actions and just look at your actions.
It's under actions, okay.
Yeah, that's gonna be the most helpful.
Um, I'm sitting on my balls and I pull out, I pull a bow and arrow out from my back.
My back pack.
I'm like alright well let me hold on okay there we go and I have the arrow in there.
Alright I'm gonna shoot you with this.
Okay roll the hit.
Nine.
Nine yeah it's just like you shoot it, it just like sails past him.
Ah Christ, Sullivan look out.
Sullivan ducks underneath.
Um, uh, and, uh, it's like, "Please! There's a whole fighting!"
There's a tip jar on the counter of, like, doubloons or whatever the fuck the money is.
-Yeah. -And I just destroyed it.
[laughter]
Uh, and it is now your turn, Evil Stevel.
Alright, I'm going to cast Chill Touch.
-Mmm. -Can I do that?
-Yeah, you can. -Yes!
Okay, cool. So with with a chill touch, you have to get in touch range. So you get up and you walk towards Oh, wait, actually, no, I forgot. Wait, chill touch.
Do I have a ghost hand? It's a ghost hand. I forgot. Yeah, actually, I would describe chill touch.
So I create a ghost hand made of probably bones and blue, blue. It gets it gets a I can touch somebody with it. Yes, it does damage
the blue blue ghost and sort of like source for which one which one of them
do you go for
my right hand
yet and uh...
no way right-handed chill touch
no which criminal act
you the closest one
the okay so one is going to be a good idea just a lot of your going in your
mouth
and uh... i felt a small like a little bit of cold in a uh... yeah that's what
i call it chill touching funny and a and that these things are gonna shrink
and that i was getting a member of the that i don't think they'll ever shrink
and that thirteen is enough to hit
and so you uh...
uh... you dislike
hit this guy for eight damage
and uh... he's just like
it goes into his mouth it was a little bit
now we've got something
they treats it like a pacifier
but it's just like hurting him really bad no home can i take his voters to
You do that, you get like a pinky in there.
Make him eat his own boogers.
Oh, God, that's got to be some other kind of damage, right?
Yeah. Yeah. No, he Grimlocks love love boogers.
I take him back out of his damn mouth.
Do you think he's like upset?
Now it's going to be the Grimlocks turn.
So that one who you did the chill touch to he's going to sort of like lumber over to you too.
And he's going to try to swing at you Patrick Yodar.
which let's see how he do it that uh... who i have the new encounter thing
we're going to have a new encounter thing
so let's see how this goes
was that work
it does work okay
is a fourteen hit patrick
well come on now
it does
why did you
well you know he doesn't know what that question means come on to be a c
it's a way you can ask patrick for the first time does a fourteen what is your
armor class. Oh sorry. Yeah, what's your armor class? My armor class is 14. Okay, so it does
beat you because the way it works in this is, it's when you meet it, you got it. That's
the saying. Simple as that. Yep. When you meet it, you got it. Hey, when you got it,
you get it. Yep. When the number's there, the number's where. You got it good. Yeah,
and so it does, he does like two damage to you. These guys are pretty weak. They're weaker
and
and just like bounces in on one of your balls.
So I do.
So you take two HP.
Yeah, you're down to HP.
This other one is going to go for you Dogen.
He's like, let's see how tough you are because you want a
piece of me, huh?
Yeah, you were going to swing that shovel at me.
Huh?
You want a piece of this?
You want it?
You're going to swing that.
Hey, I can barely see.
And he's going to try to attack you.
Does the 12 hit probably not no you're paladin, right? Yeah, so he tries to attack you with his club
And you just like you're a little goblin
You just like fucking like do some matrix shit off the aisle like just like kicking back and forth
And you're knocking over different products and so i was like no
What's up, bitch? Not the mead the bottled mead
um
And uh now the other one's gonna go and he's just gonna sort of move
towards uh
you
uh... evil steve all you can try to get you with his club
uh...
and
now when you get this
uh... he hits this year twenty one you may have to uh... this is just no way
uh...
story he does uh... three damage to you
in the air
the box you on the head
uh... this
you know i think that i think that i i mean the uh... the damage reverberated
through his body and i felt it my ball
the
and
the year just a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit it felt uh...
felt okay
yeah
this is the
here
it is now dole did
your turn
that's right
uh... i'm just gonna stand and i'm gonna hit this grimoire with my shovel
tell you i go for it
Sixteen. Oh that hits.
So is the top damage for one handed and the bottom damage is for two handed?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, I'm using a two handed.
Yeah, do it.
Wait, oh I do it over here.
Yeah.
It's confusing.
Three.
Yeah.
That's not how that does it.
No, I don't, I reject that.
I reject the way they do this.
So we'll take the, the, the, uh, we'll take the, yeah, no, I, that's ridiculous.
I'm very confused by this.
Because what it's-
It's a nine, it's a ten.
Yeah, no, no.
What we should do is take the the yeah,
let's take the five and have the two.
Yeah, let's take the seven because that's that makes more sense to me.
So yeah, you just like whack this guy in the head with the shovels.
You dodge off him off the like aisle walls and then just like
punk just like bonk him on the head with the shovel like shovel night
and just you see him like he's like reverberate like vibrating through
his body like a cartoon.
You will respect dirt.
Bye.
Like he's trying to like talk and it's back to the top of
the order.
So it's your turn Patrick.
Yodar.
All right.
Well, I'm a little bit upset at your actions from earlier
and it looks like you're close enough.
You're close enough now for me to use my to poke you with
my long sword.
I'm going to see.
I'm going to see if I can do that.
and let's see
but the local but but but but
ten damage
so there's a ten to hit and it does hit
tenders here
uh... seven
uh... yeah you get the seven
uh... actually yeah
that's because they're in range you get the sneak attack damage as well
uh... so
it described your kill of this guy
yes i said i'm
i'm sitting on my balls
and i just go
uh... how yet
the
since the weekend
well i a look at that i mean
that is that is what i like is a violent man
yet he's a c_-seven billion
out and he just crumples to the ground and dead
and you see the number one click
no
ricky and uh... he's very upset by that
uh... it's your turn though
uh... evil steve all was up was that a
gamma attack that same dude
who attacked previously she still lives
no he's dead he was just killed i would take his dead body
not okay cool
now they got who's a guy
to just meet me tonight uh... yeah you can
okay is a big dumb guy he's always my mace as revenge
okay that's not what this is damage this is damage now
it the uh... the the plus number and yeah
it was a yeah that it's your tissue tonight so everyone doesn't think we
just only transceived it
you know i'll yell image
the
I do one damage.
You're about to die, watch this!
This is gonna kill you in one shot.
One shot, one kill.
Well, you tried your best and honestly I- Shut up, Alan Holder, fuck you.
I commend you for it.
So you like, wind up your mace and you just sort of like puncture his tummy and then just
like pull it out quickly.
He's like, "Ohhhhhhhhh!"
Yeah, you're probably dead now, huh? If we waited a couple hours, you'd be so dead.
Yeah, and also everyone, we are using new character sheets.
That's why they're having a little bit of trouble right now.
Without no other reason. And it is now that guy's turn, and he's like,
He's gonna try to attack you
Again with his club. He is not very inventive
he just whiffs he just like
tries to get you and
He just sort of like tries to wind up to attack, but he misjudges a distance
So he just sort of attacks behind you with the club and bumps his stomach into your face
Got blood on my damn face. Oh
You're fucking asshole. Hey here. I have a have a handkerchief right here. You can use you can borrow that for a little bit
This is just a part of your ball sack skin
Yeah, exactly. That is exactly what it is
Do you want to get the blood off your face or no?
Okay, yeah, you know, oh, okay. Oh off his face. I got confused
I would not offer you any any kind of help. What the hell is going on over there?
Hey, what's going on? How are you doing over there? How's everything? I'm doing good. How are you doing man?
I'm doing pretty good. Just you know, I still got the massage feature on this whole time. I've had it on. Yeah. Do you like dirt?
Yeah, actually, I got a house made of dirt. Oh, wow. Can I come over?
Oh, yeah, you would you would absolutely love it. I'm gonna fuck your walls
Don't watch out
and meanwhile uh... a uh... some solvin yells token watch out what you say i'm
gonna put your walls and a club comes around and just clocks you on the face
for three damage uh...
and i'm really sorry to distract you just now
that's okay that was my fault i'm gonna tell your walls
okay absolutely i mean you
cartblanch you can do whatever you want to my walls after after a distracted you
your back walls
any at front walls back walls i mean you can you can even fuck the floor i don't
i don't really mind
so here are the floors located into
uh... yeah it's your turn though don't miss guys like wallop you
yeah uh...
i i'm you know i'm just gonna back no fancy stuff
sixteen all that connects
told me image of describe your kill
okay so i i i swing my shovel and i hit him in the face any falls backwards any
He hits one of the shelves and like a jar of like pureed carrots or something falls into
his mouth.
The carrots!
Yeah, he's allergic to carrots and his face puffs up and he dies.
No carrots!
I hate them because I'm allergic.
They actually taste quite good!
And he dies.
Look at that, he died learning something about himself.
He actually liked carrots.
That's beautiful.
the
evil steve all attacks of opportunity if you want to come with a i'm a little
bit of a narrow
i use my chill touch did
mccabe do it up
yet this is actually one of the worst things you can do is a runaway for me
uh... six on chill touch to fifteen
fuck
uh... so you're still touch your hand is sort of like grass for like the door
something that is doesn't quite help them get out
Yeah, opens the door for him, pats him on the back.
Yeah, but as it pats him on the back, what goes through your ghostly hand is a bow expertly
aimed at this guy's lung.
And he's like, "Urgh!"
And he just fucking falls and collapses on the ground.
See, that is one of the best feelings in the world.
When you set out to do something and you hit your target, that is just amazing.
I love that.
Yeah, you guys killed these three teenagers.
[laughter]
Not a problem for us, we're all 12.
Yeah, you guys...
You guys don't know that the other one is an adventurer
or would have the skills, but you know that each of you can handle
yourselves in a fight. You guys have seen your fair number of fights here, but
sort of always uh... kind of a quiet acknowledgement of appreciation for
each other's skills
uh... mc sullivan sort of uh... while out from behind caribbean countries
thank you guys and uh...
thank you guys very much you know that's that's
they're gonna get that advance and then some patrick and uh...
all-nighters in absolutely wonderful you cannot down the cans whenever you want
you to steve or and that was already been doing it already got right back to
not giving you know keep going
i don't get less dirt if you can that's
i think you hate you
uh...
you know that is one of the worst things you could have said to him
just let's in here i love dirt everywhere
will see that i have a
or are
and uh...
so you guys close up shop for the night
we just leave the bodies in the store
Absolutely. I bury them inside the store. You see Doug LaBerger take the back to his kitchen.
To cook up later. I'm behind him like twirling peas and whistling. Yeah. I'm following him to
go like eat these guys. And yeah it's you know after you guys leave the store. This is usually
during this time is when each of you does either you know goes back to wherever you live or does
does whatever sort of adventuring gig you're going to do.
And you guys all, three of you, have something that you're going to do because it is murder
day.
And, and I'm going to let you guys know what's going on.
So King Nardwuar's son Jumanji is turning five, right?
Very important age.
He's going to do his first kill today, allegedly.
It's a very big deal when you do your first kill as a Nard.
However, something that you would know, but only you would know, Dogen, because you are
a paladin hired by one of the warlords under King Nardwuar to protect the ceremony, is because
King Nardwuar is doing some changes to the murder ceremony, because he's trying to show
good faith to this idea of "we want to try to be normal."
And so he wants to hire a group of paladins that serve many different faiths, you know,
different values, you know, he sort of sees them all as just sort of pussy goody goodies,
you know, like he's just like, Oh, these guys are protectors.
They're basically dogs.
I'll hire them all for this affair.
And he's hiring extra security though, because you know that he's changing some of the ceremony.
You spend some time with this group of paladins now like some nights and some weekends with
them
the
Dan
is just your race doesn't mean you're you're like faction doesn't mean you're
a cat well because terrifier the terrifiers means like your character is
lame and like we'll die it's not like the terrifier kingdom the terrifier
kingdom looks at any elves humans etc as people that the terrifier beat and so
they're called scaredy cats where if you're something that the terrifier
didn't beat and serve the terrifier in the great war.
Okay.
In the past, they're called terrifier born.
So you're not, you're not scared.
Don't you don't have to worry about it.
You got damn right.
So and you see that the you're terrifier born though, Dogen.
So a lot of the paladins aren't there.
A lot of them are guys who came back into the paladin fold after they were freed as
being slaves.
So they're not too crazy about you.
But the head of the paladins has taken a liking to you, and yesterday he came up to you on
your final run-through of protection, and he said, "Howdy doody!
How you goin', bucko?
I've got a task for you, a special job.
Come over here, I need to tell you as an honorable paladin what you have to do.
It's very, it's very, a very secretive task, please.
And he's trying to lead you away from the other paladins who kind of like all glare at you
a little bit.
Yeah, I give them a middle finger as I'm walking away.
Yeah.
And there you see one of them like spit on the ground.
No, you fucking spit on dirt.
And you see one of them like, oh, like just like look at you confused like that sort of
changed the tenor of the fight.
So the paladin says, "So, so, uh, uh, I, uh, the task for you is that you will guard the
young Jumanji himself.
See, the king has taken a liking to you because you're a terrifier born and he loves that
stuff.
Oh, and, and, and he's a, he's a huge racist.
So, um, all you have to do is make sure nothing happens to the boy during the ceremony.
All right?
It's an easy task, I think.
After all, if anyone ever did anything to Jumanji, they'd have to deal with the entire kingdom.
So who would want that?
So are you up for the task?
I promise there's a huge reward in it for you.
A worthy award of a paladin.
And besides me getting my balls, not getting my balls chopped off.
So if you refuse.
You are or you aren't?
I sort of stumbled there.
So you, you, well I'll do it.
Okay good.
I'm just unclear on the balls part of it.
My balls will get chopped off if you don't do it.
that's bad. Yeah. Alright. Okay. Yes.
So, you'll do it. You'll do it. You'll do it. What? Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I said, yeah. Okay. Okay. Sorry. Standing there and
sitting there for like 10 seconds. So, you agreed to do
this and so now, you're returning back to the summit
tonight to complete the job and to watch over the boy and we'll get to that in a second.
Patrick Ciodar, after work you headed over to the orphanage for old guys, which is actually
just a front for Sticky Fingers Joint, the premier thieves guild in Trebuchet Village.
All the old guys at the orphanage are just thieves, they're not orphans.
So earlier this week you went to one of Sticky Fingers' after hours hang sessions, right?
So it's another flashback here, where everyone traded stories about their latest exploits
in thievery or just general roguish behavior.
Sticky Fingers of course provides the biggest and best stories the gang plays games together.
One is Rachel Chess, just a version of chess that was made by someone named Rachel.
There's a few classic card games like Dusty Gomer and Wave Race 64.
Patrick, you've been playing, you were playing that night Wave Race 64 on a team with Sticky Fingers, which is pretty cool.
Sticky Fingers kind of likes you.
And it's a 2v2 trick-taking game where the goal is to advance gold pieces you bet.
So you pick them out you want to bet, and you have to advance them across the river by taking tricks in the suit you're assigned.
So you had diamonds, Sticky Fingers had spades, and you guys had bet a certain amount and you're trying to do this sort of trick-taking game where it's like, "Oh, that's a spade, I'll try to make sure Sticky Fingers gets it, but maybe I'll get it just in case to build up my side deck."
It's a very fun game. And whoever advances all their gold pieces across to the river gets everything that's over there, plus 64% of the opposing team's stash that they didn't bet.
So that's the uh, the 64.
Um, now worth noting here is that you're in a thieves guild.
So, everyone's twirling their mustaches, they're making sneaky gestures.
Cheating is always fair, as long as you don't get caught.
So, we're in the midst of the game.
Uh, you see Sticky Fingers, and he's a gnome, he's a little gnome.
And he's like, he's like, "You ready for this Patrick?"
He's a scaredy cat born?
I'm scared cat. We're gonna wipe the floor with these guys
We're gonna crush him yeah, absolutely absolutely
I mean I have a few as they say tricks up my sleeve hey
Keep him up there, but then don't keep him up there
Them I was gonna show you I was gonna show you the the cards that I had
Hidden you know in the pockets of my school look nobody can hear me nobody can hear me right now
now. I'm actually whispering this is just how uh...
This is just how you give just the right general frequency. Yeah, this is I just uh...
even when I'm whispering I talk like this. Of course.
Yeah, I have a few cards up my sleeve. I have a lot of uh...
I have a lot of them. I have very big sleeves. Yeah, your sleeves are incredible.
I love them. I could fit almost anything in these sleeves.
Except maybe your balls, right?
Come on now, that's why we're best friends.
Yeah, you know it.
Casual acquaintances or something. I have no idea.
I mean our relationship is kind of
it's up in the air right now
but maybe we'll be better friends
at some point. Hey, who knows?
So we're gonna do three intelligence
contests between yourself
and the other team.
And of course,
you have an opportunity in between those checks
to do other means of trickery.
You know, charisma checks
It's
Picking up on all sticky finger signals. He's giving he's giving you when he shows two fingers sticking together than three
And then you know what that means under the table
He's doing like doing complex shit and you guys are crushing it. You guys have won three rounds already
And so that was one round left
You could do another intelligence check
19 I mean, yeah you won. Yeah, I mean you don't even need to do I was gonna say like
Oh, you want to try this trick?
You want to try this trick or you could try to do this?
No, you just like outplay them fucking purely outplay them
And they're just like, "Oh man, that's pretty good, Patrick. Gotta say."
Yep, that's the real nephew over there. That's the nephew of the great Trunchbull, you know.
Yeah, that's, uh, that is my uncle. That is his portrait on the wall over there.
Mm-hmm. One of the finest members of Sticky Fingers Joint ever.
Mm-hmm.
Yep, that's actually him sitting under the portrait, too.
[laughter]
he's just so i think it's
it's not a good thing
the a_t_r_ and well you do it
you'll do it
well you know it
the airway
the
yet there is a simple well-spoken and i had a stand like this because it's
c_n_n_ i get i get all of my head all of my weight from him
you can really hear the star power
well you know
i heard old cool dot dot i guess this is his voice
loops
it's important to
the
he sold
uh... it's so uh... you see at this point sticky figures pulls you aside
uh...
uh... patrick you are and he says
and i got you know is that just can
you know i come on now come on and maybe i'll go statue does right
you know you said you have his nose i it is very well his nose it's very unclear
whether or not he's my father my uncle it's a
i mean it's the olden times it's a
happily he could be he could be my father
and uh... i think our family anywhere
my family tree could be very fucked up
the
(laughter)
Okay.
Well, you know, you know, he was very impressive in his day.
And, um, you know, I, I, look, so, I want to help you.
Alright? And I want you to help, I'll help you, I want you to help me, okay?
That's how we do things in Sticky Fingers Joint.
No more working at the general store for you if you pull this off, okay?
Well, I, I just do that for fun.
Oh, well, alright, I guess you can keep working there after this, then.
I think I might keep working there.
I didn't know that about you.
That's interesting.
Yeah, it's fun to work with poor people.
Oh, well, heavens.
So as of Verdant, you have a unique capability.
You're terrifying.
See, most of the guys here, we aren't.
Some of us are.
You know, your uncle is, but he's, you know, sort of passed his time.
And then we got Doo-Doo the Goblin, but you know, Doo-Doo.
Oh, I know.
Oh, trust me.
I know Doo-Doo the Goblin.
Yeah, do do is just eating a poop.
This is like, oh, you nasty.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's just like, like it's just like in his mouth.
So look, I got I got a task for you and it's gonna pay big bucks.
Come with me.
He he leads you into his office.
He and you see that it's sort of it's very sticky everything there.
You just stick to it.
You like as you walk in the floor.
He's like, yeah, sorry about the mess.
uh... it's looks perfectly clean except that i have a christina no
my head
and sorry interrupt that what you're talking about here
my left not has stuck to your dresser all well
all you know how to get all of what's that could lead to a weekend yet you
have any if you have any kind of like olive oil or something like that i got a
couple of things for this so he's takes out his all of oil and his the thing he
he
a
the
that actually i'm sorry about that
yeah you know what no you know i don't know what a band-aid is but
i think it would be something like that
yes
it hasn't been invented yet
uh... he says uh... look so so here's the thing
i want you to uh...
today you know it's the the the the murder the murder day right
i want you to kidnap the kid
to manji
uh... hold on that let me uh...
let me just say
clarify what you're saying here you want me to kidnap the
the boy jumanji
i want you to kidnap the boy jumanji
now hold on let me just
can you repeat that for me because i i think i i think you've lost your
fucking mind
I don't know listen to me listen listen
Look if you want to get sticky fingers joint on the map and you want to get yourself on the map
Well, I will hold on first of all
Why would we get sticky fingers joint on the map if we're supposed to be thieves and we're not used to time for prime time
The terrifier Kingdom is a mess. He's trying to appease us and appease other people. This is the time to strike
We can we can upset the whole power balance me and you you could be on my left hand and you know
sticky finger in a writing yeah that is true that is true that is the one thing
I know about sticky fingers he holds up his right hand and it is a hook you got
it you got that cut off after a very particular very particular okay it was a
hooker then I did something I shouldn't have done you stole her money yeah
That's right. Thank you for rescuing me from that.
Yeah, you know, she, you know, and I mean her job putting hooks in people's hands.
It's kind of like kind of ironic that it, uh, that was your fate.
Yeah, well, you know, I shouldn't have, uh, you shouldn't have stolen money from
a hooker. I shouldn't have stolen from a hooker, you know, and then, then, then,
Then she said, "Well, now you're gonna be a hooker."
And look at me now.
That is exactly what she said.
I'm a hooker.
[laughter]
Anyway, look.
I think if you kidnap this kid,
look, it's not gonna, we're not gonna do anything to him.
We're gonna kidnap him.
Just show our strength.
You know? Bring him back.
At this point, we'll have so many people flocking to Sticky Fingers Joint.
We could be our own, like a nation of thieves.
Imagine.
a whole nation of them okay well a kingdom of thieves maybe kingdom right
and that sounds absolutely fair I would I would love to be a part of this.
There you go now you're thinking now you're thinking with your head okay yeah
so imagine. I was thinking I mean I hey I do this a lot but I was thinking with my
balls. Hey all right. I was thinking with my balls and not my heart. So are you or
my head. Are you down? Oh absolutely I'm absolutely 100% down to do this. Fantastic!
Okay meet me here on the night of the ceremony. It's gonna, I'll give you
some more information. It's gonna be amazing, you're gonna love it. I really
appreciate this and I'm telling you this is gonna make it so it's like your uncle
doesn't even exist you're your own man and so yeah we cut away okay shit what's
up he's not gonna disappear is he no no no no no no no no he can't he was
cursed he can never disappear all right well back to what the narrator is saying
Yeah, whatever
And we and yeah, so you come back that night and we'll resolve that as well
meanwhile
evil Steve'll
You arrive at the pool of blood that sits at the bottom of sin Gulch. I love this shit
You were here as you dip your toe in it into it
But once again you get sucked in appearing on the other side of this pool into a bizarre
labyrinth where the walls are made of flesh.
I hate this shit!
Filled with holes to fuck and things to suck.
You accidentally wandered in here the other day when you were looking for something evil
to do during your lunch break.
After wandering through the labyrinth for far longer than 15 minutes that you were allowed,
you stumbled onto a vast ceremonial room where a strange ritual was taking place, involving
bloody bald men fingering each other wherever there were holes.
ears, wounds, and even noses were getting plugged.
Not knowing exactly what to do, but sensing this was evil,
you joined in for a little bit.
Afterwards, they made you an honorary associate of the Pleasureman's Club.
And the dark priest Poonhead of the Trebuchet Village chapter
wished to assign you an evil task.
Poonhead is notable for not being covered in blood,
instead just being a half-elf with a vagina on his forehead.
forehead. You were excellent tonight at the ritual. Thank you I got a third hand.
That's that's what they're calling it now what you did back there the third
hand. No yeah I'm out with my with my chill touch hand. Oh that rest it was
pretty oh yes some people you know some girls like when you put like ice on the
You know that?
What?
No, never mind.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Anyway, girls?
Nah.
They're called maidens.
You ain't in this scene, dog.
You'd make a fine pleasure man, but your time is yet to come.
But this bodes well.
Come, follow me.
You said come?
Okay.
and has a little
who did
you watch elaborate fall away
revealing uh...
uh... an alter
and uh... thrown me to flash and has proven had sits on the throne here
faint
and he says not now my love
now you
evil steve or you are not one of us
makes you useful though
you see
as pleasure men really show ourselves in public
We are too disfigured, aka bald and horny,
and we need to take precautions to ensure that a plan works.
You see, as you know, in a couple days,
it's going to be murder day.
And what those imbecilic nards do not know
is that their precious mountain, Mount Honest Doodle,
where the ceremony will take place,
is actually a volcano long dormant.
We can't make it erupt, but we can deceive the foolish Nards into believing it has erupted
and cause massive pain.
So we need someone who can walk through the village undisturbed, take the secret path
underground up your button around the corner and lie in wait at the heart of
the volcano once the murdering begins we will tell you through this device and
he hands you sort of a stone and once what's a device we're in old times a
A device isn't necessarily, you know, it could be used.
Oh, this is a talking rock, okay.
I've seen these before.
A rocky talkie, dude.
That's right, a rocky talkie.
Now, it will, I will communicate with you through that rocky talkie.
And once I do, the scroll that I shall hand you now will reveal itself, and you will be
able to cast a very, very powerful spell that shall shoot lava through the dormant volcano,
erupting the calcified core on top of it that is built over the years, making it seem like
Like a lava flow is, you know, coming out, but it's magic.
And then you will kill them.
All of them.
The Nards will die.
The boy will die.
In the time of the Pleasuremen, the true rightful place as rulers of the Terrifyer Kingdom.
Goddamn.
Got some blood in your throat?
It's like the fourth time that's happened.
I took my allergy pills, but it just doesn't seem to fucking matter.
It's like a fucking placebo.
I'm a fucking...
Alright.
Um...
If you do this for us, you shall be rewarded.
Pleasurably.
Incalculably.
You shall be a lord unto yourself.
You'll have whatever you desire.
In the Pleasureman's kingdom.
Do you wish to do this?
Sure.
Can I keep the Rocky Talkie when it's over?
Absolutely. You'll get more than a Rocky Talkie once this is over.
TWO ROCKY TALKIES?
Now we're talking.
And you've returned again.
And you return, and he gives you the scroll now.
scrolls now sound that day and he says go up your button around the corner and you'll find
the cave entrance that leads into the heart of Mount Honest doodle go my child you shall
be one of the great you know guys you're not a pleasure but you know you're gonna do something
they can't call you one of the great pleasure man you really have a way with words I'll give
you that much. It's been a long, it's been a long day. Oh yeah, I get it.
Unless you got a pussy on your damn forehead. Oh yeah. It's gotta be hard. It sucks. Anyway,
I'm gonna go blow up this volcano. You stay sexy. Okay. Hey, you stay sexy. Okay.
And, uh, you know, we cut away from that. Uh, Lorne Poonhead returns to, uh, uh, or
priest who had returns to worshipping his uh his uh king the discharge and uh we go to we're cutting
backwards now in order patrick yoder you're back in the thieves guild and uh you see uh there's a
little crew gathered uh one of them being uh your your friend sticky fingers he says okay patrick
So, there's a goblin in the group, in the ceremony group, named Evan.
He owes me a favor.
Just say you're here to see Evan, he'll know what that means and he'll get you in with
the in-crowd near the King and the Prince.
But he doesn't know about the job, so don't tell him what it is, but we're just trying
to get you in there, okay?
Is there anything I should tell him?
Just say, "I'm here to see Evan, he's a good friend."
He'll know that that means I'm calling on his favor.
And then if he doesn't, call it through.
What if I just tell him that I'm here to kidnap a child, but I don't say which child?
Uh, well, that's fair.
To some extent, a lot of nards overlook kidnapping, but I would really recommend you don't bring
up the kidnapping as much as you can.
What if I, okay, here, let me try this out on you real quick.
What if I say, "I'm here to see Evan.
He saw a kid napping."
I-I-I-okay, I mean I- Like a child, like a child sleeping.
So he has like a code word that lets him know that like I'm calling a favor on him so if
you just say some weird shit about kids sleeping, he's not gonna do anything.
Do you understand?
I think I understand.
I can write it down so you have it so you'll know what to say.
Yeah, maybe write this down for me.
Okay, I'll write it down for you.
And just put it under that fold there.
On my balls.
Oh, right, that's where you got stuck last time. Okay.
Yeah, there seems to be...
Oh, it's still stuck. Okay, it's still sticking.
Some of the glue has
warped around
my nutsack. Yeah, I can see that now.
And it has created kind of like a kangaroo pouch
in which I can
put items. That's good.
That's exciting. That is where I've been putting
of my small things like ball bearings.
Okay, like ball bearings.
And now we're back to the day of the event where you, Dogen, have arrived.
And it begins, of course, with a feast.
You see King Nardwuar stroll up with his massive posse of chieftains of nards and orcs and goblins
and they're all like "Rawr, rawr, rawr!"
You see on the shoulder of Nardwuar is his son, who's sort of a smaller nard, he doesn't
have the penis scorpion tail yet.
He's sort of just sort of like cheering also like "Rawr, rawr, rawr!" on his dad's shoulder
and he gathers everyone around and the beginning, the first phase of the event, the murdering,
is the feast.
And you see King Nard sort of taking our war sort of takes
the stage sort of like the Lou says.
We are here today at Mount Honest Doodle summit of Mount
Honest Doodle outside trebuchet village a honorable village.
And we thank you for having us for this celebration speech
speech speech speech speech speech speech.
the feast is a time that we celebrate our biggest feast
it's not
our best chefs dishes
fresh flesh stew
flesh over rice
scrambled flesh flesh fleshy side up
and of course flesh tartar
and we will enjoy these magnificent delicacies yes of course but
we've given our chef some of the finest ingredients known to nards and all
terrifier born
not the flesh of slaves
but the flesh
of free men and you see a remote group
how could you do that all my god wire we slayings
uh... uh... this is our way of showing that we wish to grow and learn from the
free men from the scaredy cats
and i will take the first taste of this freshly prepared
brain bone broth
and he takes a skull any sort of
sips it
And he says it's awesome and then just eats the head
completely and then the feast begins.
So everyone's feasting.
Everyone's having a good time.
Dogen you see you feel someone tugging at your you're kind of
like fully encased in your paladin armor right now, but you
see someone tugging at sort of your little like like cloth
that's sticking out between your like metal gear right and
and you see it's little Jumanji.
And he says, "Hi."
- What's up?
- I'm supposed to stick by you.
So nice to meet you, I'm Jumanji.
- Hey, great, I'm Dogen the Dirt Goblin.
It's really nice to meet you, Jumanji.
I'm gonna protect you tonight.
Nothing bad is gonna happen.
- Awesome.
I like to hear that. - So basically,
there's several different types of soil
that I wanna teach you about tonight.
- Okay, I'm a kid, so I won't mind for a little bit.
Go on.
- So there's sandy soil, there's clay soil,
there's silt, peat, chalk, and loam.
You're gonna wanna get a good mix of these
if you're gonna have a successful--
- Let's go back to loam.
What's loam?
- Loam is a mixture of sand, silt, and clay
that is combined to avoid the negative effects of each type.
It is fertile, easy to work with,
and provides good drainage.
As this is happening, you just hear like so it's like
you're rattling this off and you have like a helmet on so
it's like going out.
Yeah, Patrick Yoder.
You are now sort of Stroud like sauntering up to the festivities
you see like lots of like, you know displays of past murderings
and you see like that guys being hung.
You guys just card around.
I'm like talking to somebody's walking by have my hands.
I have both my hands in my pockets
and I'm just kind of like leaning back and looking at him.
Like that is one of the best.
I mean, were you there?
Were you there for this one?
I'd say just like some villager walking by.
- Yeah, I was really, God.
- Oh yeah, wasn't it just amazing
when the wheels came out
and people just started getting rolled over
and their skulls were going out their mouths.
- My cousin got rolled over.
I don't know where he is.
I'm absolutely sorry to hear that.
No, no, it's fine.
He's a sucked ass.
Oh, well, well then I'm glad.
I'm glad your cousin was rolled over.
That's what's up, you're a pimp.
What's going on?
Thank you so much, thank you so much.
I'm actually Patrick Yodar.
I'm of the Yodar clan.
You may know my uncle.
You're chill as shit.
Yo, Trunchbull's cool.
Yeah, yeah.
A lot of people like my uncle Trunchbull.
Anyway, I gotta get going.
It was a pleasure talking to you.
I hope you have a great day.
I hope you fucking hang out.
You're the best man.
Let's hang out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just just to send a carrier pigeon to this address.
It's here.
He'll hold on.
Let me and I'd like reach into my balls and tiny pocket.
Yeah, this is a...
Man, sick ass balls, dude.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I'm a very proud of these.
I'm very proud of these.
All right, wicked.
And he hangs himself.
the
and it's like
and he he just couldn't handle the festivities are it will have to steal a
child
uh...
uh... and so you you had to the group of goblins and uh...
you see uh... evan evan the goblin uh... looks at the note on your balls
and uh... was a little pete uh...
uh... it tell toasty kia uh...
and and uh... and uh... who can't who you again and and
uh... and and i rate well
you're exactly the guy i was supposed to see this is actually wonderful this is
one of the uh... best things they could happen
uh...
i come up with what we we we got a mover or but i could be included in the
government the government group
uh... radius there is there anything they should uh...
measured they should know about
going into this
Oh just watch out the trolls will sit on you.
Ah right I think uh...
They will try to sit on you.
They will use you as a throw pillow.
Well they I I actually I have enough uh I don't think that'll be a problem for me.
Yeah and I slap my balls.
There's plenty of room if you want to hop on actually uh.
Oh okay man fine fine sure sure.
Just hop on the front there.
Okay tell tell Sticky I hopped on your balls.
Oh yeah absolutely.
I'll let him know.
And yeah, and you sort of you waddle in on him on your balls.
And yeah, you see like orcs are like wrestling while they're eating flesh and trolls are like sitting on goblins and laughing as they watch their eyes pop out of their heads.
You see, you see like hobgoblins like stringing up like corpses and just playing treating it like it's a pinata and just like laughing.
It's just like a completely debauched festivity.
And now, up your button around the corner, we have our good friend Evil Stevel.
You found the cave. You managed to make it through town.
There's no issue there. You're just a regular-ass dwarf as far as everyone's concerned.
And the mouth of the cave, as you walk in, it gets like hotter and hotter.
Basically, you can play like kind of like hot and cold to figure out where the center of this dormant volcano is.
You're able to sort of like navigate through but I'm sure I've stripped down all my way to a white wife beater and
Boxer shorts with little hearts on them. Yeah
Yeah, like a volcano. Oh, man, I get okay
You're like you're like it's it gets starts to get so hot you like unbutton the your boxers, uh, also
Just love my penis. Yeah, it's just hanging out. Ah, that's much better
And uh
off in the distance of the uh this place you see a you see something that that that looks like
is blocking your way from what you could tell is basically the center of the volcano um it's this
you can't quite make out what kind of fiend it is but as a cleric you're pretty familiar with a lot
of fiends and demons you've had to study you know it was sort of at one point a know your enemy
death domain and you hear it it's going
will you shut up I'm trying to blow up this volcano and you see it pop out and
it's this little hairy thing it's like medium-sized my PC froze whatever
scream you did but so it did do that it was and it's a little it's a cackler and
he he looks at you and he's like you're gonna blow this place up yeah this place
Let's go boom boom.
This place go boom boom anyway.
All right crazy guy.
Well, I got something to do.
So if you could move out of the way, stop being so weird.
I can't move.
We really not that big.
I guess I'll just walk around you.
And yeah, he puts his hand up.
High five.
All right.
Good talk.
Good talk. I just gotta let you go through I guess. It's too funny. He's like, "Hey, wait!"
He starts like trying to rush back towards you as you move towards the
center of the volcano. So now we move back towards the feast and the
celebration is kicked off and now it's the procession. So the procession
involves a long climb up to the top of a mountain, in this case Mount Honestoodle,
which is lined with 1,000 conquered slaves crucified but kept alive so that
everyone can behead each one as they go out. But King Nardwar says something else.
This year things will change instead of beheading slaves that are dead, you know
that are almost, that are almost dead. Speech, speech, speech, speech. This year
they shall be fully dead so we do not have to we can spare them the agony and
you see everyone oh how could he do that I love killing them when they're barely
alive I like listening to them scream while we do this and you know they're all sort of hubbub
hubbub hubbub and meanwhile Dogen so you're walking with the boy and he's like and so
tell me more about so you have to till you till the soil but what's tilling right like what does
that mean? Who knows?
Yeah, you can take it out.
Look at it.
Okay.
And Patrick Yodar, you're hanging out with the goblins.
You're walking up with them.
You see Evans.
He says so so so sticky is cool, right man.
He's the coolest.
Yeah, sticky great.
Absolutely.
Great guy.
I mean just one of the one of me one of my one of my best
thieving friends.
Wow, that's a good.
we've uh... grown very we've grown a very close in the the news in a couple of
weeks
near i think like a fortnight ago
uh... we've probably where it is perk up inside
uh...
you've got what you're thinking it this is the helmet
yes uh... a fortnight ago we were uh...
you know we were this close as we are now but uh... you know what can happen in
uh... fourteen days
Oh yeah, 14 days for yeah, yeah.
I mean I tell him I'm sorry by the way too.
Yeah, he'll know what that means, but but you know,
all right, I'm not actually going to prod about that.
I'm just here to do a job.
Okay. Sorry. Yeah, of course.
And yeah, so you keep going up and meanwhile you.
Evil Stievel, you approach the center of the cave and you see the cackler.
He says, no, no, no, no.
You see, you have to leave this place.
This place is going to blow.
What are you not getting funny, man?
I'm here to blow it up.
That's the whole point.
Oh, no, no, you're not supposed to be here.
Oh, no, no.
And you guys reach the top of this volcano of Mount Honest Doodle
that nobody knows is a volcano.
And you see the man that has been chosen to be murdered.
None other than solving the frog tied up in the center on top
of the volcano and he's like, this is I mean, I wouldn't I
should have known.
You see as you approach this whole is massive like top of
this volcano.
It's just looks like an indent of a mountain, you know, they
don't really know but it's like what a volcano looks like when it's sort of
like you know stops being active and you see them all look down at this crater
and it's like this like giant sort of like you know gathering of these these
beasts and you see the King Nardwaur go to his son and he looks to you Dogen and
he says hmm good job and you know thinking you know his boy safe a good
And you see the boy turn to you
Dogue and he says I don't know if I want to kill this guy you really have to kill him
Okay
Just gets brought down and
You see
It's brought down the Sullivan and you see the king to dress everyone
After this we can party. So let's make this quick. All right. All right kid. So look everyone I
Know I've done some controversial changes. Now. We're trying to learn how to be normal. We're trying to learn how to eat cheese and
You know drink drink wine and
Maybe play backgammon or bridge
something old people do I
Don't know go for a walk
Something besides the killing and the eating of flesh
though always fun
But just not fulfilling
We have learned this and so today
This
frog man
Shall not be killed. Hmm. Everyone's like gasping. It's like insanely instead. He will be stabbed in the leg
500 times
What the shit what
and
Now my son here take the ceremonial knife
You can do it Jumanji and he gives him the knife
and Jumanji looks towards Sullivan who's like sort of pinned down to the ground and
and
and gentle shakes after that first impact,
enough to knock some of the less sure-footed
and inebriated folks on their ass.
But then the rumbling grows,
and its trembles become shakes,
and its low rumbling a shattering hum.
And it comes on,
it comes on like a parent storming up to your bedroom.
You hear their footsteps,
dum, dum, dum, dum,
like they're gonna about to fucking tear your head off.
And you, Evil Stievel,
you get, you hear your stone,
it goes, "Now, Evil Stievel."
And you watch your scroll, it appears.
It's a spell.
A wall of lava.
It's a very powerful spell.
And you can now cast it.
And make lava flow from where you are.
But before you could even do that, all this is happening within like a few seconds, you
know, and you look below you, Evil Stiefel.
And you look at the cackler, and the cackler's like, "Heehahahah!
Hoohoo!
Hahahaha!
Hahahaha!"
smog forcing itself through a pool of lava down below.
Its speed and force makes all sound to you deaf.
It's just gone.
And then it washes over you and lifts you skyward,
rattling your skull until you're a brain-dead puppet
almost immediately.
Geronimo!
And then a primordial pop as the ground below Jumanji,
Sullivan, and everyone else explodes with the force of
10,000 dragons.
sound of it's fantasy.
Very cool.
I had to make sure it was in there.
I'm going to I'm going to die the sound of which turns the
rumbling into like it's a just a gentle coup, you know, it
sends all of you so far into the sky so fast you reach what
must be the top of all things the crest between the atmosphere
in space, you swear, but before the drop, pure blackness as your brains completely shut down
from the sheer awe of the force and all that's happened.
Then from the darkness, only a moment later, you hear the familiar nagging voice of life
beckoning you forth.
Guys, guys, hey guys, guys, guys, guys!
And you see a frog shaking you awake.
All three of you.
Guys, guys, guys! Wake up! Wake up!
I press the top of his head like a snooze button.
He's like, ah!
I don't work for a second, what the, hey!
I do that too.
You gotta stop! You gotta stop doing that! Please! I'm sorry! I'll stop yelling!
I'll stop yelling!
I just start kinda hovering my hand over his head like...
What's up?
Okay!
Can you... Can you... Can you press down on that real quick? I was actually having... I was having a wonderful dream. I was... I was on a gondola.
*laughs*
Aw man, you pissed yourself, dude! What the hell?
I think this is...
Ah, well... That happens.
This is probably a part of the concussion. I hope this isn't forever.
Wait, who, hold on, I'm a little bit disoriented here.
Which one of us peed ourselves?
You look around and you realize you're in some sort of weird fucking forest.
You see, you know, like squiggling little plants poking it out of the ground, almost
coordinated.
It looks like they're almost like singing little tunes.
Strange bugs fly by, they land on a tree, and a tree opens up its mouth and eats it.
you see a nest of birds and one of them cracks open and becomes an egg that
just sprints down the tree
uh...
you see a distant in the distance a rock with a sword in it
and as critters walk by it says come on maybe you're the true king give it a tug
come on who knows what will happen
uh... and you see sullivan's eyes go wide as he starts to realize
oh god
we're in whip it woods
all god we gotta be two weeks from the village bike carriage
all my god what we're gonna do
what are we going to eat i had a set
all cattle cattle cattle cattle
i think real quick and then a and the train to get that sort
unit and uh... you also see
another person
the prince
princeton monty staring intently a small furry creature
that exposes its throat where another set of eyes pokes out of it.
He grabs it quickly and just with one of his six legs and just eats it.
And he says, "I guess we'll have to make do."
And you realize that the five of you somehow launch from whatever eruption that was into
the Whippet Woods, far, far, far away from Trebuchet Village, far from the Claw Castle
where the terrifier kingdom is.
And you're sort of without a paddle.
But the three of you have known each other
from work for a while, and you kind of probably
got the sense that you all can handle a blade or two, you know?
So yeah, your adventure begins.
Patrick, you want to grab the sword from the stone?
Yeah, I'm going to take a look at it.
Oh, come on.
I know you look strong, buddy.
Hey, thank you so much for saying that. I'm actually, uh, I'm gonna actually I'm gonna give this a go real quick. Oh, hey
I I know you're gonna do it. I know you're gonna do it. Okay. Oh, I'm gonna do it and
You grab the sword back up a little bit you guys
And as you pull it you see the face on the rock that was chatting you up turn just
Demonic and as you pull the sword
You pull up this giant
fucking nasty
worm, slug, rock monster.
And he says, "Thanks, I'm hungry."
- That is not what I was expecting to happen.
(laughing)
- And we'll roll from initiative.
- I knew it. - Nope.
Roll initiative and take it from there next to seven.
- Nice. - Perfect.
(upbeat music)
Now, having been launched mysteriously from Trebuchet Village, and even more mysteriously
survived, our hero's adventures can begin in earnest. With a lost prince and a weird frog,
who knows what lies in wait for the gang. Oh, and what's that in the oh over there?
Is that the big bad? Is that the evil, the big evil man who's lurking over there? What's that?
Is that their hand hovering over all of planet Ebo? Oh, is that a little ratty attendant going,
"Yes, master!" Oh, who could that master be? I guess there's only one way to find out.
Listen to the show, Trebuchet Village!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
you