[MUSIC]
Last time on Trebuchet Village, Tales from the Sea-
Give it a little more than that, come on.
Okay, alright, alright.
Come on.
[MUSIC]
Last time on Trebuchet Village.
It's like Johnny Depp.
Mm-hmm.
[MUSIC]
Don't, just let him go.
Last time on Trebuchet Village.
[LAUGH]
That's so good.
Okay, wait, no, yeah, do that.
Just keep going.
Tales from the Sea-
You are so innocent, sir.
Eve homes where the three set on a long adventure to sail to the end of-
I can't keep doing this.
Yeah, I guess, okay.
Just cause of, you know, I just feel a lot of feelings right now.
Yeah.
Sick.
long battle, you finally defeated the glass ship and its glass crew members, all of whom,
when struck, would shatter and turn to sand.
Yeah, they would, they will.
Yeah, let's let, they didn't shatter when they were struck though, that was kind of the issue.
Yeah, let's just, I don't really want to re-litigate that whole thing.
Well yeah, we'll have to open it back up.
But I would like to just say.
I want a change of wording there.
I would like to-
When struck and struck and struck and struck and struck, they would shatter.
No, I think they jumped on and ball bearings and oil dumped on it.
I think that was like a poor choice by me as like a as a
storyteller. Absolutely and I will fall on the I'll fall on
the sword for that the sword shatters. I'm fat the captain
fled as his ship went down saying that the sandwich would
get her revenge. The sandwich being the the witch who was
protecting the rubbers, the were dolphin clan that's aboard
your ship. Yeah. until you stole them away to become
slaves.
the fight you saw in the distance the fabled hot babe island about a day's
journey out and evening approaching you all settled down to have a celebratory
meal with your crew who I will force you to get to know so you guys are having you
guys are in your in your little dining cabin what's for dinner well that's
something you would have to ask a only gonna be a sandwich a only a only
I'll explain. Aeoli is for dinner.
Before we do that, I do want to show you guys the map.
Okay. Pat, can you come over here? I'm sorry.
Did you already show us this?
I showed this to you.
Can we do it on the Chromecast?
What? The one that's all the way down the hall?
Yeah, you can stream it there and then we'll go look at it.
Pat, come here.
That makes sense.
Pat, come here. Just for a second.
So I will put this in, if you join the discord,
I will put this in the discord.
So, where you guys are is in VirtueGood.
You guys are kind of over,
kind of here.
- VirtueGood seems like almost a cluster of small islands.
- Yes, that's right, and Archipelago.
So that's where you guys were,
and then you moved over here.
- In between the three little islands there.
- Yeah, so you're in between them,
and then this is just the known world
as far as the Terrafire Kingdom goes.
So this is where you guys were.
- And you can move the clouds?
- Like, I can move the clouds on my map program I have.
This is where Trebuchet Village was.
So the whole adventure took place here.
- This map looks so cool.
- Thank you. - Quick question,
and you'll see it in the Discord.
- You will. - Quick question.
- Yeah. - If you zoomed out even more,
would you be into space?
- Take a look for yourself.
- Can I see?
Okay, if you zoomed out even more, would there be a like God in heaven?
Potentially, not really.
Not really.
Wouldn't be.
That's going to be a lie.
You say God is not really.
Which God?
The Abrahamic God?
Because yes.
Christian.
I don't know who Abraham is.
It's the same.
Lincoln.
Because he's a Christian.
Yeah.
All right, just checking.
So yeah, so you guys, just to give you a sense of like,
what you're trying to do probably is go south,
sort of similar to what Magellan did
when he went around the tip of South America
towards Bury-Bury.
You're trying to go around there probably.
Obviously you can still land in Israel
or the Dirtlands if you'd like to
and just go across these places.
You'll learn more about these places
throughout the adventure.
'Cause this is the Terrifier Kingdom in full.
We're finally going to give you a sense of all that.
We're headed to Hot Babe Island, right?
Yes, that's where you're headed right now.
I can't remember, did we decide that we're going to make a new theme park or no?
You guys were discussing making an aquarium.
An aquarium at Hot Babe Island?
I can't remember the decision and I don't want to spend another 45 minutes on it.
Who gives a fuck?
We're going to Hot Babe Island.
I think we should forget that that ever happened.
But first, you can ask Aoli what he's cooking.
What's for dinner?
Oh, oh, I'm cooking for you a, we're taking some hardtack and we're putting it in a little
pastel I'm adding a bit of salt and a bit of bit of mackerel and it's sort of
be a sort of... macaroni? heart attack no heart attack heart attack so aioli is
like sort of a fat stout elf who is your chef you're putting you're putting
macaroni in the heart attack no I don't have any macaroni forget how to do the
voice it's fine it's good you're back I know a heart attack so and then which is
It's just a, kind of just a wafer, kind of like a taste, like flavorless wafer, which
we have to have, but then I'm putting in some mackerel and some salt.
Why do we have, we have to have?
Just cause travel's easy.
What is this mac, you're not finishing the word.
Mackerel.
Can I, I'll just have a lot of mackerel.
You just want all the, you're the captain.
All would be great.
Listen, I don't want to trouble you to make all that, I'll just have two big cotton candies.
Well, I guess we have some sugar cane I could try to...
I don't need to listen. I don't want to know how it's made.
I don't want candy canes. It's not Christmas.
I just want cotton candies.
Two of them.
Two cotton candies.
What do you want?
There are... what's that?
That's one of the crewmates.
Oh. Hey, how's it going?
Cook him.
Please don't.
Hey, you heard the man, he's the boss.
Oh, I didn't know it was gonna go this way.
Do we even have a pot big enough for him?
And he knows what he did.
He knows why we're cooking him.
Why are you cooking him?
He's a molester.
It was only one time.
Okay, so now we have a molester on the ship.
He molested me.
And we're executing him.
While we were in battle, he grabbed my penis.
That could have been an accident.
It was an accident.
I tried to tell him.
his hand touched my penis I'd like to yeah an immediate murder it's not my
fault that the back of my hand has two other fingers coming outside of it yeah
my fault and they pinched me please don't cook me what do you want
already but I'm a lipid line okay hey the coin flip a coin see if you cook cook
cook this poor man he's flipped a piece of call which side I call on both sides
flipping a Pringles we're cooking him okay okay Pringles I'm gonna have to
cook it now no Pringle starts to run away he's trying to run off the boat he's
trying to go grab a so you guys are in the dining made all that molester stuff
up well he's already gone well is he's already gone like is he he's gonna be
you're not gonna cook me what okay sounds like nobody forgot about everything I
just said okay whoo okay and Pringle sits back down and let's cook Pringles
how close are we to hot babe Island you're about a day's journey out so like
this is like the evening beforehand and then you'll have a whole day okay yeah
all right well well you'll have like half like if you if you're gonna have a
a couple like crew members are going to be sailing still during this time like
doing shifts and so like only half a day after that can can we plan to because I
really would like to get into the hot babe island stuff it's real I'm really
looking forward to it yeah we plan to all fall asleep at the same time and
just wake up like right as we arrive pretty much yeah you can yeah I plan
that and I but I'm crossing my fingers by my back okay so I'm gonna eat the
cotton candy right and now I'm way too hyper to go to bed so okay it's perfect
- Perfect. - Yeah, so I am just--
- Yeah, and I've been jumping on the bed.
I ate all the food while they were talking.
Well, they were arguing about the Pringles thing.
- Do we have our own rooms or do we--
- Yeah, so you guys have, no, you guys have a--
- A captain's quarters that all three of you share.
- What's the sleep, is it a triple bunk bed?
Is it three doubles?
- It's a triple bunk, of course.
(whistles)
- So I-- - Who is the topmost bunk?
- I call the bottom.
- You're the bottom.
- There are no more bunks.
- There are no more bunks?
Nope, I was trying to tell you I ate all the food,
got really fat and heavy, jumped on the top bunk,
and I collapsed into one bed.
Aw.
- So that was one, so a twin-sized bed?
- I tried to make a water bed out of water from the ocean.
(laughing)
- I was wondering where you were gonna get the water.
- Ended up like a lake.
- That's the main issue of making a water bed,
is where you're gonna get the water from.
- From the ocean?
- Yeah.
I'm you know I'm not so I'm not a city slicker right like I can rough it on the
boat so I'm gonna pull I'm just gonna pull a couple of cannons together and
kind of put my top part in one you don't want to sleep in the same bed no it's
like when you overfill a trash can like a trash bag and it won't close so you
got to put another trash bag on the top yes it's like an egg like an Easter egg
yes I'm doing that with two cannons yeah yeah the boat swing scurvy neck is
helping you sort of do that. So scurvy neck is like...
Well yeah, I need somebody to seal me in.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's like, "Okay, is this what you want? Is this..."
Perfect.
"Okay, just... Alright, sleep tight then."
Here, I need a nice light. Light the candle that's attached to my bed.
No, no, no. I think... Okay, yep. Um...
I just want to inform you what that is.
I don't need any... No information. No hablas...
Okay.
Are you familiar with the...
works the melt blank. Okay, okay sure. And he goes over to the and lights one end of the
cannon. Oh hey there's another one on the other side of my bed light that too. Okay he runs over
and lights that. I just want to see what would happen. Okay cool. Cannon. Roll. I'm gonna have
to roll. Oh I don't have mine. Hold on. Yeah get your apps out. Get your character sheets out.
I'm gonna have to roll. Bruh. He left his phone across the room. I forgot that I'm sorry I was
I'm playing Dungeons and...
Dungeons and...
Oh, I'm not even...
I got a new phone too.
You have to roll for me.
Yeah, I mean I'm gonna roll for you anyway, so
Why are they doing this to me?
Why are they doing this to me? Let's do there we go there we go nothing all right. I'm just rolling damage. I hope you don't die
All right, where you at on health all right you do take 11 damage
From just like being rattled. It knocks me to sleep. Yeah, yeah, that's for sure
What was your HP at I think it wasn't let me check. I think it was like 17 or something. Yeah, I'm alive. It's fine
And if I get on here and it's and I'd actually you're long-resting right now. So
Yeah, of course you will. Yeah, I can look at so I also have access to your character sheet
That's part of why I did it. Yeah, I'll probably just lie to you though. Okay. Yeah, I heard he has one HP left
I heard the opposite you know, you're at negative one. You're a zero. Yeah, so yeah
and yeah, and so you're at scurvy neck helps you with that and then then Wayne who is the quartermaster is
sort of taking shifts with others to help a
Chart the chart the boat and keep things going Wayne's deal again. He's a half-orc so I could tell you so so each of these
These are did we were we like really hyped on Wayne you guys were friends with him
You guys talked with him more earlier on. I don't remember so each of them have
benefits were like like if you
bring back certain materials to
Scurvy neck who's like the boatswain so he's like ship fixer mechanic like he could improve the ship and added
It's like a different things to it.
Ebonhawk.
Yes.
Oh, fuck yeah.
All right.
Cool.
Wow.
There's always somebody who's going to help you out.
I'm so glad.
Yeah.
Ebonhawk reference.
Ebonhawk is Cote d'Ivoire?
Yeah.
You know, there's always HK47.
So Quartermaster, Wayne, like if you give him certain items, like he can help trace treasures.
So you'll be more likely to find magic items like on your journey.
If you-
I give him an item?
No.
and you'll you'll find what I find dirt I give him or not dirt not dirt I find
you'll find out you'll find out what kinds of stuff you'll have to give him
yes I find them I find out and then a Oli also like there's certain if you find
certain ingredients like you can give it to him and get certain bonuses for stuff
he can cook for you I give him water to see if I get any bonuses I'm doing like
a point-and-click adventure game where I just click everything and every
the combination of everything on screen. I work I'm giving him I'm ripping up
planks of wood from the from the ship and I'm handing the name cook something
with this.
Oh,
no,
I could try, I guess, but yeah, no so like like use water on Pringles.
Now, please don't, but yeah, so I'm going to expand the I guess Pringles. I
just do bzorak is what I'm doing
a borat Zorak from Space Coast Coast to Coast that's me showing my age. All that
is me knowing what this is a show those on the TV in the nineteen forties or
something. No space goes so you guys go to all that's animation style. That's
right. You guys go to sleep basically looks Hannah Barbera like it looks like
someone drew it with pencils. All right. Crap I hate my colored pencils. I
should say how did I and markers as well. Oh they probably didn't have markers
in
up and like flowers and stuff. We're trying to find Sullivan so that we can make fun of
him. No, the whole point is that you're getting away from Sullivan. Oh yeah, I forgot. We're
trying to get away from him and we accidentally find him. Yeah, your journey's sailed to the
end of the world. We might accidentally find him. Maybe if we don't die. Yeah, facts though.
So yeah, you guys wake up the next day perfectly in time for the approach of... I didn't go
to sleep. I mean, I don't know about these guys, I don't remember saying I went to sleep.
I did fall asleep, unfortunately. Okay, I went to sleep, fine. For hot babe, I wanted
to stay up all night with you guys. So I like I so I kick up I kick myself out of
the cannon. Yeah, explain this to me. The cannon cocoon and I'm completely just
covered in soot and I do a big yawn and then I went I'm doing I'm drawing a lot
of portraits of you in that state and I'm filing them away. Jokes on you,
that's a shadow. Thank you for drawing my shadow. Also I hit my I like you know
wake up and I yawn and then there's a kind of an outline of me in dust and
also I get everything dust I'm like pig pen from the peanuts. Okay. I'm face down
in my waterbed because I didn't have like a tarp or anything. Face down in your
waterbed? That's dangerous. I'm face down in the water. Really? You fell asleep with your
face down in the water? Yeah, I fell asleep like that.
That's what... What are you talking about?
Matt, are you going to intervene? Yeah, I know, I'm trying to figure this out.
So, what do you mean? I was... I had a water bed.
This is also... I'm just realizing how unlike any other D&D game.
This, like, re-remembering, just like... So, I'm gonna die.
And then I have to be like, "What do you mean you're gonna die?"
Like, never... Go on, go on. I'm face down in my water bed,
just a like a big like basically like I brought a tub into the thing you're dead
okay like you definitely don't know if I'm dead or not I'm just facedown in the
puddle like wait so did you were you like I rolled over in my sleep I'm just
making sure so like how long did you like like eight hours a full eight and you
literally just might have you decided that you just are dead right then I'm
just facedown sleeping in my head all right I guess I'm dead yeah so anyway
you guys wake up right in time for hot babe I'm alive Wayne says Island ho and
I'll say. You can say that again. Three-way fist bump. Yeah. Three-way fist bump. Yeah, you can say that again.
You could, yeah. Yeah. And then I'm gonna do that.
I'm gonna be doing more than bumping fists on this island. Yeah. You're probably gonna be bumping uglies. Yeah, what?
Bumping uglies. You think I'm ugly?
Knocking boots. Yep. Fucking that pussy. Oh, is that what that means? I don't know. Okay. I don't know either.
I'm a virgin. Yeah.
Hoppe Bay Island is-
I've only watched my uncle have sex, I've never had sex myself.
So-
Unless I have.
I don't remember.
There you go, I'd rather you talk about that.
Um, the-
Hoppe Bay Island, as you're approaching it, it has like this beautiful, pristine, like, sandy beach.
Like, it looks like a fucking Sandals Resort commercial.
I get so hard I pass out.
[Laughter]
We all just see the beach.
all of me is like oh my god I'm gonna fucking come oh there are you guys are
right this is so sexy oh my god on the beach though so you're not
necessarily wrong I get so nervous yeah oh my god I'm so each other soaking up
the Sun they're playing a game that looks almost identical to volleyball but
isn't so it's the difference oh it's like the it's like it's a game yeah yeah
What's that game called?
I have no idea what that game is called.
It's called Live Xtreme 3 Volleyball.
I never saw a game played.
Cameron told me that's what it's called.
They're drinking coconut drinks and wearing coconut bras.
Maybe they're drinking from their bras.
Do their boobs fit really good in the coconut bras or are their boobs so big that it's actually
spilling over?
What do you think?
Probably spilling over.
They probably fit well.
there any as there any coconut bras they took off that are just left around and
yeah is there any woman fully clothed no and also they're all absolutely a couple
of them who are just naked and they're like perfectly shaved everywhere are
there any men heads oh there is one guy there's one guy you'll know him his name
is Hickory you'll meet him later Hickory yeah he's chill and what is every single
one of the girls names. Since we're being so thorough.
Yeah. Sure. Are these all Hickory's daughters?
What are your moms names again? Patches.
They're all named Patches. Can they be patchy now?
No. Okay fine. No, they cannot be patchy now.
Alright, whatever. I'd like to, I'd like to, what's it?
Dock your boat? We're attacking.
We're attacking? No, yeah, we're docking.
Do you want to attack the women? In a way.
I don't want to dock with you.
No we're gonna dock with the women.
See I don't want to do docking with you.
What if that impresses them?
Only a few...
Like when girls make guys make out at a party?
I think it's usually the opposite.
Oh yeah it's like guys gone wild.
I don't think I've seen guys gone wild.
on the what's the like equivalent of a TV?
I've seen a few plays of that.
If you don't want to play late enough at night, they do commercials.
Well you guys had in Cal Godot, you guys had like TV where it was like magically drawing
every frame.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
It was recording, so it does exist.
I do like the-
Like the Take On Me music video.
Yeah.
I do like the idea of guys gone wild.
That's what it is in this universe.
Yeah, they don't have girls gone wild.
All right.
hot for guys to make out at parties in this world. Yeah. I've never been
invited to a party. But yeah, so I mean like only a few people ever get to go to
Hoppe Bay Island, like ever see it or it exists in this like amazing state where
it is this perfect place. Made in Israel. Israel that never is disturbed like
there's almost like a truce among the like universe to like just let this place
be perfect little it's perfect it's a perfect pussy perfect little pocket
yeah so as you guys approach you see how tall is every woman before we go what
how tall are all of them are most of them like over or like under five seven
they're like between like so if you need that sort of like five to kind of bitch
they got that. Facts. First time I've ever heard Patrick say facts and it was just so
poorly used. It doesn't make no sense. No, it made no sense. And no cap they have that.
And they have no cap there at all. Wait, do they actually have no cap? Yeah, they have
zero cap. For real? Yeah, you gotta go. Holy shit. And then they have like, they have like
like the Amazonian Queens. You know what I mean? They have any women like a
hundred feet tall, no five hundred. What about like a hundred pounds heavy?
Yeah, of course, what about they have a they have a woman there who has no
boobs and no ass and is basically a twig like a twig per like a walking stick
insect. They have a girl walking stick. Is there a girl whose spine is like an
shape no no hair and she's hooked up to a machine yeah she has something attacking
her from the inside yeah there's like a shy of oh sort of is there like a
shaped girl but it's like horizontal like the very hungry caterpillar there
is a caterpillar I guess that's the question is there is all traditionally
hot babes Playboy Mansion status or is it what the Playboy Mansion would be
these days with every kind of hot babes.
Even maybe they have a girl with no hair.
Yeah, no, it's mostly like I think like normative standard hot babes with the occasional...
Is it like 2008 beach party?
Yeah, it's FHM, Keeley Hazel...
No ass.
So it's like that, but it's like maybe there's one girl who looks like Jason Voorhees with
his mask off.
Yeah.
woman named Futter I have to go on a mission to find Futter I would like to
walk off of the boat on that wings is there a woman with bat wings yeah like a
woman with like a boost yeah like a white bat oh like face oh like from
Sonic no um what's happening boy you know is there a way there's a what is there
a woman with a hole like the gaping dragon no okay a woman with like a big
hammer and like pink hair okay and a dress there's no Amy I'd like to get off
the what do you say and I'd like to allow I know every woman in the Sonic
Excuse me, excuse me.
Is there like a squirrel woman?
Hello!
Sandy Cheeks.
I know you cannot understand me, but I am here to, I am your new leader.
We are aliens.
We are from another planet.
We are from a completely other planet.
And we're here to be in control of your bodies.
We're here to invade.
You see, you say this to the woman who's greeting you, her name is Juniper.
and she just kind of laughs and says like,
oh, we're so happy to have you guys here.
- Oh my gosh, she actually laughed at me.
- You're not happy.
- I turned beet red.
I'm doing the little, I'm dragging my foot behind me.
I'm trying to do advanced B-Way techniques.
- It makes me so horny that my head turns into a penis.
Actually just turns into a fucking penis.
- I put on a big top hat and a cape.
(laughing)
seeing a beautiful woman and just becoming a steampunk artist.
And I start to say, anytime she says something, I just say, no you don't.
[LAUGHTER]
That's sick.
That is tight.
We're super glad to have you guys here.
No, you're not.
We haven't had-- this is going to be fun.
We haven't had people here in a long time, not since, God, I believe,
like 60, 70 years ago.
He actually looked a lot like you.
he looks at you Patrick. Trunchbull was his name he had been here. I take off the
cape and the hat and I say oh my god. Yeah Trunchbull came here. I've been here before wait a
minute. And there's um is there a Verdan woman here an old Verdan woman? Now there
is. Yeah she's she's further in the island though you'll have to find her.
Yeah. I've got thoughts on this. But yeah, Trunchbull'd come here with his crew.
Oh my god. They left, they went on more adventures. A lot of adventurers come
through here. Come in, I'll bring you to the whole island. Yeah, real quick, I
gotta use the little boys room. And I just walk over, because we're in
nature, I walk over to use, I just go into the ocean. But again,
I'm just coming into the ocean and like a peace dream like Calvin and Hobbes
Hot babe island is immediately ruined for me because I realized when I was like 13 I called every one of these women auntie
Also, there's fish in the ocean they start eating my cum like when you give it when you spit in the water and a fish eats
It let me just take a note on that. Yeah. Yeah, so they might I mean who knows what that yeah
I'm like walking around hot babe island like Charlie Brown
when it goes because I realize I can't because all these women I mean I like
Christmas no like when he's depressed on Christmas you know the one okay okay so
like more like Michael Cera in Arrested Development when he's the real you're
sad yeah I'm sad we went to hot babe island they're all my aunts I'm
completely I'm I'm completely red I'm fidgeting I have glasses they're swirly
Yeah, I'm like, I don't know what to say. I'm like walking up to the different one. I'm like, ah,
Do you do you like water? Yeah water is super fun
Oh, let me get you some water I
Throw up more and more and every every second that her eyes are on me. I'm throwing up. Okay, she starts to look away
You stop suddenly
She looks over you start again
So yeah Juniper leads you guys through this through this like woods and by the hand
Yeah, she takes your hand. Oh
I'm riding on her back
Yeah, she laughs as you do. She's just chill. You still have my macaroni painting. I
Don't know. Maybe I'll fast a queen. Okay
Queen dips
Small flame fluorescents sort of hover magically along the path and they kind of like guide like they like they will like
are on along the path through the woods,
but also will move out in front of Juniper
and steer her as well and lead her through.
And it leads you guys to Hot Babe Central,
which opens up into this lush green field
filled with thatched roof,
thatched roof sort of like cottages
and expand outward,
punctuated by these white gravel pathways.
And there's these multi-storied buildings
made of red clay
that have a lot of different folks living inside of them.
And the place is somewhere between like, you know,
it's like kind of like Eden, right?
It's like, looks like a garden,
but it like has this kind of like lived in feel into it
and this kind of wild, wildness to the grass and stuff.
In the main square,
there's like a ton of like plants inside of it.
As you, you know, like these like plants
that like swirl and twirl and like these flowers
that like bloom and sort of like move and sway.
And the town square has like a fountain in the middle of it
that has the likeness of the Queen Bee herself.
It's like the queen of Hot Babe Island.
- What does she look like?
- It's based on the statue.
- A bee?
- She looks like a beautiful bee woman.
- Really? - Yes.
- Yeah, it awakened something in me.
I never knew, like a beautiful bug, rule 34 type of--
- Yeah, I never knew that a bug--
- I was wondering, is that an aspect of Hot Babe Island?
Like if they have monkeys and bugs, are they all like hot?
- Yeah. - Okay.
So any like, if you see like an animal swinging from a vine, yeah.
Any indigenous species is hot.
Yes.
Okay.
What about the plants?
Uh, the plants?
The plants are- Like a sexy penis flytrap maybe?
I was about to say, but the plants are sometimes like shaped like babes.
Like they look like women.
Okay.
It's fucking awesome.
Yeah.
Um, and then she's sprouting waters from her eyes in this like statue, which is like tears
of joy it's supposed to be.
Um, the statue occasionally moves and like changes poses.
Does it ever orgasm?
Uh, no.
I'm so much of the water and the water from this fountain like spills out into
these like small canals that like go along these like those like cottages and
those like other buildings where there's open marketplaces and you're drinking
from the live and yeah I'm weird I'm downstream from me these streams have
like it's no I'm right up I have my mouth on the eye hole and then those
filling me up like a water balloon pool in different sections of the the island
that are like and then are like magically sanitized and then those are always like
pool parties that are like introducing new locations so it's like Market Square
or like an arena or like a you know financial district or whatever it's just
like this like self-sustained place of just like bounty and yeah like bouncy
heard that. Yep. And as you guys approach the center you meet you see like a guy
looking at the the first guy you've seen just like staring at the statue. I immediately try to fuck him because I'm confused.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! That's the hottest girl I've seen yet. Hey Hickory. Hey knock it off. Oh, Patrick how you doing? I'm good.
Oh, you came back here. Oh my god. Yeah, I forgot. I don't really know where time goes. Yeah, so everyone's my mom here. Oh
Yeah, you want to oh
No, I just wanna say hi
Okay, I forgot my mom lives here. You forgot your father's also your uncle. Oh, right
Is that revealed sometime at some point?
No, you just sort of decided that that was a man you insinuated that right now. Mm-hmm wasn't that revealed at the end?
Mm-hmm. I thought what we do the dance not the uncle-nephew dance
Okay, then this whole idea that I had was I'm open to it's all bunk
It's total bunk complete fucking bunk. Let's let's let's just forget. Let's forget that I had the whole
Everyone on the island is my aunt joke. I still think it's fun. Okay, we already did it though. So yeah, it's gone
done. So now you can just, you can either decide you're confused. Those people
already had their fun listening to that. Or you could have had like a revelation. Let's just
start the episode over. A combination of you finally arriving to Hot Babe Island
and you having the bit of the from the other realm inside of your body that
gives you perfect memory where you're able to suddenly like coalesce all the
details in your life that goes, "Oh, he wasn't my uncle. He was my father and he
pretended to be my uncle for reasons I don't understand. I feel like it's better
if it's a big reveal. Yeah but it's sort of like too late right? Okay so we'll reveal that later.
It is true but you already knew it, your character already knew it in the game
somehow but now it's gonna be a big reveal. It's like when people don't like
they kind of know what's going on with them but they don't want to admit it to
themselves. Yeah. Is this woman, it's like a reveal, is she bringing us to
anybody specific she said um she's gonna bring you guys to the Queen all right
you're in visitors but we didn't even get to talk to Hickory I'm curious
yeah yeah why so yeah why what I'm just gesturing to him just why why are you
here oh I just never left oh okay you can just stay here I'm just gonna walk
right past you because I do not care what you have to say you got it okay
okay honestly I hope I never see you again that my you are so fucking just
annoying to me yeah yeah yeah you are what does he look like is he looks like
an old man okay he's just like an old guy you still have
gobstoppers oh yeah always he reaches his pocket he gives you a couple yeah
how's your uncle doing your father he's dead reveal that don't say it don't say
that until the big reveal. We're gonna reveal it later on. How's your uncle? He's dead?
Right he's dead. Yeah he died at the end of the last campaign. Let's wait to reveal
that. Yeah we'll reveal that too. We already revealed it. Let's do a second reveal.
He's revealing himself right now to all these women over there.
I tried to tell them you guys you don't have to leave here this place is like
untouched by time but they all want to go on an adventure who does your uncle oh
yeah yeah I was like this is it why wouldn't you just stay here
I'll be my see Hickory was part of my uncle's crew and he he was the the
minstrel what he was the part yes I sang many a shanty tune back in the day I
would sing off my body saying that of saying party rockers in the house I'd
sing a singer one two step right lots of songs I would sing I'm sorry you really
set him up for failure there you know he has to just go with it yeah unless we
break a rule but you know as you can hear I lost my voice since then I smoked
a lot of cigarettes here you could do like a cool like Tom Waits thing maybe
never thought about Earth Dying Screaming by Tom Waits you can sing that one
I don't think the babes would like it, but I think the fellas on the island would.
That's babe scaring music.
You're the only guys here. I haven't seen a man in like a hundred years.
You should...
You must be so bored, am I right? What's up?
How could he be bored? He gets to sit here and milk all the girls.
But he doesn't get to play any video games?
No such thing.
Oh, right.
Yeah, they don't let me milk the girls anymore.
anymore. What? He's done it all. That's like the whole point of him. Look at him, he's got it. Look at him, he's wearing a badge that says I've done it all.
All right, I'm gonna get the milk. You see this one he turns around on his ass as a tattoo that says I and I've seen it all too.
Yeah, he says you guys gonna go see the Queen then. Yeah. What flavor milk does she make?
Bee milk. Honey.
Then yes, I will see the Queen all right well. You know if you ever want a guy's perspective. Let me know
I'm just chillin here. Why would I need a guy's perspective?
Yeah, we are guys with three of three guys. I wonder the same thing sometimes
All right bye Hickory, okay, good. Bye. Yeah, and so yeah juniper leads you guys past the fountain
Towards another little like sort of wooded pathway. I'm milking her you're milking her
*makes squidward noises*
making those noises
oh my god it's squidward he's walking up to us
*makes squidward noises*
stop milking her
*laughter*
he just walked away
what the fuck was that
juniper
juniper what the fuck was that
that wasn't a babe
it's like he walked right out of the ocean
and just walked up to us and walked back
what the fuck was going on he was so blue
and grumpy made no sense I'm so glad I'm not neighbors with that guy he's playing
the clarinet guy looked like a blue bitch
what's under this island all right now let's go
hand comes from the left side of the screen and pulls us to the queen
that ukulele music
as you guys walk through the woods I can't address any of that reasonably
there's a big crystal lake sort of in the center of it it's like this like
shiny almost like chrome looking water
and you guys are led through it
and as you do you can breathe under this water unlike your waterbed
And you can see that there's like a hive inside,
like a large hive inside the bottom of this lake.
There's like this--
- Like on Naboo.
- And very similar to the Gungans.
And inside of that hive, you go in
and there's this beautiful palace
with portraits of babes, of babes from bygone eras.
- Like Mario 64.
And a throne.
- Like Game of Thrones. - Like Game of Thrones, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- You guys are quick.
couldn't even think of a throne show.
And you see a queen.
Like Game of Thrones.
Like, deck of cards.
And it's the Queen Bee.
Like bees.
(mimicking Queen Bee)
Like the alphabet letter.
Beaming out one.
So there's the time.
Yeah, you see the Queen Bee.
And she says to you all,
"Welcome to Babe Island."
Like D&D.
Alright, alright, toots, listen.
Who's your boss?
Oh.
Show me the real boss here, okay?
I can get it.
You're a beautiful secretary, okay?
But, come on.
Let's be real.
Uh, roll just a straight charisma check on that.
I think that was pretty fucking charismatic if you ask me.
That's not why you're rolling it.
I think it was pretty charismatic.
A saving throw or?
Just a regular, it'll just add your charisma stat.
That's gonna be a 14.
Okay, yeah.
She, uh, she sort of smiles and like, thinks it's like, kind of, maybe like a, just a little
joke.
Um, she says, uh.
So now I'm funny to you.
Oh, um, I suppose if you're...
Who are you three?
I'm a comedian.
Okay, and your name?
Stievel.
And you?
And you
That's how it's pronounced
But I'm a
Patrick
Patrick yeah
Said auntie earlier
Said hi auntie Wow
Auntie why you've grown?
Yeah
Well, are you looking for your mother? I don't even know don't reveal
No, we're trying to know father. That's not it's the father thing that isn't revealed yet and you Goblin. Yep
Your name it's Goblin. Oh
I'm Rod
Why did you come to babe island I'm Rod Oaken
basically dig I
Think we came to have if I'm remembering correctly
The time of our lives you certainly will be able to do so he is and
Milk as many women. There's only some of them who are okay with that. But yeah, you can certainly and also did
We gonna eat her. I missed so many Mother's Days. I
Have oh, yeah, I guess we should I guess we should stop by his mom, too. I
Have all I have is a bag of ball bearings for her though, but okay, so here's the deal we are adventurers
As you can probably tell.
Only adventurers with adventure in their heart can find Babe Island.
That's right.
Yeah, that's how my uncle got here.
Very flowery. Not exactly how I would say it.
Yeah.
You know, you're a girl, I'm a girl.
When you're cruising for poos.
Yeah. We're trying to get some sloop.
Okay?
[laughter]
And basically, we thought this would be a nice pit stop.
We're trying to get as far away as possible from one part of the world.
So we're trying to get to the end of the other side of the world.
You're trying to go to the end of the world.
Yeah.
Do you have like a thing we could put on the ship that makes it go faster so we can do it faster?
Nobody's been to the end of the world.
Not who's been to Babe Island.
Okay, she's ignoring me.
I don't have anything for that.
I'm sorry.
All right.
Done it.
Worth a shot.
What if we got every girl on Babe Island to sit on the back and milk themselves to make it shoot like a thruster and make the ship go faster?
Is that possible?
What if we put a woman on the front of the ship?
Like, I don't know.
Like the thing in the Titanic?
I don't even fucking know.
That's how milking... it's not always a thrust.
Okay, or they fart.
Yeah. They could fart.
The girls here at least gotta be farting all the time.
None of the women here fart.
Okay, they at least gotta be doing queefs.
They all queef.
And little pees with power. You know how powerful a girl's pee is?
Pushing pee?
That's funny.
[Laughter]
Is there anything you can do to help us?
Well, I can certainly steer you in the right direction.
We already have a steering wheel on the ship.
Oh wait, we're getting an upgraded steering wheel.
I suppose I want to first hold on um and she she she goes back behind her throne
I follow her I look to Patrick I'm giving them a thumbs up I know what she's doing
back there I know what they're doing back there
seriously they're hugging really I seriously think they it's my aunt I don't
I don't want to think about that.
Bro, he's seriously hugging her.
I don't want to think about my unhugging.
Can you imagine the whole...
She goes back behind there, I mean she comes out like pretty quickly after, so you're just
like...
I'm still back there.
I got lost.
I got my foot caught under the throat.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, lady, you're wearing the same outfit you were wearing 40 seconds ago.
She has a...
Walk of shame.
Walk of shame. Walk of shame. She been hugging. She hugged someone back there. I told you she was hugging.
Quietly chanting, "Walk of shame." So yeah, she comes out with like a sort of like a this
like diamond and she holds it and as she holds it out your stomach starts to glow
Patrick and she says I see what you should just know that the journey you're
going on you might not be able to come back from
steve-o right uh-huh what if we just go back
what if we just call the journey off you're not supposed to
be here do you know that oh yeah he's not allowed a hundred feet
within within a babe within a babe within any
babe or man no that's not babe that yeah
You've been told this a couple of times.
Yeah, yeah.
Throughout the last arc.
And she says, "I'm... but not just like here. Anywhere."
"I'm not supposed to be anywhere."
"I don't want to drop too much armor."
Real as fuck.
She looks further into the diamond.
"This is from another realm."
Are you saying I should just kill myself?
No, no, no. It's far from it.
Okay, then can I milk you?
Um, no.
Okay, finish your diamond talk.
Could I...
have a hair from your beard?
Is he gonna eat the diamond too?
The way Joey drew you, you had a beard.
Yeah, you can have some hair.
Okay.
She plucks a hair from your beard.
If he didn't have a beard, he'd be just a completely hairless dwarf.
Yeah.
He'd be kinda out there.
Wait, am I bald?
No, not-- I mean, you had a-- so in Joey's drawing,
you have a beard, and you wear a Yankees fitted--
Yeah, but what's under that?
Do I have hair?
Be real with me.
It's up to you.
Your character.
OK, I'm bald.
OK.
Damn.
So yeah, she takes that and says,
I'm going to try to analyze this for you.
And she turns to you, Patrick, and says,
it's been some time since you've been here. Do you still want to be a great adventurer?
What? Do you still want to be a great adventurer like your uncle? Yeah, well I already am one.
This is true. I'm pretty much already, I mean I've done probably a bigger adventure than he did. I
went to uh another dimension or something. I don't think he's ever done that. We met a talking toilet.
We met a talking toilet, uh...
You should be aware that danger is going to seek you out soon.
Because of the thing in my belly?
Yes.
What if I... what if I poop it out?
I'm afraid you can't poop that out.
So it's not in my belly?
Some things you can't poop with you.
That's so beautiful. Wow.
So danger's gonna... what do you mean...
What? Sorry, no, you should finish.
Who's danger?
I can't tell exactly, I just know it's coming.
This crystal here that I have, this diamond crystal, is from a realm of all-knowing.
And I use it to try to understand better what's happening in our realm.
That's how I've been able to keep Hot Babe Island preserved.
I tried to eat it.
Please don't eat this one.
[Laughter]
This is how Hot Babe Island has been untouched by the forces that live in this planet.
So if he ate that, basically all the babes would turn into saggy old grannies?
No, no, no, I don't--
And then we just walk around, they're so stupid.
stupid. You see, when the Terrifier won the war, the police had to retreat, but
they've protected us. If you destroy this, I don't know if the police will be able
to protect us anymore. I'm still, I'm still behind. I'm still... Remember there were two
major forces in the war. The Terrifier and the police. The God of Good, the
police. Your idea. And the Terrifier, the God of Evil. I'm still, I'm still stuck
behind the throne I don't realize that the Queen went back out and is talking
to them and I think that they still think that we're having sex so I'm just going
like oh yeah you've been touched by the dirt God what back there for him you've
been touched by the whole new meaning to backing that thing up. You know what I mean?
Yep. That's right. It's an entirely new meaning. I don't want to kill myself tomorrow.
This gives a whole new meaning.
You've been touched by the dirt god, no? Unfortunately.
Un-fortunately. Have you ever been to the dirt lands?
No. You haven't been to the dirt lands?
I don't know. So the dirt lands are-
No, I was in Trebuchet Village.
The whole time of your whole life, right?
Well, actually, I guess I was a dirt farmer before, so maybe I -
You might have been - I'm asking you.
Can I see the map again?
Yeah, absolutely. It is far from Nardzia, which is where -
I don't think I was there. I don't think I went that far.
You've never been to Dirtlands? You've never been that far?
Yeah, so you're sort of like kind of like an odd transplant then that you have this
like dirt worship background, but we're in Nardzia, which is like sort of the capital
of the kingdom. So you've never been to Dirtlands. This is what I wanted to know.
You could have been there, but like I want to know.
We were in - it's like the Chinatown of Nardzia, but for dirt land.
Oh.
It's dirt. I was from dirt town.
Dirt town inside of Trebuchet Village.
Yeah.
Because Trebuchet Village is the capital.
Okay, yeah.
Is what I -
The dirt neighborhood.
Yeah, the dirt neighborhood of Trebuchet Village.
Hell yeah. Yeah. Okay, cool. So I'll go back out. There we go. Okay, cool. So she says,
Perhaps you can find something there if you wish to reconvene with your dirt God. I sense a longing
You've come in call a I've that guy with that with that guy more like a shorting I don't want don't want to go
Don't want to but I secretly do I?
Secretly miss dirt really. Yep. I didn't know that
Well, you've come. Oh, we won't reveal that yet. Okay. Well, we're really
Big if you keep listening, we're gonna do all the reveals at once we're gonna do one of these episodes only reveals
Yeah, it's gonna be epic
Why did you even close the chips in the first place oh
My god, oh I
Would like to hear the Queen B. She says I
I just wanted to know where each of you stood in your adventures and your journeys, but
It's good to know. I hope you find your answers. You're looking for if not here elsewhere
We'll hear it will be able to resupply you so you guys know you guys only had like a few days left of supplies
So you can get fully restocked here
So I'll wait a gene that you can I have it for a little while until next time you have to stop
Okay, whenever the big the main thing is over. I want to do a huddle with these two and I have a plan
Yeah, she says um you're welcome to stay here for as long as you'd like just like Hickory
Later this evening we're actually going to have a pillow fight if you want to join
Oh my and how often do those happen only once every year. Oh
It's a big pillow fight on hot babe Island. I won't be watching
It's all my aunts
Do you want to participate then?
Feel like that's weirder
Probably he is weirder. I think do you still have my coloring station?
Yes, and I have your macaroni art. Do all the pillows get covered in all the juices?
Well, if any of the women are
juicing
Then yes, I suppose incidentally that happens. All right, then. Yes, I'll show up
Oh, I don't know if any of them bleed. Does anyone menstruate on this entire island?
Unfortunately, we all know we will be leaving. I don't think we were gonna make
Yeah, I mean that so that so it's over she dismisses you guys I'm huddle okay guys huddle up
Okay, so on our ship. We have a lot of barrels filled with a lot of dolphin men
Now what if we?
one-to-one
Pulled a little switcheroo
Replaced each dolphin man with a babe
Sailed away in the dead of night. Oh my
You want to put all my aunts in barrels? They don't have to stay in the barrels
We won't get all of them to you know, they we only as many only I'm like, we only have any seventh out
Okay, I was 20 of those guys or something. Is there a line I could draw around human trafficking?
We do it. We're not
shipping them
We're taking it for one place. We're taking for one place. We're bringing
a better home. They hate it here. They hate it here. They've always wanted to
see those. I bet the rubbers will love it on Babe Island. Yeah. We're actually
you know this okay fine. Maybe we're human trafficking, but we're actually
doing a good deed for these rubbers. What if we leave all the rubbers on this
island? Yeah, we are human trafficking, but we're also we're freeing an
equivalent number of slaves
exactly
so it's zero
in the eyes of god it's nothing
it's a zero
what if we leave all the rubbers on this island
and then
i get a bunch of cousins
i mean they are a part of the reason why
your supplies are draining quickly
is because you added
you guys added like
basically like 40 more people
to your boat
What if we breed them with the women on the island?
- That's what I just said.
I said I get more cousins.
- Shh.
What if we breed the dolphins
and we look at every single second of it?
- What if we just eat them?
- The rubbers?
I wanna eat them.
- We're running out of supplies.
- No, I would rather watch them--
- We're getting a resupply though.
- I would rather sneak them--
Wait.
I got an idea.
- Okay, what's your idea?
- What if we take, right, a bunch of pillowcases
and we put the rubbers from the barrels
into the pillowcases
sneak them into the pillow fight. Okay. And the babes will probably, they, cuz they like
put the pillows on their things and crap. Yeah, maybe they might. They might get pregnant.
Yeah, they would do a mommy-daddy dance and then all of a sudden, a special seed, and
we could have basically an endless supply of dolphin slaves from Hot Babe Island. It'd
be our slaves island. That's a great idea, but you have to remember that those are all
going to be my new cousins and we're going to have to treat them with a lot of respect.
Okay. You have to treat them with respect. Yeah, they ain't shit to me. Alright, fine.
And I get to be, I don't know, the de facto leader/big cousin? Of them? Yeah. Alright.
Or I know we were bringing these rubbers. What do you mean, it's a perfect game? These
They were telling them they were gonna build a theme park somewhere.
What if we put them all to work and it's a...
These babes, right? There's only hickory here.
They probably never get to have babies.
They probably are really sad.
We could make a store where the babes could go to and pay money
to have a baby with the rubber.
And then we get the cousin slave and some money.
And it goes on forever.
But what if they only give birth to girls?
Then we'll kill them.
Okay.
Just kill all the girl babies.
I don't care.
Yeah.
It's a great idea.
And then when those babies get older, they'll fuck more babes.
Yeah.
Like they'll fuck their moms.
And then we have kind of an endless...
Exactly.
And it just, yeah, it's perfect.
So we have endless...
It is lots of fish people.
Alright.
We'd like to...
You're dropping it all right to me?
Yep.
Yeah, we lock it in.
We'd like to...
You're locking it in, gang?
We'd like to go to the...
We're gonna make a sexual story.
The board of directors for Hot Babe Island, is there anything like that or is it just the queen?
Yeah, Mary Kate Ashley runs the...
Okay, we'd like to apply for a permit, for a business permit.
Okay.
Yeah.
Alright, so yeah, you guys can head to the market district and apply for a business permit.
We do so.
Okay, cool.
So you guys leave the hive, you kind of walk out of the lake and you take the path through the woods.
Same one.
Wait, shouldn't we tell the Queen Bee that we're just gonna build a slave store?
No.
Why would we tell her?
We wanna do what seems convenient.
He's trying to sabotage it.
I'm not trying to sabotage it.
I'm just trying to get the proper permits.
No, shh.
He's trying to sabotage.
Shh, shh, shh.
Let me handle this, okay?
Okay.
You get to the fountain and you take one of the little streams on a, you ride on a little
like tube on one of the streams.
That is so cute.
It's adorable, it's like a lazy river.
To, yeah, the market district.
And you see a lot of babes selling crystals and incense
and things that babes like.
- This is all completely, this stuff works, really.
(laughing)
- And yeah, and you see one of the babes,
you're sort of directing more of it,
and that's Mary Kate Ashley.
So yeah, you guys can go talk to her.
- Hi.
- Guys, I know how to talk to girls.
- All right, you handle it, you handle it.
- Hi, welcome to Hot Babe Island.
- Oh!
- Duh, we want to get a business permit, duh.
(laughing)
- I mean, yeah, sure.
Okay, what's your business proposal?
Let's, actually, hold on, let's come to my office, please.
And she walks a little bit further in,
beaded curtain to a sort of modest little office room,
and she says, "So, what are you gentlemen proposing?"
"We wanna make a store, and that's pretty much--"
- Hi, Auntie.
- Oh, Patrick!
- We're doing this every fucking time we see a girl.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
Can we open a funny store?
- Of course you can.
- Okay, we're good.
- Well, yeah, I just wanna know
a little bit more about details.
- He's with me.
- It fulfills an important need.
- It sells medicine.
- Okay.
- Yep, we found a miracle cure.
- And it's part of the service.
- It's a sexual favor store.
- Yeah, okay, it's a sex store.
It's gonna have smokestacks.
So we basically got 40--
It's gonna pollute the sky.
We have 40 of the hottest guys,
who have dolphin, in the entire world, right?
And they have agreed--
Because they're slaves.
They're shiny and oiled up.
That they are going to,
they're very shiny, waxy skin almost,
and that they are going to donate sperm by fucking--
And that's a type of dolphin.
By fucking it, shhh.
By fucking every girl on the entire island at our store.
For a price.
For a price, of course.
That's the business part.
We're not giving away free service.
Nah, come on.
Roll...
Roll awesomeness.
Roll persuasion and...
Can we assist?
Yeah, and then deception.
Persuasion and deception? I didn't lie about a single thing.
There's no lies except for both of these stuff.
I said everything right under my breath.
- Persuasion, I'm rolling persuasion.
- So persuasion and deception.
- So to assist, you're just gonna roll or just hit?
- I got, okay.
Advantage, okay.
- That is a dirty 20.
- 19.
- That's his, just his roll with advantage.
- Okay, so I got a 19.
- That's good.
- Plus two on precision, so a 21.
- Nice.
- And deception.
- Also advantage?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Let's see.
11.
- Okay.
22 on deception. You don't have to roll a single. So, um,
I mean with the 21 that persuasion she's,
she finds your like proposal compelling.
The idea of, um,
she finds it compelling.
Cause you know, it's like there are,
isn't a lot of options for those who want to have sex with,
with sort of a, uh, with dolphins, dolphins, really just hickory, right.
It was really just for people who want to fuck a penis. And yeah,
for people who want to do that, like, like, I mean,
some penis options but it's mostly Hickory who's like down. And then as far
as believing that they're not slaves, she does think they're slaves probably. So
based on what you're about to read body language wise. I use my nephew's glint
ability. Nephew's glint? Yeah. What do you do? I make my eyes go really big and I
and I put my hands under my chin like I'm taking a photo at Sears.
Well that's... Do you have that ability? That ability, yes. I do think it's cute though.
Then I put... is she about to talk and say no to us? She's about to talk. I can't tell if she's gonna say no.
I'm gonna put a bunch of cotton in her mouth.
I guess roll an attack roll? Never mind. Well just because it is like...
I don't want to hurt her.
It wouldn't be hurting her, it's just to see if you're going to succeed.
Alright, okay.
She's going to get caught in her mouth.
Alright, I put a bunch of...
Just a...
But I'm saying roll an attack roll because that is what is happening.
It's a...
I think maybe don't roll attack.
But you won't do damage.
Alright, alright.
Okay, as long as I don't do damage, I wouldn't want to hurt her, okay?
So I'm going to do...
Alright.
So I rolled...
I rolled a 17.
Oh yeah, I mean, that beats her AC.
You get caught in her mouth.
So it's pretty hard to, I mean listen, I know you're gonna say something but it seems like
your mouth is fucking full of cotton at this point so it's pretty tough to-
Why did you do that?
I put it back in her mouth.
Roll again.
She was gonna say yes, dude.
Yeah, I think you're ruining it.
She was gonna say yes.
What'd you get?
Seven.
A seven? Okay, yeah. She like moves aside so I was like, "I'm sorry, Patrick, but I-"
No, that's how we say hello where we're from. I'm very sorry.
sorry like a gnome or something yeah we I'm a gnome or something like that and we
say hello roll deception we said I'd like to be specific here we say hello
about you guys assisting him about I I have left okay and I'm but I'm also I'm
walking back in with a fake mustache and I'm waiting in line are you assisting
him Patrick yes and I got a 19 all right you're still rolling without advantage
because you would be a disadvantage 14 14 okay yeah yeah I mean she's just like
She's like I don't think that the assist no the assist was that he didn't roll with disadvantage
You don't do that shit in the office bro, oh
Right now do not give him in the finger. Oh
You know what put it all on me give me the finger all day just not patches, okay, thank you man Cameron
I'm really sensitive. He can work for himself.
Pat, let's fucking do this!
You know I'm a little bitch. Don't do that to me.
Where did he pick it up? Where did he learn this?
TV? Listen, I told my mom, don't let him watch TV.
I know, I told my mom that too.
Okay, so she doesn't believe me.
No, absolutely not. She's ready to kick you the fuck out.
I'm actually just a crazy guy. I don't even know these two.
Can you hurry up?
can you hurry up up there? I have a business idea. Okay, yeah, you come in
with your mustache. Yeah, what do you do?
So you're from before okay, I'm from a long time before
and I'm I'm I'm in my head in the door. I'm like he's he's really old. Say
you're really old is what you mean by I
you so old that you can even grow a mustache.
I'm almost eighteen years old.
(laughter)
- Wow, wow, that's so old!
- It's the oldest guy I know.
- And I'd like to start my first business.
Actually, I should say my second business.
I have a highly successful first business already.
(laughter)
- But the details are a secret, you can't go into that.
- I misspoke, curse the 17 year old tongue of mine.
the
here's the seventeen-year-old uh...
yeah uh... it doesn't have a whole the networks on her at all
okay i'd
take a permit off of her desk
to the department was you can see a whatever papers you as i take it
i start for a drawing the she's some kind she has some kind of business
paperwork
- Does he have a filing cabinet?
- I just start crying and I start saying,
please, please can we start a business?
- You could start a business, just something small,
something nondescript.
- Okay, yeah, yeah, just, well, okay, it'll be small.
- Just give us-- - No sex.
- No sex at all.
- No, I wouldn't even think of sex.
We're just gonna sell white goo.
- For women's bottoms. - We're gonna sell
to glue store.
- Like glue?
- Yeah, it glues up. - Yeah, glue.
- It helps you hold your pee in more,
so you glue your bottom up with it.
- What the fuck does that mean?
- You throw the goo.
- It's just like a, okay, it's a toy.
- It's a goo? - Yes, it's like Play-Doh.
- It's exactly like Play-Doh,
but it's really not that much. - It's a white and green toy.
- It can be used as medicine. - And we're shouting,
"Green?"
- Yes.
- Green flecks in it.
- It's got green little flecks in it.
- Yeah. - Depending.
- It's called green slugger.
(laughing)
- Okay, you win.
- I'm just trying to figure out what you should roll.
I guess deception again, or?
- Okay, we're gonna start a farmer's market.
- A whole market?
- We're gonna start a little market.
- I got an 18.
- Okay, we'll start a news booth.
- We're starting a flea market.
- Where anybody can sell whatever they want.
- We're starting, it's called Hudson News.
we're starting something called hudson news here if we just say we're starting
something else
i'm talking really quietly she can hear me she's really just waiting for
dissidents as they were starting a library or something when i was a little
permit just cross out library and writes every role or if you're a little
bit early smart that's what i've been trying to make happen
i've done and nineteen deception eighteen eighteen four
i don't remember you said world deception those four specifically if i
I'm recalling it was to say that you were just gonna sell play-doh like a toy like white. Yeah, ooh
She says okay, you can sell like a toy
Store, I guess
Okay, okay
But just just for today just just for fun. But what if the store is very successful?
Then we'll have a conversation at that point. Okay, we have work to do. Okay, we have like already
There's already a stand in the market. There's already there's already like, um, yeah
We've already told them the slaves to start building it.
Yeah, there's like a Civilization V animation of like a huge factory going up.
Yeah, and then on the sign it says "Boy Toy Factory."
That's good.
It's right in the middle of the market square.
It's amazing.
It's gigantic.
If she tries to give us any shit, we're just saying, "Yeah, we're building a toy store,
but it's for boys."
That's why it says "Boy Toy Store Factory."
Yeah.
Yeah, and you as you guys are building this factory. We're not building it. Where's your I'm drinking a lemonade
I'm cutting limes for the lemonade on the rim you hear a
Bugle horn and call this drink sprite
Here bugle horn blow and you hear a voice a the pillow fight games will begin
And next time we'll take it up from there.
Wow.
OMG.
That's crazy.
Bye!
[Music]