(Dramatic music)
So like, it's crazy that Cartoon Network Studios is shutting down completely.
They've been completely vertically integrated with Warner Studios.
- Before we start recording, I had to do a one after two.
- Wow.
- Last time on Trebuchet Village.
(laughing)
SpongeBob encounter.
- Oh yeah.
- I forgot.
- The three heroes had a fight to the death
with a bunch of apes on top of a freaking SpongeBob.
The yet pound who had been chasing them
since leaving Hot Babe Island appeared again
and was handedly defeated by Dogen's critical attack.
This beast was then swept up by a Kaiju Manji,
features Longfutt Dead, whose awesome ghostly presence freaked everyone out but ultimately
he was pretty chill about the whole thing.
Spongebob the Speeding Island then dropped you off directly onto Port Los Berry Berry,
the port city south of the academy town of Berry Berry.
You hope to find a necromancer who can bide Quadro Mudmarks, your beloved mud companion
who has followed you for some time now.
You will, however, need some help getting into the academy.
You can certainly ride the Popo River up to the town, which is more like a half-sunken
metropolis, but you'll run into some difficulty getting there without proper letters of introduction.
The magic that is performed at the academy is under strict control since the Terrifier
and Exit Territory 100 years ago.
Albert the Witch had offered to make those introductions,
but literally right before she was going to give you
the letter of introduction, you said, and I quote,
"We completely exit out of this conversation.
"It escaped 100 times, whatever it takes.
"The Witch does not exist to me anymore.
"We've already started.
"Even though you're not describing it,
"the clock is ticking, we're already gone."
(laughing)
- What do you say with that?
I don't think we meant it like that at all.
I double checked.
I went back.
I was like, "Maybe -- did I get her to give them the letter?"
And right when she said, "I could make a letter -- I can make an introduction for you," Cam
says, "Completely exit -- I won't say it again."
And then you follow up.
Anyway, that does not mean all hope is lost.
Okay.
There are several ways you can get into the Academy that you'll have to do some digging
around Port Loseberryberry to figure out how.
And I'll show you -- I'll show you the way to get into the Academy.
And I'll show you the map.
And I sent this to you in our chat, but this is, you guys are basically like here.
You're just right off of the town.
This is where the town is.
This is where you will end up.
Okay.
And then the goal would be to get into Popo Lake, which is over here,
and then ride up the Popo River
all the way up to the Academy Town over here.
- I'm gonna be dead ass with you.
I don't want anything to do with the Popo.
- So the other way you could go is--
- Do we have to go through that dark forest
or should we just not even try it?
- I think we should go through the dark forest.
That seems like it could be fun.
- You could go through the dark forest too.
That would be the other option.
But yeah.
- Could we not sail along the coast?
- The only thing, here's the thing.
The reason why, yeah, you don't have to go
through the river necessarily,
but the only way into the place is through the river.
- Oh, well let's just go up the river.
- But if you don't wanna find passage to the river,
you wanna go up here.
The thing is, it's just getting the access to the town.
That's really what it is.
So however you wanna get there, you just get access first.
- I've always been of the mind
that if I can get the interview, I can get the job.
- Right, yeah. - So as long as we can get
to the entrance of that river,
and you can get me, sit my ass in front of
some kind of superior officer.
So who's guarding us there?
- So it's a barrier that only allows
certain things to pass through.
I can explain how that works.
- So it's like a--
- It's like a bear, but even more.
So it's--
- Where, the woods or--
- So--
- I was drawing this creature.
- Take a look, Pat.
- You're gonna have to explain everything else to me.
I drew this kinda Grinch-like looking--
- That's still gotta be the worst drawing I've ever seen.
- It's not a Grinch.
- That's Five Nights at Freddy's.
You're over here drawing,
describing an amazing magical third world and I made a character for it
because I thought he would appreciate it I love what the character that I have to
keep around okay he doesn't look like a clown he has a jello he looks like a
bunch of hot dog buns put together he looks good he doesn't look bad okay so
who's here yeah Cameron so there's a barrier and he's ever seen I didn't say
that I said that Caleb said who's guarding I mean look at mine though
Who's guarding the barrier, so there's no one person guarding it. It's it's like a magical barrier here
I have a description of this I can tell you
And find my discredit got us all colored pencils
I'll never give you colored pencil. Why you don't trust us
No, we're gonna draw nipples
We're all drawing us when we grow up
So the way that you look like the way that like
And I'll explain this more when you go to the
When you can when you go to the town, I'll explain this more but port
Lowe's Berry Berry is kind of the economic arm of the Academy Town and the University which is pretty much
Isolated from most of the rest of the kingdom. So we have to go to a school
That's where you'll find somebody who can vive mud marks
Okay
So if you go up this river and go to this town, what happens is at a certain point
There is like an exchange of goods
So there's like these vessels that are these crystal vessels that are taken from the mines that are by
the Academy
Ships reach a drop-off point they account for the goods. They finalize negotiations, you know, check the ledgers
yada yada yada, trade representatives from the town
and from here meet.
They transfer the goods onto these crystal vessels.
- Has my character been here before?
I don't remember.
- You probably would have been.
One of your, your character's been around a while
and he's been kidnapped a lot.
And--
- So I might have, can I do an investigation
to see if I know the area?
- I mean, you, I can tell, what I can tell you
is that you know, you know what Port Lowe's Berry Berry is.
You've probably been here before.
I think, let me think if you would have.
You probably have been here before as one of your characters
on, if it was either in an escape attempt or on business,
because a lot of unscrupulous like magic shit,
that a lot of that goes on in the academy for sure.
- Unscrupulous?
- Yeah, it's a good word.
But a lot of those who leave the academy
and then don't like, for good reasons and bad reasons,
end up in Port Loseberryberry
because they're kind of more free to practice
what they want to practice.
- Okay.
- So I could see you having been kidnapped
by somebody here at some point.
- Or doing business.
- Or doing business here, yes.
There's a, and I'll talk more about the,
there's a black market in Port Loseberry Berry
that's a pretty decent part of it.
But anyway, yeah, so basically you get to that barrier.
If you can either, if you can get onto those
like crystal vessels, then you could potentially
slip through the barrier.
- All right, well let's just run up this,
not run, don't quote me on that.
- I won't. - Let's run.
let's swin don't let's ride him all the way up the river. Uh-huh let's
commandeer a crystal ship and then let's go into the the building. Okay cool. All
in all in favor say aye. Aye. Aye. Aye. Perfect. Do we say it in the voice? I guess yeah.
What just happened right now is is Chuggie said aye first and then we both
just that all of the I I didn't I wasn't paying attention what we voting on we
were voting on
so I I take my I'm bad
so so yeah I vote I on you swimming
me swimming up the river up the river
I go proto okay I will say you'll
you'll just wanna be if you do that you'll just I think
being in a submarine kinda mood will be ideal because
again, a lot of the trade is monitored.
- So you need the right choice.
- People know what the best is.
- And we stay under the surface.
- Yes, so if you're gonna do that,
I would do it that way.
- Yeah, what are you doing then?
- And also, as far as the entrance to like docks to board,
I mean, there's a number of different ways you can,
obviously you can go to Port Lowe's,
very, very to stay there,
and then there's docks from there that you can,
you'd have to, you couldn't really just like board a guy,
I guess. - Yeah.
- So you could either, you could do that,
or you can just stay there and then go down,
maybe find a little clearing where you can go
and then board him and then ride the river right up.
I think that makes sense to me.
- Okay.
- Or you can just go right now.
The only thing would be that like--
- Oh yeah, he's in guy mode, right?
- He is in guy mode.
- Which guy are you?
- You can still sound like you if you want.
- I could be in guy mode.
- You could be guy mode.
- I'm trying to remember, I could be guy mode.
could be a new whole guy could be someone you saw my god wait guy mode Kruger
what I don't I don't want anything to do with Fred I'm not even gonna entertain
that thought that's terrifying yeah try again fuck yes dude Freddy Krueger
the fucking shows up and I could scare them you're already a submarine with a
face that's fucking scary as shit scary I have to pause really quick to on to
okay we're back it's very Jewish just do it all right okay so I'm in guy mode
your last character Freddy Krueger we're different you would have had to have
seen Freddy Krueger and it's been established that my character is the
only one who's seen Freddy and I will walk out if you become Freddy Krueger my
character will quit the fucking I'm not kidding you will quit the adventure
because of how terrified I can get at movies.
- Please don't do it.
Please don't do it.
Please do it.
- All right, then I'm in guy mode
and I'm gonna be my fourth and final version,
which is Daniel Rabineau.
- Okay, Daniel Rabineau.
- Okay.
- So what does Daniel Rabineau look like?
- Daniel Rabineau, he walks like this.
- Mm-hmm.
- That's good.
- He sounds exactly like the guy at the hardware store
that nobody except me has met.
(laughing)
That's pretty crazy.
- And Chuggy has met him.
- Yeah. - Oh yeah.
- Yeah, right.
- It's a great hardware store.
There's two brothers.
One of them is like a old,
like they look exactly the same.
One of them's like, "Hey, how you doing?"
And the other one's like, "Hello, how are you?"
They're great.
- I think this is based on,
it's a voice based on Harvey Fierstein
and also my driver's ed instructor.
- Nice, same guy?
- No, but they could have been.
(laughing)
- Oh yeah, I don't know.
I think I remember this place.
I don't really know.
- What does he look like?
- He's four foot one.
- Dwarf.
- That's what I was saying,
was describe yourself in the third person.
- We're both dwarves too, by the way.
- I'm four foot one.
- That me up.
- I have tons of fun.
- Yeah, that's how all dwarves are.
- And I have just normal clothes on.
- Okay.
- I don't feel like describing what this character looks like.
- I'm having a strong urge to mate with you
because you are of my same species.
- I don't have any parts.
(laughing)
I come plummeting.
- Is that why you sound like that?
- No, I sound like this 'cause of I've been smart.
You're making it yourself.
Let me see.
I rip off his clothes.
Oh my god.
You can wear a strength jacket.
It looks like you're pulling this.
It looks completely like porridge.
There's nothing.
It looks like porridge.
I look like you put porridge in a bag.
I have not been taking care of myself in my old age.
You look really bad.
I haven't been taking care of myself in my old age.
Can I start using him like a duff where I go up to people and I'm like, "You think I'm
ugly and fucking fucked up and short.
Look at him."
I mean, people know what dwarves are.
- Something like the--
- I thought, this seems like a particularly bad specimen
of dwarf maybe.
- It's my memory of a dwarf.
- And you said he looks like porridge.
- Yeah, I look like a bag of porridge.
- Did you, wait, the guy who this is based on,
did you see his genitals and it looked like that?
- Oh, absolutely.
- Okay.
- Okay, cool.
So yeah, you guys are in this little cove
where the SpongeBob Island dropped you off.
And you hear some faint sounds of struggle going on from the far
back of the cove.
And you hear it kind of increasing in sound.
And then all of you roll a dexterity saving throw right now.
Thank you for adding right now.
Right now.
This instant.
Can you tell me what I got, Caleb?
Yeah.
You got a 5.
OK, plus 1.
And I got a 7.
I got a 6.
What did you get, Pat?
Fifteen.
Okay.
Pretty cool.
Where's my notes for this guy?
Do we still have the same HP?
Yeah, you do.
Oh, okay.
Oh, yeah.
Wait, is it full?
Do we do, like, a long rest?
No.
No, you guys just showed up here.
It's the same.
Brah.
He rolled a one.
He rolled a two.
Okay.
Will he get three?
That is...
All right, so you two are going to be the first to get three.
Okay.
That is -- all right.
So you two take seven damage as these feathers come flying at
you like arrows, but it's just feathers and they're just
sticking inside of you.
And you see pouring out of the darkness this like one wing just
flopping around, shooting feathers out of itself.
And you see this young elvish woman jump on this thing and try
to stab it.
We need you all to roll for initiative.
Oh God.
Wow.
Wow, just wow.
13.
Welcome to our strange adventure.
And it will be strange all day.
I got a 12.
Oh my God, 11, 12, 13?
Holy shit.
Whoa, 13 means she's evil?
My name is Evil Star.
What did you get?
Five.
You got five?
Stop cheating on the homework.
Who?
You!
Oh.
Well he's putting it right in front of us.
That's initiative order, guys.
It's not secret.
Mm-hmm.
It is secret.
It's not secret.
And if you paid attention to any of our D&D sessions,
you know that's actually some of the most sought-after information
for any combat situation.
And it should be fucking secret if it's so fucking important.
It's for the people.
I'm gonna press this button.
There's no buttons in here.
See, something happened exactly...
There might...
There's no button...
There might be buttons in here by now.
There are buttons around.
Shuggy...
There might be buttons in here by now.
By the time this is, there might be buttons.
There's a switch.
There's switches that I'm pressing.
Yeah, those are buttons.
No, those are lights.
There may or may not be buttons.
So this stout, elvish woman, she's trying to wrestle this thing to the ground,
and she takes out her dagger and she just fucking whiffs it.
She tries to stab this thing and she misses.
She goes to stab it again and she misses again.
That time she doesn't even hit where you're supposed to roll the dice.
Yeah, she just does horribly.
I mean, this is also meant to be a map.
So if you guys want to see the layout of this.
So here's the cove kind of right and here is where the feathers are.
This is that Frankenstein?
No, it's more now.
It's more.
This is the elven woman.
This is the feather.
So we are literary expert.
So you guys we didn't actually know.
I just really didn't pick your pick your figurines for this big.
I'm getting the big fatty.
You're going to get the big fatty?
Yeah.
This will be just for this combat.
Where are we going?
Where do you want to go?
I'll be the little.
As long as you're kind of like around here.
Oh, as long as you're -- okay.
Go anywhere as long as you're right here.
I'm the little.
In this space.
Okay.
So now I put my piece down.
You picked it up and ran it around.
Sorry.
I'm right there.
Where are you?
Right there.
You're not there.
You can be anywhere in these like squares over here.
Just put them down.
I guess you decided for me.
All right.
Cool.
So, yeah.
She misses and I'm going to be the little.
Alright, cool. So, yeah, she misses and she's not even really regarding you guys.
Evil, you're up.
Alright, I'm going to kill her with my crossbow.
Okay, she's attacking the feather thing that attacked you, just to remind you.
Yeah, but I don't, I mean, okay.
You can attack her too, I just want to make sure you knew that.
I knew that. I knew that.
I knew that.
Okay, alright.
But because you spoiled my original plan, I will now be attacking the feathered man.
And I will attack him with long range on my crossbow.
It's sort of like a wing that's just flopping around. Go for it.
That is a 16.
Okay, that hits for sure.
And I roll 1d8.
Now my armor is low.
I'm going to take you on 1d8.
That's not a d8, is it?
No. I forget which one's which.
I'm going to take you on a 1d8.
to
- Is this the strongest character we've ever faced?
- It's one of the strongest characters.
- Oh my god.
- And yeah, she sort of regards you for the first time.
And she's like, "Oh, good shot!"
She's excited to see.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, it's pretty much almost dead,
but you can probably finish him off.
- Oh, oh, oh, okay.
She's still struggling around.
Dogen, you're up.
- Okay, I'll run up to the wing.
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm gonna hit it with my attack,
Which is a -- that's a 17.
Does that hit?
Also, here's what I'll say.
Now that we're doing the grid and stuff,
you can move here and we're playing flanking rules
where you're going to get plus two to any roll if you're flanking.
Okay.
So that does a 19.
That still hits.
That is 11 damage.
And then I get another attack?
Yeah.
Because that doesn't kill it,
wing thing and it's not looking too good.
Okay my second attack is a, I guess a 16 with flanking.
Mm-hmm, that hits.
Okay, that is three damage.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, three.
Nice, yeah.
Okay, so yeah, this thing is like flopping around, it's not looking so good.
It is now gonna go though, and after getting like started jabbed, it's shovel, you're jabbing
your shovel into this thing.
It's an oar now.
Yeah, the oar, sorry.
I'm sorry.
Wow.
Yeah.
So just try and keep track of stuff like that.
Yeah, I should.
It's going to like sort of retch and like split.
You're going to see it kind of like almost like build with meat inside of it and then
split into two wings and then flap.
And it's going to launch three magic missiles at you.
Which automatically.
That's not a real thing.
Three magic missiles?
So magic missiles are like the most classic spell ever.
And what do these missiles look like?
Magical.
Purple.
What are they, just a floating green missile, basically?
Greenish-bluish missile with white sparkles coming off the back of it?
Maybe they're made out of wood?
Yeah, and they look cool.
I don't know why they're wood.
It's a pretty good description.
Because wood is basically what it is now instead of in the future when it's metal.
Are you sticking this bullshit from him?
So that is 15 damage.
15 damage to me?
Yeah.
Oh man, I'm at 2.
Whoa!
Don't sell yourself short.
You're not at 2.
You're at 10.
Chuggie, you're up.
That's not 10.
That's not getting exciting.
So when it does that, it's kind of like almost like it's flying, like it's batting its wings
at you, but except these missiles of light are just shooting out of its wings.
i've seen this woman
in a tree
consistent to meetings
these two floppy quicks
so
so what i've been doing a bit inside talking about the way yeah
good i'm not talking about the woman who just saved us i'm talking about the
way so i was honestly doing a bad job so
europe though uh... chuggies slash
i need some water
I need some water before I do anything.
So you did wash up on a shore, so if you want, you'd probably have to use both your full
movement but you could probably get to the shore and have some salt water.
I'm like, I'm not doing anything until I get some water.
And then I do enthralling performance so that everybody has to listen to me complain.
Okay, cool.
Describe Enthralling Performance for me.
I believe it should be --
Enthralling Performance is creatures that watch and listen to you perform for one minute.
Each makes a wisdom saving throw.
Unfortunately, you have to do it for a minute.
Yeah. Daniel Rabineau is going to do it for a minute.
So you can start doing it now, but every round of combat is only six seconds.
So you can just like start --
Why did you make it like a minute and not like 30 seconds?
I didn't make that. That's an ability you would use in like -- not in combat.
Can we edit it?
is
What do I have for actions again?
For attacks, I mean you got...
Oh right, I got the spell cards.
You got tons of spells. Yeah, use those spell cards.
Oh, okay.
Do the same thing.
I'm gonna do the same thing and I'm gonna use Dissonant Whispers.
Hell yeah.
Which is, you whisper a discordant melody that only one creature of your choice within range can hear,
wracking it with terrible pain.
The target must make a wisdom saving throw.
on a failed save it takes 3d6 psychic damage and must immediately use its reaction if available
to move as far as its speed allows away from you the creature doesn't move into obviously
dangerous grounds such as fire or hit.
What if they succeed?
On a successful save the target takes half as much damage and doesn't need to move away.
So it did succeed.
Ah fucker.
But it takes half as much damage so still roll those 3d6.
4, 5, 5.
That's pretty good. So that's 14. So that still takes a 7 damage.
That still kills it.
Describe your... what do you say to it then?
You killed the wing?
I'm completely parched. I'm completely parched right now.
I don't know why nobody is getting me any water.
It like starts retching. It's like horror. This is like the worst thing it's ever heard.
And you see this thing, and as it's retching, it starts to sprout legs.
You see the beginnings of a head start to sprout out.
And then it just...
And what are you doing? You look disgusting.
You look completely disgusting right now.
It folds into itself into this ball of meat.
And just lies dead.
Ball of meat and feathers. You immediately go to eat it?
Boneless wing.
Oh great, the food came out before the drinks.
Okay, yeah.
Amazing.
You go to run over to eat it, and the elven woman says,
"Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, please, please, please."
Blah blah blah, please please please, that's all y'all ever say to me!
Put it in my mouth.
Okay, yeah.
She's like...
What?
I suppose...
I burp out a feather into her mouth.
Thank you for...
I do it again.
Thank you for your...
Thank you for your help.
You're welcome.
I just...
Well, alright.
Who are you three? Thank you.
I'm Daniel Rabinow, and I am parched.
Do you have any kind of water?
Yes, back at the Nimrods I can get you some water.
Oh, how about you just go get that right now?
Because I've been waiting.
Do you want me to go get the water
and bring it back to this cave?
What are you talking about?
There's water all over the place.
That's salt water.
I can't drink that.
I run to the cove, and I start drinking the ocean water.
You're just eating everything.
I just start slurping up the ocean water.
I need you to roll a Constitution saving throw
eating yet ball of meat and then the nine
now what's your what's your concept my
council's a fucking fuck you it's plus
two so all right okay yeah you're able to
hold it down well actually the point was
that I want to throw it all up again you
do yeah just you know you're gonna what
kind of message that's into our audience
of young girls if I'm fucking pulling
the trigger in an episode of D&D says
- Nerds can be sexy too.
(laughing)
- Alright, first I gotta get,
Dogen because I forget his name.
- Daniel Rabineau.
- Okay, well still, now I don't like you.
Do I, how do I, do I look thin to you?
- You look disgusting.
(laughing)
You look completely, look.
- You could stand to lose a few pounds of water
and win me.
(laughing)
- I can see your stomach skin poking through your chain mail.
- You throw up the salt water and the wet meat,
and she runs over and she's like,
"Oh, thank you, can I take this now?"
I'm gonna take it, she takes the meat.
- Oh my god, you're touching his throw up.
That's turning me on for some reason.
- I've been trying to tell the Nimrods
that there have been these winged creatures
lying around all across the coast.
- That ain't gonna prove it, that's a meatball.
- I know, but it's a star.
- The ball of meat doesn't look like a wing at all
It looks now just like this with this like like is it wing shaped at all could you unfold it?
It's kind of like a reveal a wing now. It's like almost like a congealed as I was
Angel mud oh my god, that would be amazing. That's a really good idea, but I don't think we have I think maybe
You know what to capture one of those things alive. You know we or we could just kill a bird
No, or just kill it rip its wings isn't it made out of mud couldn't we make mud wings with feathers?
But that basically, but it's a Mud Marks,
but we want it to be winged.
If it's all just mud.
- It's got human heads.
- Yeah.
- It's gotta be multiple, I mean, come on.
- What's Mud Marks?
(screaming)
- Shut up and don't ever talk to us again.
- You don't get to know about Mud Marks.
- Okay, well.
- I just learned about it, and I honestly, I don't like it.
But I have to see what happens.
- Well, okay, I'm gonna head back to--
- Oh wait, I got a question.
- Sure.
- So, there's a whole school at the top of the river.
- The university?
- Yes, sir.
- Yes, of course.
- Okay, so you didn't know that, you looked it up.
But listen, what?
- Wait, did she look it up?
- She looked it up, she looked, I don't know,
she's a witch, we gotta burn her.
- I'm not, I'm a--
- Okay, you're not a witch.
- I'm a rodman.
- Fine, you're just a--
- No, wait, you're a what?
- A rodman.
- Straight Dennis.
- And then there's nimrod.
- I'm a part of the nimrods.
- Okay, wait.
and then i thought you just a nimrod okay do that do it
rodman and then we're out of steel
this thing is a way to do it
we just say we're gonna do it to see the things do it
nimrods
the way it their monster hunting company
up in
portlose very very
rather say portland
thought that places we had any evidence that i like a lot of nimrods of
important are you know much
you know i'm not gonna be treated like an npc i was gonna stop of his top right
there with more questions
well okay what's a rare what's a rapid
stamina proven in ron
why is it called the nimrods that if if it's not you're not in a rock this
opposes made somebody laugh along the way
so do you or any of your nimrod brothers and sisters ronan broadman uh... yeah
do you know how to get
into that
uh... academy
- Oh, well, you would need a letter of introduction.
- So do you have one?
- Well, all, all Rodman do, you have to pass the crucible.
And once you do, you can get in.
- So is the crucible easy?
- No.
- How, okay, all right.
- Let's go on a scale of easy to hard.
- On a scale of 20 minutes to two hours.
- On the two hour side.
- On the two hour side, how are we feeling?
- But then after, but then after you finish it
and you get the, and you get the letter of introduction,
And once you have that, then that's one minute to just vibe something from the letter.
Oh, you want to vibe?
And she finally sees the mud marks.
Just like, just kind of drooping over in the background, just comes into perfect focus.
It's just like, yeah, the frame is just totally-- All the tongues and all the heads are just
out.
Oh, he's thirsty!
We start throwing water on his pockets!
The heads are like, decomposing.
Yeah, I'm stuffing meat into the mess.
There's a crow eating one of the ears.
Get off of them!
Get off of them, Unbox!
Shoo!
Do you have crow problems?
Um, well, I mean I suppose, yes, if you...
Are a crow, is a crow an animal you would hunt?
Because we need to get crows away from this thing.
Because they keep, I have not seen, look, sometimes I'm a submarine, okay?
And...
I was just gonna say it.
And, I'll just tell you right now, sometimes I'm a submarine.
And the amount of crows that I have tried,
I have seen tried to pick through my skin.
- What? Listen to me.
- What?
- Not him.
- Okay.
- This one's weird.
- I was done talking.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- There was like no real,
the question was.
- There was not, he just.
- He was a crow.
- Yeah, right.
- That's the question.
- Listen.
So the crucible, tell me what that entails exactly.
Well, it's a trial of both combat and survival.
It takes place underneath the Nimrod's Hall
in Port Los Berry Berry.
There are other ways to get to the academy.
I mean, I wouldn't recommend,
it's not for everyone to make it through that.
But could it be for us, just by looking at us?
And maybe we all go back to back to back like this.
I mean, you handled that creature better than I,
so I suppose so.
You're damn right we did.
You sat there on your hand and excuse my language.
You sat there on your fat ass the whole time.
No, it's understandable.
I don't even believe you're a Rodman.
I think you fucked your way to the top.
Yeah, where's your-- can I--
If you're really-- if you're--
Slut.
I can tell.
If you're really a Rodman, then take out
your letter of introduction right now and show us.
Otherwise, we're going to capture you,
bring you to the Nimrods, and show that you're
an imposter to everyone.
I don't know why I do this.
Well, it's a snap situation.
She's not going to think.
I'm already walking towards her with a big butterfly net.
I'm not going to show you my letter of introduction.
So we have to search you.
No, it's not.
They're specific.
They're not just for --
I tend to be you.
Oh, look at me.
I'm a hoe.
I'm a stupid hoe.
Oh, my God.
I'm seeing double.
Wow.
You really are an imposter.
are an imposter. I think we're gonna have to kidnap you and kill you and torture you and
roast you and eat you.
She's going to...
He's just kidding.
You wanna try that?
Listen to me.
He has behavior problems.
He's hyper. That's what we call him.
Listen.
They're gonna diagnose what this is called.
Pretty soon. It's coming up.
My nephew's just gonna offer it.
In 2000 years.
The diagnosis is coming for the alchemy and shit. In a couple years.
2000 years they're gonna make a little bit of money.
Yeah, I'm not gonna lie.
I'm not gonna lie.
in a couple years they're gonna be 2000 years they're gonna make a little orange pill that
this guy can take.
Now listen up.
Can you introduce us to maybe is there maybe like a way to we don't have to study for the
crucible?
No, no, this it's it's so how do we get in?
Do we have to pay a fee?
Is it like is there no doctor?
Let me let me ask you this.
Is the crucible a play by Arthur Miller?
Yes.
But I don't know what you're talking about.
She said yes.
No, someone else said yes, but I wasn't sure you were asking.
So she's going to say, he is going to lose his mind.
She's going to say, she's going to say,
the Crucible is just a trial that you can get to it pretty easily.
You have to prove yourself first.
My cousin's on trial.
On a hunt, which you've already done.
If you get done, I would vouch for you provided you don't rob me.
I would vouch for you.
And then once you do that, you just have to go do the --
I can introduce you to the folks at Nimrod Hall.
ZAC: All right. Let's do it.
Okay.
TIM: Okay. I say okay really loudly,
and I'm behind her.
I'm wearing a stocking over my head.
She didn't notice me.
[LAUGHTER]
ZAC: Okay. Let's go.
So today you guys walk up the coast to Port Los Beriberi.
And this is some -- I'm going to give you guys some context for
the place and also describe it as you're approaching it.
So where the academy is able to fund its operations through a
combination of money its students bring in,
its mining operation in the southern Dirtland Mountains,
and its exclusive trade deals with and lordship over Port Los
Berry Berry and and and it's exclusive trade deals with Lord and Lordship over
Port Lowe's Berry Berry which the Academy treats as its main economic and
political ambassador to the outside world and like I said the only people
who can enter the Academy are those who demonstrate extreme magical promise and
then also have the money and the tuition generally to to get in and then also
getting that letter of introduction the Academy town itself rarely accepts
outsiders.
But anyway, I'll keep going.
Port Lowe's, very, very meanwhile,
is not so occult about everything.
It's a sizable port town.
It's governed by a council comprised mostly
of academy mages, former academy mages usually,
members of the Nimrods, as she's saying,
and a few merchants or influential members
of the town appointed by the Merchants Guild.
Despite being a port town, it's not so raucous
like Port Virtuegood, which is where
you guys had come from at the very, very beginning
campaign, or other areas in the archipelago.
It's an economic entity that runs like a well-oiled machine, albeit a machine with a few dangerous
quirks.
To keep up with the demands of being beholden to the Academy Town is well known that there's
a seedy underbelly in Los Beriberi that hums along with little conflict.
Whatever desire there was to stamp it out in the past has been supplanted by a need
to negotiate with the inevitable criminality of a place whose industriousness is due to
its subservience to a big, fancy Academy Town.
The port is beautiful. It's a town of full color, varied architecture,
courtesy of a rotating members of its guilds and open-mindedness of its people.
So it's got these, all the buildings, the streets and carriages are infused with sorceries and spellworkings.
Again, it's like former mages kind of retired, so they've infused it with all this stuff.
And it's a classy place, correct? No twerking allowed?
No twerking at all.
Shipping supplies ferry off of boats by translucent purple conveyor belts fluttering along the docks.
So these boats get kind of brought in by these sort of like sparkles that float in the air
and they're, then they like port in and almost like a magnet, like they fix into the dock.
It's like a really weird combination of mechanical stuff and arcane stuff.
And then there's shops in the marketplace that advertise their goods, so you'll see
the marketplace as she's going to lead you there.
The Nimrods, you'll see them as you're walking into the town or parading around their latest
I'll explain more of this stuff as you guys get into the town.
But you're in the town.
It's this really pretty magical place.
But kind of like everyone there is kind of working.
Everyone there is kind of doing something.
And you enter first into the marketplace.
And she will lead you.
Whoa.
Oh my god.
Wow.
Oh my gosh.
You knew we couldn't resist a crucible.
you can resist a bunch of things. So here's where you guys are. And there's
Gough. So the marketplace... Wait, we brought the feathered guy with us? Oh whoops, sorry.
Wait, no, that's Mud Marks. Yeah, can that be Mud Marks? I didn't know if you wanted to have a cursor.
Yeah, let's have Mud Marks. Yeah, we have Mud Marks. He's in a radio flyer.
The market, so the market has a few different places. There's a few
tents that catch your eye. There's the one that's made of bones and meats and
pelts and fangs. It's a nimrod tent that's right over here. She'll lead you
there. Then there's the hanging garden stand with these vines spilling atop. It
has those plants that are gently swaying and sort of like moving about similar to
what you saw in Albert's Cove and that's over here. There's a little kobold woman and
and her elven assistants that are running this little tent over here.
And then further down, you see this sort of like,
strange sort of orange-ish, reddish tent,
with these little children running around it,
and sort of an unscrupulous looking dwarven man with a hood on,
sort of sending these like little imps about.
And yeah, she leads you to this tent.
And maybe there's another tent with like a guy selling like iPhone chargers.
Yeah, there's another tent with a Lebanese guy
who's selling iPhone chargers and other things of that nature,
like power bars.
And then, yeah, so you guys get to this, the tent and...
- I go to the guy selling belts.
- Yeah, you can go to the belt guy.
Yeah, sure.
Belt guy, if you wanna like,
she was gonna introduce you to Nemrod's guys,
you wanna go to the belt guy, the belt guys are here.
- I wanna go to the orange red.
- The orange red tent?
Okay.
- I'm the big fat one.
I wanna go where mommy told me.
Mommy's going here.
Yeah.
I'm still with you, mommy.
So, everyone else left, but me and Mud Marks here are still with you.
Yeah.
Mud Marks is with you?
Mud Marks is with me.
Oh my god, Mud Marks is with me?
[laughter]
Wait, then I go over with Cameron.
It's like me and mommy's date.
I go over with Cameron and I'm like, "Oh my god, everything over there, but like..."
[laughter]
"Completely."
Okay.
- And not even the good kind that you can't even tell from,
you can't even tell from far away.
You can tell from far away.
- Bud Marks has a bootleg,
and a leg out of a boot.
So we'll resolve her and we'll resolve this first,
and then we'll go over where you guys are.
So...
- Can I hold her hand?
I'm like really short.
- Make a slight of hand check.
- Slight of hand?
- All right, you know what?
You said it, not me.
- Oh my God.
(laughing)
- You just, yeah, you, you're,
- Fell right down.
- She's just like walking and then like suddenly
she's holding your hand and she doesn't even know why
and you just, yeah.
- So what are we doing here, mommy?
What's going on here?
- Oh sweetie, she's like,
here, this is, this is a commander Owen
and you see this like imposing human man in front of you
and he's got these two.
- She's a lot taller than me, right?
- He's huge.
- No, she is.
- She is, yeah.
Oh no, she's, she's an elf.
She's like, she's like, I mean, yeah,
She's she's taller than okay. Yeah by good amount. So yeah, I'm like at like chest height basically like holding her
Yeah, holding up to hold yeah
And this guy you see that the beast that was brought in by the
by the members of the
Team the excuse me the Nimrod hunting group. It's a big beast behind them. It's a basilisk
Really a cockatrice. It's just like a massive one. You see he has like these earrings
he just made out of their eyes.
And you see as his comrades sort of look over at him,
whenever they do, the eyes have this residual magic.
And so they start to turn to stone for a second
and then stop, and then he like laughs at them.
And he looks to you two, and he says,
oh, hey, hey, Gough.
What, you brought your son today?
- Hello, I am me, and this is my mommy.
And basically we are wanting to do the crucible,
me and my two brothers.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
They're, they helped me today with the, well I was, I was uh.
Oh you were, you were, you were not doing too well in the fight again.
Alright.
Oh so you guys.
What the fuck, did you just say something rude to my mommy?
Oh no, no.
Your mom.
I start puffing up my chest.
Like stomping on the ground.
Is this, this guy is not your kid right?
No he's, he's not, he just, I don't know how he.
I was just gonna do a confusion.
A check?
You confused me.
And I got an E.
It worked, it worked.
Do I have a Ray of Confusion?
You may have Ray of Enfeeblement.
I have so many cards.
Thank you for noticing.
Let me look really quickly.
Yeah, for sure. So we'll go over to where you guys are.
I have a Crown of Madness.
That's a really brutal spell.
You go look through that.
We'll go to where you guys are.
So you guys are by this tent.
You see these little urchins running around.
You see this sort of unscrupulous looking dwarf.
Now he's got this sort of --
uh...
he's got this sort of you are one of the most and group
dwarfs i've ever seen shes second time we show where today
and you do you like the dress
the
will debris
the breed it right in my my cut was such a good name i really wish i had to be
tight-knit my fault yet
but uh...
uh... or to try this to bring here
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- What do you two want?
You looking to buy something?
I got something for you.
- What, I'm looking to buy something?
- What do you have?
- Wait, hold on.
He said I might be looking to buy something.
What is that?
- Chill.
- What is that?
- So, we're going to the Shady Goods shop.
- Shady Goods, I like the sound of that.
- Here.
You guys want to take a look at what he has.
Holy shit!
Oh my god.
We planned Skyrim also.
Wait, wait, go up, go up.
What was that acid?
So many poisons.
Oh my god.
A whole section for poison.
I would like to sell him my hands.
Dog pepper?
What the?
What's dog pepper?
Let's find out.
Similar to aniseed, but less potent.
You so went to go make that a fantasy thing.
Similar to aniseed.
Aniseed.
It can be used in a pursuit to throw dogs off the road.
It's a very powerful poison.
I'm not see on it can be used in a pursuit to throw dogs off the scent
When a dog comes within 10 feet of your you can't hold it by the cord the cable
It hurts dogs, it's dog pepper mm-hmm that scares dogs could be youth you youth could be useful
glass cutter listening cone
Pinring
Oh, dog pepper.
No, dog pepper.
You guys aren't looking for work, too, are you?
Cane sword.
Yeah, I'm looking for work.
Poison, basic, assassin's blood.
Look, I'll do whatever.
I'll do whatever it takes to get more money.
I don't care.
We're not looking, we're trying to get.
We're trying to do a...
Whoa, want to read this item out for us, Patches?
Sure.
The name of this item really quick?
Oil of Tagit.
Hmm.
That's not how I'm reading that word.
Well, that might be on you.
That's supposed to be on your problem, right?
Yeah.
The oil of Tagit.
I'm not sure what that is.
That's not how I'm reading that word.
Well that might be on you.
That might be on your problem, right?
The oil of Tigid.
Okay, wait, go up.
What does Assassin's blood do?
Yeah, read that one. What's that say? Ass, ass, use blood?
What the hell?
Creatures subjected to this poison must make a DC 10 con saving throw on a failed save.
Alright, I don't care about it.
Okay, cool.
Now read the bible.
I would like to buy some poison.
I'm just gonna ask. Oh, a truth theorem.
the
here
If you let me buy one really deadly poison, we can call it even and say I have zero left.
[Laughter]
I think that actually might be fine.
I'm willing to make that equalizing move.
I do want to see if it exists here.
Where's your fucking...
Oh, it's Chuggy.
I feel like I have at least a thousand.
I know. I feel like you have a shit ton in your coffers back in Trebuchet Village.
Yeah, I don't think I have a thousand.
But, yeah. Because you guys have a business.
It's like...
Okay, I'm just gonna...
Here, how much is your...
What's the deadliest poison you have?
Deadliest poison I have...
Maybe one, man.
I've got...
Purple Worm Poison.
What does that do to somebody?
Well...
Does it turn them into a purple worm?
Or does it only poison purple worms?
Well, basically...
What he'll say is...
Or is it the poison of a purple worm?
on
a lot but fair and i had her for more important and then he's gonna also get
to truth serums and give them to me
i don't have any gold left you can get to treat your own school we have that we
can cap it at that
and i'm gonna go back to join my brother
will look at you know i don't know if you know you're trying to
you look for any work that you can just come here my insurance
My name is Sherman.
Sherman what?
Sherman Merman?
It's just Sherman.
Your last name isn't what?
Sherman Merman.
No.
He looks really upset and he starts looking down and he starts thinking a lot.
I don't know what my last name is.
Sherman Merman from Burry, Port Burrybury?
I'm just Sherman from Port Burrybury.
I guess I didn't really have...
That name sounds familiar to me is what I'm trying to say.
Well, I didn't really have traditional parents.
My dad was a farmer.
My mom was a farmer.
That name sounds familiar to me, is what I'm trying to say.
Well, I don't really have traditional parents.
My dad works in an art house.
He's not my real dad though.
Okay, I don't think you're who I'm thinking of.
I don't think so either.
So um, cool.
Yeah, so you guys wanna...
Yeah, I'm gonna rejoin the group.
Come back to me?
Yeah.
The group.
Wait, I'm asking you about some work.
Don't leave fucking...
You guys almost left.
No, he almost did.
You guys wanna ask about what I am?
You said I rejoin the group, you didn't say Ann I bring the squadron.
So who's left there?
It's his responsibility.
Sherman, if you ever need a boat.
Or a submarine.
Well actually the work that my master has in mind
My master/father has in mind
Woah, this guy's his own dad's slave.
Oh my god.
Would involve some sort of sea travel.
You can go up to the lighthouse and meet with him if you want to.
I'm sure he can make it worth your while, he's a powerful guy.
This guy's a good choice.
He's on a sea travel diet.
You're gonna go up to the lighthouse?
Yeah.
Okay, so that's gonna be like--
That's what you were saying, lighthouse?
Lighthouse.
I thought you were saying nut house.
I said white ass.
White ass.
So that's gonna be a little trip.
He'll take you up on that,
but that's gonna be a little journey if you wanna do that.
So I think you, it's up to you.
You can just go, I guess, too.
But I'm letting you know that like--
Okay, I'll do that later.
Like you can either, yeah,
that would make more sense for the party,
but you can also just go.
But I wanted to make sure you knew that.
Okay, cool.
So you guys are back here and Owen then says,
all right, so, if you guys really did take down that,
there's your brothers, I guess, okay.
He just regards that you're here in the mud.
So if you guys really did take down that thing,
I guess I can let you in, have you guys do the crucible.
It could be a--
- Great, so--
- You guys like to hunt beasts?
You guys killing the other beasts?
- Oh yeah, yes, hound.
We've we wrote on a sponge Bob
bubbler
Yeah a spongebob a squidward er
What water a water a water walker?
Wait I have a drive to ring a drooping dragon. I have the king monkey staff
We killed a monkey kill a bunch of monkeys once yeah
laughing loudly all right
We embarrass people. What are your names? I'm
I panic and I go, "Blurb."
- That's blurb. - And I'm blurb.
(laughing)
- That's also blurb.
- And this is-- - I will say.
- Blurb. - I don't know how much,
news doesn't travel like that much,
but you guys did like, do a lot of stuff
in the Terrifier Kingdom.
- Good stuff or bad stuff?
- Uh, you know. - No, the riotals.
- You're Renown. - Would we think
that these people would think it was bad stuff?
- They wouldn't think it was, no,
I don't think they would think it was bad stuff.
Alright, you caught us, we're Evil Stevel and the boys.
(laughter)
- Oh, okay, Evil Stevel.
Oh, you guys are the ones who, uh,
you guys saved the prince, right?
What are you guys doing here?
- I don't know anything about the prince.
- We're trying to go to the, alright, listen to me.
- One of us died or something.
- Do you see, don't look now,
but do you see behind me the mud marks?
The quadro mud, sorry, quadro mud marks,
just in case there's another mud marks in your purview.
(laughter)
He's really, he's-
There's a trio.
You see him like really trying not to look.
You see him?
So basically, well I guess you can look at him because he hasn't been vibed yet, but
one day we want to vibe him, so we want to take him to the university so that we can
get him vibed.
And when we say one day, we mean one day from now.
Alright.
So if we can go ahead and get on the fast, quick crucible.
So basically we want the introductory letter via the crucible so that we can vibe this
Quadro Mud Marks.
Alright.
Capiche?
That's a new thing I'm trying in the world.
Yeah, in the world.
I think in many years.
Yeah, I know Italian.
Yeah, okay.
I think many years that will catch on.
I think so too.
Evil Stevel, first Italian ever.
Yeah.
[Laughter]
Alright, yeah, I mean, hey, that's good enough.
I'm not, look, I'll tell you what.
My vote, if you're strong enough, you should get a, you should get a, you should be a part of the Nimrods.
That's how I always feel.
So, sorry.
So what, good?
Well, I'm not the final say, but come on, let's get back to the Nimrods Hall.
Christ.
Yeah, let's get back to the Nimrod song. My feet are killing me right now.
Okay, so do you want to inquire further about this guy or do you want to head to the Nimrod song?
I'm asking you just because you were talking to Shurn. If I go that way will I be able to go back?
Uh, I mean yeah, but you'll just be going towards the lighthouse. You guys can follow him in that direction too.
If I'm going to, wait we're going towards the lighthouse to go.
I actually even forgot to say this, any kind of crucible stuff wouldn't happen until night anyway.
You do have time now where you can go.
This is why I was saying you could probably,
you should probably long rest anyway.
- Yes. - You're probably pretty beat up.
And then you can either do the crucible
or you can just go to the lighthouse beforehand
and then long rest after.
Like, you go to the lighthouse,
you're not gonna get like attacked.
- Let's go to the lighthouse and then go long rest.
- Sounds good to me. - Just so we have the--
- That sounds just about decent to me.
- Cool.
So yeah, you guys are gonna head towards the lighthouse now, so Sherman's gonna help lead the way.
You go on this like, sort of, this dirt road, and you see as you're walking down that because Sherman is with you,
you see these like, little like, bandit looking guys popping their heads out.
You see Sherman like, kinda like, like shush them and tell them aside, like they're good.
So if you guys had gone up here without Sherman, you would've just like been...
- Gotten owned. - Yeah, you would've gotten jumped.
And he takes you to the lighthouse.
You see this lighthouse, it's not like what a light,
it's not really like a lighthouse.
I mean, it's like a refashioned sort of wizard's tower
into a lighthouse.
And Sherman leads you there and he says,
he says, "We just gotta, one second."
And he presses a little, a glyph on the side of the tower
and you hear echoing in all of your minds,
"Yeah, come in."
And he's like, "All right, we can go."
I just had the weirdest daydream guys.
- What was it? - It was so short.
And there's no pictures.
- Oh my God.
- I think something evil is happening.
- And the door to the lighthouse,
to the stairway slides up, stone against stone.
You guys climb up the tower into this warlock's lair.
And you see this tall human man, blond hair, blue eyes, very handsome looking guy.
I don't like him already.
And he's using his hand to shine a beam over.
He says, "Hey Sherman, Sherman, come here, take a look at this."
And he calls Sherman over, and you guys can kind of see this too.
You see he's like, he starts saying, "Now look, see, so if I move the light here."
I
You just see these two silently.
Giant oil drum explosion.
Yes, like just these ships collide and you see them.
Holy fuck.
And he says, "Sherman, go get the guys to --"
That was awesome.
"Let's get some of that."
And Sherman, like sort of a --
He goes, "Yes, father, master."
And he goes down the stairs and you see out the window,
on the other side of the other window,
there's like two windows, one out to the sea,
one out to where he probably saw you guys coming in.
You see all those little bandits kind of come out of the woods
and go towards where that ship crash happened.
And he says to you, he turns around
and you can sort of appreciate like how like,
like, like handsome this guy is.
He's like, it's like weird.
And he says, "Oh, what can I do for you fellas?"
- I don't know.
Sherman told me you had a job for us.
I honestly, I think. - Oh, okay.
- All I care about is money. - We want to do the crucible.
My name is Condoleezza Carlo.
What's so funny?
and
do you have any i asked him if you know i think i remember that he started to
you're thinking of you're thinking of you jean merman
from bostonia yep
sorry he has those funny slides well it's not let's try not to mention
sherman's last name is that's what i think it's a pick something so i don't
really want to know what this means deal with him getting in at the latest or
uh...
so i do have something
and the sherman that that you guys so you see your pretty
capable we are evil steve all
is a lower and uh... daniel randall you'll rabbit he's a new it is whatever
we're about to do gonna interfere with their ability to take a long rest
cuz i need a long rest i don't know how to go to the other side of the state
not at all not look at all of you don't
look as long as you don't do anything to me
welcome to stay i just wanted i just wanted
positive
of song
uh... i need a long rest
I need a long rest.
Okay.
HP is not the best.
I'm going to throw that into the ether and then we're just going to forget about it for
a little bit.
Uh huh.
Nice.
Cool.
I love when you throw shit into the ether.
Yeah.
Um, yeah sure you can rest here it's no problem.
That was my cap.
But what, listen, I want a letter of introduction, an introductory letter to the Academy of Arts
and Sciences.
Do you have a viver or a necromancer?
Oh, I have a necromancer.
Whoa!
Then we don't even have to do the damn crucible!
No, I mean, I don't know why you would join them with those fucking morons over there.
They're nimrods, they're not morons.
Okay, so...
They're actually rodmans.
Yeah, they're rodmans.
I'm standing in the corner and I hold my finger up in the air.
Yeah, they're both. Somebody thought it was funny.
So we don't need the introduction...
You asking me to skip school? I'm fucking meet- I'm meeting you right there.
I don't want to- I want to skip school.
Evil Stievel, it's a pleasure to meet you.
Shake my hand, look me in the eyes.
I will, yeah, he does shake your hand. We can shake hands.
You want to shake hands, Caleb?
Oh my god. Why is your hand so blue?
Why is your hand so cold?
Mine's wet.
Can a necromancer vibe things?
Yes, the ones I know can.
Mud even?
Mud? Yeah, that's not an issue.
You'll probably need some-
Probably need four heads or something on it.
Well, you got that, but you'll probably need some more organic material to make, you know, lungs, heart, a little bit more, uh...
Okay.
It's just gonna take a little- but, but, but, but, but-
But we can get those.
We can get that for you at the academy. Now, now, here's the thing.
It's gonna have to be a familiar tit for tat, right? So you'll have to do a little bit of something for me.
Let's do this.
But it's not a crucible, and it's not anything fucking stupid like that.
What you'll do for me will involve...
Are you a changeling?
- Yeah, so usually I'm a giant submarine, okay?
And I have three other, this is one of them.
This is Daniel Crabbeano.
And then I'm also Mr. Cutie Pop Superstar.
- Okay.
- And then G'day Cunt Hole.
- And then you're a submarine.
Okay, this is--
- He's the guy who replaced, you remember Patrick Yodar
from all the stories about us?
Yeah, of course, I know that there's a...
He basically died.
You're kidding.
Trunchbull's nephew's dead?
Trunchbull, oh my, wait, so you all know Trunchbull.
Everyone knows Trunchbull.
He's one of the greatest adventurers in Terran Fire history.
He's one of your friends?
Well, look at, look closely, look closely at this mud box.
There's gonna be a familiar face.
It's Patrick Chiodar's head.
It just melted.
Also, you fed, you ate his head.
Did I?
Yeah, you guys threw his head into your mouth.
Wait, can we get a head count real quick?
Who's on the mud mark?
It's three, it's three, and three five out of ten women.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, yeah.
(dramatic music)
Okay, wait.
(laughing)
Oh, whoa!
Yeah.
That does look like him.
Hold on, did you see how big my mouth just got?
Yeah, it was cool.
That was cool.
Look.
I've been holding onto this for such an occasion.
So maybe we can vibe him while we're at it.
We're gonna vibe.
Oh yeah.
Since we still got the head.
I never thought about that. I do actually really miss him.
Yeah, this new guy. I fucking hate this new guy.
Well you could vibe him, but yeah sure, why not.
I mean look, once you get in touch with my people.
We could put him in a jar like that show, Pastorama.
Pretty good.
Damn.
Well now we have to do it.
Now it has to happen.
So what I'll need you to do
Damn it
So
In the other direction from the Academy there's another tower now
You guys familiar with the fog yeah like it like a
So here's what you guys would be you guys would be familiar with the fact that you guys have seen the world map
There's all this like white fog around where the terrified kingdom is right? I remember this he says um
now
There is more beyond that fog people go into the fog
They never come back or they're too afraid to go into the fog
But I know for a fact that there's more to this world
Now, I'm not going to send you just there.
Since your deeds, which helped destabilize the Terrifier Kingdom, so I do appreciate that,
we've been able to make some interesting developments in Bering Beria.
Among those has been able to get kind of increased support within the court to make these kinds
of explorations.
The only thing is that there's another faction inside the court that wants to get there first.
So I need you to all go there.
Go down to this tower.
I thought this was just going to be like us picking up a package or something.
Oh no.
No.
Fuck.
I mean look, I can find other people to do it.
No.
Because I don't want to go to school today.
Yeah, we're going to do it for you.
Alright, that's what I like to hear.
And here's the thing, unlike the crucible which will get you a letter of introduction,
I will get you passes that allow you to be considered visiting professors at the academy.
Oh my god, we get to cut to the front of the line with the people in wheelchairs.
Yes.
Oh my god.
Just a little bit more elbow grease, okay?
And then you get, you will get full access to the academy in your next campaign.
And with tenure.
Well, I can't guarantee tenure.
You'll have to show some sort of, you'll have to teach a class every once in a while to
maintain the illusion, but I have enough people in there.
- Trust me, I have a lot of classes I could teach.
- I believe that. - I have.
- Just looking at you.
- He taught a class on student-teacher relationships.
- Are your genitals just a smudge?
- My genitals look like when you spill an ink quill.
- I saw it earlier, it's like cracking an egg
into a deep fryer.
Yeah, it's really bad.
- It's foamy, it looks like crap.
And also, it smells.
- I can also confirm that it smells.
- It smells terrible.
- Well, I will demonstrate how much it smells once again.
- Ready?
I'm gonna pull the zipper down.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- I'm gonna pull the zipper down on my pants.
We're just gonna sit here and just smell it for a second.
- All right, so we can just continue talking.
Just if your eyes are start watering, you know why.
- You'll know why, so go on.
- I think you're probably the perfect guys
for this job, Alex.
(laughing)
So the thing is what you need to know about the group,
all I know about the group is that you'll be
trying to interfere or hunt,
depends on your sort of,
how you define interfering and hunting,
is that they used to be a member of a thieves guild
and have since been appointed to the court
as a kind of espionage arm.
So you guys would know that this one is taking the lead.
- Yep.
Whose group was basically made that was trunchbulls group organization. Yeah. Yeah the
We have a head up actually trunchbulls little boys head we do have trench balls only
Boys head premium meats
Hold on I'm trying to find what we called it
No, I put in my other notes
Check out this check out the just look at this quote
Feel good ink
Etnies yeah, and then mirrors reflect the body music reflects a soul CP CP
I
Wrote some stuff on my folder to my wallet when I grow up
Just some stuff about when I grow up
I also drew a picture of my mansion when I'll grow up where I'll let your wallet
I'll look like my no my wallet when I grew up in 2014. Oh
Okay, and I did a whole Sudoku on my 60 tricksters eating chicky tinders, and they're mixing genders with their
120 fingers okay, I remember that I remember that now that was trunchbulls group which became sticky to cry which became
- It's a bad pentagram.
- No, it's good.
- And it became Sticky Fingers Group,
Sticky Fingers Thieves Guild.
And then that--
- They became what?
- Sticky Fingers Group.
- That's what I first said.
- Sticky Fingers--
- But then what did they become?
- Sticky--
(laughing)
- Go ahead, go ahead.
I forgot the first time, you need to say it again.
- Sticky Fingers Thieves Guild.
And then that, which you were a part of,
Well not you, Patrick was, RIP.
And then, because at that point,
Trunchbull was kind of just a figurehead.
And then they became part of the espionage arm
of the Terrafire Kingdom with a disempowered king,
Nardwar, who now is just like, kind of struggling
with the power.
And so this guy wants you basically to go out
and interfere with Stinkyfinger's operation
to get to the New World before the people in Beriberi do.
So Beriberi is technically a part of the Terrafire Kingdom.
were annexed. But there's sort of a mutual understanding that they are scared of
Beriberi because they do magic and Beriberi does not want to deal with these
fucking stupid like oafs in the Terrafire Kingdom. However, Ola, who you guys know,
your business partner, who developed magic among orcs for the first time, has
sort of changed the power balance in the Terrafire Kingdom's
favor because now they could do magic too. I get you. But then things got
destabilized after you guys kind of like came in there, saved the prince, but also
revealed King Nardwuar's, you know, he was mad. And so now there's kind of this
opportunity. Okay. Is what's happening. You guys would have some contextual
understanding. Well then let's fucking do it. All right, well. Yeah, let's go. You're
welcome to stay here for the night and then I'll give you guys, I guess, proper
permits to use the docks and then, yeah, be on your way. And just let me know what
you find. And you don't have to, look, if it's too hefty of an operation, there's
too much stuff going on, don't worry, just tell me what you find, you can come right back.
Alright, how does that sound?
Sounds great!
Alright, so we leave tomorrow?
Uh, yeah, leave tomorrow.
Stay here for the night, or you can go to the tavern and stay there.
That sounds good.
And you know what?
I'm gonna turn back into a submarine right now.
Oh, well let's, let's, um, are you gonna do that?
Right in your office.
A 30 foot long submarine.
- He doesn't do that, he just expands the office
extra dimensionally, and he says,
"I can only do this for an hour,
"so I need you to turn back, please."
- Okay, then I'm not gonna do it then.
I wanted to be, I wanted to create a--
- That is a spell I gave him.
- Two holes in the wall.
- I wasn't thinking you would do that,
but I did give him that spell,
and I'm thinking I must have been thinking
that you were gonna do some fucking shit.
- How do you think about this,
How do you think that far ahead when you're doing all this?
Just with every single person you think,
"How, they're gonna ruin this so badly."
- I can't predict all of it.
That's why this happens.
Sometimes it doesn't work out that way.
I just did a lot of prep for this
'cause I knew it was gonna be a big, like,
this was like a big, like,
there's multiple ways you can get to where you need to go.
And so I just did a lot of prep.
And so in doing that,
I just was like thinking of everything.
- Okay.
- But a lot of times I'm just like,
I don't know what this session's gonna be,
so I can't prep for everything.
And then that's when you guys completely run ragged.
We do our best work.
Yes.
Sometimes, yeah.
I would say so.
I fart.
Okay.
Sorry.
Time.
Julio, keep this in.
It's an hour and nine minutes.
Okay, cool.
I probably need to wrap up in the next ten.
Me too.
I have to go to the pet store.
I forgot to buy a bunch of cat food.
Okay.
So, I was looking online while we were here just in case I didn't get to the pet store
run time and it said that scrambled eggs are perfect to feed a cat.
Yeah I agree.
We're a guy.
So are you guys going to do the crucible or are you going to do this?
I think we do this.
This sounds way more fun than the gay ass crucible.
This is obviously the cooler mission and also it seems like...
I want to see past the fog bro.
And this seems like you are basically rerouting our course to go back to the story you had
planned.
No no no no not at all.
Which, if that was the case, I respect that a lot.
The end of Zoo World.
No, no, no. So this is very much like you could, but I very much want you guys to be able to
Vive Mud Marks. That is 100%. If that is what you want to do, I have created...
There's a scenario where we can have our cake and eat it.
There are other options besides these two that you could stumble upon if you stay in Port Lowe's
Berry Berry that will all lead to ultimately Viving Mud Marks, but you get a little bit more
context for what's going on in the world so that if say next campaign you just
want to do a freaking Harry Potter in the Academy you can do that or you can keep doing the world.
Which I really really want to do. That would be really funny. So you could do that I mean that's how I see
this ending if if if you instead go that way. And it would have to be a school for adult magicians.
But it could end it you know we'll see like you can you can end up dying or you
can end up getting thrown off course. Yeah. Alright okay cool so you guys go to
sleep you guys wake up the next day he had you he bless you he had you in just
sort of like little like bunks that exist you see that there's a little
there's a little cubby where Sherman was staying and Sherman lives in I'm in a
bucket like Odo from deep space okay gross you can turn into that too that's
awesome yeah um it's gross that he does that but um yeah you guys wake up next
day and Sherman says all right I'll lead you guys to the docks and you'll be on
your way I'm glad my father master likes you guys he said you know he's he comes
off as kind of tough but he's a he's a really nice guy from the bucket I'm just
like see do I have to carry him in the bucket okay yeah I would have been if
you need me to carry you now I don't want you to carry me mate oh you like me
now I'm like you now and guess what I'm
your dad no you know my fucking god wow I
made that up but what if I was and you
hear you here in all of your minds what
did I tell you guys about confusing
Sherman about his father let's go let's
cut that out right all right all right
big voices you did you guys walk out of
the tower so it takes about it takes like
probably like a couple hours to walk
through all of Port Lowe's Berry Berry and go through the market and go past all
the other shit and you get to the port area now this actually I have to look at
my notes for one second nerd alert I must look at my notes quick haste quick
haste quick haste what a nerd say quick haste yeah they like saying quick haste
It was actually convenient I drew the cove kind of to look like this because I knew
You have docks you have sort of a boathouse here
And another sort of supplementary boathouse here, mm-hmm cool
And where's your pay pay paces?
Where's our damn pieces this is what this is the cove this is the dock so let's just I mean let's fucking
Mm-hmm listen
Chuggy I need you to turn back into Chuggy and park your sweet little ass in that dock right there
Okay between those two dogs. Oh, yeah, wait hold on before before you do that. How am I already the boat then?
You see okay you do that you see one a guard come over and just go oh well what the uh
What the fuck is this? It's just oh, so I'm very thick. He's really sick. We got to take him to the hospital
So excuse me, excuse me, move out of my way, thank you.
Oh, yeah.
Mack, it's all good.
They're with me and Carlo.
All right, OK, with Carlo.
OK, just-- yeah, I guess get better, buddy.
I'm actually not sick.
I thought you were on the south side.
Let's keep going.
And he gets you guys in the boat.
And he says, OK, so you're going to want to go through the lake.
And make sure you stay on the south side, which
is where you're going anyway.
If you go on the north side--
Sorry, where's the map? There it is.
- Sorry.
- Sorry. I'm looking, I'm pulling up the map.
Pulling out my map.
Make sure you stay on the north side.
And if you go, sorry, make sure you stay on the south side.
If you go to the north, if you go, sorry about that.
(laughing)
- He's just pointing at random places,
going, sorry, no way.
(laughing)
Okay, you want to go here? No, sorry.
No, okay, go here, sorry.
- You have zero confidence in where you're going.
- Okay, I'm not sure about this plan now.
Are you sure?
Show me exactly where we're supposed to go.
- Where is the crucible again?
- What'd I do in the crucible?
- So you guys, he's saying like,
make sure you hug the southern coast,
but do not get near this rock.
This is one of the drop-off points
for the Academy's shipping goods.
They don't need to see.
So if you're gonna need to go underwater,
is this submarine thing,
do it in the beginning of your journey
you can pop out. That's my specialty. Alright. And be on the lookout because. We're going
south? We're going south. So that we can get into the ocean? Well, I would not recommend
going all the way to the ocean. You're going to reach the fog. We don't actually. Oh yeah.
We know there's more out there. We don't actually know what's out there. At least that's what
the master father tells me. But what you're going to be on the lookout for. You gotta
- I'm sorry. - You gotta get it together, man.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- You guys need to come to talk to me.
- This is my first time.
This is my first time.
- First time talking.
- Talking.
(laughing)
- That's okay.
Hey, believe in yourself.
- I've instantly loved this character so much more.
(laughing)
- It's very endearing.
- That he just messes up and says sorry over and over.
That's such a good character.
(laughing)
- He's so nerdy.
- I'm sorry.
(laughing)
Stop apologizing!
- You're with friends! - No, but, buddy, it's okay.
- Yeah, it's gonna be fine. - I just want this to go well.
It's gonna be okay.
It's already going swimmingly!
You don't...
It's gonna go bell-- oh, sorry, I mean well.
- See, we all do it. - Yeah!
Thanks, guys. My dad gets really mad.
You're welcome! Welcome! Fuck!
I know he seemed really nice, but he's actually...
[farting]
Okay, yeah.
So, when you get to the river, you're just gonna want
to be on the lookout for the sticky fingers ships. Now they might be disguised as you know
shipping ships, shipping goods. Shipping ships! You know, but just be on the lookout for that
all right? And if you're gonna dock, if you're gonna dock, make sure you do it at night and
make sure you if you're gonna camp out do not light any fires because anything if you have
some sort of magical way to keep warm if you need to,
you should do that, all right?
You good? - Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Okay. - Word.
- Good luck, guys.
- Thank you. - I love you.
- I love you too.
- Keep your head up.
- We'll be back for you.
- Thanks, guys.
- You're gonna be our new little brother.
- And you're gonna be on TV.
(laughing)
- You're gonna be superstar on TV.
- I would love to be on top of television.
(laughing)
- He was a man.
- I know.
- And so you guys get inside of Chuggie
and you start sailing south.
And next time we will pick it up from that journey.
- Wow.
- We'll start from there.
- Exciting.
(upbeat music)
Yup.
[Music]
(upbeat music)