[MUSIC PLAYING]
Last time on "Tribuchet Village,"
Tales from the Seabomb.
Our heroes, after landing on the shore near post-Port
Los Beriberi, sprung right into action,
beating up a weird wing monster and rescuing
a young woman who was a member of the monster hunter
guild, the Nimrods, whose members are called Rodsmen.
After telling her that they need to get into the academy, she said she would advocate for
them to become rodsmen themselves, which would allow them to have access to the academy,
so they could buy mud marks and take monster hunting contracts.
All they would need to do is survive the crucible, a notoriously dangerous trial that all rodsmen
in the nimrods take before being given their nimrod badge sewn magically into the lining
of their queer ass.
However...
What?
I know what that is.
It's a queer ass.
It's a breastplate.
it's usually for...
you have to be a fuckin' queer ass to know that bullshit
oh, a curious
a curious
no, a genius
it's pronounced queer ass
you're not
you're not pulling my leg
but you knew what you were doing putting it in that thing
he raised his eyebrows when he said queer ass
you knew exactly what you were doing
what about me right now
makes you think I know what I'm doing
that's a good point
Anyway, Curiosity got the better of Chuggy, who spoke with a shy and sweet cutthroat named
Sherman who led the party to Condoleezza Carlo, a strange and strangely handsome and very
evil seeming warlock, who spends his days tricking boats into crashing into each other from his
fake lighthouse tower and then sending his henchmen to pick up the scraps.
His many connections in the academy, including some that would allow evil Raudogan and Chuggie
to become adjunct professors there, and the promise of a way cooler adventure than a crucible,
had the crew ready to take on the challenge of heading to Popo Tower and scouting/rooting
out the Terrifier Quartz Intelligence Network run by Sticky Fingers so that Beriberi and
Condoleezza can claim whatever rewards lie beyond the fog for their own.
We'll talk about the fog a little bit more on Tuesday.
So now the crew heads south through Popo Lake and down south, south Popo River to the Popo
Tower.
Will they-
Hey, hey, Popo!
Will they confront Sticky Fingers?
I wrote Sticky Fongers, so it's-
That's its new name.
- Like he fongers?
- Yeah, it's like he fongers.
- I've heard of a finger.
- Heard of a finger.
- Yeah?
- Heard of a monger, like a warmonger.
- A fonger?
- To see what he knows about Mama Yodar's death?
Does that matter now that Patrick is dead?
Will they get to see what lies beyond the fog?
Will they finally get to vibe mud marks,
their dream of all dreams?
Well, this is it.
- Oh yeah, you sound real excited about it, huh?
- I'm very excited, actually.
I'm extremely, extremely excited.
- Okay, well then bring the fun!
- I'm bringing, here's the fun.
Do a little almost just spilled something is it completely that was full of water
It's spill it was full of poopoo. It's spilled to check this out the whole campaigns full of magic
And we're almost near the end so we should be yes. It is very exciting on here, so here's what's happening, okay?
You guys are right now traveling south
Along the edge I'm in chuggy for based on Sherman you know Sherman gave you guys the the information you need to know about
Okay, travel south along the edge of the lake avoid the the you know the the fucking networks of
of Academy, excuse me, Academy Lake shipping lines
that take goods from Polo's Berry Berry.
And so you've been doing that,
and now you're gonna be heading south
on the South Popo River.
So you can see here, there's the lake,
the North Popo River going up,
and South Popo River to here, the Popo Tower.
Now, do I have it here?
No.
- So.
- Well, I already memorized it as soon as you showed it to me
'cause I have a--
- Actually, it's a very old map,
so it's probably not even important anymore.
- Here, take a look.
Here's the map you know of. - Like the story.
I know of this.
- So, this is the kingdom map,
like of the Terrified Kingdom, of the known world.
This is the fog that you've seen,
like that you know of that surrounds it
and covers the world and indicates to you where it ends,
typically, in this flat world, as it's known as.
- Sure.
- So you're all the way down south.
- Like in League of Legends.
- Can I predict what's gonna happen?
Just ruin everything right now?
- The fog is gonna clear up.
- You absolutely can predict what you want.
- You guys ever seen "The Village"?
I think it's a "The Village" kind of situation.
- I think, I agree, I think it's either "The Village" or--
- I think it takes place in 2004,
and we're gonna get through the fog,
and we're gonna walk in and it'll be like,
"George Bush has been reelected!"
- Yeah, this whole thing has been about 9/11
the entire time.
- Yeah, something like that.
- I would never do that to you.
- He's scratching things,
he's trying to scratch something off his computer screen.
- He's breaking my computer.
- He's cracking his screen.
- So yeah.
- Is the village about 9/11?
- What's up?
- If you're a film theorist, then yes.
- Yeah.
- Wow.
- It's about America's isolationist ideals.
- That's pretty good, Pat.
So...
(laughing)
- Yeah, as you're going...
- Through the lake, the crystal deposits in the lake
give it sort of this like shimmery viscous kind of feeling.
It's like moving through like a,
like kind of like a runny jello.
- Come.
- No, no, no, no.
- What the hell's going on?
- Don't say that.
- You said that out of your mouth.
- I said what?
- My mouth was closed.
- Like you're wading through like a liquid metal.
- Hey, I'm waiting to see if it's come.
- For you, Chuggy, it's not come.
You've been in a lot of water.
- It's not come for him.
- But not water quite like this.
- I've never been in water quite like this.
And while swimming in it, you do get a +2 to any savings row.
- Whoa. - Oh.
I wanna swim in the water too.
Give my fucking white ass in the water.
Well, you guys are--
Use my blood platelets as refs!
- You guys do-- - I jumped in.
You guys do get--
You guys do get +1 because you're inside of Chuggies.
- Okay, jump out. - Okay.
Yeah.
- We're inside of Chuggies. - That's just while you're inside of the water.
Shut up.
Come on.
It reminds you a bit of Percocet, by the way.
Your favorite herb.
Oh, boy.
But it's not quite the same feeling.
You have your faculties, you don't have a gnawing void where more Percocet is supposed to be.
I know what it is.
It's like slipping into a better version of yourself.
Cover your ears, Patches.
It's Walkie Slush.
Oh, like, holy fuck.
You think Patches knows what Walkie Slush is?
It's Walkie Slush, guys.
Is this like a...
Is this like a Zoomer thing?
What's Walkie Slush?
- What's a walkie slide?
(laughter)
- We got it, move on.
- Move on.
Great.
- So, um.
- We got him to ask what it was.
(laughter)
- As you, so, while the Popo River Valley
is not without dangers, the flood of trade
and Sherman's very apologetic instructions
guided you through to the tower with relative ease.
You guys would have traveled for a couple days probably.
Couple days?
Yeah.
It's not the easiest trip.
It's like, you know, if you look at the map and see how long it takes you to get to places.
What helps here is having a river.
It's long.
Yeah, it's long.
If you look at the map you'll see that.
But also having a river, that current will actually help speed it up a little bit.
So when you get to the, where the tower is supposed to be, as you approach, you see an
encampment set up near the tower.
At a glance it appears empty, save for two cloaked figures sitting by a small fire.
It has a stand for armaments, so it's likely some kind of military operation.
Maybe a sophisticated group of brigands or a mercenary company, I mean, you guys have
an idea of who it probably is or what the group probably is because of the insolent job?
So we should avoid them.
Potentially, yeah.
But, so about a hundred yards from that encampment stands the Popo Tower.
It's a massive structure, it's like stately stone, has like, I mean you'll see this more
when you get close to it, but it has these very elegant, strange etchings.
Maybe you'll just die I guess before that happens.
But if you do get close to it.
What?
What the fuck's wrong with you?
Wait, what?
We talked about I'm gonna die.
I just realized that I'm describing something that you can't see yet, so I was like, oh
I feel a little silly.
So he's putting stuff, so you're saying we're about to come up on something real rough and
No, there's really no reason okay, then I go like 30 feet underwater
Yeah
And then I just avoid all the enemies, I don't know okay, that's a good yeah, I got your bitch
And now we guess what now you can stop describing that shit
Cuz I was definitely no way we can see that 30 feet under the water
You hear me describing?
Sounds like you're under water
But it's good, so it's um, it's these has these high half oval windows a couple of significant drum towers
Crowding the imposing main one. There's like a sort of this big imposing like main one
That's like rectangular and then like a couple drum towers that are also pretty big
It's stone is like a it has these are connected by a few like Merlin battlements like, you know, like just like
They're basically what battlements are but like they have these like little like so kind of like sideling that goes up like
They kind of look like palisades almost, but they're not.
They were clearly designed to connect these towers at one
point, but they're kind of dilapidated, so they don't as well.
But yeah, so the stone is a mixture of weathered grays and
reds. The corbels against the tower.
So corbels are kind of like these etchings that help kind of
keep the corners of different castles usually.
Usually they have like faces on them or something.
It'll look like it's sort of like a gargoyle.
Yeah, kind of like that.
Or like a gah-goo-ee.
Yeah, like a gah-goo-ee.
You can't really tell what, like, you wouldn't be able to tell what the visage is.
It's so gone from time.
Perhaps it's Policeman of Legend.
Or something else entirely.
Like who? Name five Policemen of Legend.
The ones that are coming to mind are not ones I want to say.
[Laughter]
So I passed you the ball.
Yeah, that's right.
uh... it's a so it's said that there was a really good one of the cops a good one
of the other three of serbico
here's uh...
s
i'm just i was listing on the news that i could think of that's why i didn't do
it
was that what about what it was a bit both of you know what i want to know
and in that
i've got a good jaco and schmidt
jingo and chained from twenty one jump street jaco and schmidt jaco and she and
ice cube i'd like to give you jim her alter
Jake Peralta is good.
Holy shit.
Uh, uh, Chase.
Chase.
the tower's considerable height as lookout.
Beriberi's long resistance to annexation can be traced back to the region's ancestors being
affiliated with the police.
Where the theory about the realms deep being west past the virtue good archipelago has credence
in the magical and academic community, what is south beyond the tower has no consensus.
Some say it is the edge of the world, just as realms deep in the archipelago are believed
to be the western edge, the isle of gauntlet in the gauntlet sea that extends from it to
to be the eastern edge, the uninhabitable icy, the northern edge.
But where icy has yet to be tamed, and the seas stretch so much further from the east
and the west landmasses that you can't even see the fog, the Popo Tower in the south is
able to overlook the very fog that perplexes so many.
Many, however, no expedition that's been to the tower has known to have survived, ever.
You guys would know this, you probably would have spoken with Han and Lisa about this.
Much like the expeditions into the southernmost fog,
but those expeditions were long ago,
before explorers like Virtuegood and progressive kings
like King Nardwar began to reignite interest
in the closed-minded Terrafire Kingdom.
Members of the Academy, like Condoleezza Carlo,
believe there's something more in the fog.
Just wanted to sort of give you guys
a little bit of a refresher.
- I think there's something more in the fog.
- Yeah, I don't.
- I'm thinking Federal Reserve.
- You guys are right now a little bit out of the encampment.
I would say that you can comfortably, Chuggie,
You can comfortably say that they can't, in the encampment, those folks can't see you.
They don't quite have a visual on you.
So you can try to bypass them and go towards the tower and get a better, closer look at
what's going on there.
Yeah, it's really up to you guys at this point.
Yeah, I guess we should go closer to the tower, right?
Yeah.
Let's go up to the top of the tower.
I'd like to go to the top of the tower.
and
I'm already a boat swim it up. So so you can make a giant wave, right?
Yeah, well, so why don't we use your why don't we use your wave thing?
My character also has the ability on my sheet to walk upstairs. Well, no
Wave won't be tall enough
But the wave will be tall enough for us to do a surprise
Tidal wave attack and wipe out every single person who's on watch right? It won't wipe out every single person who's on watch
Here's the only thing is every single person in the world every
Be a Noah's Ark style way, so you could do that here, so here's what I can here's what I can tell you
Actually, you know what chuggy. Why don't you roll a perception check right now?
How'd you do
Yeah 12, that's not bad, so here's what I can tell you
The tower is only 100 yards out you have a pretty clear sense that there are other members of whoever this crew is
is, like stationed by the tower. If you did the tidal wave, it would...
Yeah, couldn't it get us there faster without...
You could reach the encampment, but you couldn't reach the tower, because that's like 100 yards
out.
Okay.
It's 100 yards inland.
Yes, thank you. Sorry. Yes.
Okay. I thought that it was like an aisle.
No, not quite. Yeah.
There was an island.
It's more like there's like a shore with like a bit of a beach, and then like a bit of a
beach, and then like a bit further out there's like grassland, and then this like tower.
Okay.
You're being a bit of a beach about this whole wave situation.
situation I'm just trying to um this game then then yeah I won't do that then we
won't do the tidal wave yeah I wasn't gonna do the tidal wave in the first I
thought that it was like right there but I'm using my it doesn't matter what you
could do physical I'm not using my wave on this chuggy you could certainly move
across you could certainly like park yourself to the other side of the shore
away from the encampment I'm getting out of chuggy yeah you're gonna get out yeah
I'm out all right, so I would roll here's the thing chuggy makes no sense
If you're gonna get out and be a person flailing in the water
You just have to roll stealth is all you see what I'm saying just cuz like they're not like clocking chuggy is like a you know
It looks like nothing. He looks like a big. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, it's just they there. Oh, it's there. Oh boy. Is there maybe rock is there any is there any?
There's like yeah, there's vegetation. There's woodland around like there's there's there. What about in the water?
I would say in the water. Yeah, I mean there's like seaweed. It's a can I do can I try it?
Can I get out into some seaweed? Yeah? I would say and like poke my eyes and nose out like a frog. I'm green
I'm a goblin don't
But yeah roll okay like a dead frog
Roll okay, yeah, we're like a water jumping lizard roll stealth, and I'll adjust the DC in my head because you're trying to be
be tackable about it.
SID: Ooh.
That is a -- it was a 9, and I touched it,
and it moved to a 6.
Do you believe me?
JUSTIN: I do believe you.
SID: Okay.
What's my stealth?
It's plus 1.
It's a 10.
JUSTIN: Okay.
Yeah.
I mean, you don't see any obvious stirring from the
encampment, so you are likely successful here.
SID: Okay.
And I can just -- can I breathe in the -- can I --
JUSTIN: Yeah.
Yeah.
You -- what you described to me is happening.
SID: So I just kind of hang tight here for now?
JUSTIN: Yes.
SID: Okay.
I'm just going to hang tight for a minute.
Yes.
Why don't I shoot somebody out of my blowhole?
Yeah, you guys do that and I'll hang back.
Put me in your blowhole, shoot me maximum speed to the top like Super Mario 64.
Okay.
And then I roll perform.
And I'd like to hear it go...
As we aim it.
Okay, but let him shoot at least...
At least let me die, you bastard.
At least let him get shot at the enemies.
I'll let you shoot yourself towards the encampment.
Not to the top of the tower.
How about that?
And in the confusion of that, I'm going to run around behind.
What do I roll?
Oh God, right?
What are you going to roll?
Do I roll, is that a performance?
I think you said performance.
Let's do that.
I guess performance makes sense, right?
I would say it's actually a little bit more of a dex.
It's like a range attack.
So I would roll a d20 and add your dex.
plus proficiency because it's your blowhole. You know how that works.
You got a crit one? Alright well I don't know that so I'm loading myself into this thing.
Here we go. Death from above.
You get jammed in his hole. Let's go alright Chuggy.
Press a button. Let's go. Describe what that's like Chuggy.
I'm a hands up Superman.
I'm so ready. I accidentally
I see like a sexy fish
(laughter)
- Swim under me and I go, whoa!
- Well, so you're not a fish though,
you're a humanoid who transforms into a fish-like creature.
So you just think, you're just a guy
who thinks a fish is sexy.
- He is a submarine.
- A submarine's not a fish either.
- Yeah, I'm a guy, I see Angelina Jolie in Shark Tale.
- Okay, wow.
- Is that her?
- I can't even blame you then,
because she is actually fire.
- And I go, and I go underwater and I just--
- Wait, and I'm just being dragged down?
- You're in the blowhole and there's,
it's just filling up with water.
Okay, alright, uh, okay yeah, at this point I have to say, I mean like, with that, all
that commotion of those, of you, I will say with a one, you literally go "Oh boy!" and
just like make that noise, so they hear that from the river, and the two guys who are stirring,
they get up and they start to wander over closer to the shore.
You don't know that this is happening, you do, Raw Dogon, you.
Am I just flying through the water like I left my bungee on?
just like inside his hole.
He decides to stop trying to fuck the fish.
The only thing that happened, you thought you were getting shot out, but you like, you
were in my, your head is out like a mini corn dog.
Yeah.
Like, or pigs in a blanket.
Okay.
You're like, your head is poking out of my flesh.
Just the top of my head?
Top of your head is like a pig in a blanket.
Okay.
So what about you?
They're walking are they walking towards me. I mean they're walking towards in the noise. Where were you in relation to them?
I guess it's a better question. I mean I'm in the sea where right you're like
I'm in the senior them so like cuz you just cuz you I kind of pictured I guess in my brain
Yeah, tell me cuz I didn't like describe that that like like like I'm next to the shore like lily pad
Yeah, that's kind of I see it, too
So they're kind of like approaching like at your they're not approaching directly towards you
They're kind of coming from like they're gonna be at your like 10 o'clock and are those these the only people who I saw the in
the
sneak up and try and get behind them I think.
We're doing a great distraction over here.
Yes, we're going to have to start, it depends on what you do.
Are you going back up or are you going down further right now?
The fish turned out to be a piece of trash.
Okay.
I'm going to say.
And you're still following it.
I'm still following it because I still want to fuck it.
Okay, I need you to roll a d20 for constitution saving throw.
Yeah, yeah I figured.
But the water.
The water is good.
The water does give you plus two.
You get pluses.
You get plus two.
Fourteen.
Nice.
I will say the blowhole smells like a fat guy's belly button.
You ever do that?
You ever have a fat friend, you stick your finger in his belly button, you smell your
finger?
Yeah.
Try that next time.
What does that smell like?
It smells really bad.
I'm going to find out.
It smells like barbecue chips.
No, no.
It smells bad.
No, no, no.
Oh, no, no.
A human shouldn't smell like barbecue chips.
That's true.
You smell like barbecue chips.
I ate some barbecue chips.
Yeah, so you're a human.
Barely.
I wish I had barbecue chips.
You got plain rough.
So you're--
So I'm starting at it.
You're still-- yeah, so you're able to--
the magical properties of the water
were able to help you sort of maintain composure.
And it makes my hair grow.
It's very composed.
Yeah.
It's like sticking out of a blowhole.
Perfect posture.
And it makes my hair grow.
Yes.
You get one hair, like a little baby.
Oh, yeah.
And you, you roll a stealth check, Rodogon, you.
Okay.
That is a 17.
Nice, okay, yeah, I'm gonna roll for them.
Where's...
I have a D20, things, I'm gonna go on.
Okay, yeah.
So you, you are able to sort of get around them right now.
Mm-hmm.
And they don't see you.
They're pretty distracted by what's going on underwater.
chuggy however is
beeline for the surface right now
uh...
so there you have a little bit of a time i think these are not my spells
the monopoly uh...
but i know you have don't know what you know you have to find smite i know you
have uh... here we are think what i would like to hear a couple of several
okay but i'm not going to spell i think now i'm thinking that what i'm going to
do people is a
okay i've not using a spell and i'm telling you what i'm doing
uh... which is i'm going to use my way for them to try to push them into the
water with my way of and i'm not them and try to push them down
may i don't know you it's on the truth he does
well you do i have concern
ivory of sickness over here which i know i don't have you both i know you do have
you both share a couple spells and i didn't have to look at parts of for that
i definitely don't have yes many spells though
no you have a good amount you inflict wounds you've held tribute
You know some of these are mine, okay, all right all right wait wait. I can figure this out now
But anyway, I'm pushing them in I think either way do your big war attack. Yeah, that's what I'm doing okay cool
But I'm so roll an attack roll
Wait do I still have that?
Which the blutter know the the arrow of inflict poop no Patrick had that right?
That's an 11
Burrito total yeah, I mean roll again you have advantage you're stopping. Thanks. I didn't get any of Patrick's inventory. That's a 17
That's gonna do it so yeah
now roll for damage, so it's gonna be
2d 8 2d 8
Okay, you said 2d 2d. That's 4 okay cool, and then I'm gonna roll for them
Their stats either stats, okay, it's 1 HP and 0 of all stats
So he gave him to you, so please respect your boss did not do too. Well
So here's the thing they
You swing your oar around they are able to turn around just in time to see not you
But just a giant fucking thing of water
Crash into them and knock them into the wall into this the river yeah, chuggy eat them you have okay?
I would say you have kind of this like this is your opportunity or else is there gonna like start doing shit
Yeah, I was doing this so yeah, he could eat them alright chuggy. I want you to roll a
Attack roll so just roll d20 and add your strength
18 nice okay, you were able to swallow them to eat them at you
This is the only thing I'll let your submarine do we did establish that it can do this
You able to put them in your mouth right now. They can go you can either swallow them to go inside your submarine chamber
and oh
No, I guess it would kill you if you transferred back. I was saying that'd be fucking brutal, but no yeah
It would kill you and or you can and you can or you can like kind of spit them out and drown them
you can kind of
Do that?
What if I you like kind of trap them?
I mean, what if I should I do that and and dissolve them in my stomach acid I?
Didn't really think about that
He sounds so scared it's a lot of power. I just gave him he'll be dead soon. Yeah, it's true. Yeah, you digest them
Nice well here's here's what I'll say it's ones per log rest power you can eat humans
Okay, you need people that doesn't see because it maybe it ups because it's so full
I'm gonna throw up next roll. Wait. Did you show up?
They just maybe I roll they are they use here's what you see I have to roll like
Basically inside a force, but it would it would I guess if you were inside the okay?
It's like you would see them like traveling through underneath the floor. Oh my god like a gust of
Yeah, great. Yeah, you see them like in the like in the Adams family
movie from the 90s when uncle the uncle fester imposter goes up the tube because he pulled the wrong chain behind the bookcase and he's
Going through the water tube and they're like guess uncle fester's messing around with the chains and then they go outside and he came out of
That little door. It's exactly like I'll cover the water on the ground outside the mansion of the house
I should say they call it an uncle fester situation. What's happening here? The hell are you talking about?
He knows he just told me to watch that movie because I had not seen it so you know I don't know Christopher
Lloyd, Uncle Fester
Why are you talking about Christopher? We did a performance for the ages. It's a good performance
So funny, I guess
Roll like a golf and I
Roll like yeah constitution saving throw to see if eating them
Doesn't make me sick
Yeah, I like that okay. Let's do that and it'll be a DC. What's your con to DC 12 keep it safe, okay?
Well, I got a 17. Yeah, you're fine. So you're able to digest them very easily and
It's like when you eat
Oysters, I think it's still once for long rest
But now instead of like if you fail your DC
I think I'll probably have to raise it to 15 or something
But I think from now on if you fail the DC though. It's like you vomit them up. They take like
Yeah, they take like maybe like like 1d 8 damage just from like the acid in the churn
But you know then you'd fight them or whatever, but if they you succeed you get to swallow a guy
And you have to be a guy who has to also do like you said we'll also have to figure out like you know
It'll depend like are they aware of this is happening versus like this which is a pure surprise so a pure surprise
So yeah, you guys took care of that encampment
The tower is yours to approach keep in mind there are a few guys on the outside man was my favorite scroll that came out recently
with all those singing
All right, go you can know any time you can go you can go right through the front door
There's a few guys outside of there where you can I would recommend maybe looking around the tower a little bit
Okay, I'm looking around the tower my eyes becomes searchlights in there going back and the map the map the man. Yeah, so
yeah, roll a
investigation anyone or all of you.
- Me!
- May Caleb do it, he's the one with who has it.
- My investigation added the bonus ability, that's 17.
- That's very good.
- Thank you.
- So, all right.
I should be much better about hiding.
- You should just be better.
- The little map of the tower.
- Holy fuck.
- I memorized it, don't worry guys.
- Basically there's stairs that go around
and around and around and they go up one floor by one.
- And they don't stop, they go all the way up.
- The top of the tower is its peak.
It's actually a Soulsian style.
- One of them is Soulsian.
- Listen, I would be able to tell what it is,
but Pat is not a good gifted artist.
- I am not a gifted artist.
I'm actually, you know what, I'm not bad.
- He's pushing back.
- I'm pushing back tonight.
Yeah, so you guys--
- He's allowed to push back.
- Yeah.
So you guys, as you go around, Steevel,
you see a, you know, and you're kind of far out, right?
'Cause you don't really-- - Whoa!
- I mean, I was like, is he gonna, but he didn't.
- So, you know, you're trying not to alert the guards
in the front of the tower. - Okay.
- But you can see what looks like kind of like scuffed
like ground beneath one of the edges
of like the larger tower on the left side.
So if you're facing the tower-- - Is there any beautiful
golden braided hair falling from this tower?
- No.
- Well, there goes my plan.
Okay, well, is there...
I press the up elevator button.
There's no up elevator button.
Okay, I press the down elevator button.
Fine, you go down.
(laughing)
But no, yeah, you see like a hole
that leads to underneath the tower.
Okay, I'm hopping in feet first.
No, head first.
Dug the board.
And I use his butt as a pillow, I go right behind him.
Okay.
Using his butt as a pillow, you guys both go down
into what is the, essentially the basement of the tower.
(snorting)
(laughing)
- These guys are having a smelling fight.
- So, oh you're G'day Cuntole.
- And I'm winning.
- Oh yeah.
- Truce.
- Someone needs to lose.
- It smells just like home.
- So in this basement area of the tower,
compared to the outside of the tower,
what you had seen which had this kind of like,
it was a bit like, it was a bit like,
it seemed a bit odd and a bit ancient and all that,
but it didn't seem like fully,
like a different, a completely like alien architecture
like this basement area does.
You see to your right, this,
like a, what looks like a sealed off door
to like a smaller room in this room, you know,
it's like jutting out from the wall.
- Okay.
- And then--
- Like a shed?
- Yeah, basically a shed, but it's like inside
and it's like affixed to the top of the wall
of this basement area.
It's not like a very high ceiling.
- Okay.
- And you see to your left,
more of that sort of burrowed tunnel that you had seen
that kind of like led you in here.
- Round two.
- That goes further in.
From in front of you, you can sort of start to hear like the,
you can hear like the, like vague like conversation
between, yeah, between like guards or, you know,
members of this group who are inside the main area.
- Can I do, should I do a perception or investigation
to try to make out what they're saying a little bit?
- This would be, I would say this is perception, yeah.
- Okay.
- It's either that or insight really.
I think perception though is really good.
- 18.
- 18?
Yeah, sure.
And you could hear them saying like, "I don't want to go back up there again with that beast."
And you hear them talking about this stuff.
Like waiting for Sticky Fingers, not wanting to go back up there because of a beast.
Don't we have an inn with Sticky Fingers because we have Patrick's head?
I mean, you don't know if Sticky Fingers was responsible for anything, if he's your friend
or your enemy still.
like it for all you don't they know that sticky fingers no no I mean they so what
they all they know is that code like the word sticky fingers led most likely to
Patrick's mom's death they don't know how sticky fingers connected to that at
all so in sticky fingers might regard them as friends you know but they are
right now in a like interfering with an operation that he's in the middle of but
like this so that's like but that's like what you I mean they could have debriefed
you
We don't have to do a scene about this.
So this is on the other side of a closed door, right?
What?
The voices are on the other side of a closed door?
No, like the other side of like a wall.
Like a wall in dirt.
Okay, and is that the only door?
No, no, no. That's like, it's not a door.
It's literally like...
It doesn't have a door?
Yeah, it's foundation.
Like there's a door out one way and there's like that weird shed.
So there is a door though.
So the voices aren't coming from the shed?
No.
No, that shed that shit is like that shit like the shed is against the wall and like it looks like it would just stop at
The wall, okay, maybe we should get another shit. Yeah, I want to get in the shed
I'm itching to get in the shed. I'm trying to pride the shed open
Wanna take a shit?
Exact way to open it here. Yeah door does not open from this side. Yeah
We'll get back there at some point try to bust it down
Busted busted busted. Hold on. Let me look at it gangster
this is it made out of one said I will say he said doors not open from this side and as a as a
RPG as an RPG player that means we should keep we should just go somewhere else there
I mean look it's not that they're not away, but it's like it'll it'll be tough
You'll have time you'll have you got a wow me
One thing about me is that I'm tough.
You are tough.
Can we...
Hold on, hold on.
Wait, I'm getting close.
I've been holding on.
I'm looking at my spells.
I'm getting really close to a switch.
Oh, wait.
Can I detect magic on the show?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, you can certainly do that.
Real quick.
Okay, I give up.
Go for it.
Okay, I don't know how to do that.
They say something about a beast, right?
Yeah.
You do just detect magic.
You notice that there is a little bit of a, like,
a little bit of a, like,
You notice that there is --
We don't know what the beast looks like.
I can make a new beast.
I can make a completely new beast.
So you can -- you detect -- you definitely detect some kind of --
I'd say it's closer to evocation magic than anything from within the shed,
but it also could just as likely be --
it's like it has shades of enchantment magic as well.
There's some kind of -- basically it's like --
it's the composite magics that would make a mechanism, right?
Like a machine kind of work.
Does anybody have anything to like dispel magic or anything?
Dude, like an anti-magic field or something like that?
I have invisibility.
Yeah, you do.
I'm trying to think.
That's something that you should consider using at some point.
Also have Shatter.
Yeah, this is the... So here's the thing.
You guys also each have, I believe, two good health potions.
If I don't have it in your inventory, I have it in my notes here.
I have Leomund's Tiny Hut.
Yeah, this is the one where...
This is like the... If I didn't write it down there,
that's... This is something that...
And I can use Invisibility for up to an hour.
But this is gonna be the...
the
door is not the thing we came through.
- Yeah, sorry, let me make sure I aptly explain this.
Here, wait, let me draw.
- I know you have invisibility.
- I can just walk in this room.
- There's no room.
- You guys came in from here.
This is where you were hearing the voices.
This is where that weird shed is,
and this is that other tunnel.
- Okay, I think we should go in the other tunnel then.
It's the only way forward.
- I think so, yeah.
- Yeah, I agree.
- All right, well let's get in that there tunnel.
- Okay.
Alright, so you go around this winding tunnel and it looks like there's like these different
like claw marks that are like marking the wall, they're allowing you to go up it.
You see bits of rock and rubble sort of falling on you.
As you're like looping around, you notice that you're moving further away from kind of like
where you were in the center of the tower to like further back.
And what you might have noticed actually, Steval, while there is sort of these like makeshift
palisades around all of the, you know, around the drum towers, is that there was
like a back section to that main tower. It looked like made of different
architecture and it seems like you're moving up that as you tunnel through
this and you approach a window that looks into a...
I'm sorry, not there. My apologies. Oops, I read the wrong thing.
There we go, yes I got it right.
It looks into the second floor of the main tower area.
As you were going around you saw this other area, this other stranger architecture,
but then you looped back around into the main tower.
And as you poke your head out you do see a guard immediately on your left.
Does he see us? He does not see you just yet.
You're on the second floor of the main tower, so it's like you were underneath.
Is there any way to sneak past him?
It's a pretty small room.
It would be very difficult to just sneak past.
Can we sneak attack him maybe?
Sneak attack, doing something with invisibility, maybe.
A number of things you might have to do to make this work.
I think I'm going to cast Vampiric Touch.
Just try to sneak attack kill him with a single hit.
Okay.
Yeah.
Read for me Vampiric Touch. Let's hear about it.
Okay, so I guess I'm a fucking book to you.
The touch of your- is this what you wanted?
The touch of your shadow wreath hand can siphon life force from others to heal your wounds.
Make a melee spell attack against a creature within your reach.
On a hit, the target takes 3d6 necrotic damage, and you regain hit points equal to half the amount of necrotic damage dealt.
Until the spell ends, you can make the attack again on each of your turns as an action.
Okay.
Yeah, that's good.
It's good. Why not touch him so first thing you're gonna want to do though is sneak
That's true check
That's a 70. Oh, no. That's a four plus one five. That's a nice tripod you almost got me by saying
Sure is oh wait. It was a 20. I'm so stupid. I'm stupid
Yeah, he did the math wrong. Yeah, you
It's to make another spongebob reference. It's you stepping on the floor in here
(quack)
Well he wouldn't even look, it's normal to hear a duck sound.
A duck? What?
And he turns around.
I pretend to be a duck.
Who are you who is so wise in the ways of science?
I don't know.
What is up with you today in movies?
What is up with you today in the Holy Grail Witch Scene?
I got you.
I would like to...
I'm the loser, yeah.
I would like to pretend to be a duck if I could origami my body a little bit.
(laughter)
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What if I turn into a duck?
What if I shapeshift into a duck?
Whole squad turned to a duck.
So what are you gonna do now?
I just saw you.
Okay.
Well, I just...
I... wait, actually...
You said "look a duck."
Oh my God, there's a duck behind you the other direction!
Roll initiative.
Initiative like I'm going out for a job interview
because maybe I could become a guard?
A job interview.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Can you lure him down the hallway
and then as he runs past our hallway opening
we just we just get all that's a good idea
so it's it's it's a yeah it's it's a bit of a smaller room but what you could do
if you
pull him for far enough back
unlike like by moving back yeah you could conceivably go around and leave this
room
and into the no i just meant to sneak it like what he walked yet to go with this
to see a cam
all yet you do that to you know he is a no you guys are there yet yet again
you have been on all fours
for my pants down
show my asshole
uh... and i'm and i'm putting my balls in my dick behind my asshole and then i'm
like squeezing my thighs together
and it kinda looks like a duck
and then you run down the hallway like that
while holding my balls behind my thighs
i kinda waddle
galloping like a horse
I'm hitting every creaky floorboard on the way down the hall.
[quacking]
He does like...
And you're doing a fart that sounds like a duck.
Yeah.
[quacking]
I'm waving my fart in my other face.
What the fuck are you doing?
Yeah! Yeah!
He's approaching you and he has his sword drawn.
And he's just like...
He's like trying...
Alright, I gotta... you gotta get the fuck out of here.
And he goes to grab it, he is now past the hole that you guys are...
Attack of opportunity.
Yeah.
Me too.
We both...
Yeah, you both get attack of opportunity.
I'm gonna shoot him with my crossbow.
Oh my god, I got a crit one.
Okay.
It's a sneak attack though.
Yes, you get a sneak attack.
Is it a sneak attack?
Yes, it is.
I got a nine.
Okay, that time I got a seventeen total.
What's the... what do I add?
Add your attack.
What are you attacking with?
a
is
I would like to put my hand over his mouth when we do this too.
Oh, I see.
Let's have you do --
I would like to continue waddling.
Or maybe -- yeah.
You're not quite in the initiative order yet.
I'll --
Is there a conthometry suppress noise at all?
Or does it just make noise?
I think it just makes noise.
Okay.
Sort of a live guy spell.
You can make the inverse of whatever noise he makes and silence him.
Invert the phase.
Yeah.
Okay, that is a 14.
Okay, I'll say you got the jump on him.
Yeah, you're able to put your hand over his mouth.
I'm a goblin, so I'm really small.
That's why I had to jump up on his shoulders to do it.
You hear from outside this room, though,
this hallway, you hear,
"Uh, Kevin, what's going on in there?"
And I do vicious mockery.
Oh. Oh my God.
On that guy. On that guy who's outside the hallway?
Yeah. Just copy--no, just touch--
just copy this guy's voice. You just heard him talk.
you're a changelog. Oh right, right, I copy his voice. Yeah, what are you saying this other guy's voice?
Um, hey.
Um, I'm pretty uh, I'm, I'm fucking.
Um, I'm all right. My uh, I was talking to my daughter.
Yeah, okay Kevin. All right. Um, god that guy's so fucking weird. Just, they just walk away.
Why would you give him a detail like you know our daughter this guy knows you on it?
You thought you were doing Louie
Yeah, I mean that's a classic Louie reference - I was talking to my daughter she's a cunt
Just kind of like like pitch down Brandon Ward
It's your turn
Yeah, let me roll a performance check.
You have a chance to kill him!
I got a... performance...
Plus I got three, so I don't really seem like a duck.
You just seem like a...
*quack*
When my ass is out, my dick and balls are behind my thighs.
I'm crying out. You know what? Because my performance got worse, my forearms are getting real sore
of waddling, so I go down to my elbows.
I'm not looking behind me at all to see the fighting just
*imitates fighting noises*
This is really getting me
*laughter*
He's gonna try to break free from me
He's like so set on killing me
He hates you
*laughter*
I'm taunting him
I'm just pure bait that he's still going for
really
uh...
of shit or a role against the units you know the streets and florida straight
you're all straight the general strength against
that's a sixteen
okay yeah he breaks out
he's going to attend
but uh...
uh...
what is your a_c_
by a_t_t_ is uh... fifteen
okay yeah he definitely hits you
that's fine
yeah and he does
uh i need 2d8
yeah you need 2d8 another man
woah
holy shit
okay he does um he does 10 damage to you
you just step like stabbing you in the ass with his sword
i don't react at all
i just take the damage
and he's going like
*grunts*
because that's what you think a duck would do
I will also say though he moved right out of your range too.
My range?
So you have an opportunity attack here.
Ok, I will.
Use your action last time.
That is a 19.
Nice, use your action last time to impersonate him.
That hits, so roll for damage now.
What are you attacking him with?
I'm attacking him with my crossbow.
Ok.
Which I don't care about the range rules for that.
Nobody can tell me otherwise.
Four.
Okay, plus one.
Oh, plus one.
And you got, what'd you get last time?
Four.
And what did you have? You had 14, right?
I had 12, I think.
You had 12? Oh, okay, yeah.
Yeah, he's...
Why don't you write it down? You got the biggest friggin' notepad ever in your life.
Yeah, we call it a computer.
No, it actually has a giant notepad.
Oh, I didn't see that.
But it has all my map designs on it.
Don't touch things.
Yeah, he's still, he's still alive.
At this point, the guy's...
It's my turn.
- It's gonna be, yeah, it's about to be your turn,
but, well, no, it's actually gonna be your turn.
- Yeah. - Okay.
- It's your turn.
I mean, this is, I will say, like, you gotta--
- I'm gonna jump back-- - You gotta take care
of this now. - Yeah, I'm gonna jump back up
and hit him and put my hand over his mouth again.
- Yeah. - Just do the,
just run it back.
Oh, wait, I got two attacks last turn.
I completely forgot.
- Well, no, you didn't, 'cause it's an opportunity attack.
- Okay, well, this time I do.
- Yeah.
- Okay, that's, that is an eight.
- All right, you can roll again.
Yeah, that's it.
- Okay, that is a 19.
- Yeah, that hits.
- Okay, okay, and my damage is a three.
- Wow, yeah, you just didn't kill him.
- Damn, can I still try and put my hand over his mouth again?
- I'll let you do that as a bonus action.
Just 'cause he's pretty bewildered.
- Okay, that's eight.
- Yeah, I mean, like, we'll have him roll against that.
- Or maybe even stick my whole fist down his throat.
- Is it my turn now?
- No, instead, other guys are like,
all right, Kevin, what the fuck?
And a guy kinda comes in,
and as another guy in the term i wrote what's our ruling initiative we can i
need to unite
because we're i'm still gets the wall right
uh... tonight i mean you attack opportunity on this guy no cases walking
into the room he's not like leaving your range right now of your like
melee range which is what i should be making
and already marty giving you
sears so you to have to roll this year in t_v_ issue initiative order now
he he was still a doctor
okay my initiatives a
sixteen
okay
and it just turned a seventeen put it down
i'd add an eighteen
okay cool
you're up to
I'd like to use my mace.
Yeah.
Okay.
Ah, that's an eight.
This doesn't work, you're just clenching your ass, I guess.
Yeah, I try to pop the mace out of my ass.
Yeah, it just doesn't hit.
I HATE YOU!
He's adding more props to the back side of my body.
Uh, Pat, you're up.
Okay.
Nineteen- oh, what are you trying to do?
Eighteen.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm trying to shoot him with my crossbow.
Yeah, okay. So that'd be a 20.
Yeah, roll for damage.
Oh wait, what do you add?
Plus one. So I got a 19.
You will kill him.
Wait, is that...
No matter what damage you roll, you're gonna kill him.
This is what you add to the attack roll?
Oh, and that would be like a 20.
You already hit him.
And I got seven damage.
Describe your kill on this guy.
really wants to kill evil steve
I can't believe it
the easiest number to add
I shot him in the mouth
yeah
you fucking duck
wait it shoots like through the
back of his head
and then can he die by falling
maybe the arrow goes all the way through
clears him completely
he falls into my ass and maybe my balls
go into his mouth
like when the dentist holds your mouth open with that thing
thing. Yeah, right. And then I just and then to make his other friend mad now I'm dragging
his him. You know what actually the arrow goes to affix him to me the arrow goes into
my asshole. It's like a barb and it's stuck in me and I'm just dragging his lifeless body.
You have to take damage for that. It's completely worth it. How much damage do you have to take?
roll the a you just you decide
seven six seven damage to you
why
no
uh... this
uh... that this other guys gonna go now he's like
what you do to kathleen and he's gonna try to attack uh...
because you pat so
what do you need
teach one
uh... still be
you put it
That was a one.
It's a one, yeah.
It's actually a one.
It's a one and then a six on the same.
It's a 16.
It's a 16, okay, cool.
Yeah, thank you.
Yeah, he's going to hit you for sure.
Fucker.
He draws his sword out.
You take your damage out.
He tried to hit you.
He'd do 15 damage to you.
Did we take a long rest?
Yeah, you should have your health back.
Oh, okay.
You're at full HP.
Yeah.
Oh, I need to get seven HP then.
Yeah, and you are up now.
Me?
Yeah.
Okay, I better run up and hit this dude guy.
Do it.
Well, I already had, I erased it, but I still had to.
Okay, that's a 12 on my first attack.
Yeah, no.
No hit.
No dice, Bryce.
Okay, that's a 7 on my second attack.
Yeah, and then I basically am doing the duck thing, I guess, now too.
Yeah.
That's what we should do, we should do it in opposite directions so he gets stuck in the
middle.
Yeah, I start doing the duck thing.
I run up, take two swings, and immediately drop to a high point.
He's like no reaction just drop not even yeah, not even close to
Completely just
This might make him go crazy at the very least he's gotta be taking psychic damage from this. Yeah
He has to take
He's going on your ass. Yeah, we had needed to open it. I love Europe. I'm up
shit
What can I do without interrupting my shit?
All right, I'll do vampiric touch you have a you have a
Crossbow no wait no I need to touch him you have a crossbow dart in your butt if you fart hard enough
You could shoot the crossbow dart out of your butt into his head
Can I cast blindness deafness? Yeah, I'm gonna make him blind. Yeah, don't make him blind. Oh, no
Before I'm gonna use ray of sickness, okay. Yeah go for it. Describe it to me. All right, so
Let's see, let me let me
Cassie first asshole
that's a
What do I add to my range plus four that's a nine you only have plus four to your spell attack or no
Sorry plus 11. I mean 11, okay
Okay, so I did that for fucking nothing I could have done another performance check yeah
Then I pass is raves is sickness a spell attack or is it a it is a
third or sub first level necromancy
Necromancy buddy I'll have hickeys
- What?
- Yeah, it's a spell attack.
- Get it?
- All right, you are up, Pap.
- He looks so thoughtful right now.
- I love that.
During everyone else's turn, he's literally looking at the ceiling,
trying to touch the ceiling.
- He's trying to pull the commander that holds the light.
- And it gets pissed, you start slowly picking up one card by one
and reading them one by one.
- Can I actually buy you a fidget spinner so that you don't ruin the set?
- Okay.
Awesome.
Alright, I guess I'll just use my crossbow again.
I can't think of anything I can do with these.
- In D&D 2.0, all spells will be so simple.
so
in
monkey
is
you
it's not now
was it
which received
well
she's
k_e_c_ damage to you
okay he's gonna keep seven have five h_p_ he's gonna keep talking talking you
guys up
we need to get out of here
alright i'm just i i i am
here i will say like an i_k_s_ inflict wounds out of my butt
yeah of course
always stop you from doing i'm gonna go for that
okay that's a nine
my god to the spruce hate my
fucking life you know i think you're a bit easier up
uh... i'm gonna try
i'm gonna try the rates it's again vehicle for let's do this
This is so fucked.
I'm so dead.
Total?
Dude, this is it.
Alright. It's gonna end like this.
Pat, you're up.
I'm going to use...
Before you do it, let's look at your spells.
You've got really good spells.
You have Dissonant Whispers.
That could do 3d6 damage on a failed save.
Okay, I will use...
And they have to be afraid of you and run away.
So how about we'll do that.
And what's your spell save DC?
Look at your sheet.
Go to the next page.
You should see your save DC at the top.
Bro, there's a spell called message.
Got a smartphone.
It should be at the top of the sheet.
What does your save DC say?
15.
15?
Alright, so he's going to roll against that.
Not you.
Me.
Me got to roll against it.
Oh, I have to roll against it.
No, he has to roll against it.
No, no, you don't roll.
You got a 13.
Patches.
I got a 13.
And I got a 19.
My guy's wisdom is that he's not that wise, so...
Um...
Hopefully, let me see...
I remember him being...
Not that wise.
Nice!
Yeah, that hits!
*Gasp*
So he's gonna take...
So, Pat, roll 3d6.
So the regular dice.
1, 2, 3.
Nice, okay.
Uh, he is afraid of you.
So he is...
You are so excited!
To see your favorite numbers!
*laughter*
He is afraid of you.
Uh, so I'm not afraid of the two ducks.
So he is gonna start to move away from you immediately.
Towards which duck?
Get away from me!
Yeah, which duck is it?
How is he not afraid of me? I got his fucking front stapled to my ass.
Cause he didn't do like this and it whispers. He played a discordant melody in his ear.
Okay.
Fucked him up.
So did me too.
And he starts to run away, and he runs out of this hallway.
Uh oh, he's gonna go alert everyone else.
Good!
We're done, we're dead!
*laughter*
You just hear him at the end of the room saying,
"Get away from me, get away! There's more people!"
It's over.
Should I shoot him?
It turned invisible.
Oh, okay, I turned invisible then.
Okay, yeah, you can turn invisible.
Are we out of initiative?
Yeah, you're out of initiative.
Okay, yeah, I think we need to...
And this the only way that to go is the way that he just ran there's so there's three doors out of this room
Okay, there's one that is walking out of the tunnel here map time map time
You guys walked out of the tunnel, so this is you guys walking out of the tunnel here
Hallway uh-huh this guy ran out of here uh-huh there's a door over here that leads to
More there's a door over here that leads to more
Okay, this one he walked in the middle
Okay, it was also where he walked in from maybe let's go to the right side door sure right go right cool all right
I'm by spelling. I'm not no longer a duck
I get up, but I still try the guy still in my ass cheeks mm-hmm
So dragging you see this you see a hallway when you go out another hallway, okay?
So we're gonna go it's probably gonna go to where he's like barbarian. We also see a you also see a window over here
Can we sneak past this door? I would just like to... who is the best sneaking?
Mine is +1. My stealth is +1 as well.
Mine is +4. And I'm invisible.
Roll a perception check too.
Can we all roll perception? You can all roll perception, yes.
I got an 11. I got an 8.
I got a 21. Damn, you are noticing shit all the time.
9 + 10. Yeah, 21.
You can see, you kind of like eagle eye, look through the window, and see there's like this drop, and then one of those, um, uh, uh, sort of like, battlements I was talking about.
That you could conceivably hop onto.
I think we hop onto there, right? I think we need to get out of-
Alright, alright, get the hell out of Dodge!
Let's go hop out of that window!
Okay, you guys sprint down the hallway, you hear the clamber of guards in that room.
I have an idea. Oh my god, I have an idea. Okay, because they'll still see us through the window, right?
If yeah, I mean they come outside to get you. Well, I'm gonna let them go into the window first
And I'm gonna go last and I'm gonna sit at the windowsill with my butt in up in the air
So it looks like just the back of that guy
Just looking out of the window kind of like I'm holding up his body from his head and he's just like looking out the window
I feel like that's more suspicious than yeah, he's got an arrow through his mouth
They didn't care that could be a pimple on the back of his head from far away. I think you're trying to get us killed
No
you might be trying to get them killed okay, then I
Hmm. I'm trying to feel like we should try and barricade this door or something all right
I use his body to barricade the door
You can you can yeah, you can like deposit his body from your ass in front of the door
Okay, and then I also nail him like
to the door like Jesus I'd say you have to roll a
a
It's a little bit, it's definitely more upsetting to see.
Maybe I missed the frame of the door.
It's like you got part of his cheek, but not like, it's not a lot to go like.
But it might, maybe it'll just make them be like, "Oh, we shouldn't fuck with these guys, they're crazy."
Yeah, you guys run towards the window, you see that there is this like, palisades kind of like wall out there,
and it's leading to one of the drum towers.
So you guys could jump on there and run out.
Yeah, let's do that.
Yeah, okay.
You guys jump on there and run out.
Where are you now in my wonderful world?
Wonderful world.
Are we just toys to you?
That's a cassette tape they found in a serial killer's house.
Where are you now in my wonderful world?
You'd be upset if I was a serial killer.
I would not be, though.
You ran out the window.
That's kind of why it would be cool, though.
So you guys get to the top of this drum tower.
You hear clamoring coming from behind you, you hear them go "OH FUCK KEVIN!"
And uh, um...
I don't even care about the other guy.
And uh, you are able to like,
I mean, you're able to balance, you don't need to like balance on these towers, you know, they're walkways.
There's no like, acrobatics trick or anything.
You get to the top of this drum tower,
and this is the first time you can see the fog, really,
'cause now you're up high enough that you can see past the shore and on the other side and see the fog.
And the first thing you also kind of recognize is that it reminds you of the Kaiju Manji fog.
And the smoke that came from them.
There is a similar kind of flavor to it.
It's this like white, billow-esque thing.
Vanilla.
And you also see...
There is a...
There's... Right in front of you, you can go in here and there's like sort of a spiral staircase into here.
You can also jump down onto a smaller drum tower.
And those are your options.
Hmm. I...
So you can like kind of get away further or you can go into this area and like just start
trying to go further up the tower.
I kind of want to keep going further up the tower.
Okay yeah.
Okay let's go.
That's where you go in my wonderful world.
It's not going to work a second time.
Yeah that's fair.
So you guys are in the, in this sort of like spiral area and it looks kind of, it looks
more like the way the original tower looked, less like sort of that weird sort of like
kind of alien look that those other lower parts of the tower looked. But it also has these
etchings that look otherworldly though. It looks almost like somebody's trying to depict
something in these etchings, these wall etchings. It's like sculptures of these like birds, like
flying. You see the, you see sculptures of old battles between the Terrifier and the
Policemen alongside these like feathered creatures. And as you're going up the tower you see these
gargoyles lying inside of it.
And they're pretty horrible to look at.
They look like they were melted, but that seems to be just the way that they were made.
It's kind of cool.
And as you climb up this tower and you reach the top of it, you see another walkway.
This one, though, looks like it was not intentional.
This looks like it was a suspended bridge and you're really far up now.
And it's through this window here.
So if you walk through, you can walk through here and what you'll be reaching is the main
tower again.
So you've gotten pretty far now.
And that's basically all you see, like there's nothing else here.
There's a spiral staircase with all these ghouls and creeps.
So to get to the main tower we have to walk through this window and through this way,
which does not seem like it was intended to be a bridge.
It looks like it was intended to be like a --
something to hold the tower.
Can a duck fly?
No.
Really?
Not in this universe.
Can you -- does Chuggie have a secret airplane form?
A helicopter.
That's kind of the opposite of a submarine.
Yeah.
No.
He doesn't have an airplane form.
Sorry.
You're looking at me.
No.
I don't think so.
Chuggie, do you have an airplane form?
I mean, can we just look at this and try and gauge whether it
would hold our weight?
- Or like even just put a foot out on it and kind of test it.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Wait, how long is it?
How long is it?
- It's about like 45 feet across.
It's a pretty far walk.
- What if we took turns?
- Yeah, I think we'd take turns.
- I was gonna say, 'cause I could turn
into my submarine form, but I would be 30 feet.
- Miles.
- And you could walk on me.
- Just fall right off.
- Well, it would be hard to balance on is the only thing.
It's not gonna be a lot.
- So who's heaviest?
probably chuggy actually. I could turn into a ball and go in someone's pocket.
No, you could turn into a smaller guy is what you could do.
I guess the heaviest person should go first because then everybody else can go.
Well, I guess you're kind of a stout dwarf.
Because if you can make it across then we know the rest of us can no problem.
You know what, I've been convinced I'd do it. I just start running full speed ahead.
A couple things. First, roll athletics.
Or acrobatics, whichever one you want.
Let me see. It's going to be acrobatics.
Make sure you can maintain balance as best as you can.
17.
Nice. You're able to pretty much scale this pretty quickly.
Alright.
What you also hear is the distant sound of lightning and thunder.
And rainbow.
And as you look...
It's okay, I can block it with my metal shield.
You look up, kind of like diagonally, you're sort of your northwest, and you see this beautiful bird woman with this,
and she looks sort of like a harpy, and you see her, and it looks like she's coming down to attack you,
But then you see her almost get you, lightning streaking by you, and then her shooting up
towards the top of the tower.
And you see some sort of vast, like massive ghostly spirit arm swipe at her.
It's like something's going on at the top of the tower.
And you're able to get a sense of that.
I want to get to the top of this tower so bad.
Oh my god, I want to get in with that girl up there.
I like the hand.
I will say that you getting that 17, you guys can just run across.
There's no reason why him...
It would break the fiction if for some reason he makes it and you guys don't.
I'm not gonna do that.
Yeah, because I don't have a +1.
Yeah, I think it's shit stupid.
So you guys just make it across.
You climb up the rest of the tower.
I do a cartwheel across.
You do a cartwheel?
Don't do this.
I have +4 acrobatics.
Give a mouse a cookie, right?
Do you guys have that one?
Give a mouse a cookie?
Yeah.
Okay.
So you guys run across.
Eat for a week.
I remember that old book.
That old, old book came out years, so long ago.
Did Mark Twain write that?
I think so, yeah.
Shut the fuck up.
You guys make it across the tower.
Me, I like If You Give a Mouse a Bus and Starbucks Coffee.
That's the one that I read.
Damn, that's crazy.
Kitty got claws.
Oh my god.
That's fun.
Yeah, you guys approach the top of the tower and you see
The first thing you see actually is right in front of you you see an elevator
I'm fucking new it. I knew it. Oh my god. I fucking knew it whoever designed
this is a turd and he knows that and
Then you see you your heads whip right as you hear the crackle thunder again, and you see
Sticky fingers or what's left of him?
uh, bloody and bleeding out against the side of the wall.
Who's this bastard?
And then above you,
you see this,
this,
oh, sticky fungus.
Yeah.
You see this spirit that looks like
the holy police that you guys know and love.
But it also seems to be morphing and changing into a beast.
And also it's starting to like, sprout feathers
and it's this spirit that is attacking
hacking this feathered harpy creature you're watching them fight each other
if you guys get in the way of this you know for certain you will die
I'm hitting all fours
hitting all fours
I'm trying to blend in with the other ducks up there
I'm still invisible there's veins popping out on my neck and forehead I'm watching
I'm invisibly probably for certain I will die as I get in the middle of it
for
head got fucked I open up my mouth opens up like the sandworm from the clay
sandworm from Beetlejuice so I know where I pull I pull quadro mud marks out
of my mouth and put it oh yeah you see sticky fingers go what marks yeah that's
right and it's got Petrich his head the way he died he just died he did he did
the slump over in the eyes open thing yeah he fucking died and you see this battle
that is going on and you were watching the battle I've turned to them and I'm
like so if we get in the middle that we certainly will die right unless we have
a bird lady and then I'm saying like hmm what if like what if we just put one arm
just a little bit what if maybe like what if I put my finger in between me
- I mean, you could try, it's worth a try.
- I mean, you could try.
This is the most tempted I've ever made you guys probably.
Okay, I stick, I stick.
I do I have, do I, I do I have like rope or something?
- What if I--
- I would like to hold just a stick and to--
- That arrow's still on my ass.
- Okay, I hold, I'm holding the arrow.
- Ow.
I just hold the arrow to see what would happen to my finger.
Uh, luckily for you, the arrow just bursts into flames, but you're able to drop it in time.
You were about to take some serious damage.
Okay.
Okay, I'm gonna cast...
No, it's fine, 'cause I didn't take any damage, so we're probably safe to go in there.
So maybe I should put my head in.
How big is the spirit?
The spirit is, like...
It keeps changing size constantly, but it's like...
And it's fighting what exactly?
This, like, harpy.
- What's like the maximum size you would think it would be?
- When you see it get particularly enraged
and like cast some gruesome spells, it gets like 60 feet.
- So it's outside of the tower?
- It's like in the tower and also like among it
'cause it's like kind of phasing through it at the same time.
- Okay, it's like jumping in and out of the, okay.
- Yeah, it's like kind of like--
- And why are they fighting?
- Are we on top like open air?
Are we inside a room?
- You're like on the stairs that are like
kind of moving up towards the tower.
You're like kind of like looking out
and seeing this from the very top.
- But this is happening on the top.
- They're flying on the top.
- They're outside.
- They're on the top, yeah, outside.
- Okay, and so he sticks his thing basically
above the threshold of the floor from the stairwell.
He sticks the stick out and it bursts into flames.
- Okay, I use thaumaturgy to make my voice
boom up to three times as loud as normal for one minute.
I say, "What's going on?"
- Okay.
Yeah, the harpy first whips her head towards you,
makes direct eye contact with you.
I pee my pants.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I cast major image and I,
so it's his voice, but it's like the image
of Quadro Mudmarks, I guess.
Oh.
Like a giant version?
Yeah, like a 20 foot Quadro Mudmarks
'cause it's the highest I can make it.
All right, yeah.
She sees that.
She turns her head and her eyes get like ferocious.
like, going to attack this thing.
And then, *poof*, like, she just gets fuckin' whapped to shit by this spirit.
And you see her fuckin' sail across and crash into one of the- crash into the spiral tower you just came from.
And you see the spirit and it looks to you and it gives you- all three of you- it gives you like a knowing nod.
And you see the little police cap and it tips it to you.
*sniff sniff sniff sniff*
And it phases into the tower.
And you see the harpy fall to her death.
[laughter]
What the hell are we doing, man?
You guys have made it to the top of the tower, and...
You...
You've never seen the fog up close,
but seeing it now, it is clear that it is the same fog that followed the kaiju manji a bit further, amazingly.
You see the faint glow coming from a spire that's just above the fog,
So you're looking out at this vast field of the fog that is like the other side of the world
From what you can tell or where the world should end
It seems impossibly far away a miracle you could see something like that from where you stand, you know
You don't know this but the curvature of the earth should prevent you from seeing this
As you observe the fog and the spire across from you
Your sense of place begins to waver across a flat expanse the fog no longer sits, but doesn't move either
Or it's not it's not rolling forward. It's in a smoky stasis shifting its position in relation to you roll perception all three of you
Great 121 13
Crit 1 yeah, and what'd you get?
13 and 13 I'm standing I'm Stan. There's like one cloud. That's complete. I'm lost in a cloud
Completely I'm like a lot clipping in a video game cloud and my whole vision is white yeah
What you do notice is that when you look behind and around you whatever landmarks you registered appear to be moving away
The effect is not unlike a dolly zoom a shift in perspective that you were experiencing potentially literally you
Evil steve-o who's been on his perception game this session?
Mm-hmm you also notice that
When you look away from the fog the movement of those landmarks seems to decelerate as if you're resisting a pole
In all this the tower from across the way remains exactly in its implacable spot even as you feel the world around you shift further and
The fog closer that tower remains fixed
You observe the land around you again all the landmarks continue to move further from you however
They also begin to look like smears of earth, so you're kind of like drifting into this non moving fog
I'm looking at it with my ass
(laughing)
- Backwards.
That's why I'm so perceptive.
- And you can now make out the details of the tower.
You see on that tower in the distance,
not only that in place of mud mark,
not only that it's you, it's you there, all three of you.
You see yourselves in that tower.
You also see in place of mud marks,
a frog whose vacant, sweet, and receptive gaze
begets an unperverted masochism.
You know way too well.
It's Sullivan.
You feel within you the unshakable present fight to be redefined.
Something is pulling at you from a void in your gut.
This is no longer just a reconfiguration of Vistas. This is real.
You are going to that tower if you want to surrender to the fog.
So yeah, I... well, so here's my thing.
Is that I got such a bad perception roll that I can't even see...
I don't even know that there's the option to go back to the sub within.
- I think that Evil Stevel just died.
I think he just walked off the tower and fell and died.
I'm like, damn, that's really sad.
I guess we should go back to that magic academy, huh Chuggy?
- Yeah, I guess we gotta go back
and talk to Condoleezza Cartlow.
- All right, well let's just go do that then.
I thought there was gonna be something
at the top of this tower, I really did.
- Evil, evil, evil, evil.
- You are in, I don't wanna describe too much.
What I am gonna say is you are among
the kissing continents
with Sullivan the frog
and two versions of your friends that we will one day-
I realize that I'm just alone with Sullivan
and they didn't come with me
and I do a full Vader just-
NOOOOOO!
(Sullivan screams)
(laughter)
- You also, Sullivan also, on his knees
looking at the sky.
- But he's saying hi.
- Yeah.
(Sullivan screams)
(laughter)
- That was your Sullivan voice?
- Yeah.
(Sullivan screams)
- Yeah, like that.
- I didn't wanna do a dead disservice.
- Thanks.
Anyway, so Evil Steevel is--
- In our minds, he's dead.
- Evil Steevel, from what you guys can tell,
he just like, is gone.
- Yeah.
what has happened to countless people who've approached the fog, we will one day return
to the adventures of Duck-Ass Thievel and figure out what's happening there.
What a way to go out.
For Dogen, both of his friends died now.
He's basically the most depressed and anxious guy on earth.
So we'll see what happens.
He has to hang out with a submarine.
Well yeah, you guys head back to Condoleezza Marlow then.
Okay, well yeah.
- Yeah, so you guys, that elevator,
you can take that elevator,
it brings you all the way down to that room.
- Yep, I knew it.
Yeah, the little thing you couldn't get into.
- There were actually, there's actually a lot of stuff,
but you guys already cleared out stuff,
so we're gonna move on.
There's actually a lot more awesome stuff, as always.
- Okay, there's always a lot of awesome stuff.
- I'm sorry.
- That's what I would say too if I were you.
- Yeah.
- Okay, what's up, sorry.
- So we're going back.
- Yeah.
- We're about, we're.
- Yeah, you're gonna have to, yeah, okay.
Yeah, the cave is fine, it's gone, you guys can get back inside Chuggy and like, or sorry,
Jogan and Mudmarks can get back inside Chuggy and just go back to all the way up the river.
Back to Port Lowe's Prairie Berry.
Wait, wait, wait.
While we're in the river, I don't know the rules of Chuggy, okay?
And I just saw my other best friend die and I'm really depressed and I want to fucking
kill myself.
I'm like, "Chuggy, I just wanna die. Will you just turn back into your human form and kill me right now? Just crush my body? Just fucking..."
Um, say like, uh...
You're like, "I just need to hear one of CutiePopstar's... Mr. CutiePopstar's great songs."
I just need to hear one of CutiePopstar's beautiful songs right now, and I just need something to pick me up, 'cause I wanna fucking die.
Anything for my best friend!
Don't say that, though.
All right, I'm gonna turn into him right no
Chuggie turns back into you a person while
Well dog it's inside of him, but don't get a bum arches and you just I guess explode I
I've I turn into ribbons of meat
My eyes turn into goo. I like all that's it's like it's like you
Like you look when you pop the balloon and like smash
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - Like the, do-do-do-do!
- Yes. - It opens up with all of my guts.
- Oh. - I float into the, I do like a free-willy
jump into the air, and then just all of my guts open up,
and all the hands is toking and mud marks just plop into the water
like a shit. - And I'm just carried by the river
all the way back. - And you see there, Sherman is there.
- You're floating on mud marks. - And Sherman is there.
- Like a lazy river. - No, you're holding him like
Aaron Brockovich, you know, like, you're just walking by yourself
by yourself with mud marks on your hip like a baby and Sherman Sherman goes
because oh god are you all right where the other two come come come and he
leads you back through town back Oh to the tower where you see it on mud marks
revived not yet okay to Condoleezza Carlo who is watching the ships crash into
each other and smiling to himself he turns around he sees he says you've made
it back oh what happened to your friends
that's too bad um can you just any plops you down to sit there it's possible
down pops you down in a chair and he points his finger at your head and he
just extracts everything you saw and he just goes oh oh yes he's dead and then
And then you see his face go white, and he's like,
"Oh, that's bad."
- Well, I guess I better tell the Academy.
You, congratulations, are gonna be
an adjunct professor next year.
- Woo-hoo!
(laughing)
- We're gonna get you right to the Academy,
and you're gonna start your magical adventure.
- I'm dancing.
- I hope you find two new best friends.
- You're so alone.
- Yeah.
- Oh my God.
(laughing)
Just like walking in the rain.
- But I'm happy now.
I was like, woo-hoo.
- But your friends, all your friends have died.
It's actually, yeah. I say, I say, okay, I say I do, I do Homer Simpson,
WooHoo instantly when I find out I'm going to be an adjunct professor.
And then immediately after that, no transition at all. I'm, uh,
Freddie got fingered. Nobody knows my troubles with God scene.
Walking to the school with rain, it's raining. I'm completely soaking wet.
You're walking through the underground tunnel that he has. Yeah.
You hear that song. It's raining in the tunnel. It's raining inside the tunnel.
It's raining. He says, it just fit the mood. I don't know what to tell you.
I made it that way. Yeah. You're just walking through.
And next time, we'll perhaps see that.
Perhaps we'll head over to wherever Sullivan and Stievel are.
- But we definitely won't be going wherever Chuggy went.
- Chuggy has turned into the meat confectioner.
- Chuggy actually died.
- Yes, Chuggy is the only person who's really, really died.
- We're introducing the trebuchet,
we're starting to fracture things.
- It's like Pokemon.
- It's like Pokemon, red and blue.
- We have red and blue.
- And who knows, maybe one day Stievel and Duggan
may meet again.
They might, there is, I mean there's, they might, I'm not gonna say it.
Oh my god, this timeline has turned into Kingdom Hearts.
I'm not gonna say it's not Kingdom Hearts.
It's completely turned into Kingdom Hearts.
Holy shit.
Kingdom Hearts!
It was really good.
Thank you.
Alright.
I love Billy Zane.
Okay.
Goodnight everyone.
Goodnight.
Wow.
Well, it's been kind of weird being stuck in this void, realms deep, you know, after having
sort of a strange, or a death experience inside the Terrify Realm, but it's been nice getting
to know you.
You're a good kid.
I hope that one day, I don't know when, but I hope one day you get to meet your real dad
and can experience the world because it's not so bad, you know?
It can be kind of harsh, but it looks like I gotta go.
Looks like I'm being called back into something else.
I don't know what it is, but I hope I'll see you there.
Doug?
And it's not Doug Stiebel, right?
Nope, it's just Doug.
And one day I'm gonna get out of this.
Get out of this void and meet my dad.
I don't know what I'm gonna do when I do, though.
Whoa, I'm getting pulled away now to the void!
Out of the void now!
Whoa!
What is that tower?
Whoa, that's crazy!
Goodbye!
Goodbye, Doug!
Goodbye! I hope you get... where are we going safe?
Thanks! I hope your dad remembers you! Goodbye!
I hope he remembers me too.
[MUSIC]
[Music]