[MUSIC]
Last time on Trebuchet Village, we were introduced to Trebuchet Village,
a village that existed long ago on planet Ebound.
And the kingdom of the terrifier, a kingdom filled with orcs, goblins,
trolls, and other nasty beasts that won a great war against the forces of good. Chief among
these beasts were the Nards, terrifying furry beasts with yellow eyes, a terrible fanged
underbite, six legs with talons on the ends of them, two arms and a penis tail that blossoms
when they turn 18 and whispers dark thoughts in their ears. We also met our three heroes,
Dogen the Dirt Goblin, Paladin and Dirt Enthusiast, Patrick Jodar, Master Shoplifter and nephew
of a famous uncle, Evil Stevel, a vile cleric with a hip-hop edge. When they began their
day, our heroes were just simple sales associates at ye olde Sullivan's General Store who moonlight
as adventurers. They dispatched some unruly teenage grimlocks threatening their place
of work, and then split off afterwards to perform their adventuring duties, which took them
all to Mount Honestoodle, where the Crown Prince of the Terrifier Kingdom, the Nard Prince
Jumanji, was celebrating his fifth birthday. For Nards, turning five years old is an important
event, because the young Nards will perform their first kill in front of their community,
and in this case, in front of much of the kingdom's important monsters and beasts.
Mount Honestoodle is a mountain sacred to the Nards, prominently located near Trebuchet
village just outside the royal family's home of Claw Castle.
There, Dogen the Dirt Goblin was tasked with protecting the boy during this celebration
by a group of paladins hired by King Nardwaur, the prince's father.
Patric Yodar was meant to perform the greatest of heists by kidnapping the young prince in
order to further the ends of the Sticky Fingers Guild.
And Evil Steva was sent by the Pleasure Men, a cult who worship Discharge, the disciple
of the Terrifier, to destroy the boy and many prominent leaders of the Terrifier Kingdom.
The ceremony itself was a controversial affair with King Nardwar amending the ceremony.
Instead of any of these things happening however, our heroes, along with the entirety of those
in the ceremony, were launched at possibly high by some unknown force, possibly volcanic,
bursting forth from the mountain itself.
Dogen, Patric, Evil, Sullivan, and the Prince awoke to find themselves in Whippet Woods,
a dangerous and bizarre woodlands, nearly two weeks by carriage from their home.
As they began to acclimate to their situation, Patric Yodar grabbed a sword, sticking out
of a cheeky stone that begged for its sword to be pulled. This act awoke one of the many
strange beasts that threaten our heroes in these woods. So far from Trebuchet Village
and a battle ensues. How did our heroes survive? How did they land intact with a child prince
and their frazzled supervisor, Sullivan? Is it the work of the gods or the natural tempur-pedic
cushion that lines the forest floor.
Who's to say?
But what is known is that there is a lost prince and perhaps a reward for his
return would be greater than any reward offered for his abduction or destruction.
So yeah, you all were supposed to roll for initiative I think at the tail end.
But let's just install that.
I just did.
That Cameron, that is...
Oh Cameron, that's a...
I think you just sort of got a little
confused here. I think that's how it works.
I rolled for initiative, I got 139 successes.
No, so that's 100 D4s.
I got 134 successes this time.
Okay, let me roll for...
I got 18.
Okay.
I got 15.
I got nine twice. You got nine twice somehow, yeah.
Okay, nice. You seem to get to go twice, dude.
Oh, is that true?
And what did Sullivan get is the greatest question of all.
Ice me out.
Oh, no, you don't, sorry.
Ah!
I'm gonna ice you out when I get there.
What did Sweet, my Sweet Sullivan get?
if I remember his dex is yeah so I'll make everyone wait oh okay not bad Sullivan all right and
Sullivan got a 12. You are going to go first uh Dogen the dirt goblin so uh what happened was
is Patrick Yodar you grabbed the sword from the stone that was saying uh come on give it a tug
who knows and uh it then sort of pulled out from the sword's hilt you pulled out like a giant stone
worm monster that said I'm gonna eat you and so dog in the dirt goblin you're
sort of like on you're sort of got the jump on this thing so what do you want
to do
hmm you know I just want to say it's a worm and you are a dirt guy okay but
it's also it's made of stone right mm-hmm and stone is like that's like the
natural enemy of dirt. Well you were talking to the kid in the campaign about loam and stuff.
That's dirt. What was your plan if he was into dirt? I thought he had an advantage. Was he going
to climb through him? You're right Patrick. Seeing that it's a worm, a natural friend of the dirt,
and stone, the greatest enemy, it's shaking me to my core and I can't take my turn. Nice job,
Really, really clean.
I have to spend the whole turn commuting with my god to restore my faith.
And as you, what do you do to commute with your god?
I kneel down.
And is there dirt on the ground?
Yeah, yeah.
I scoop up a handful of dirt and I put it in my mouth.
Because that's how I, that's how it gives me a vision, you know?
You know, yeah, like I have Oscar or something.
Yeah, you hear a familiar voice of the dirt God himself Dogan.
Yeah.
Yeah, as he says through a mouthful of dirt, what's the
problem?
What's going on?
Oh Almighty Dogan hat tell me that riddle me that worship pray
tell me this.
Yeah.
Okay.
How can a worm, which is a friend of dirt, also be a stone, the opposite?
It's shaking me to my core so much I can't even take my turn.
This is a good question.
From my experience, when you see stone, think of it as just really hard dirt.
That's what I did.
Oh, okay, thank you.
Yeah, no problem.
And so, you're gonna give me the tithes next week, right?
What?
tithes do you know what tithes are?
you say tithes.
alright I gotta go.
I spit out the dirt.
you hear ptah.
can we hear the dirt god?
no just dogen.
he just edited me out saying it.
yeah so that's your turn.
it is now patrick.
it is your turn.
so you're face to face with this thing as it's sort of towering over you.
And do I have the sword?
Uh, no. So the sword like stayed inside of it. It was almost like his, it's like a baby's single hair sticking out.
Yes, exactly.
Uh, well, uh, well sir, I just want to say I'm uh, I'm very sorry for, for pulling your hair.
Uh, I really don't want any, any trouble at all. Uh, if there's any way that I could, uh, you know, get you, get you a glass of water, get you a glass of water or something, get you, uh, get you some...
to
a sandwich that I have in my bag.
That's just, you see how big I am.
Yeah, you know that is a good point.
It's just not sufficient.
I, honestly.
How about this, how about this?
You come with us.
No, I'm gonna eat you.
No, no, no, no, hold on.
We can ride on your back and we can find you an even bigger meal.
I mean, yeah.
Wait, can I add something to this?
Yeah, you should tell Patrick tell him because we're all tiny. We're all small. We're dwarfing goblins and shit. We can't find him a person
Yeah, we'll find you some humans. We'll find you some big people
You know cuz I mean, we're all we're all tiny people roll a persuasion check. Let's see how this goes
We have a big fat friend in the other neighborhood
See it. Okay. Yeah, he goes
You say you have a fat friend. Yeah, and this guy he is big
He is one of the biggest guys. Oh, he's gigantic roll deception now
Why'd you have to add that little fucking icing on the cake biggest guy we know 10
All right, you caught us he's the second biggest guy we know all right, you know I he's the biggest guy
I know I guess these two know somebody I know I have a lot of big friends. Yeah, he has a friend named fat Joe
Yeah, big pun
(laughter)
Those are two friends of his.
Yep.
Um, I only know that 'cause I, I, we were talking as we were falling down.
If you...
Yeah, and I know a guy named Patrick Doran is what I would have said a few weeks ago.
(laughter)
Now that, now that's just wrong.
Well, if you can find me a fat friend...
Well that's the thing, we're gonna ride on your back to the city to find you a fat guy.
You can't ride on my back.
I don't trust you.
What's that supposed to mean?
You could eat us so easily.
I mean...
Why would you say that?
Alright, roll persuasion.
Me?
Dogen.
I got 26.
Nevermind, we'll just keep yours.
That's about right anyway.
You kind of said the same shit.
Fine, you may ride on my back.
Ah, well that is great.
If you do not find somebody fat, what if we find somebody fat?
I'm not going to ride on your back.
if you do not find somebody fat
what if we find a couple hours what if we find a big tree on the way that is
like a reason i was no i need organic
but me and other organic that's
what i mean it me what if we would have we had a lot of field and i misspoke
i'm a stone
it's the way i think i think you can't
you did you know there's something that you can
if you find cows that would be great that's a great start
there are no cows or have you seen this place it's all like
momentarily i don't
well he's a good deal here with the area monkeys any thrown poop in
and weird birds that way that she sees and speak spanish it's not like a normal
place i need food well you speaking spanish is a normal
with the birds hold on where you are not going anywhere with you
i don't know
and deals all here the deals are prepared to have a lot on our races back
to dot what is the idea of yet just reality of the deal i was all i'd say
roll initiative. Nope, we already said it.
The deal's off.
For 18.
18 hits, yeah. Roll for damage.
8. Or would that be 10?
No because you're the only one who's in like 5 feet of him. If somebody else was also in
5 feet of him, then like you would get the sneak attack bonus too. Yeah, you get him for
eight damage but as the uh... arrow sort of uh... and by the way told nerds out
there were saying well it's supposed to be disadvantaged if you're using a
brain's weapon in
five feet of range fuck
that makes
that doesn't make sense and i was going to use my dad
and i'm not a good guy just don't i just don't agree with that
yeah i'm bits this is better i was supposed to be funny it's funny to shoot
a bow and arrow up close that's right a hundred percent
Yeah, but you see that it's sort of a, it doesn't seem to do as much damage as you thought it would.
Um, I've obviously...
What if I just use the two as a subtraction?
I bet, I bet because he's a rock, I bet you need, you gotta do something, you gotta do something.
Yeah, so we didn't do this much in...
Water.
...in, when we were in our last session.
It's not Pokemon, but we didn't do this much in Gun City, but some creatures are gonna have resistances.
So, when they do, I'll sort of be kind of coy about it like that.
But, since it's like the first creature you're coming across that has that, basically it just means that he's taking half damage for like, physical attacks.
This guy in particular.
Some will take half damage just from piercing attacks versus blunt attacks.
But in this case, it's just a big stone guy.
So if you shoot an arrow at him, you know, he's still organic enough to move around and stuff, but...
Okay, so we will ride on your back after all.
It's his turn now.
And so he got he got sort of checked there by Patrick Yodar.
It was a pretty hefty blow, even though it was it was sort of cut in half there.
So he's going to sort of bear down on you, Patrick.
He's going to try to attack you.
See how he does.
And I'll describe what he's doing to attack you and everything.
What's your AC?
My AC is 14.
Okay, yeah, so he
Like gets shot by the arrow goes oh we were good up you were gonna show me a fat guy
Yeah, but then you said something racist and he whips himself around. It's I don't want I did
I tell you whips himself around and tries to like, you know
Get you in like a coil like a snake like a snake do but you managed to sort of just
You miss about you. He's the he was bounce on your balls
Bounce above him as he tries to do that and he misses
And now it is actually
Sullivan the frogs turn and so do not fuck this up Sullivan
You what what do you mean? It's all on me. I believe in you something to let us ride on him again
You're such a good boss Sullivan and you're a great person. I'm your biggest fan
But I won't be if you don't
There's a lot there's a lot riding on this you see also that the little kid you know who seemed sort of brave before Prince
Jumanji is sort of cowering behind Sullivan now in the face of this monster loser
Five
And that's the guy that you chose to cower behind
He was nearest to me
You got to grow up. It's very funny. You're gonna do a lot of growing up in this
I forgot to choose spells or solve it hold on
I just didn't give him any spells.
He's kind of spelled.
Yeah, he's a bard.
Yo, yo, magic Sullivan.
Fuck.
All right.
All right, I'll give him this is a good one.
So you see him you see Sullivan takes out his piccolo and
begins to play it and it plays like I'll just a sort of weird
horrifying screeching note and he casts a fairy fire.
Um, and I think he is so bad.
Like, I made him so bad.
Alright, so let's see how this guy does against, let's see if this guy is able to resist fairy fire.
So you see this like, like weird like sort of uh sparkling flame start to go around this uh snake stone monster thing.
Um, as it tries to roll uh resistance against being uh entrapped in this thing and set a glow.
Which would mean you'd all have advantage on attacks on it.
So fairy fire does.
And he actually fails.
Yo!
Yes.
So, Solvin finishes his weird screeching note that blasts from his piccolo, and this thing
is sort of glowing now with this amber light that sort of shifts between amber and blue.
And you can see now, like, the vulnerable spots on him.
You can see sort of his movements become almost like, you can see the echoes of them.
You start to understand his patterns better.
He just says fuck.
So it is now your turn evil Stievel and Sullivan is a smiling smiling quietly to himself.
Okay, good.
So I'm thinking because Pat was able to lift him out of the earth by that little sword.
That's got to be some some weakness area up there on that sword.
So this thing is just onyx right?
Pretty much.
I'm realizing.
Yeah.
But I'm gonna use my chill touch and I'm gonna try and grab his sword and fling him around like Bowser.
Go for it.
Okay, that hits. That's gonna do necrotic damage regardless. If you wanna try...
Yeah, I would like to Bowser him, please.
To Bowser him?
Yep.
I mean...
We're on a big floating platform, right?
Yeah, I forgot to mention that earlier. You're on a big floating platform in like negative space.
That's great.
You're going to have to roll a strength check to do not a
problem.
Yeah.
Okay, go for it.
Six.
Okay, so you do that you see the hand sort of just like the
ghostly hand to sort of like get tired and go like like it
sort of like waves itself like it's panting and but it then
in in that it grips the sword handle harder and you see the
the Onyx guy go, "YOUCH!"
'Cause it's just like, it's just sort of like concentrated more necrotic damage.
And that, that does, that does full damage.
So you, you did hurt this guy quite a bit.
He's not looking too hot.
Um, uh, okay, cool.
So we're back to the top of the order.
Um, uh, Dogen, it's your turn.
Now that you've communed with your god, and he told you to think of dirt, stone, as just really hard dirt.
Yeah.
Does that help?
So I can't hurt dirt.
I could never attack something made out of dirt.
You could like mentally hurt it though.
Okay.
You're not even dirt!
You see, I turned to my friends and was like, "That'll really get him!"
Try stabbing him while you say it.
When I turn around to whisper that to Evil Stievel and Patrick Jodar, I'm holding my
war shovel over my shoulder and I turn around and it just hits him by accident.
Yeah, it counts as an attack. Roll attack roll yeah.
16. That hits.
It's 11 damage. Fuck yeah, yeah. So you're just like,
yeah you just uh, donk, like donk him on the head. You say that to him he's like, "What?"
And then you whip around and hit him with the shovel. And uh yeah he takes uh, so he takes
some pretty significant damage there. It still is going to be like halved, but he's looking really
bad off now. He's sort of like, is kind of woozy. He's probably regretting not taking you guys up.
Let's get him. Let's now, let's get, take him to the city. Let's get him to drive us somewhere.
Now that you're about to die, you ready to go on a road trip?
Roll persuasion.
Whoops.
You take the first one.
Well, I do.
Yes, wow, that's a great 20.
You see him do the
do the from the Hercules cartoon.
I'm not worthy.
Worm bow and you see him go.
Just.
Okay.
You want me to stab you to death?
No, don't do that.
That's actually, that's something I'm very much into.
I, I love murder.
*groans*
You see his face sort of change back to the chipper, uh, happy, cartoonish sort of looking stone that you saw earlier before you pulled the sword out or tried to pull the sword out?
*inhales*
He goes, "Come on, I'll put my back! It'll be a good time! Who knows what'll happen, where you will go!"
See, I like this guy. Let's keep this guy around, alright?
Maybe we won't have to do that again.
You're like the mayor from Nightmare Before Christmas.
I don't know what that is.
Yeah, me neither.
Sure, it's awesome.
Sure, basing your personality around that's fine.
Yeah, I'd love to get some fingerless gloves from that movie.
Up on my back, you see he coughs up like a couple of pebbles.
He's just in a lot of pain.
Is the sword still in his head?
Yeah, it's still in his head.
So we don't have to find you a fat guy or a cow now?
No, no, just don't kill me, you know?
Alright, alright, and I like put my knife away.
I sit on his head, on his sword like a dildo bicycle.
Yeah, I like stuff in my ass, I told you I'm evil.
What about that is evil?
I don't know, I'm evil and I like it.
Alright, well your logic there is sound.
I'm not going to look into that any further.
Thank God!
Okay. So you all hop on his back, including, you see the Prince Jumanji is a little hesitant,
but he manages to sort of just crawl and get himself up there.
And Sullivan's on the back as well. And this thing now, he says to you,
"Where do you fellas want to go then, huh? Where do you want to go?"
- Where, what, I don't think we know.
- So, out of the woods.
- Out of the woods.
- Over the river.
Through the woods.
- Through the woods to grandmother's house.
- Oh, take us to grandma's house.
- All right, sounds good to me.
And you see him just about face
and dive deep into the woods at like a very quick speed.
- Uh oh.
- Yeah, you guys pass by all these weird woodlands
these these sort of this brush and this this like these weird critters and
plants that are like squawking and chirping it's a very weird surreal sight
and he just sort of abruptly stops in front of this clearing and you see a
massive tree in front of you in front of this clearing and he says grandma's in
there if you want to see her now I feel I feel like there's a little bit of
deception here I think that you're a little bit mad at us your voice is
starting to change a little.
- No, come on.
I mean, I am, look, I'll be honest with you.
I'm very scared of you.
- Yeah?
- So I'm not gonna do anything crazy.
- How scared?
- On a scale.
- Is this like your grandma?
- No, she's sort of the grandma of the area.
You know what I mean?
- I know exactly what you mean.
- Every area has a grandma.
I think we all know that.
- Well, the Kubler elves sort of have
a matriarchal structure, right?
So she lives in here.
- The Kubler elves.
Yeah, they're kooblers.
Alright.
Say no more.
Yeah, I get that one too.
Yeah, we know. We know.
Is it crystal clear?
Mhm. Okay.
Right as rain.
So, koobler elves.
Yeah, anyway, so, this is the grandma in here.
Okay, I go knock on...
What, did grandma's in the tree?
That's what he said.
This guy's weird. I'm gonna go knock on the tree like a door.
Mm hmm. As you do, you see uh the sort of an outline start to
form in front of the tree that looks like a door and you see a
little, you know, little slider slide through and you see these
uh little spectacles peeking through and you hear uh uh who
who is it? It's your grandson. Oh dear, please do come in and
And you see the door sort of start to peel away bark by bark
and then just sort of fall away into the ground and you see a
really beautiful little like hobble and a beautiful little
grandma and she's she's got a little coobler elf ears like a
seven described the grandma.
Yeah, so she has in detail.
Yeah, so she's head to toe.
Okay, sorry sizes bust size bust is a triple H like the
wrestler.
And her hair is of course a it's just sort of like a turf
bang sort of look.
She's very in these days.
Not that turfs are and she now I love her.
(laughter)
- Dogon.
- That's what turf bangs are in this fantasy world.
(laughter)
- It's the blade of grass.
It's the grass that's hanging on your forehead.
- Yeah, it's the turf bangs.
- Yeah.
And she's wearing otherwise,
sort of like a very like dowdy,
sort of worker elf kind of outfit.
And she sort of like looks around
and she sees the sword and the stone and you look now if you turn around you see it is
now just a stone again.
And she's like, "Oh, you ran into old sword stone over there."
Is it sword stone stuck in my butt?
That's his name?
I don't think his kind have names.
They're just sort of mean, you know?
Oh, you're a racist grandma?
No.
racist stone and like her grandson.
Come in come in.
Please.
I have some cookies for you.
All right.
Well, I can't pass that up both in and out of game.
So yeah, you guys go in it's a pretty small hobble.
You're you're kind of all you're all obviously fine to fit in
there because you're all also little Sullivan and the boy
included and when she sees the Nard her.
sort of widen and she says, oh, I haven't seen a nod around
here in a long time and you see the prince sort of like just
sort of looks left and right.
He's like a little nervous.
She says no, you're welcome to come into I'm not afraid of
you like other elves are and she sort of brings you guys a
little plate of cookies.
She says now what ails you?
What are your troubles?
What are in these cookies?
milk sugar
dirt dirt
And she winks at she winks at you Dogen thinking you mean chocolate maybe or
Anything other than dirt?
When I tried it, can I use my um
Divine sense to see to detect a good and evil. Yeah, absolutely
Okay, I'm gonna use that. Mm-hmm. I
I use it.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, so when you do that, it's basically you're checking to see if there's anything
in the location that's affected by, you know, that is a...
Yeah, I just want to see if the cookies are like evil magic or something.
Yeah, no.
Yeah, they're just cookies.
They are straight-up cookies.
You're not detecting anything crazy about them at all.
Do I detect evil Steevel?
Yeah, you just...
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, when you look over at evil...
Do I have to use detect Steevel for that?
When you look over at Evil Stevel, you just hear the seer in its entirety somehow in a moment.
I'm popping my balls with a needle while you look at me.
[laughter]
You see Sullivan the Frog, he takes off his hat. He's wearing a hat, Joey, if you're listening to this, somehow.
It's all that says, uh, uh, uh, Ms.
Ms.
Grandma, uh, you see me is okay.
I got some info.
Did you do see that?
She, uh, does not have a ring on her finger.
Baby.
You ever thought of being a movie star?
Where he, we're three casting directors.
You're looking for our, our, our lead role.
I guess roll deception.
Mike love 3.
I'm going to put my foot down if he has to roll deception.
I've already rolled it. No I have not.
Oh no.
I'm not going through with this.
It's a hand.
What is happening?
Never mind I guess.
Kind of another reality up.
It got kind of stopped, kind of halted.
I'm sure there's a world.
You know what I want to do right now.
Oh it's crystal sir.
I'm sure there's another world and another podcast where this all ends very differently.
It's probably on Gas Digital.
Yeah, probably.
Yeah, anyway, continue with the cookies or whatever.
By the way, we're three casting directors.
to cast you in our play and it's nothing nothing sexual about it.
No, but do you have a black couch in this hobble?
No it's not that.
That is not what's gonna happen at all.
uh... probably problem
it's because do you know what do you do you know do you know oklahoma
can you see you sing a few bars from oklahoma for us
that exists in this time
uh...
all
all right you guys i don't know we're feeling that he's really not a citizen
she's horrible and uh...
and i know why we ever wanted her in our sexual play
So what ails you my children?
I was trying to distract you.
So I could talk to my boys.
We're trying to get back to Trebuchet village.
We got launched here by a volcano.
With a force of 1000 dragons.
It's 10,000 first of all.
Oh, it was even worse than we thought.
(laughter)
Oh, when she hears 10,000 dragons, her eyes go wide.
You better believe it.
Which is incidentally the name of our play, too.
Well, wow, that's quite the story.
I haven't heard of this kind of being launched so far.
This is, this is, you're quite far from the village then.
Yeah, we know.
As far as getting back.
We've already said this lady.
This lady's old.
God damn it, she's so old.
As far as getting back goes, you'll have to probably have to cut through, well, the bog
of the mud men.
At least-
Ooh!
I like the sound of that.
I figured you would since you hoped there was dirt in my food.
I thought you thought I meant chocolate.
No, that's what the DM said.
How'd you hear that, bucko?
I'm confused now, these men are made of chocolate?
Like a...
Well, some say they're made of chocolate.
Wait, the DM is making us go through the land of the chocolate men?
And some say they're made...
I don't know if I want my character to be in this campaign anymore.
You know, you're now sort of bringing the racial elements to the one.
That's sort of on you a little bit, right?
No, actually, we're trying to go back to trebuchet, so that we can meet racial elements.
uh, it's a girl I had back then.
[laughter]
It's a girl, it's a girl I was, uh,
quite fond of.
[laughter]
Oh, yeah, we're trying to, we're trying to rescue
the princess Rachel Lee charged.
[laughter]
So how far
away's the bugman
bought, the
uh, mud bought
the place?
How far away is that shit?
Hey, uh, hey, hey, grandma, I just, uh, not to alarm you,
but your carbon monoxide detector has been beeping this whole time we've been in here.
Which is magically powered by the--
Yeah, your carbon monoxide bird has been squawking.
Yes, like the Flintstones.
Yeah, like the-- yeah, I'm getting a little confused by the setting of this whole thing.
(laughing)
She says, "Well, to get to the Mudman Bog,
you'll have to cut through a good few hours journey
north of here.
I would suggest you take your stone friend.
It'll make the going a bit easier.
And and I also suggest you take this and she and you got each a little sack
filled with
An extra day's rations. So you guys have sort of two days rations now. Oh, I already have one day's rations
I don't need this. Oh
Okay, well, actually I'll take his rent
Sure, and
she
turns to
the the little prince and
she says
now
Do you are you safe with these men and you see the prince no
Not at all and you see the prince sort of look to you all and
He remembers Dogen and yeah, I smile really big at him and then my teeth are just covered with dirt
Yeah, and he sort of like the kid sort of like laughs at this, you know and goes yeah, I'll be okay
All right. Yeah, and they're safe with me with me. He's saved with me, too
Yep, and so you seem nervous Sullivan do you have a crush on this grandma?
We can we can arrange we had a we had a nat 20 roll we can
Up, I don't think that carries over the way you think it does. It's pretty much
For the that, you know that action, please don't I'm tired of fucking things in these things
I just I want to be normal
All right. Let's go to the bog frog
There's something about it's like a black hole we try to recall that yeah
Mud bug bug yeah, but the bug box and
As you guys are bugged as you guys are leaving. She says to you and and do
Beware that the mud men are not
their
Kind they're fearful
But do stay away from the kitsune. They are
Terrible fox creatures that worship the jester of the woods. I
Know that's what sounds like a lot of a lot of information right sort of wrapped in that I'm realizing now a little confusing even
There's a jester in the woods a jet. They the Fox
Foxes are the it's oh, so this is like a worthy Fox
It's the jesters in the box and the bugs are in the box is like a Fox worthy of of it being exalted
it's the whip it would be where the laughter and
She shuts her door and
That's kind of weird now we got another step all right, I guess I'll open his door I
I open it and I leave.
You see her like, when she shut the door, she just like, was like, hmm hmm, like carrying
on doing her things like you guys weren't there.
Uh, yeah.
And you turn-
You guys, just real quick, uh, I think that lady's completely out of it.
I think I'm gonna, I think I might, I think I'm gonna do some thieving.
Yeah, okay, here.
I can distract her if you want.
Yeah, that'll be great.
Can you actually, uh-
No, I got a whole, I got a-
Yeah. Thank you so much. That'll be amazing. I go back inside. I don't say anything. I take out my
what's it called my pouch of forever dirt, which is a it's a magical pouch that's filled
with infinite dirt and I open it up and I just spray dirt into her face.
Okay, I'll have her roll a god I guess it doesn't deal any damage. I know that I'm just thinking
I'm double-checking for myself. I don't want to hurt so I don't stealth right now. Oh
They do take damage if you spray 30 feet of dirt, okay, okay
Wait, I don't would be very funny if you just kill her just fill her whole house with dirt
Okay, I started I shoot it around her feet I started casing her in dirt
Okay, she's like oh, oh your pouch is spilling and my bad Patrick. Yoda. Are what are you up to?
I'm just like looking through
What does she have in there describe the house? Yeah, sure
So it's sort of you know, it's sort of a classic like a like gnome hobble looking kind of place except it's a cooler elf
so there's like wooden cupboards and
Like pots and pans some like vases that are like made of wood that hold little flowers
It's like a very homey looking place
So kind of Nate if you want to look at one in the coverage you can but also name something
That's kind of like that and I'll I'll sort of be able to figure out if it's in there or not
I
Find this safe
You find
If you look in a cupboard I look at covered this just a safe on the wall
If you want to do this stealthily roll roll stealth
It'll be a little bit easier because she's a little distracted by all the dirt 25. What are you doing? What the fuck?
What is happening? It's amazing
All right. I mean, yeah, you get you kind of get free range of the cupboard
I just take the safe out of the wall
You uh, I'm trying to think what you get from this. Let me look at my notes for
I've organized everything very differently from this. It's very exciting for me. I can't wait to share it with everyone
Yeah, okay cool so she has in here you managed to get from here like a
About 45 gold pieces and a wand of some kind
as well as sort of a box of her cookies that are sort of like boxed up.
So you managed to get all of that and just like shove it in your
like sack and just sort of bolt out of there.
So wait, what do I get now? So you have 45 gold pieces.
How do I add this? So go to your
in your equipment, there's like a currency option.
Yeah, you can add the gold in there. 45
And then what else?
You also got a wand. It's unidentified right now, so just put it in your notes.
And if you... somebody has an identify spell, they can figure it out.
I'll just...
Anywhere.
Like in other possessions, in equipment, you can put it there.
And then also you got a box of cookies.
So, those box of cookies count as three uses of a healing potion.
Okay.
So, you can add three healing potions if you click "Manage Equipment".
and add those in there.
And that's basically the same amount.
Wand and cookies and other possessions and then three healing potions.
Perfect.
Do I have healing potions already?
No, you don't. So this is good.
Healing potions are very valuable.
I have healing too, just so you guys know if you ever need.
Yes, you have Lay on Hands.
Okay, so I just added those.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, so the dirt is just slowly filling up.
Like, Dogen, are you just like
looking at her? Just like...
I'm looking the other way. It's an accident.
Oh, okay. So, uh, yeah.
Boy, I sure hope my pouch is closed.
[Laughter]
So you manage to pick up some of the dirt, I guess, and sort of help her clean it up.
Oh, no, I don't.
You don't? You just leave?
I shovel her out.
She's free, but the dirt's staying in. Dirt belongs in houses.
That's one of the main tenets of my religion.
Yeah, she's sort of all turned around by all this.
this
I'm
Okay, cool. So you guys get out of there and you look back to
find that the the stone guy is gone. I mean he ran like the
second he got a chance to my **** started frowning.
Yeah. So what do you guys want to do? You can head start
heading north. It's a few hours journey. She said to get to the
mudman. If you'd like to start on that journey, I start the
journey. Yeah, I want to meet these bugs. I gotta see these
mudmen. So you guys are traveling through the woods and
you reach the sort of you reach a another sort of point in
this. You've been traveling for a few hours. You're getting
a bit tired. You know the kids getting a bit tired too. He's
sort of trying to keep a brave face on. He's a nerd. so
They're pretty tough, but you know, it's a few hours of travel, so it gets a little exhausting.
And as you it starts to feel like a little bit, you know, more humid around here.
You think you might be approaching some sort of bog or swamp or something, but instead you
sort of come upon a small Creek.
It's flowing gently through the woods and you see on the other side of the Creek, you
know, that's further north.
That's kind of where you need to go.
The Creek's not going to be hard to get through.
It's not like you have to roll or anything for it, but you see on the other side of the creek also a sort of
mangled like tent like the first signs of like other sort of you know
Bipedal, you know like creatures with you know who are normal regular
And you see just like a completely mangled tent and you also see they like
massive like
15 foot by 15 foot iron cage with the bars bent
and
Sorry if the person in there can't hear me.
Whoa!
Hey, you know, I'm, uh...
Oh, keep going, man.
You know, I take pride in good design.
Oh, yeah!
And this is actually upsetting me.
He's very upset.
I don't have any other emotion than this.
Can I go? I'm gonna go inspect the cage.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, go for it.
Yeah, you have to roll for that.
I mean, you could just walk over and inspect the cage.
It is indeed like a iron cage where the bars have been bent.
You see, you do also as you get closer to it, you like your
and you see like a pile of like shit, like big, like a big pile of shit.
And, you know, and look at that.
I mean, they know that makes more sense.
You can leave the cage bars nice and big because that shit ain't going to escape.
You know, when I when I first first second there, I thought this was a hotel.
That is a bad hotel.
Yeah, this would have been the worst hotel I've ever seen.
When I see the big pile of poop, I scoop up a handful of dirt
and I put into my mouth because I have a question for Dogen.
The dirt God. OK, yeah.
No, what's up?
Well, how am I supposed to feel about poop?
What's the relationship to dirt there?
It's this brown portion, you know?
Oh, well, you know, so
I'm trying to really figure out the voice for this guy and I think I think this is kind of funny if a guy sounds like this
so
Real poop's not really dirt, right? Yeah, I mean, it's not really dirt. It's brown. It's brown and people don't like it
So the sort of like a cousin, you know, right? It's like the cousin you don't like
It's just you know, you can see it as like a I your sexy cousin no, that's not don't take I would
Can you get straight to the point here?
So you can, what the hell are you talking about?
You can talk to my God right now.
Okay.
Patrick, can you, you can look, you can regard poop as something that is to be
respected, but not necessarily touched.
Okay.
All right.
Good.
That was okay.
That was a close one.
They will not touch the poop.
Okay.
And, uh, yeah, he sort of vanishes.
I just needed to establish that.
was
I have a minus one investigation. I'll invest in mine though. I have a pretty good investigation. I got an eight. Mm-hmm
I got a seven
Damn that's not very good. Are you gonna invest? I guess I can
Yeah, thank God I saved your ass. Yeah, so you
Evil Steve-el from your time seeing causing messes like this where there's mangled
Shit everywhere and actual shit everywhere. You sort of are able to parse the wreckage
You see in the tent as you sort of peel through it. You see what looks like a flyer
for
Something it's it's it says
Come one come all see the magnificent Vegas brothers in our beast. That's too strong to hold in this cage
And as a picture of the cage you see there.
And also next to that note, you notice actually a severed hand
resting on it and you see a picture of the beast in there.
It's not a picture of it rather, you know, it's first of all the
drawing but second of all, it's like silhouette right?
So it looks like a big hulking creature from what you can tell
sort of like troll like almost or like an abominable, you know, Sasquatch-y type of guy.
And you also find a small iron dagger that seems pretty unused,
as well as 15 gold pieces also sort of lying around, abandoned presumably in haste maybe as they left.
But also with that 20, I'll say that you can also sort of see
you start to get the sense of where of tracks of where
this beast could have went.
They're pretty big.
You see sort of claw marks in the ground going further down
the Creek, which isn't explicitly North, which is where the
mud men are, but it is sort of that's sort of where you're
seeing those tracks going.
can can also it will all take a gold
he he he he
well you know that nobody else is going to jump on it output fifteen gold pieces
in my
inventory what's mine is you and then you know all all all all lick the
footprints or whatever the fuck patrick was to do
fifteen
you want to have it do you have a uh... relationship with dirt
so yeah yeah
you know it away and i'm gonna make you stop i think that i pick up the dirt
from the
I could let it out in the money for one instead. No, it's a survival is all about tracking. Oh
13 roll again, you got advantage advantage. I didn't hear that for it. Okay. Wow
Yeah with that 14 you have a pretty good sense of where this guy where this beast
went you could see sort of it probably went down the creek because it was
Either it was chasing something or because it just would stay by the creek as something that creatures tend to do.
And the creek you can also see bends a bit north.
So there is a chance that it could lead into the bog, which makes sense because it's a creek.
So you could follow this track to, at the very least, make sure you're not ambushed by something like this.
That would be sort of the advantage you're gathering from this.
But there's also no reason why you can't continue to cut through the woods where you were going
also, so you guys landed here probably closer to
Where you woke up sort of towards daytime right the ceremony was kind of in the evening
And now it's about mid afternoon approaching late afternoon. So
You know you travel a few more hours. It'll be night. You might want to rest
Set up camp or something
traveling at night in the woods is not always advised.
I say we I say we follow the footprints because that sounds fun.
Is there like a
you're like a hotel around here or something?
Why are you asking me?
I really I'd love to, you know, I'd love to just go to like a restaurant
that's inside of a hotel.
That's kind of kind of my thing as a man who was was born with luxury.
I uh, you know, I have to say that actually that sounds pretty good.
I mean, I know restaurant right now.
I like the little, what they have, the little butters wrapped up.
And oh my God, you are so right.
Sullivan, I love you.
I'm your biggest fan.
Yeah.
Can I bunk with you tonight?
Uh, well, there's no bunks, but yeah, really close to you.
Uh, I mean, I don't see why not.
I'm such a big fan of your work.
So I haven't, I haven't rolled it in the way you played the piccolo is so allure.
okay so i i uh... sort of a workplace violation maybe
i don't really know what's going on between you two but uh...
if we could find like uh... maybe like a four star maybe a five star hotel
that's kind of the uh... the life i'm uh...
accustomed to
why not a six star one
you know i i don't- it's fantasy world that gets infinite stars
yeah let's try and find a one hundred
six-star can was just talking that's ice high sorry sometimes you guys
and jim on g_ the prince you have not said a word this whole goddamn time
i said why said was that he said some words that i i i guess i just uh...
i'm sorry listening to you 'cause your child yet that's
like it that a lot
at home so yeah
responded to that whole life
that's bad
the
so now that you've bought it
what don't want become a some hotel
yet think i think you would probably i mean
is the uh... the son of
of a royal
you probably uh...
yeah probably the most about
hotels well there there's a six star when i was just saying inside clock
hassle
uh... maybe when we get back we can all go
also you're not talking about right now you're talking about
no let's go back to trebuchet village uh... i'm five so you know
i've never really been to the woods i'm pretty scared
now that's probably why you've been so good anyway stay quiet also i was sick
of hearing you talk also i'd like to apologize to the frog here
uh... i wasn't gonna stab you five hundred times in the leg on our
i'm over that
is it does although i would have had to have addressed that earlier
that to make logical sense i feel like i can't
among keep up that emotion now
that's all gone now
all right now we've forgotten that up. I forgot where I was going with that bit
anyway can we just go on with the story?
yeah sure. Should we follow the footprints?
all right I think we should follow the footprints
yeah let's just go
we can just like step in them like it's
plus none of us took any damage right? we should be good to just keep going.
actually i'm gonna use my... who's damaged?
uh... it's good i have a look at the negative two health points and less
than a year old all-time and also
i do not have a negative two point sorry i'm subtracted to have seven sorry
you know i don't really think it's not a good idea but i have actually
you've been a ghost this whole time that's a plot twist that would be a fun
yeah i'll tell you all feel you to for me and you both the full age because i'm
missing again i can feel up to five h p prolong rest
Just in case, because I figure we're going to, we're going to rest pretty soon.
Anyway, you never know.
All right.
So you keep following the footprints.
Yeah, me too.
So yeah, that 14 again, you're pretty, you're able to keep track of that.
Those footprints you're able to sort of get the sense of, of, uh, you're able
to sort of keep up with them even as they grow a little bit fainter as you, they,
the, the running, whatever sprinting this beast was doing got more intense and you
follow along the creek. You see sort of a you see a birds
jumping out of the water and fish flying in the air above
them swooping down to eat the birds in the water. You know
that's so that's seriously strange. It's **** wacky here
and you also as you follow the creek, you also start to start
to hear. A bit of laughter you start to hear a bit of that.
Oh boy, that sounds great. We should know what's up with it.
Uh, it's not coming from any particular direction.
And you guys walk for another hour or so.
And, uh, it doesn't feel like...
Uh, actually, you know what?
What's everyone's passive perception?
Ten.
Mm-hmm.
Um...
Fourteen.
Mm-hmm.
Do you wish you...
evil swell you for a day
weird
that patricia are yet yet you got such good
you know you know you know i don't know if it will be crazy okay uh...
so yeah patrick you know there
uh...
youth
began to notice that
the sun has not moved
uh... or whatever
plenty but i'm not touching that it's a football yet he had that the son of the
Hey, you guys, the the king's son has not moved.
He's still he's all the way back there.
Oh, yeah, we got to go get off.
And as you walk back to pick up the boy,
you realize that the sun in the sky is also not moved.
Maybe he can try.
And as the sun moves, the sun in the sky moves.
It's a puzzle. You see, it's like brain
courtesy of Jonathan Blow.
So yeah, but you notice that the sun in the sky is not moved as you guys have been walking down the creek.
Hey guys, the sun in the sky hasn't moved either.
And as you...
I just realized this.
And as those words sort of leave your mouth, sort of leave your mouth,
so you hear the laughter grow a little bit louder
and you see what looks like kind of
pixies of some kind sort of fly around your head patrick she o'derr
uh... i see some pixies flying around
uh... it's not going to make it
it twice as long
Yeah, literally, yeah, just double it.
I'm doing this for the fans!
[laughter]
That's right, you guys want long episodes, right?
This is...
This is how we do it.
[laughter]
Yeah, and, uh, they, they, uh,
they, they are
flying around your head, and they're,
they're sort of giggling and laughing,
and, and, uh, um,
you see them sort of, uh, uh,
look toward you all, and they say,
here to see the jester? No. To see the jester and you see them
they're kind of repeating it back and forth and laughing as
they're saying it. So the the jester the uh the kitsune
jesters? Oh no not the kitsune. They just worship the
jester. They worship the jester. They see
they're just they're sort of like talking in time in like a
weird rhythm. And that's and that's the and that's the uh
The worthy fox you were you were talking about jester fox worthy
That's what worthy fox meant, okay
All right. I'm back now. I get it now. Um
uh, you see them say
Uh, if you wish to see the jester you can if you want to see the jester and they say that again again
No
Uh
And you see them one of them starts to cry
When you say no
Alright fine, I guess we'll I guess we'll see the no don't
They unless we should I agree. I said it was like evil or something
Grandma was an evil because I'd use detect evil when we were in the you did just use it on the cookies
You guys could roll an insight check. See what you think. Yeah. Oh, yeah
I'll use it again right now. I got a 15 in sight. Yeah
I mean, the divine sense is only going to be able to tell you if something is celestial or fiendish really.
Which in this case, no, I mean, they're neither celestial nor fiendish.
So they're not good nor bad from what you can tell, at least in that classical sense.
For example, like if you used divine sense on a demon, you would know it was on somebody and they were a demon.
You suspected they were a demon, then you'd be like, oh, shit, that's a demon.
Um, uh, but yeah, sorry with 15 insight.
What are you trying to get insight on exactly?
Evil.
If the, if the, um, you can't really just gather like from what they're saying,
whether or not the jester is bad, but what you can gather, I'm trying to get insight
on vibes.
Yeah.
That's a good thing.
I mean like they're fey creatures like pretty clearly.
So the vibes you're getting are like they are dangerous and weird.
And there's no real way to know how to predict what they're going to do next.
Let me ask you all a question.
to you like to play tricks on uh on guys like me see you see you're laughing
right now I you're laughing you're laughing harder after I say that all
right you're laughing is as hard as you can I don't want anything to do with
these pixies yeah and it seems like you're gonna get very upset if we don't
see the jester so we don't have in a it's kind of a we don't know that I mean
Let's just try walking away.
Yeah, maybe we should...
Maybe we should walk.
Let's just keep going. Maybe we should walk and like make sure that there's none of
them behind us. So maybe we'll walk. Yeah, one of us can face backwards.
I'll stand guard.
Okay, one of us stands.
You stay here, you make sure the pixies don't follow us and then
we'll keep going. Yeah, no, you guys go on without me.
Yeah, we'll do something like, okay, so we go forward.
And if the pixies start to move, you run and catch up with us.
Tell us and then you can go back to see where they went.
Something like that.
But when you do that, make sure you walk backwards so you don't lose an eye.
You don't want to lose sight of the...
Yeah, don't lose us.
Maybe I'll do the moonwalk so they think I'm actually walking towards them.
Hey, if you can do the moonwalk...
Not a problem.
A dance created by the ultimate evil.
most evil dance you can do. Moonwalk. That would be amazing. That would just be top notch.
I would absolutely love it. Evil Steve, roll performance. I don't have to start yet, right?
No, you don't have to do it yet. No, you know what? I'm calling your bluff. I'm about to
fucking blow your mind with this performance check. Wow. A pretty fly moonwalk. You see
You see them like sort of like, huh? I'm almost at you guys pretty soon here. Give me a minute
They're like watching and they're like, huh? Like like confused. I'm almost there
You can see I'm walking towards y'all I'm like I'm like I'm about to be at y'all so you gotta fucking chill right now
Cuz I'm almost there. Here I come
My also I could be under some sort of shrinking spell also
Logan and I have not left yet
I might have pop my shit too early
See the pixies are laughing - they're laughing along and they say the Chester will see you later
and they just poof they vanish and sort of like a cartoon you see the sunlight
and it becomes night. I turned to the party and I just say now you
see that that does not bode well. I mean that right there that's good
conflict resolution I don't see any way that that could you know that's that was
fine that was easy we didn't have to fight anybody. They said the jester will
see us later that's that's a that's like maybe maybe it's like how they say
goodbye yeah right yeah maybe or maybe the just oh my god Sullivan we are on
the same wavelength that's crazy I have a nice wide sleeping bag by this is so
much worse how far away is evil Steve oh I'm super far away and I see that they
left and I open up a notebook to a page it says dance offs one and I put a tally
the
was
is
not a map that's not what I was asking. No, I could draw a map. Yeah, that would be great.
We could actually figure out where we're going. Okay, I draw a circle and then I put a dot
in the middle that says "us." Something like that. I like take the paper out of his hand
and I just kind of like slap with my back hand. I'm like, "Yeah, this is perfect." Yeah,
So it's night time now, so you guys can either set up camp or keep walking to the creek.
I can't wait to set up camp.
Okay.
So you guys spent some time getting some logs together.
I'd say you're all adventurers, so you have some experience and knowledge of how to set
up camp.
You see while you're doing that, little Prince Jumaji is trying to do the moonwalk with his
six legs and he's just not quite able to do it.
It's just kind of a little confusing.
Wait, can evil Steve just like be like a dance mom for him now?
Yeah.
It's just like getting mad at him for not doing the steps correctly.
You're still walking forward!
I just, I don't, I have too many legs for this I think.
Who made this dance you said?
Stop making excuses. It doesn't matter who made it.
He was, man he was evil.
Okay, uh, alright. So let me try...
No, also the talons I'm realizing now also make it really hard.
'Cause I have talons.
Maybe you just weren't built to dance.
I don't know if I was built to dance.
Then stop trying. Go ahead, give up. See if I care.
I'm not gonna give up!
You know what happened to me? You know why I'm so good at dancing?
Wh- why?
'Cause I lost my entire family.
Oh, yeah. So now you still want to quit?
That's what made you evil. No. Yeah.
Wait, that's what made you evil or that's what made you good at dancing.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
You guys are sitting like cooking up food for you.
I think we're sitting on those chairs where, you know,
you know, conversation hits different in those chairs.
That's so true.
So like, tell me about like your experience before your family was gone.
I mean, pretty much I pretty much I had a family before that.
Damn. And I didn't know how to dance.
You know, I didn't. And then I did.
I I didn't believe them when they said conversation hit different on these chairs.
I mean, it's got to be something in the in the craftsmanship of these chairs.
I mean, maybe maybe a witch put a spell on them or something.
But I really I feel like I'm getting to know everybody here a lot better
than I knew you five minutes ago before I started sitting in this chair.
and uh...
it's absolutely it's it's fantastic is one of the most lovely experiences i've
had the whole trip
and uh... i want to say uh... i think i could see myself becoming best friends
with you guys
you're very sweet i hate you
uh... well
you know
a uh... com
you know what you know what pat rich
i have to say i feel the same and you know when we get back
i'm gonna take you up on that promise i'm gonna fuck your walls after all
uh... yes
I'm glad you will. It'll be lovely to have company.
Oh, you're not gonna be inside. I'm not gonna let you watch.
What, do you think I am a freak?
Fellas, if we return this prince to the village, to the king,
we'll have all kinds of walls to fuck.
I'll tell you that. We're gonna have just...
- Even really... - You wanna fuck a wall?
No, I mean, I'm just trying...
- 'Cause the expression... - Are you serious?
No, I don't wanna fuck a wall. I'm sorry.
- I was trying to... - Why'd you bring it up then?
i guess i'm not really in the same chances you guys are realizing that
yeah
and that's what sort of preventing
you're sitting on the prince
the air-conditioned i laugh
uh... all know
uh... i'm good
uh...
i think i know you had no i thought about it again and yet
under my favorite box
uh...
well i did real sleepy
uh... do actually
Yeah, I'm getting pretty tired myself. Is there a
so like a
You know like a five-star hotel a five-star hotel or like a king size king size bed
You guys can do a watch too so you can have like somebody watch for half the night and somebody watch for the other half
Yeah, I'm not gonna watch it all
The whole night that's that's fine. He's younger. He's got better eyes. He likes to stay up late. He's a how about how about
Prince and Sullivan, how about you two watch? Oh, no, Sullivan's going to bed
All right, well, I'm not gonna I'm not gonna I'm not gonna do anything about that
I'm actually just gonna go to bed right now. I'm gonna
Gonna completely ignore all of you and go to sleep. Okay, so you're going to sleep
Anybody gonna stay up to keep watch or just I ever instance. I'm going to sleep did fuck this. Okay, what about you?
Dogen I
I'm gonna stay up and watch Sullivan.
(laughter)
Hitze Sullivan. You can like... roll perception, Dogen.
Five.
Okay.
You can't... you love watching Sullivan soundly sleep.
I was gonna say, if you got high enough, your character would be able to tell by his breathing,
he is not asleep and he's just...
just
like a little ways up from camp
uh... sleeping like a log
uh... but you're awake
uh...
the prince tried to stay awake and he fell asleep
uh... rolled for him
uh...
so it's good that you're awake though dogan so
and then do now
Is you're you're dogan
You hear a cry from in from in the woods beyond past the creek, right?
You guys have been walking along the creek or sort of further wooded area
uh, um, you know nearby
And you hear like a cry a yelp of pain
like oh
Um from deep in the woods
You don't have to do anything with that
I take a mouthful of dirt and I just say, "Hey, what's up?"
And I just have a conversation with it.
Oh, what's going on, man?
How you doing?
I hope I didn't wake you up.
I'm just bored.
I mean, there's literally nothing going on.
Yeah, no.
If you try, it's a kind of dirt.
It's outside Granite Town.
Oh, the granite dirt.
I've heard about that.
Yeah.
I heard about that in the dirt newsletter.
You got to try that because
Sorry, yeah, you gotta try that because it gives you a little bit of a bush - you know
I don't tell you that but some dirt she kind of fucked up
You know that I I actually didn't know that that's you know, this just goes to show you how much interesting stuff
There is to learn about dirt. Yeah, I think anybody who denies that is, you know, yeah, you know that to me
They're heathen, you know to be honest, you know, and you know, I'm your loyal servant or whatever
I would probably kill them or you know, maybe no, you know knock him around a little bit
So I'll get a cleric in there see if you can convert them and if they still are pagans, you know
Then you could do your work, you know, yeah, it's not a problem with me
Can you keep that down over I really I need eight hours I kick him in the head
And who do you kick in the head? I'm Patrick
I'm not I'm not asking you to keep it down. I'm asking the person screaming to keep
Kicking me was very unnecessary and I'm okay. Sorry. I misunderstood that. Yeah, you know what?
I do I feel mad at you. I feel really bad. Uh
You here, you know have some dirt the stuff tastes really good this I can actually I can do nothing with this but I do appreciate
You hate I know this means a lot to you. Oh, I'm not handing it to you. It's going in your mouth
I
Don't believe a lot of you with your brother
If you could actually just get
In my bag there's a magic epi-pen. If you could grab the magic epi-pen and just DM me at the leg real quick.
Please, I mean look at my face, it's swelling up.
I can't see, it's so dark.
I can't wait.
You know my god says dirt heals all wounds.
No, it's not gonna, actually I'm pretty allergic to dirt and I need you to hit me with an epi-pen.
Fine, I'll do the epi-pen.
the
and then uh... as you're going to have a good patrick you know it are with the
epi
you here don't get any guess you've had to answer your week
you've made your point
and
you know anything else for the rest of the night
Well, that was random.
And yeah, it's a long rest even though I took watch
No, that's why you do it trying to do it in shifts so you can fuck you guys
You literally wanted to stay up and watch fucking i wouldn't have done it if I knew I couldn't like sorry
You don't know the rules. I can't heal you guys now. It's your your fucking funeral. I'm fucked. I'm full
My belly's full dude. I feel like fucking thanksgiving
I could kill you in your sleep if you don't wake up.
Okay, wait.
Well, actually, I should say...
I shake evil people awake and I say, "I'm going to kill you right now unless you take
a second watch."
Well, actually...
Don't care.
Well, actually, you know what?
Because a long rest is technically extended downtime of light activity.
So it could be sleeping, but it could also be eating, drinking, reading, and tending
to wounds.
Or standing.
That's right.
It better be...
We're standing watch for no more than two hours.
So, that's the only thing here.
Is there short rest at least? Please?
Um, well yeah.
I guess the short rest doesn't help me at all, does it?
I mean, you definitely got, yeah, you could use a hit die for that.
But I have full health. No, I can't. I just can't recharge my abilities.
Yeah, no.
I mean, I guess it's you guys that suffer.
Yeah, you guys suffer.
How do we suffer?
I don't care.
Because I can't heal you anymore.
You didn't heal me in the first place, so...
And I was already kinda mad about that, so that's... that's fine.
You did heal me. You said you were full health!
No, I lied.
I wanted to, I wanted you to... I'm so much healing on Patrick,
and he thanks me by having a fucking allergic reaction
and making me tense again for a little bit.
I wake up, I wake up, and because of the EpiPen,
my just, like... I'm like shaking.
That was a...
That was a pretty weird night. Okay, I took all of their gold in the night.
You didn't take all my gold! No! No, I did.
Okay, then no! Oh, I thought you were asleep the whole night!
Because if you're sleeping at night I can take your gold.
You gotta at least roll a fucking stealth check.
I woke up with an epi pen.
And then you went back to sleep, right?
Yeah. Or did you stay up and take watch?
Because I need an
it's an either or here.
Do you want gold or do you want me to have my ability stashed?
I woke up, okay?
But I stayed in bed
and I acted like I was asleep.
So you didn't
Well that's
that is long rest territory.
it.
All right.
So everyone had a long rest then.
Okay, it sounds like everybody.
Yeah, anytime anytime sweetheart.
So I think you all got a long rest except Sullivan who was
terrified the whole night of something happening to him at
4 30 a.m.
I walk over to Sullivan and go how do you sleep?
that you know if he's like so pretending he's asleep anybody starts a
fine
uh...
uh... so yes the next morning uh...
you hear a cock a doodle do you hear all the the critters start to stir about
uh... and yet the path the path along the creek
same as always so you can still make it to the mud village
where the mud man's uh... bog
uh...
uh... you can keep walking there for a couple more hours and uh...
do you guys want to do that or do you want to do something else?
I think we head to the box. Yeah, so you walk a little bit further along the
creek for a couple more hours and it's sort of mid-morning now
and you reach
a sort of a more of a really dense forested area, right?
uh... you hear lots of croaks of
non bipedal frogs.
And you start, you know, weird fungus that like hisses as you walk by, things like that.
And you come across a bit more of a clearing and a bit more sort of reed sticking out of
a swampy muddy water, sort of cakes along your legs.
And you see a mud hut.
And you start to see another mud hut.
And you see sort of these mud men poke their heads out of the windows of these little mud
hovels, these mud homes.
And as they pop out, each of them smells either like poop or like chocolate.
And it's sort of anyone's guess which one they smell like at which time.
And you see now as you guys are walking through and you hear like a lot of hum and a hum
and a and then you see sort of three larger ones sort of gather in front of you as you're
walking past these little hovels and you see the mud mud children sort of like hiding behind
the skirts of their mud mothers and you see these three ones who say.
the
as
Please don't do that. Please don't do that. Please don't do that. Yeah, come on. Hey, is this chocolate tastes like some damn mud?
That's right. We're made of mud, but just we smell like poop or chocolate
You see one of them to the right goes like yeah, I got the short end of that stick. I
Like that one
What is your name sir
Who are you? My name is my name is mud kip
That is that like one of the laziest
things I've ever heard
Look I'll admit
Didn't come up with a name for this guy
Okay, I've been trying to have less named NPCs. His eyes are white right now
But you my name would not be understood by your kind you may call me mudkip, how's that is that chill
the
seem like you're around from around here you know. Because we're not made of mud.
Well yes but I mean the woods do you wish to leave? I don't remember. Yes yes yeah
we're trying to get to trebuchet village. Didn't you want to go to a hotel? Oh yeah
that's yeah do you have like maybe like a mud hotel or something here? Yes one star.
the
That's what it's called.
Maybe there's like a maybe like a resort or casino here or something.
No, I'm just looking. There's no gambling allowed.
It's something I like to do. No, we understand. Many people do. We simply cannot afford to gamble.
We are made of mud.
Our gamble was made long ago.
You know, we were once not made of mud. What were you made of?
of
clean it off, don't...
I just, I look at, I look at Dogen.
Yeah, you really...
You think I didn't realize what mud was?
You really, you're just, uh, you're made out of dirt and water.
Do I, what are you trying to do here?
I put, I put the mud man's fingers in my mouth and I ask my god, do I like water?
Dogen does not answer.
Thank you.
He nods to you.
We do not normally take to outsiders, but you see we were
recently ransacked by some beast that tore through here and
you see sort of a destroyed mud huts a little mud house.
It's all like kind of like broken into.
He says it was a terrible sight to leave.
I'm sorry to interrupt you.
Oh, please.
Yeah.
What did this just suffered a lot of trauma but go on?
Yeah, I don't care.
What was the what did the monster look like?
He looked like a big
looked like some type of Sasquatchian type of creature.
Very furry, covered in fur,
and when he moved, he would stomp on the ground
with these fearsome claws and then roll.
- Did he leave footprints?
- I mean, yes.
- I think this might be the same beast
that we were following before.
- I mean, they all got sort of absorbed in the mud
any, you know, sort of, uh, you could, you could certainly look to see if, is that going
to look, we just, I'll help you.
Uh, I can help you leave here.
We will.
And typically we will not show the way to outsiders.
We don't want people to come in and find us, but if you are able to find this
beast and perhaps slay it, bring honor to our people, we can show you out.
and we have to slay it i can't just uh...
who established like a friendship
there's something in the maybe straight away we'd like to have my thing is that
we have some we exchange harsh words and it knows it we it understands no
uses voice booms easy the mud ripple
so i have to kill it
these things have this thing has
destroyed our people we have so little
when the jester cursed us thousands of years ago
we were all as he see i told you that jester
not a good guy you did not tell you thought it was a good guy do you want to
go see a no i wanted to
i didn't investigation
you did nothing
i think i did you stood there you drooled and you'd you said hotel under
your breath
uh... run that shit back turbo
and what if i fall in love with the beast
this is a made me murder it
I will not make you do anything you do not wish to do.
So I'm- it's okay if I fall in love with it?
I mean I'm just not gonna- I'm not going to- I cannot trust you if you do not do this for
us.
I'm putting it on lipstick and I look- I don't hear him and I look at him and I'm like "What?
What'd you say?"
I'm down to do this quest but uh first just like check this out.
What do you mean quest?
What?
this shit out and I just take out my my pouch of forever dirt and I just start
spraying dirt all over the ground oh that's lovely wait I've got an idea and
I well he's just like that well he's throwing the dirt I pick up like a
bucket of water and I start throwing it at the dirt trying to make a mud guy mm-hmm
we can make you a baby please do not see you guys know about spelling it cuz
we're with a child you see that you turn you see that Prince Jumanji is like
a half way in the mud. And he's like, "Get out of there!"
"That is their home! Get out of their home!"
"I'm not, no, I'm sorry, I'm sorry." And you see the mudmen, they go, "Oh, nard."
While all that's happening, I have Sullivan and I'm taking some of the Forever Dirt and water and I'm just like...
They realize Sullivan's there for the first time. "Oh, shit! We just thought that was like a frog."
I'm covering him in mud so he looks like a little mud guy.
I'm making like a mud snowman but it's surrounded like it's surrounding Sullivan.
Yeah we're gonna make you a baby so you can have SEX.
please yeah it's been it's been a long time for me
I can't believe you did the episode.
You see the mudman? The mudman sees your balls and says, "I can see it's been a long time."
[laughter]
Um, yeah.
Okay. Cool. Let the quest begin.
Yeah, sure.
I just want to--hold on--I want to clarify...
[music]
[MUSIC PLAYING]