[Music]
Last time on Trebuchet Village, our heroes had a very weird and fucked up fight with a walrus
involving taking bits of his meat out of his body and doing stuff to it.
Dogen turned into a Oreo-centric, oath-breaking paladin.
Patric Yodar proved a capable shot with a crossbow, and Evil Stevel developed a new catchphrase.
After they won the fight, they decided they would try their hand at fighting Ola to field her offer as well in this orc tank scenario.
In the meantime, Evil Stevel's catchphrase, "Get me out of this hotel."
Oh, that's okay.
Alright.
Was causing him concern as he traveled back to the hotel he was staying in.
The, uh, the Blinky's Warm Place.
So Patrick Yodar got a crit 20, disguising him as Lindsay Lovely, a pop star with 38G tits.
Yeah, they decided to help Blinky's Warm Place get the three stars for the hotel.
two and a half stars or has been never been a three star hotel by
performing a concert because Lindsay Lovely is also like a
musical artist.
Yeah, like Hannah Montana. Yes.
It almost went disastrous. It's disastrously. But Patrick
Yodar's insane keyboard guitar playing save the day. What
happened was was during the final moments. You lovely Lindsay
Lovely screamed your catchphrase and then got a crit 1 in your performance check so
your tits fell clean off. Dogen, you were obsessed with Lindsay Lovely, wanted to
be her very sexual backup dancer so you did a Keith Moon tap dancing solo but
you got a crit 20 on your keytar playing so everyone turned their attention to
you and you guys found a way to kind of play it off that it was just me in
disguise I'm like doing a Hannah Montana thing and you all ever in the whole
crowd and all of you screamed get me out of this hotel and we kind of ended the
episode there on that high note yeah so I want to know kind of like the rest of
the night how did that go down the concert ends it's a roaring success
you're in Blinky's warm place Blinky's all excited he thinks this could be his
chance to get a three-star rating from the Gal Gadot Hotel rating agency mm-hmm
So what happened? What went down? Well I've got I still I have Lindsay Lovelies fake
tits and I've bronzed them. Yes, you bronzed them. And I carry them with me forever now. Yeah. And you hand them to
yourselves like awards. Yeah. Did you bronze them immediately after? Yeah there's a
bronzer in the hotel. Yeah right. Really? You didn't know about that?
Well that's good. Alright well then I go down to the bronzer and I would like to bronze my
right hand okay cool during the crazy after party I took a shit in the
bronzing machine Steve will just stuck his hand in the you can't no no picked up
a can't picked up a bronze lizard you can't go back in time after I already
said I did something no I'm gonna you shit in the thing okay all right well
I'd like to say okay the rest of the time that he ever eats anything I shit in it
fair no no it's not fair take it back you didn't shit in the bronzer shit in
the bronze and I didn't do what you guys be adults and try to resolve this I
I didn't bronze my hand.
I think you guys have to roll.
I'm trying to think what's the roll.
I think it's a T20 off.
D20, D20, wait, don't roll yet.
D20 against each other.
If, okay, if you win.
That's not a D20.
This is not a D20, you're right.
There you go.
No, there's one right there.
Give that back.
If I win, if I win, you get your own shit.
I divided it perfectly.
I'm sorry.
If you win, then I didn't just bronze my hand, I bronze my tongue also.
Okay?
Okay.
All right, ready?
Wait, hold on, hold on.
There are, yeah, what are the rules?
win then I didn't just bronze my hand I bronze my tongue also. Okay? Okay. All
right ready? Wait hold on hold on there are yeah what are the implications if
you actually bronze your hand right? Yeah. Yeah well that means he just has like a
stronger fist. That's not. Well I bronze it into a into the middle finger. It's okay he's a
he's a he's a cleric he doesn't need to use like a two hands or anything.
If you bronze your your hand if this is what happens like you actually do we can
come up with stats for your bronze tan
so it like maybe does like one one d_-eight budgeting damage or something
like and that just like
on its own inside a weapon you just have
because you brought your hand it's that the thing is is he's holding it's a
bronze and holding a turd
it doesn't hold the terrible deterred if you have patrick wins the d twenty okay
will work all right but then what is he'll he needs to have something at
stake here
i think i should have i think this is a is a lot of all got bronzed
yes yes yeah and it blocks all his poop yeah okay all right he poops out of his mouth
already and so hold on so we'll figure out but i think there will be some sort of like
hmm maybe there's like a toxicity sort of damage i'll figure that out it takes septic
trying to figure out all right you're going down you pussy bitch oh man hey you are oh man 18 oh
oh no four okay i win enjoy enjoy never shitting again never having that sweet release you fucking
This is what you get for shitting in the bronzing machine.
Your asshole gets bronzed.
Because he dips down to shit in it.
Mm-hmm.
What a crazy night.
Do you still bronze your hand?
Or no?
Fuck no.
Okay.
So your asshole gets bronzed.
We're just going to play this out.
Your asshole gets bronzed.
Yeah, I think we can do that like...
Can we count on from now on there being a bronzer in every tavern that we go to?
I think so, yeah.
Okay, I bronze the oreo I made out of the walrus. This is my new collection thing.
Okay, you got an oreo. Your asshole's bronzed. You didn't bronze anything.
With a bronzed asshole, let's think. What?
I bronze my pinky.
You bronze your pinky? Okay, yeah. I mean you're just...
And there's poop in it.
Well, for some slight of hand checks, the difficulty class will be slightly higher.
I have to make notes of this.
I don't bronze my pinky then. Tell me this shit before I do it, man.
You need to tell me the consequences of my actions.
if you're a person my pinky when I use my pinky okay imagine like just holding
anything and you got your you're just have slightly less grips you should
bronze like just your wrist like it like it looks like a watch hmm
I'll allow it it's he's have a watch on here no it's not I'll just get a watch
this is all right I don't bronze anything I'm being peer pressured he has
to he can never shit again I put no you put some confetti in the bronzer okay
bronze the confetti I think I think Eddie bronze that what we'll do is it'll be
like we can do it looks like it's got sprinkles on it here's what we'll do I'm
trying to think is I think I think because because this resolved in a weird
way I want to do this fair so what we can do is that every like four hours of in
game game time we'll roll a d20 okay I have to roll a d20 and if you're higher
than 10 you don't take 1d4 septic damage can there be there could be a cure four
hours is good four hours that's that'll never come into play I don't think I'll
forget sometimes yeah I won't forget I'll figure out a benefit for it
eventually maybe well if someone tries to fucking fuck his buddy yeah and there I
have a buttfucker enemy coming up you saved your ass dude I just saved your
fucking ass okay all right okay it's not
like but I also got a record deal okay
you don't know what the fuck is my even
serious man okay no no I got a dancing
deal no bronzing no dancing are you
gonna go to start the whole episode over
that's eight minutes and 30 seconds down
the drain Oreos bronze your asshole is
fine okay is that better fine and sheen
and shiny and bronze. It hurt though. He lost the roll. I know but I'm not trying to.
He's, look at him, he's so upset. I'm not upset, I got a record deal. Alright, give him the
record deal then, if that's what I have to do. He's got a record deal. Okay. So uh. My
keytar playing was amazing. It was a crit 20 on the keytar playing. This is the actual Shark Tank episode.
This is crazy. Negotiating with the dealer. Yeah. Okay, so yeah, you get a record deal. And I
bronze both my hands yeah you brought I bronze them holding my weapons I'll
treat that seriously oh no I'm sorry oh no you put your weapons in the bronzer
what if I put my weapons I'm sorry these two are wasting your time okay we
already bronzes asshole he's got an Oreo can we just fine all right get to my
part of the story? Yes we can. Yeah. So you guys wake up. Well we gotta continue talking
about my record deal. You guys wake up in your in the hotel room, fucking trashed,
you're, it's it's late in the afternoon basically you have to get the shark tank
like pretty quickly or orc tank. You guys go downstairs I guess to do that. You see
a blankie comes up to you and he says, "That was amazing last night even though
your your tits fell off unbelievable yeah I'm glad I fucked you I think I don't
remember yeah I don't think you fucked me yeah I don't yeah God what your two
exceptions disadvantage see if you can make this guy thinking you fucked him
17 okay disadvantage though so roll again take the lower number 13 okay yeah he's
like yeah you did didn't fuck me I thought then who did I oh good who did
you fuck oh no I think you fucked himself with the bronzer and then I walk up to
him there's a continental breakfast I walk up to him holding a big bowl of
Penang curry here may have some of this but be careful it'll run straight through you
yeah here do you want some coffee here we're all drinking coffee I don't
remember what some maybe some nitro cold brew I think will do you right yeah
sitting in the hotel blinkies hotel lobby like he's like singing you guys's
praises is a thorax and he's with his group again that group you first saw back
when he first approached you guys the group you saw when you were in the the
tavern he he sort of entreats you guys and he he comes over and he says all
Alright so today you guys wanted to fight Ola right?
Nah.
Yeah I think so, well hold on I gotta.
Let's just take the fish and leave.
I gotta world.
You guys are serious about that right?
I gotta world tour, I gotta plan.
It's a lot of money on the line here.
Yeah but I.
How much money?
Look I'm trying to focus on my music right now.
Oh god, okay.
I'll go.
No we can't just have one of you.
I will go alone.
I'll go too.
No!
I will go alone.
Just fight one of them that's actually offering us money, please.
Alright, we'll fight the green lady.
Why don't you fight with us? You're so invested in this.
No, no.
Yeah, I'll fight the green lady, whatever.
Why do you care so much if you're not making any of the money?
I'm making some of the money.
Then why are you not fighting?
Yeah, why aren't you fighting?
You shouldn't be. You're not gonna make any of the money if you don't fight with us.
You're not part of it.
Okay, fine.
And we're gonna tell them that.
That you don't get money if you don't fight.
I've got you guys here. I made this connection for you.
I get you can't hear, I mean it can't hear.
He's doing, he's saying what he said.
You guys are making fun of him.
You look over and you see that shaman who was giving you guys the stink eye a few episodes ago.
And he's still giving you the stink eye.
That's the stinky shaman.
And you see the shaman says,
Don't listen to them thorax.
Just fight the orc by yourself and take the money for yourself.
You don't need-
Hey, shut up, bitch!
And you see, the shaman like glares at you.
He doesn't find any of this very funny.
He's like pretty mad.
I flip him off.
You wanna see something real funny?
I pulled down Petra's-
Yeah, the balls are huge.
Wait, no, turn around.
Look at that.
Boy got, boy got fuckin' bronze dipped.
You can see like a few like streaks of his balls are bronze too, 'cause he couldn't get
it clean.
Yeah, the bronze went down out of my balls too.
It went down?
crazy night. Look, I'll fight with you if that's what it's going to take for you guys to not
accept... I actually don't remember the logistics of the offer with the walrus, but...
We won't fight unless you fight too.
I'll fight with you.
We all agreed on that last night.
We still get the fish from the walrus?
I don't know if there's...
I'm going to bronze it.
We're going to bronze the fish. We'll see if we can get fish from the walrus. I just
don't...
It sounded like you guys were going to give the walrus away with us.
All right, we're going to bronze the gold coins too. They might be worth more. If you
had bronze to the point I think bronze is more valuable than gold I'm pretty sure
do not do that what well it's extra metal on it wait which one is better gold or
bronze gold is there a gold ur in this town I don't think so you can operate
for free for no reason this is the best hotel in this town and it only has a
bronzer but have you checked for a gold ur what's the finish this arc we should
maybe go looking for a golder from far away. Do an investigation check for golders. Do
an investigation check? Yeah. Okay. That is an 18 plus. Oh I never did the. Hold on. Shit.
What is it? Investigation? Minus one. That's a 17. Okay. There is a golder but it's two
towns over. We're going there later. Is there a golder? Holy. Does it, in an investigation
You just have to like tell him if there is or isn't one.
No, that's not actually how it works.
I'm just saying shit.
(laughing)
You're supposed to like say what you're doing
to investigate, are you talking to people?
There's all kinds of things.
We, since you agreed to fight with us, let's go kill
Oh, hola.
We don't kill them.
We don't.
Yeah, we're gonna, we do not kill them.
I would never kill a woman,
but let's beat her within an inch of her life.
Last time you said you only kill women.
I'm a liar.
Okay.
I think that was Lindsay Lovely that said that.
Yeah. Was it? It was okay for her to kill women because she was a woman.
Alright, let's just... Here's Max, I'm taller than you.
Nah, I think I'm three feet taller. You're definitely not. He's a
orc and you're... Look at me, I'm so... look at this. You're a dwarf, yeah.
Fucking huge.
So you guys, uh...
Yeah, you guys, uh... walk out of the hotel, um...
Say it. Go back to the, uh...
Say it.
To head to the arena.
man is hotel yeah I see some guy grab his camera and I think I think it's good to
like you realize a little bit more color as to what Gal Gadot is so the city is
filled to the brim with all manner of terrifier born so goblins ghouls zombies
you know orcs Nards they look at everything and everyone like pieces of
meat, rotten meat, which they like more than regular meat. Any
influence felt from the kingdom's more progressive
stance of like anti-slavery or like, try not to eat humans so
much is virtually non existent here. Most scaredy cats are
slaves, they pull carts, entertaining their masters,
performing odd jobs for no pay and odd favors for no pay. As is
customary in the Terrifier Kingdom, and particularly in Gal Gadot, if you pass
by a slave you are to spit on them. But because, Evil Steeble, because you're a
scaredy-cat born, you're occasionally mistaken for a slave and spat upon here.
But then a lot of times people remember that you're the, recognize you as the
get-me-out-of-this-hotel-guy. When people spit on me I catch the spit midair with my
tongue like a frog in a fly roll roll a roll straight decks check okay let's see
how you do it that overall yeah you do all right occasionally it gets in your
cheek but like you're mostly catching it yeah yeah the the as you guys are
walking there you can hear the shaman under his breath saying shit like peekaboo
scaredy-cat about you because that's like a sort of like a slur you say the
scaredy-cats is peekaboo they like say nasty things he really doesn't like you
guys he's crying you're making him cry by saying that not crying he's sort of
just ignoring you guys you walk by the skies of Gal Gadot are crowded with like
outstretched claws legs hands shoulder blades tails spikes and mandibles that
sick from the ground.
This place scary as hell.
These are all kaiju manji, right?
These are all like the dead
beasts of the past.
Is Prince Jumanji named after them?
He's named after the kaiju manji.
It's a...
Because a lot of people who are
terrifier born like worship them
because they were like these great
terrifying beasts of the past.
Precursors of terrifier born.
What?
They weird.
Yeah, they weird.
That's true.
It's a metropolis, although there is basically no vertical living,
as the orcs are resistant to any and all change, preferring to spill out into the street,
sleeping all over each other, fighting for space, scraps, meat, and bone,
rather than live in the sky, a thing that gives them great fear.
Agriculture is a recent innovation, courtesy of Ola, actually, and her magic.
The Kaiju Manji were once worshipped at this grim gravesite,
but any religious fealty for the beasts has gone by the wayside in favor of the Terrifyer.
So like whatever the kaiju manji were like these sort of, you know, pagan gods almost.
And the terrifier is now the god that these people worship.
And the shaman, from what you could pick up on his wardrobe and his general demeanor,
he's one of these people who worships a terrifier.
There are a number of big churches in the area.
And most people do. It's like saying you're a lapsed Catholic, you know,
it's a lapsed terrifier worshiper. Like you just kind of do.
But yeah, so you guys just, I wanted to give you guys a little bit more what Gal Gadot looks like.
As you walk through it you walk back to the arena which again is a giant kaiju manji pelvis
You guys walk in there
You're immediately greeted evil steve-o with people being like hey get me out of this hotel like slapping you on the back like they all
You're kind of just like stop. You're hurting him. Yeah
He has a weak back. Oh
I'm sorry. I'm said you could touch the talent. No, I
Don't know. Oh get out of here Patrick. Yoda touch me touch
"When you coming out with a record?"
And he's like being dragged away by somebody.
No, I'm actually, I'm more famous than him still.
Um, uh, yeah, and as you guys approach sort of the, uh, the, the arena training grounds,
you see Tit for Tat, the two Goblin Brothers, you see, uh, uh, you see also, uh, Fuck You there,
he's already there.
I walk up to Tat and I kick him.
Yeah, you walk over to for Tat and you kick him.
Uh, roll attack roll.
Which is for Tat the small one.
for tat no they're both small which is the one we stole the idea from a man
15 yeah yeah that hits for tat so you roll d4 why are you kicking this guy
so it's the triangle pyramid yeah - and then add your strength to that why are
you hurting this man I don't know he's just to do it though the fuck is wrong
with you my strength is zero okay yeah so you just like kick him and kind of
bloody his shin up a little bit he's like oh wow why did you do that
because I'm famous now and I feel like I can do that to people oh I guess okay I
could see how you nobody's gonna believe you you're not Bill fucking Murray good
God you have any fries wait hold on do you have fries? No?
Shit, are you having like a wedding soon? I'm bleeding is what it is. How you can't have a wedding if you're bleeding
I start sucking on that leg
Like a chicken bone all right just roll I guess roll the tack roll
Trying to help him. I know it's not gonna do
You're welcome. I'm also famous and nobody will believe you about that also.
You're smoking up in him with your mouth covered in his blood.
I have a ligament in my tooth. Oh God
Okay, um that wasn't very nice. Yeah, no one's gonna believe you though. No, there's there is like 15 people around here
Yeah, let's check tell that guy what happened
Well, uh, my my brother. Yeah
What happened? Oh that asshole kicked you in the leg. No one's gonna believe him
No one's ever gonna believe this asshole.
Look, ask anybody else in this room.
Yeah, ask me.
Yeah, ask him.
What do you think happened, asshole?
I don't know.
I don't really have a good response to that.
I don't know what I expected.
I wasn't looking.
Yeah, I kicked him and no one's gonna believe him.
Oh.
Yeah, do you believe us?
Yep.
Do you believe him?
No.
Didn't think so.
There you go, tip for tat.
That's a solid routine you guys have worked out.
Yeah, you guys thought tit for tat was a cool who's on first type of shit.
I did! I did!
Nah, this is the real one and nobody's gonna believe you.
[Laughter]
Uh, yeah, so you guys, uh, uh, I guess brutalized this guy.
Um, you see fuck you, he's like, has like a, he's like, has like a, a, a cloth on his head,
like a wet cloth, he's like trying to like, just like get his head right, and he's like,
"Uh, how are you guys doing?"
"There's a party last night."
That's what I say to the other guy. I'm doing good. All right
Anyway, so you have any fries I can take
I can try to conjure fries. I don't yeah. Yeah do that. Hold on do that. You know what you know does it has
because of material components to
Conjure french fries to do all the okay. I'll just do it. And yeah, he just like on juice french fries. Okay, well then
The fries
Oh
Thank thank you, and I take like just it's like a McDonald's like yeah
I got a small like the like the little red package I grab all of them out of it
And I throw my mouth and it's go no one's gonna believe you
Oh
All right, I I could just kill myself at this point. Maybe oh
No, I'm busy. Well then I gonna go back
To the other guy all right wait. Well hold on what are you saying?
I guess let's do this right
Thorax, are you gonna fight with them then? Yeah. Yeah, I'm gonna fight with them. Yeah. Yeah
I'm gonna ride on his back into battle
Hey, be careful your back there thorax. This guy's riding parts are a bit stiff. I've seen his balls
Yeah, yeah, no, it's fucking
Asshole you fucking idiot we talking about. Yeah, there's a little bit of bronze on my balls, too
You want to see the bronze on my balls you already showed me earlier. No, that's right. I did show you we were in a hotel
You took your balls out. I don't
All right. Let's just go to the arena. No one's gonna wait. Hold on
That's no then wait. Hold on. I gotta I'm holding on I go over here. I go for to dad again
They're all attack roll
For
You tried to came to the oh nice try you fucking asshole not gonna get this leg again. I
Believe that you hit him
Yeah, you hit me
What why don't I just hit him? I'm I'm I don't know what I don't know who to believe except him
And then he you hit him right then
Listen, we have to go do some work. Okay. Will you just stay here? We bring them out stay right here. Well, can't hate
I don't know yet. Do you want to do you guys?
Have you ever been you ever wanted to sit at the end of a fishing line like bait?
No
You're not the right guy for us never mind
What if it was against your will oh
No
Almost that's the right spirit. That's what I'm talking about which which oh, okay
But could we maybe like use you like a like a bait on a giant fishing line to try to get this bitch
Do you like you the cops are super lax here? This is not here. We're gonna dress you up. I gotta go get an autograph
We're gonna dress you up
Like like Dogen and we're gonna send you out there and then we're all gonna attack
What what are you gonna attack? What are you we're gonna dress him up?
The other guy up we're gonna dress your brother up like like Steve. Oh, okay, and then there's a third guy
Maybe Thor X maybe maybe Thor X plan any
Me cut to the arena
Yes, I think that deception plan would have worked. I don't know why thanks now. We're in this big arena was three hours ago
We we haven't talked about that once in the waiting room you're bringing that up now right when we walk into the arena
Yeah, well, thank you. You had so many chances the Sharks make you wait hours like Lorne Michaels to try to get in your
Yeah, see if you crack on Lorne Michaels the Michaels was an orc actually it was one of the works on Orc Tank
That's the one the walrus sat on
Yeah, so you guys walk out to the arena
See the orcs are there in case you don't remember
The
we find the
The offers that were made. Oh, yes, I put it on we're fighting. Oh, right. Yes
Offers that were made to you guys. I don't care about the others. Okay. Well Ola's offer then
Whoa, yeah, sorry, we're recording in an Iranian barber shop
(laughing)
Might hear some music.
- Ola's offer was 300,000 gold pieces at 40%,
plus 5% in the advisory board,
and you join Ola's family of products,
which means you'll have to sort of like
adjust your vendor relationships,
but you'll get discounts, you'll have a lot of stuff
already sewn up for you.
- Plus one billion gold coins for 1%.
- No, it was not.
No, that was-- - All right, let's fight.
- You guys gonna do it?
- Yeah. - Yep.
- Okay, cool.
walk out there and what do you say then because you're out there the idiots by
the way are still there the hundred idiots you guys sent out to just like oh
can they fight with us no they're too stupid they're literally too dumb to
fight what if they are they've been starving I'm not gonna I'm not gonna do
it but like what if never mind okay I throw a hot dog up in the air and I hit
it with my shovel like a baseball bat and it flies into the the crowd of idiots
Okay, yeah
That's what I was that's what I was trying to think of like a way to make you were not trying to think of that
I just thought of that we see we're trying to steal his dog Wow. I actually was thinking of that
Cameron stole my idiots are like pretty good at like
One of them is like very good at like grabbing the hot dog and like the other ones are like picking at it
They're like picking at a hot dog. Yeah, it's like pulling all
like the worst
keep going and it gets to a skeleton.
Yeah, literally the worst way a bone can eat.
The worst kind of hot dog ever.
That's what hot dogs are like in this fantasy world.
They come from an animal that looks exactly like that.
It's an animal's penis. Some animal's penis basically.
Some animal's like finger or something.
It's just a terrible thing.
No, it's a hot dog. A hot dog is an animal.
It's an animal. With one bone.
Yeah.
worm with a bone in it.
Oh yeah, that's canon.
That's so good.
It has to roll around on its side because it can't wiggle like a worm.
Just hoping somebody eats it.
The sound it makes is like...
And the buns are a plant.
They grow near the hot dog.
I'm just sucking on one.
You're just making me hungry as hell.
I want a hot dog so bad.
I want a hot dog.
Let's pause and go get a hot dog.
And so we're back.
um and yeah - full of record that's that's might happen so yeah you guys
what do you guys want to say the the or say they sort of entreat you they say
like Ola says so you've had time to think since you beat the shit out of our
walrus friend here you see the walrus he's like in a sling he's got like a
black guy. Nope it takes us way longer than that to think. We haven't thought
about anything. I gotta tell you one thing Ola. I'm in love with you. This might
actually work. Are you actually? I'm in I'm like fucking fucking assholes. So
that's what's my... You have like an insane charisma. Yeah so I add charisma to
this yeah your deception skill I think you have proficiency in yeah I think you
can't thank you Cameron 13 plus 6 or no no 12 plus 6 so 18 yeah okay yeah she's
like kind of convinced you're in love with her she's like that's very
flattering you still have to there are rules though we can talk but there are
there rules you have to fight true love true love breaks the rules love
transcends all rules and regulations no not these rules except they do let your
hair down Ola. Come on. Your hair is down. Ola I gotta confess something to myself baby girl I'm in love with you as well.
I think I have really bad deception. With disadvantage because he already sort of it's very clear that one of you is maybe in love the other one
has some weird competition thing. Is Sullivan with us? Yeah. Sullivan's in love with you too. No no no no no no no.
12 and... No, not no offense. I mean... 16, 12. She's like, I I think you have a weird
some sort of developmental thing going on. I don't know if you know. I'm into...
And Sullivan's in love with you too. No, I'm not. Sullivan is in love with you. He's so bashful.
He's the bashful frog. Oh, I was not
Would you get
18 plus 6 right? Yeah, you see her look at y'all solving you like
Sort of shy look at turning green with shine green with love and you know what? I just wanted to say that
Sullivan's in love with you so much that I'm gonna let him have you
I'm not gonna. I'm not gonna. There's no having me. Okay. What look do you want to fight? Do you love him?
No, which one you got like him one
Look at us
You have to go on a date with him
All three of you four of us look at the frog look at me
Hey, look at me
Pick up I pick up Sullivan
Like
Forgot we're the same size
Pick him up. He's gonna roll. He's gonna try to resist against that for okay. He's probably gonna resist
He
Pathetically try to lift him up and he's trying to hold him up - one on strength
Yeah, let me double check his stats
I forgot to have that up.
Um, D&D Beyond is not working.
Well, let me try, um, let me try the app.
We'll just say that he lost.
He lost, yeah.
He definitely lost, right?
No, I don't, I mean, the attempt was made.
That's kind of what's interesting here, is that, yeah.
So how can we fight you if we're all so god damn in love with you, Shorty?
I'm not in love with her, right?
Except for him, you can fight him.
He's not in love with you, so...
I cast Inflict Wounds.
Oh my god, okay.
Roll initiative then. Let's do this.
Everyone roll initiative.
Alright.
You roll an initiative when you love the girl?
You wrong for that.
I guess I'll roll initiative.
Yes.
I got a 19 for initiative.
I got a 13.
Don't forget to add your bonus.
Add your initiative bonus.
I think I have a zero initiative bonus. Yeah, I'll say
Internet is working. All right, that is Sullivan's initiative, which is terrible
Yeah, I saw it and that was all us. Nope. That's all us. Sorry. What the fuck I didn't I don't make
Literally make the rules jinx. Whoa
Caleb can't talk for the rest of the episode and please don't really got to talk please
That was good. We said the exact same thing at the exact same
I don't literally make the rule first of all. What are you doing? Where are you going? He's leaving. Caleb come back
Caleb come back. What are you taking out of the garbage? I don't want that
Dude he had a
Talk again now you want me to
Well, he pulled a coke out of the trash. That's pretty cool. I
I guess just pause the recording now.
No, it's okay.
No, we're gonna keep this all in.
This is why people like this, I think it's because of this.
Um...
I can't confirm that.
I didn't say your name three times. You're just racking up...
Stop.
Dude, that is one of the...
If you don't respect the rules of a jinx...
You don't respect the rules! I got you a Coke!
Yeah, but then you kept talking.
He got you a Coke?
Yeah, I got you the Coke. That's the only rule.
only rule no yeah what's going on with Ola so Ola is gonna go first so you guys
are all got 21 she got natural 20 oh I do it if she's so beautiful I'm gonna let
her go first I do initiatives with a critical initiative both of them so
she's gonna charge you evil Steve oh fuck I said I was in love with you you
stupid-ass bitch okay don't talk to her like that um
Jinx what I don't know how Jinx works
jinx is a dark magic in this world yeah she's gonna say that yeah she's got a
she's got like a you see for the first time as she's approaching you that she
has like two huge metal two huge what and where are they metal claws on her
hands and she's holding them in front of what her body and which looks like an
orcs body which which looks like which number what which number figure eight
all right it is so she swipes at you and misses on the first swipe she's gonna
swipe at you again though. Okay that's gonna hit you for sure. Come on.
Which she's gonna do some damage to. She swipes at you, you either deflect it or
pretty deftly dodge it. And then she's going to do some damage now. So let's get
some dice out here. Okay. And then plus that. Okay. How much? Nine damage. She just
swipes at you. She just claws through you. Yeah, she's pretty strong.
I'm glad we got Thorax to fight with us. She's hit a third of my health. Yeah, and then and so
she's just she's she just did that to you. Can I, can she do all of that damage to
my penis? Uh, you know what? Roll dexterity. Let's see if you can adjust yourself in
time. Okay. To have it be on your wee-wee. One. It is the, what's the opposite of your
penis my brain yeah she just claws the top of your head no no my balls the
opposite of my penis your butt wait no your butt no that is not the opposite of
my buddy yeah she just like you like adjust it almost just right to get it on
the penis and then but like the the like force of your balls swing it upwards and
And so it's like your balls swing up and so she just like claws through your sack.
Okay so back to what we were talking about earlier.
Is there water in your balls?
We were talking about that before recording.
Let me look it up.
Google is there water in your balls.
It's not water, it's blood.
Is it blood?
There's not blood in your balls man.
Yeah there's blood.
Yeah if you nick your balls, I guess it's the skin.
That's true.
Well in the sack I mean.
I've cut my ball sack so many times.
Well there's blood all over your fucking body.
What is, what are your balls?
Are your balls dry?
Dry?
Dry.
- Balls floating in. - During development,
each testicle has a naturally occurring sac
around it that contains fluid.
- Okay, my fluid comes out,
and it tastes like Baja Blast. - Wait, you said
during development?
Yeah, it's during development, though.
- Isn't that when you're like a fetus?
- Wait, what's hydrocele?
What is this?
- Hydrocele is a sac-- - Just get a yes or no answer.
Is there water in your balls?
- 10% of males are born with this?
- I'm in the 10%, my shit comes out,
it's mag carbonated. - I Googled,
is there water in your balls,
and they gave me like a fucking disease.
What do you mean hydrocephalus or?
*laughter*
Reddit, ask science.
What are your balls surrounded by?
Juice?
*laughter*
Sorry.
It's a strong question.
Okay, my juice comes out.
And I lost 9 damage.
Yeah, you lost 9 damage to juice.
The juice just like goes on her claw.
Now you have to marry me.
*laughter*
Some orc rituals require this, but no, not mine.
Well, mine do.
And so now, Patrick, you go.
I'm going to launch Cupid's arrow at her.
Your regular arrow.
Oh, you do have an arrow to make her shit her pants.
Yeah, I'm going to do that.
Yeah?
That's a kind of Cupid's arrow.
And then you can offer her a moist towelette and then she'll fall in love with you.
I look at her and I say, "Maybe I'm going to hit you with Cupid's arrow."
put girls in this hole I can never put a woman in this thing yeah we've been
trying to tell you this for a year and I keep trying what am I doing I'm an idiot
sorry that we're three love constantly my role whether an attack roll yeah do it
well isn't there do I have to like go for the arrow no that's your arrow so
it's like that's just the arrow that's being shot okay it's the same amount of
damage as like an iron arrow it just or whatever kind of arrows you can't have
It just also can make them shit their pants.
So I think it's +6 for you?
Okay.
Got an 11 +6. Yeah, that hits!
Whoa. So she now needs to make a constitution saving throw against
your DC. Can you look at that and tell me what that is?
My DC? I think it's your spell save DC. If you go to the
and print spells it says save DC mm-hmm this character cannot cast spells that's
okay you still have a well okay in this case it would be let's say I think oh
yeah is nothing oh yeah I guess I guess it's a plus 20 then I guess it must be a
thousand plus 1000 - 13 he can use mine well I was gonna say I think it's
intelligence only because the rogue spellcasting subclass is the arcane
trickster and they use intelligence. Okay. So they want to go with intelligence.
What's your intelligence score? My intelligence score is 13 and it says plus
one. This is plus one? So then that is going to be your DC is 8 plus your
proficiency bonus plus your intelligence so your proficiency I think is 2 so I
I think your DC is 11 then, so let's see how that goes.
I want to make sure though, I think I just did that right.
Yeah, I got it.
I was just double checking.
Paranoid.
Yeah, she resists it.
So she like prairie dogs.
The poop kind of comes out.
She's like, "Ugh!"
Like she tries to like steady herself.
She got balls juice on her hand.
What?
Is there a way I can get the arrow back?
You could take it from her after the fight right now. It's after the fight. I can't like run up on her and okay
Yes, you can try to do that. Okay, not this turn. You're gonna get fucked though. Can I have just somebody else?
Patient not doing a roll but also roll for damage. Oh, yeah. Why much is it check your?
It should be I think it's a d6. Okay, plus your
dexterity
One plus my dexterity so that's a four okay cool
So yeah, you do like you kind of like you break this you break the skin you almost break her whole it doesn't work
But yeah, so that was the first damage on her. She's like she like turns to you like glaring at you
I love you so much
She knows you almost made her shit her pants in front of an entire stadium of people
But yeah, you are up now Dogen. Okay, I'm casting um, oh wait, I should start with evil. What did you get again? 13?
Oh, what did you yeah?
Yeah, I got a nine. Yeah. Yeah, I'm casting inflict wounds
Right. That's how the started. Yeah. Yeah, and I
Think and this time the what's gonna happen is I open up a package of Oreos. I throw them like shurikens. Yeah
Yeah, like that as you throw them you hear like the distance laughter of the Oreo God
like as you like flow these Oreos yeah that's how the Oreo God sound oh he's
evil you were a guy to do it again how does he sound that's cool yeah it's a
start what if I do sugar in uh 17 he also goes that's what I'm looking for
patches yes maybe you like yeah that hits her for sure okay let me get a few
it's 3d 10 yeah it's a lot of demo huh okay this is 7 8 18 damage that means 18
Oreos hit her yeah yeah where do they hit her where they hit her they all hit in
the same spot and they create an Oreo out of her flesh wait no no make it make it
push the arrow in more they push the arrow in more yeah I mean I don't think
that make or no they make an Oreo out of first flesh I need it for my collection
that's my guys new thing he makes Oreos out of people on bronzes them very it's
very and maybe golds them later yeah yeah we two towns over if we get to
exactly yeah I hope you find a platinum er yeah I want a diamond er and I want a
older yeah I want to order - yeah a redstone one would be pretty cool yeah
what did you say an or a calcum or Calgium plus how about a hamburger yes
Kingdom Hearts hamburger would be would be hamburger would be huge you ordered
her though her leg briefly turns into an Oreo flesh he's like huh and then like
it's like a it flies into my hand like a pokeball yeah or her leg well the Oreo
Yeah, the Oreo casing of her flight, like she like sees that happening and she's like thinking like thank God he's not in love with me
Just wait
She's like wait, how did you hear that?
He's holding up the Oreo to his ear like a kid to hear the ocean and he hears her thoughts
Yeah, you're up
I'm sitting there
You're sitting on the ground. I'm sitting on the ground
just like
This is like
Indian style
Dick hard as hell
Because she actually touched my balls with her claws. Yes, sir, and then I
Use chill touch. Yes the classic. Yeah for it
On your balls or
Wait, what do I roll here? I
Rolled damn just roll a d20 right? Yeah, it's an attack roll. All right
- All right.
(dice rolling)
Four.
(laughing)
- So does she die?
- She dies immediately.
- No, the hand's sort of a,
like--
- You know what, if I already rolled the four,
can I just-- - Do you wanna describe it?
- Put the hand on my penis,
'cause it's already-- - Yeah, you do.
- Okay.
- It feels like a different-- - It's like petting your penis.
- Ghostly hand when you,
something about that. - Yeah, ghostly hand.
- Yeah, they call that the stranger.
- Yeah. - Yeah, right.
Ghostly stranger. Yeah, it's strange to put a cold hand on your penis. It's pretty normal to me feels like the inside of a
Like yeah, get me in a hotel guys doing something new. Yeah, I mean out of this hotel. Yeah
They're all trying to figure out if you're jerking yourself off or I'm pretending that I don't know what's going on
Reading it from a big spell book
Everyone everyone like in the stands can like see on the like jumbo Tron that the paid the spell book page is called like a ghostly
hand jerk off
Yeah, I'm just saying Latin to myself
Blue ass hands touching my cock jerk his office jerk his office immediates
Make his penis comas
uh...
uh... so you're doing that uh...
and it is now mister the frogs turn
he's a little bit or x
dorex
oh yes ship did you never roll in and i know i know he didn't
i know he's trying to focus over
was not trying to fuck you over a few days he's one of the worst d_n_a_'s of
ever misses not nice this year at the end of the season yes so chaotic and i
And you guys are being so mean to me.
Yeah, your energy is chaotic tonight.
My energy is, I think...
Yeah, you're Doomer's Millennial-ass.
Yep.
Yes, sir.
You're being chaotic neutral right now.
Yeah, your crackhead energy is seriously crackhead.
Don't say that.
You have quadriplegic vibes.
It's probably the $10 tier.
We can say that.
Mm-hmm.
that dollar here
we can say that
mhm
you're giving joseph watson
right now
oh my god it's a big it's a big it's a swan so you're serving scat
yeah
here
stop doing anything you're serving trashed and i
Yeah, you got Rachel Dratch vibes tonight.
Yeah.
[Laughter]
You fine in a freak way like a circus.
This is just fucking weird, man. You're just being fucking weird.
Okay. Alright, I found it.
I was wondering, I buried it somewhere.
I'm gonna bury you somewhere.
No!
In my asshole. Your face in my asshole.
Aww.
I'm gonna bury your face in the asshole.
I would like to make it clear that you do not have access to your own asshole.
he does go before solvin
so he's gonna uh... he's gonna take out his battle acts and just swing it
towards all i think i like
very deliberately like side step you jerky yourself off
and sort of what i'm gonna get your all you know whatever
that does it because of his strength is really high
uh... and let's do some damage
this is uh...
k
(laughter)
Do it in the mic, you pussy.
He does, uh, 16 damage.
He just fuckin' like,
cleaves into her fuckin' side
and like, rips the axe out
and he goes for a second attack.
Hey, hold on, before you do that, can you get my arrow back?
He's like, "Ugh!"
Oh.
Please. Don't do it.
Please. Don't do it. If you touch the arrow, you'll shit yourself.
No, you won't, you won't.
It's the tip of the arrow that makes you shit yourself.
So if I pull it out, he's like holding his axe there.
Hmm.
So if I pull it out, and if I don't touch the tip, I won't shit myself.
Yes, you won't.
Jerry's out. Don't do it.
Don't say pull it out right now.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna try to attack her again.
Okay, but after that, can you get the arrow out?
Yeah, sure. I'll use, I'll use my bonus action.
I'll give you 20 gold coins.
I'm doing my own deal in the orc pitch.
So he's gonna, first he's gonna try to attack.
Um, that does not hit.
And so he swings that for her again, and she's able to like, sort of curve around it.
it. He can't like try to grab the arrow right now, but he can try next turn. So now it's
Brim.
What? You're wasting, he's a strong guy, you're wasting his attack.
Now it's Mr. The Frog's turn. So Mr. The Frog missed, he tried to shoot darts. And the darts
just like limply fall directly in front of him.
I don't even want to say what that looks like, the way he's holding his hand right now.
What do you mean?
He looks like Sullivan keep that near your lips for like 20 more seconds. What are you talking about? That's exactly right?
Yeah, it looks like he's eating hot dog
Why are you me? I know you killed it for me. This is my darts. Okay, wait, it looks like you're sucking a penis. How about that?
Does that help yeah
He's naughty as hell I'm I'm I'm I'm pointing there to solve them looking at the crowd and be like this is a new celebrity
This is sucking penis guy
what about a shirt no no that's gonna be the most famous guy in the world don't
do it roll persuasion I had petrified our famous musician and this is sucking
penis guy nat 20 whole crowd at once in unison like fucking scanners just turns
to face all of it it goes socking penis
so I did the jumbotron it's like drawing
images all the time yeah you see
something like that's the face that goes
up the t-shirt - it's him like distraught
okay no big big Oh yeah that's the
second penis guy mommy look this sucky
penis guy he's gonna have a feature on my next track oh no it's like high school
all over again then I was the sucking thumbs guy this is way worse so we're
back to the top of the order it is Ola's turn she's looking pretty fucked up by
the way you guys did a lot of damage to her oh wait sorry no Dogen you didn't go
no I went I went yeah yeah yeah it is you know I didn't I was just thinking I
was trying to I was like thinking like oh I didn't see her I didn't hear about a
shuffle attack in my memory no you heard about beautiful Oreos it's my new thing
it's the only type of attack I'll ever do again so Ola is going to retaliate
it
to do a uh... spell attack on you
policy of the house
uh... numbers i can see
that's right she's got a few like flaming raise
and you just we park or as a warrior shield magical uses
parking it's a yeah you cast up what is the magical or a shield looks like the
cream
yeah yeah
was a nice i don't really was the advocate
and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and
I definitely should have said that.
A cookie, which is bad.
Yeah.
No, cookies are great.
I'll say it.
The cookie's my favorite part.
The cookie's really good on an Oreo.
Yeah.
It is.
I get it, no cream.
I will do anything to go to the next turn.
I get the double cookie.
What do you need me to do?
Patrick, it's your turn.
So I don't have the crap arrow.
Don't have the crap arrow.
You have normal arrows, though.
Why are you so fixated on this?
I do have normal arrows.
And I say, "Okay, this one this time is actually Cupid's arrow."
Yeah, roll deception. Yeah, just lie.
16 plus 6.
22. That's actually a pretty good roll.
Yeah, she's like a little concerned that that could be Cupid's arrow.
She's pretty sure you're a huge liar, but like you're extremely convincing.
Yeah. So I wind up for the attack.
I wind up like I point the arrow like Babe Ruth. Yeah like Babe Ruth.
The crowd's like where on her body are you pointing? At her butt.
Her eye?
Yeah.
Badass. I'm pointing at her
because I know she's prairie doggin' still.
You know she nasty down there too.
Yeah. So I'm pointing at her butthole.
She's fucking disgusting.
I'm pointing at her butthole. I'm hoping that this arrow
that this arrow hits her butt and poop comes out.
Okay yeah you can hope for that all you want.
I can't stop you from hoping that.
I think I have to give you permission to hope.
Well if I get a high enough roll I think that'll happen.
You know what? I think so.
Alright.
That is 18 plus...
What do I add to that?
I think 6.
What are your attack is oh my attack your bow and arrow attack
Is it under equipment or yeah, okay
Plus five
Yeah, you shoot it
She's like not her backs not to you, but your arrow just like
Makes us like winds a corner. It's like a bullet and who framed Roger Rabbit. Yeah
Exactly, and it's like it's like Faust in a guilty gear and she's making the face of like oh
As like it goes into her butt and
Doo-doo does come out and and it is stinky what color it is it is blue blue
(laughter)
- Damn.
- Okay.
- Yeah, I told you.
- It usually doesn't look like this.
- You taking me to Sea World.
- I told you guys I would make your crap.
- You didn't lie.
- Yeah.
- You see the announcer's like,
I cannot believe this is the first time
an orc has crapped in the stadium.
This is an amazing moment in Orc Tank history.
We are watching live an orc take a crap.
- I pull out a big cigar.
like the like like Babe Ruth and I just start smoking the cigar.
It's poop.
Yeah, I'm walking the bases.
Yeah, they're her bases.
[Humming]
[Screaming]
Um, yeah, roll for damage.
You also hit her.
That doesn't even matter anymore.
She already doodooed. She lost.
It's gonna be four damage.
Yeah, she is not looking good.
Take it home
Yeah, I'm gonna say no. I'm gonna take it home. What oh my turn. Can you skip your turn so I never one turn
No, okay, you got the jerk off man. Yeah, that's more than anyone else got to do
But what if I was setting up for the most amazing turn to ever?
You should tell me exactly how much HP she has right now. No, why not?
No, please we
We've actually been playing, but imagine the integrity of the game has been thrown out the window.
Just imagine if, let's keep, imagine if you told me that she had
3 HP left and I knew I could do a finishing blow just with my, with punching her with my hand.
Wouldn't that be so cool for the story?
No. I will say Patches, we have kind of been playing with this other DM who does tell us like what everyone's HP is.
And, uh, it hurts me so much.
Is it? His name is Scratches.
is
my guys
that guy you guys know what he was like when he's talking college
faxes discuss you know that he was actually pretty cool
so
and he was actually is probably doing
and he's probably doesn't even have any the the the
uh... modules so it is in the know
he rolls everything for us first of all that's not fun
if it's not right to run a show i don't know what now on
yet natural one yahoo which cratches to which cratches i let him when you
refused to close out of the other scratches it's not all scratches as is
the scratches scratches you don't know that i had all cratches
and uh... what actually does it have you seen it and i have a great you get in
that way to give you tell you i'm not one counts as a twenty one
you know it's it is a blackjack yeah exactly it's blackjack rules well yeah
Different game, so that's another yeah, we exactly he does he has a cooler game
Yeah, he knows how to meld games together cuz he's like we play
That's somebody you you
You're the worst crunches and dragons
Looking DM ever compared. I don't play crunches and cragons. I play Dungeons and Dragons
Yeah, what people over that is you made a version of crunches and dragons called Dungeons
You know which we tow it. Yeah, that makes sense
Which we tell at Yatches when we play yungins and yagins.
Like I know I'm tired of hearing about my brothers. Well, okay, so I
Rolled in that one. So just like do something to me. Yeah, sure. Yeah, okay
Were you trying to do I was trying to punch her. Oh my god, you ever seen that?
Charles Charles Bukowski great guy had this book he did with Robert Crumb where this woman punches herself square in the face
So that Robert Crumb draws the drawing
You do that. You just punch yourself square in the face. Yeah, is that okay? Yeah, that's good
What scratches do that or what? He might be like cooler what but he probably described it like a little better
But yeah, yeah, he might do something funny where like he punches himself in the face and like places his teeth like piano key
Yeah, and it goes like "awooga" when he plays the piano keys, even though they're piano keys.
Well, Scratches sounds like he has a 45% chance of being a racist, too, by the way, so...
Yeah, and he chases a little mouse.
You're gonna want to bump that number up.
Alright, your turn, Evil Steeble.
Okay, I...
I did steal my turn for you.
...been sitting crisscross applesauce style.
I learned that it's wrong to call it Indian style between now and the last turn I had.
You've been hanging out with Scratches too much.
I get up, I've cum all over my face, and I'm smirking.
Color become yeah blood red
But viscous like come yeah
Yeah, well I have I've had a kidney stone for a really long time and
It cut the tip of my penis. Yeah, so all the cum was boy. I understand and now I'm gonna cast level two inflict wounds on
This stupid ass. Oh
Damn level two. Yeah
Yeah
19. Oh my god. 3d10s. Damn, she's about to fucking die dude. I think 3d10 is level 1.
No. Mine is 4d10. I don't think so. Mine is only level 1 and I got 3d10. Yes, I think
you got 4. No, 3d10s is my level 2. You can roll it in there. Oh, did you trick me? No,
it says 3d10 on mine. Unless I'm casting at level 2. You might have casted at level 2.
No, look, first level, 3D10.
Plus four is my attack bonus on this,
so it's actually like a 23, right?
Yeah, that's weird.
All right.
Maybe his spell is just worse than mine.
It probably is.
You're better, you have a better character.
That's not how the spells work.
Oh, thank you.
I mean, that's fine.
All right.
I'm gonna tell you what, unless you do something,
unless you do it horribly, you're probably gonna
not kill her, you can declare that you knock her out,
which is--
You know what, if there's one thing
we've learned in this campaign is that I've never had a bad roll. So I think
this is gonna be pretty damn golden for old baby boy. Damn! 16. Yeah I mean describe
your knocking her out. Unless you want to kill her. I walk over with cum on my
face still smirking, still smirking walking in her like Frankenstein and
then I headbutt her so a little bit of it gets on her face. And then how do you
inflict wounds and then yes you cast these spells and it's just like I'll say
you know what your inflict wounds the red come on your face when you headbutt her
it like wraps around her skull and singes her head that's what I meant to say and
she's like and like just falls to the ground and you guys win you can accept
yeah I go over I go over and get my arrow yeah first thing and what happens when
you touch it I touch the the hilt yeah I yeah when you're picking it up and you
pull you you pull it out too hard and you fall back and it grazes me and I go
I'm trying to get up I'm trying to get up and I'm like going like and it hits
Steve on the leg - I walk over here while she's knocked out and I suck my ball
juice off her hand nice a hands off the merchandise do you all I reabsorb it
into my body. I wish I could just veto that. Yeah, and then I fart.
*fart noise*
Um, yeah, all that happens.
Everyone lets that happen in the arena. The arena, they all still like you guys for some reason.
Here's why. Get me out of this damn hotel.
Yeah, he says that and then I do, uh, just like,
I just play piano man on a keytone. Do y'all wanna see penis sucking man suck my penis?
No!
Yeah!
Let's see it!
Let's see it right now!
Come on!
Sullivan, we gotta put on a show for him.
I don't wanna suck your penis, man.
Have I ever given a fuck what you wanted?
No!
Alright.
Oh no, he's right!
So yeah, the announcer comes to you and he says, "Well, it looks like you three, four,
five," remembering the characters that Patrick is playing, "don't do this to me."
Seven.
about Dolby Dolby Dolby come on out come on out yeah yeah you see like a a like
fat like like a guy who looks like he looks like um Phil Collins from trailer
park boys but he has a single eye on his head and he's like this is why we don't
use you in battle you guys this is does it the sounding make does that come from
his eyeball he doesn't have a mouth I think it's coming from his butt
You see his butt and it like licks its lips?
*laughter*
It's like, "Mmm."
The butt starts singing "Brown Sugar" by the Rolling Stones.
"He's nasty and I'm glad he's gone."
*laughter*
And the announcer then says,
"You have two offers. One where I think you give the walrus two fish, and the other one that's a little bit more legitimate."
We give him a fish and then...
We'll do both.
Yeah, we'll do both offers.
"You can only pick one. That's the rule."
Fine, the walrus.
(laughing)
- Is that your final decision?
- I think, hold on, let's just ask this,
ask fucking Thorax, I'm busy, I gotta--
- Hola, hola, please, if they pick anyone.
- I gotta--
- I wanted Ritter Finn, but I'll take Hola.
- I gotta plan my world tour, I gotta do all this stuff,
I'm going to buy, I have to go buy sunglasses
on ye olde Rodeo Drive.
- You keep talking about this record deal
and nobody seems to know what you're talking about ever.
- I, uh--
- I think you may have come up with it in your brain.
Tell you what you do have.
- I think there's a lot of things going wrong in my life.
- You have a brass bronze ass.
- A brass ass.
- You got a, it may be a bronze ass,
but it's a brass ass.
- Yeah, maybe, you know, maybe, maybe,
maybe big time stars do weird things all the time.
- I hit his ass with my shovel.
- Maybe sometimes somebody puts a diamond in their forehead.
- And it goes like, boom.
- Like a little Uzi.
- Please pick, please pick Ola.
- Walrus.
- Wait, is Ola the walrus's name?
- Pick Walrus.
Walrus?
You want us to pick the walrus?
He just left his hands, he like, can't believe he brought you here.
Alright.
Okay, here, we'll flip a coin.
Oh my god.
If it's the walrus, then it's walrus.
If this is one, two, three, it's the walrus.
If it's four, five, six, it's Ola.
Okay, I'm glad you brought your dice with you.
I'm doing this in fiction.
This one.
Yeah, we were playing on a plane.
That is a huge coin.
Oh, oh, fuck.
Thank god.
That was a four.
I'm gonna go ahead and flip a coin.
I'm gonna flip a coin.
Oh, oh, oh, thank God.
That was a four.
Oh, God.
Wait, wait, what's your minus?
All right, I have a minus one.
All right, you're going to go with the walrus?
No, no.
Oh, the dice already spoke.
It's a lie.
Okay.
Yeah, the dice already spoke.
Ola, does your offer still stand?
And she's like nodding in pain.
That's all right, everyone.
And she crept.
The
Yelling at the sky
The less you know she cried those pants yeah, she got three homeless guys
Amusement Park idiot land stupid ville will be funded by Ola for
evaluation of
300,000 with 40 per at 40% she gets 5% on the advisory board and they get to be a part of Ola's
amazing
magical service group so that's
pretty stellar
Congratulations fellas
Yeah, I already we already all left. Yeah, okay, so as you guys walk back
I
want to
One second here. I'm just I'm waiting in the stadium. No, they left
I'm waiting in the stadium because like nobody's really clapping. Everyone's just kind of like
You see the walrus he's like
He's like it's alright. Don't worry about it. Like he just wants fish. Why isn't a
No one's clapping for us
The arena area, everyone is pretty stoked for you guys.
They're like slapping you on the back.
Thorax gives you guys a big hug.
What did I say about his back?
Ow.
Don't touch it.
That shit hurts, man.
Thorax gives you guys like a big hug.
He's like, "Thank God."
Ow.
Like, "Fuck you."
He's like nursing the hangover, but he's like,
"We're gonna be like, 'We're gonna be fucking rich.
I'm gonna get my tower.'"
He's like so excited.
I don't remember you fighting with us.
Sullivan is like...
[laughing]
Sullivan is like, "Ugh."
Sullivan is like is happy. He's like imagining his general story. And I don't seem to remember you fighting with us either
I did fight with you! I don't think you were there. I think you just sat out there and you sucked a cock
Yeah, you became the dick sucking guy. And as you walk by everybody and you walk by
Everyone that's going on
You recall however brief despite your best efforts to black it out entirely that bouquet toss
from way back when.
A shared moment of deja vu, time slows down again like it did that time when you tossed a bouquet,
but this time you know your destinies, or you know them by their weight, of which you know there is none,
but you know them all the same.
The knowledge,
so secret to the mortals as within your grasp, reaching, you make futile connections and patterns in an instant,
but it's the process of reaching that grants you the new weightless and
Indefinable wisdom you're just sort of like have this moment wash over you all where it's like you know something
You don't know what it is. It's that feeling again when you beat the jester. It's this feeling of
You're being tied to something larger
Something inside you recalls, but doesn't retain a frightening truth that you're worthy
These developments are incremental
You know that some part of you knows that part of you that doesn't know anything knows that
The spirits that live in the planet have made themselves known to you. The large informal council of energies conversed loudly about you.
The non-presence of the intangibles tips towards darkness though in this city.
As far as your conscious mind is concerned you have a single realization
from this larger cosmic non-episode. In Gal Gadot,
the most prominent pro-slavery voice amongst the terrifier porn,
you are surrounded by enemies of the king.
Which means enemies of the prince
And as you walk further and towards the arena you realize there are two people missing
the shaman and
the prince
after party at the gold or
I guess we'll take it up from there next time.
from there next time
[laughing]
[Music]