[Music]
Last time on Wally Wankoff and the Candy Bombs and Toilets Factory.
The four remaining winners of the Brown Sticker Competition finally entered the factory, where
they were greeted by the sterile chaos of a modern mega-corporation.
While it appeared to be a well-oiled machine, Wankoff led them to a room that was suffering
from a peculiar plague of mismanagement or non-management.
The Chocolate Swamp.
The room was supposed to be where all the chocolate is made, but no chocolate has been made in
years since the swamp and the poop from the sewer system and toilet manufacturing part
of the factory has infiltrated the chocolate swamp, making it a confusing, smelly mess.
A babble-like tower made of chocolate and sludge lingered in the distance of the swamp,
and so Wankov suggested they head in that direction on his speedboat, attended by one
of the frog workers, known as Sullivans.
The Sullivans sang their song about how they are slaves, and lamented to Wankoff about how
they built the tower to protect themselves from the swamp monster that has been terrorizing
them for years.
The swamp monster then made an appearance, and after Waylon Au Revoir cleverly appealed
to his better nature by feeding him treats, the gang spotted a tube sticking out of the
swamp monster's backside that was pumping it full of shit, making it big and angry.
Our heroes acted quickly, defeating the two, though not without some serious casualties.
Weyland suffering the most damage, and nor without Pinocchio discovering that when he
tells jokes, his nose grows in diameter, turning him into some kind of horrifying freak with
essentially a tree trunk on his face.
Afterwards, the gang determined that they should head to the control room where Wankov could
fix most everything.
To do that, however, they needed to travel through the very dilapidated, now sewer-like,
toilet room pipe network from which the tube that was pumping the monster full of shit
had sprung.
That's a lot of tube there.
Arriving there, they found a beautiful woman made of shit named Lady Dibby, who led them
to a weaker portion of the piping in the toilet room network of pipe things that they're
in, sort of a weaker portion of it that they could reach the control room from if they're
able to break it down. However, Turdevils, a quickly reskinned enemy that are turkeys
with devils inside of them, hover around that area of the pipe. So, they have to be taken
care of. So, after Waylon did some looney-tuned antics, the battle began in earnest. And here
Here we are at the battle.
What did we get for initiatives gang?
I didn't roll it yet.
Oh my god.
I got distracted.
17.
Nice.
Create one.
Three.
Okay.
Pinocchio.
I forgot Pinocchio, did you prepare anything for this?
Or no?
I well I was thinking I would stop spinning around like a top and
Then maybe I would maybe fall over and start kind of rolling towards him very slowly. I like that
So you're in the middle of doing that?
Yeah, I'm like, I'm pretty busy with that. So if you could like get off my case like that. Yep. Sorry
We've had this problem before I'm sorry
Okay
And that's her devil's whose move set has been adjusted
it
Oh wait, Bibby!
Oh yeah, I have a sling attack.
Prepared.
Things have gone south.
Thirteen.
That's enough.
Eight sling damage.
Good gosh.
I'm shooting, also my sling ammo is my teeth
that fell out.
Which one are you shooting?
My tooth.
Which turd do you have?
I guess I'll just go for the one
that Waylon is also stabbing. Yeah. Good. Yeah. That one is
not looking good. It just got stabbed in the throat and then
a tooth I guess hurled at its cranium. Um so he's looking in
dire straits. Uh you're up now Waylon though. You just stabbed
this guy in front of you. Oh, whoa. Okay. Um I will cast uh
Dissonant Whispers. Beautiful. At the same one or a different
different one. I'll do a different one. Hell yeah. I'll look to his friend and I'll
point to him and I'll whisper like "I have to go out to Wabbaja, put my money on it." Baby talk. Yeah. Fuck him up. Yeah, go for it.
Where is... yo, shit, there it is. Alright, what'd you get on that? I got a four. You got a four
damage? Okay cool. Wow, that's crazy. Alright, I'll roll the resistance for that,
which is not very good. It'd be to 14 right? Yeah. Alright. They're not very uh wise.
So says you. Yeah. Well, they could have been wiser here. They actually really just
rolled very low. So, yeah, they're gonna take that full four damage. This uh you
get the one in the back or the one that was near it. Uh I'll do the one. Yeah, the
one right next to him. I'll like point to him like you're. Yeah. Yeah, he's just
like freaking out now he's like eyes are wide like a woman just stabbed his
friend and a tooth came out of nowhere and he's like just so so upset and
you're going by the way good at it and like it's it's not a pretty sight for
him unless you want to do like a bardic inspo yeah I'll do I'll do a bardic inspo
what is that sorry I don't remember what that is or does so as a bard you you can
basically like look to somebody and do a little dance or a little jig or play a
little tune and you give them 1d6 that they can use in any like ability check
or saving throw or okay yeah yeah I'll look at John Candy who I think is like
right next to him too. I'll do a little dance for him.
Go! Go! Yeah!
Okay, cool. So you got a d6 you can spend on shit now. You're raging by the way, John
Candy. We have to resolve that. We've got to resolve that. So roll that table. Let's
the
to
hits you with the attack roll before your rage ends.
That creature takes 1d6 force damage as magic lashes out in
retribution. We now know what happened to your nephew.
Cool. Yeah. So you have these like magical tendrils sort of
whipping around you as this lawyer boy is doing a lawyer
dance for you and you're feeling pretty good there, but
we're going to go to Bibby.
Yes, you're up.
You just lost a tooth at one of these two devils.
Yes, I did.
I'm going to run up to a different one.
There's one is there one that hasn't been damaged yet?
Yeah, that one.
I don't know if you're going to reach on like one round of
movement.
All right, then I'll go to the one that's been damaged a
little bit.
Yeah, if I can reach that one.
Yeah that one you could reach.
Okay, and I'm going to use I'm going to attack with my
crutches.
Amazing first.
Mm-hmm. That's a 20. Yeah, that hits 3020.
That's 12 damage. Jesus Christ and then I'm going to spend a
key point to do a flurry of blows to make two additional
unarmed strikes. We're going to be a one to kick. Hell. Yes.
That's a nine. Nope. Okay. That is a twenty. Yep. That is six
damage. Nope. Nope. I'll put that out. Sorry. Yeah, describe your kill. Yeah, I'm just going
I'm just kind of going crazy. Like I just I just I bound over there on my on my crutches
and I swing my crutch and like when I hit when I hit the turd devil with my crutch I like
fall over because I lose I lose one of my crutches and I kind of just accidentally kick the bottom
of the turd devil and the devil flies up out of the turkey and like lands in the poop water.
Yeah exactly. Yeah I was flying up and just face plant into the water.
It's little little red asses out and he's face down like a little turtle.
Yeah, you say that too. Uh and now it's the turd devil's turn. So,
the one that um attacked you or you attacked uh Waylon is uh
going to try to like like clack at you with its little uh
turd devil beak. Um. Yeah, fair's fair. Yeah, right? Makes
sense. Um let's see how it does. Uh what is your AC? I should
Just have 1212 OK just misses it.
Clack see you and misses and
then it's going to whip around
and look to you Pinocchio as
you're rolling towards it.
It suddenly gets alarmed by you
and its stomach slice opens up.
A devil opens it up and goes and just
shoots lasers out of its eyes at you.
Yeah, yeah, now that's happening.
Yeah, thanks a lot.
Okay, and he misses though.
Great.
And yeah, the other devil now from the back is going to
shake its feathers around creating a little like sort of
shit stirring up a little bit of shit around it making it a
little bit harder to hit for a little while and then the devil
that's gonna rip open the stomach out of that turd devil and
shoot at you, uh, baby.
After you killed his friend.
That's right.
That hits you for sure.
Oh yeah.
Oh, indeed.
How much damage?
What?
Oh, sorry.
I just rolled something and say by accident.
Uh, okay.
There's 11 damage.
Okay.
You dead?
I'm at eight.
Yeah.
Okay.
Awesome.
So now we're back to the top of the order.
Waylon, au revoir.
You are up.
Wait, so I didn't really get to go, huh?
Oh, I'm an idiot.
I'm so sorry.
I just, I'm like nothing to you.
I'm like trash basically.
Did I, did I?
I went with the-
John, you go.
Actually, John came.
And then Pinocchio, I'm so sorry.
I was looking at the turn order and got confused.
You're looking at it and you thought, "I'm just not going to follow this?"
Yeah.
I was like, "Oh, I'm just going to follow this."
I'm like, "Oh, I'm just going to follow this."
You're looking at it and you thought, "I'm just not going to follow this."
Yeah.
No, wait.
How is you looking at the turn order make it?
That makes it way worse, actually.
Precisely the issue.
The things that were at my eye level were not helping.
It still doesn't help.
You know what?
One day I'll draw a diagram and it'll make some sense.
All right.
Yeah, you're up, John.
Are there any magic items nearby?
*laughter*
Yeah man, what's up?
Is there any magic items?
No, no, no, what are you- what- I need- what's the motive?
Well, well, well tell me first.
To use the magic items.
Are you trying to trick me?
No, there's no magic items nearby.
Tell me what the motive is, let's figure something out.
Are there any spells nearby?
Yeah.
Do you mean like spell scrolls?
Yes.
No.
Okay, then never mind.
I won't use this action.
Okay, what are you going to do?
So I'm in a I'm in rage now, right?
That's right.
Yeah.
And I have the so anyone takes damage from me.
Uh, what was it again?
Hold on.
Let me read this.
Somebody hits you.
They're gonna basically have to deal with them like a meant magical.
Oh, yeah.
One d six of force damage.
Yeah.
Okay. In the meantime, you have bonuses to your attacks while
you're raging. Oh, alright. Then, I'll just yeah, I guess
I'll just like how close am I to one of these turd devils? I
mean, you're in range of I would say of the one that is
like nearest that's the one that's near Arvo because you
haven't really moved yet. So, you're the one that's near
We learn.
All right.
I'm just going to hit him with my whip.
Then.
Yeah, you take out your belt.
Do I roll that with advantage or something or no?
So instead you just you're just going to add more damage when
you when you hit.
Okay, so roll first.
Oh 2419.
They both hit.
Yeah for damage and we're going to add an additional two to
that.
Okay.
Yeah, let's describe your kill.
That was just enough.
Yo, okay.
I see that I see that Waylon stop dancing and I'm like,
what the fuck?
What the fuck? Keep dancing.
I want to whip to him to keep dancing.
I miss completely.
And I just just take the head off.
It's her devil. Yeah.
Yeah. And it runs around with its head off.
And then the devil's head pops out and its head comes off and it UHF style.
I want the head off. Yes. Perfect. Yeah.
And it just sort of sputters and calms down forever.
Wait, so you said he whips the head off and then a second head comes up.
The devil's head.
Hit by nothing, it also falls off.
Yeah, it just falls off.
From sadness.
It just also falls off.
Yeah, we play fast and loose when it comes to death here.
Anything can happen.
My head flies off.
Yeah, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Pinocchio.
What's up, Playboy?
Um, okay, so I'm gonna use...
So I don't have this pillar face thing on my attack list, do I?
You have it. It's gonna be...
If you scroll down...
Oh, okay, there it is.
So I'm gonna start... How many turduckins or turdevils are there left?
There's only one.
Okay, I'm gonna start rolling at him pretty slow at first.
I was gonna say, because this one is the one that's a bit further away,
but you have an extra five feet of range on this thing.
range on this thing so you can reach it. So I'm gonna use
pillar face. Hell yeah. Seventeen that hits roll for
damage.
Nine great. So how do you do you just collapse on them? I
want you to I keep rolling and II like I flatten him like
like judge doom at the end of who framed roger rabbit yeah and his eyes get really big and
they like kind of pop out the devil's head pops out of the the turkey yeah exactly yeah
he's just doing that that whole song and dance yeah that whole song and dance yes yeah amazing
yeah you just flatten this guy um we're back to the top of the order now waylon au revoir
I think I'm so afraid of John Candy who just said dance and whipped at me.
I'm gonna keep dance. I'm gonna give another bardic inspiration to him. Can I do that?
Yeah, yeah you can.
Yeah, I don't think I take any other action though. I'm terrified.
It's normal.
Just with panic in my eyes.
What dance do you do? Yeah, what song do you sing?
I sing under the bridge and I do a little like...
I started crying. I'm crying so hard because it's so beautiful.
*laughter*
*unintelligable*
I'm thinking about every mistake I've made in my life.
*laughter*
Including the one you like just made.
Oh no no no no no mistake mistakes in my mind which are like I didn't buy like
that candy or like I like listen or you know yeah exactly I didn't buy certain
types of candy yeah it was like oh I could have bought I could have bought a
Reese's at the store
Oh man, yeah. So that upsetting domestic tableau, we move aside, we go to Bibby.
What's happening? I'm on the ground because I ended my last turn on the ground and I haven't
gotten up. I don't really feel like getting up, so I'm just gonna shoot my sling at the last
or devil from the ground. Yes.
That's a 12.
Oh, that hits OK.
That's 6 damage nice.
Yeah, you do 6 damage.
Yeah, you just shoot another
the tooth at it.
It got rolled over and it's like
flattened and just as it's starting
to like spring back up, you just.
Like just whack it and it's sort of
like like wretches its head back
and it's like blah blah blah.
Yeah, I try to stand up and I fall back down.
Good as as as as the Lord.
Yeah, what?
I don't know.
I had a problem there motor motor.
Oh God.
I'm sorry.
I'm moving this week.
Okay, is it's her is it's her devil's turn now.
And so it's going to as it's starting to spring back up Pinocchio.
it is going to try to clack at you because you are just sort of rolling around nearby
it.
Um, and you did also my, my vision is so blurred by the speed that I'm like, I don't really
know what I'm doing.
What's your AC?
Uh, 14.
Yeah.
It's itch you.
Okay.
Again, I don't, I have no really awareness of my sense.
It might as well be like a mosquito bite.
Yeah.
Well, and hopefully it'll only feel like one.
Five damage.
You take it.
Yeah.
I'm going to take it.
you take. Okay. And then it's gonna mosquito bite that takes
30% of my entire life. Yeah and then it's going to attack you
again with the clack. It's gonna try to clack at you again.
Okay. Let's see what this does. Yeah. No, it got a crit one. So
just like tries to get it your wooden nose form and it like
gets stuck in it for a little bit and starts to roll with you
and just like sort of shakes off and shakes off and
stops doing that. John Candy.
Because I've been crying so much because of how inspired I was by the song.
Yeah. I don't do it, you know.
(laughter)
- I get like, what's like around me right now?
Like what's close?
- There's a lot of shit.
- Yeah, there's a lot of turd devils or?
- There's a couple turd devil corpses.
- There any more turd devils?
- That are alive?
- Yeah.
- Right, there's one that you're fighting right now.
- Oh, it's fighting me?
Well, it's fighting everyone.
I just grab how close it is to me.
You can get over there at this point.
You're close enough to this guy.
Okay, I'm going to I hear him because he just hit Caleb,
right?
So I hear him being loud.
And I go over to him and I just like grab pick him up and
start shaking him and is like don't you fucking hear that
song that you pick up the turd devil.
Yeah, they're great.
I'm reprimanding him for not listening to the most beautiful song I've ever heard.
So you're gonna grapple him I guess.
So oh, are you attacking him?
Oh shit, you're hitting him?
Well I mean I'm in a rage and I also can't control myself.
Okay, oh you're just gonna do an unarmed strike.
You're just grabbing him and like throttling his neck.
Yeah.
Alright yeah, roll for damage.
That does hit him.
Four.
Okay, yeah, you just almost kill him.
You choke almost all the life out of this guy.
Oh wait, shit, we add two to that.
How do you kill him?
I'm grabbing the turdevil by the neck and I'm like, "LIZARD, I'M FUCKING SORRY!"
And then I just snap the neck completely off of its body immediately and then the devil
head pops up and just grabs that by the neck too and do the same thing.
Yeah, you guys have defeated the turd devils.
Um, uh, and yeah, that's great.
You see a lady dibby comes out and uh, um, wank off.
Um, and lady dibby says, this is wonderful.
You've taken care of the two devils for me.
Thank you.
Yeah, I did it all by myself.
No, I I was watching the fight.
I know you did a very good job.
I did the best job.
And she sort of looks at you three and she says, if I say, should I say yes here?
You're all sort of varying levels of uselessness.
I'm waving at her right now.
I'm waving like she's like behind a mirror or behind a window.
And I'm just like, I'm waving at her like she's behind a mirror.
I somehow have gotten I'm somehow on my back flat and the weight of my nose is just slowly
just crushing my own face.
Completely flat.
I have not much to respond right now.
Okay, we'll let's you know what?
Let's address that now.
So, Pinocchio, as you're getting crushed, your nose starts to change a little bit more.
It starts to crush into you, this part of your body.
And to the point where it's crushing down into your face, crushing down into your body,
and now you have these two legs that are just coming out, and just this pillar for a body.
And you start, your eyes start to pop up from the top of this pillar.
And a mouth slit starts to form.
You're making me go fuckin' Thomas the Tank Engine now?
You're becoming a tree.
Oh wow.
You're too, okay.
I have a new character to assign you.
Because I can't possibly allow you to be that big and different without you getting a whole
new character.
So I'm gonna assign this to you.
Because I've evolved.
Pokevolved, your new Pinocchio, as far as I'm concerned, you can call yourself, I don't know,
whatever you want, Bill Hickory, if you're doing the comedian thing. I don't know.
That's all you had. Just don't.
I was thinking about that the other day and I was like, that's kind of funny. And I couldn't
think of anything else. I couldn't think of any other comedian tree puns. Spruce Spruce.
I don't know, Lenny Spruce.
How about, how about, how about like a...
That was a, that was good.
Yeah, it was very good.
That was good.
How about like a, uh, like Red Fox, like giant, like giant red fox.
Redwood Fox.
Redwood Fox is what I meant to say, basically.
Yeah, Redwood Fox.
Yeah, you're Redwood Fox.
Okay, well, I can't wait to hear that voice.
So, let me...
Okay.
But he has my normal voice so that I can stop getting confused with Bibi.
Alright, so click on this link I sent you.
Alright. Whoa. More HP.
Yep, you have more HP, lower AC, you're some kind of tree, deformed tree man now.
Um, uh, when you lie, we'll see what happens.
Um, and yeah.
And yeah, it's pretty soon because I'm curious. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah. And so that just like happens in front of everybody
it's horrific by the way you see my my arms. Okay. So yeah,
so I'm I'm sitting there the last thing the last time that
I'm recognizable as Pinocchio. I have this giant tree trunk
just just crushing my head and you see the wood around my my
face start to splinter and crack and then at some point it just
bursts and then the tree the the trunk hits the ground roots
shoot out of it. Yes. And those are my new legs. Yes. and then
it just slowly like it grows maybe another five feet or so
tall and just drags the lifeless boy body with it kind
of it's like it's wearing it as a cape at this point and then
my eyes pop out, my mouth pops out.
I say, "Hey, everybody."
(all laughing)
- What's the--
- I feel a lot better now and taller.
- Was that puberty?
What was that?
What did I, what was that?
- I'm not even gonna try to begin to explain
or pretend that I know what just happened to me.
- I hope that happens to me someday.
- You know, probably more likely,
I'm going to fall on you pretty soon.
Yeah, I'm already I'm trying to climb.
Pinocchio or I guess what?
What are we going with?
Redwood Redwood Fox Redwood Fox.
I'm climbing Redwood Fox.
Yeah.
So.
Cool, she says Lady Debbie says.
There was the weak point.
The pipe is just this way and
She leads you a bit more down this sort of sludge toilet,
both piping and also showroom for toilets.
You find sort of a weaker area of the pipe.
And she says, "In there,
we'll lead you to the bombs room.
So just be careful going down."
- Are you telling me to be careful specifically?
- Yeah, yeah.
Yes.
(laughing)
- I'll be very careful.
I'm I'm instantly I'm flying across the room hitting walls. I'm ricocheting off of stuff. I'm yeah, of course. Yeah
So yeah, you guys want to break through that pipe?
You can do some attacks on it to break it open or we can just use I guess you could just use some
Pinocchio or red redwood Fox as a battering ram also
Let's do it. Yeah
Yeah, you gotta now go ahead pick me up
I decided to do the voice now.
Fuck yes.
Okay, yeah, you're picked up.
Why does he sound like Louis Armstrong?
That's what Red Fox sounded like, bro.
No.
Go watch a Red Fox video right now.
Okay.
Don't watch a Red Fox video.
Just like that.
It also sounds like a big tree, so I think that's a good voice.
Yeah.
Yeah, Pat's gonna watch a Red Fox video.
I see the lights.
This guy was pretty funny.
He was very funny. You were one second into the video.
Yeah, look what he's doing.
Check this video out, he's so funny.
Keep this in. Let's see what the video. Let's see what this video is.
Oh, that's funny.
All right.
That's pretty funny.
Red Fox hilariously pounces headfirst to the snow from the Smithsonian channel.
Does that mean that you search Red Fox hilarious?
That's how Matt gets a lay of any stand up comedians.
There's just their name plus hilarious.
Any good?
Most hilarious clip.
You don't want like their serious moment on Marin where they talk about their divorce.
No, not at all. I don't want to hear that bullshit.
To the point, it's funny.
Remember when Redd Foxx went on Bandit and talked about his divorce?
[Laughter]
I type in the comedian's name and then pounce his head first into snow.
So I also got this video.
They all do it.
Yeah, you gotta do it once.
Oh man, okay.
So yeah, you use Redd Foxx as a battery grab.
And you bust through this pipe.
and sort of slide out and sort of sludge and gunk comes out after you and you slide out
into this beautiful like the opposite looking place.
Beautiful pristine room with all these like bombs of different kinds in like glass cases
that are being protected on you see frogs and robots and lab coats working on these
bombs.
Um, Wankoff sort of dusts himself off.
Um, and he says, uh, uh, uh, this is okay.
So this room I'm in all the time.
All right, this is kind of, you know, this is where the real money comes from, to be
honest.
You know, I got to make sure it's in tip top shape.
Got government guys coming in, always buying shit from me.
So this room I could tell you guys about.
We got tons of bombs in here.
We're working day in, day out.
We got H bombs, C4, C5, C6, nail bombs.
We got the Moab, the Foab, the Goab, the Doab, the Shlomoab.
We got it all.
So yeah, there's not really anything we have to do in here.
We just have to get to the control room, I guess, and unclog the toilet.
That'll be great.
Well, okay, I'll just walk a straight line through this room.
I'm like, yeah, I'm falling one way coming so close to like a glass case with a bomb
in it.
disrespect should we moisty kill Bibby?
Moisty kill.
I'm frankly not against it at this point but maybe we could just tie him to the tree guy.
Oh boy!
Hell no!
We try to put Bibby up on one of his branches and it immediately snaps.
That hurts me.
Okay.
Okay, look, uh, baby, like, uh, wait, you, you've got a belt still, right?
Do you have another belt?
John.
What?
Fuck, dude.
Oh my God.
I don't have to deal with this bullshit right now.
Do you have a spare belt or can we just use your belt just while we're-
I have a shoelace.
Okay, you know what, fine.
Okay, and so yeah, they're just tying your shoelace as a belt.
You tying the shoelaces your crutches together, baby.
So you're just sort of like a slug on the ground now and yeah,
wake up goes but my favorite bomb by the way, and he snaps
his fingers and you see a robot come out and lift up lift up
in a bomb and it looks this like beautiful like like orb.
It looks almost like a little glass orb that has like this swirling pink mist in it.
Similar to the mist you saw outside the factory.
Because this is my candy dream bomb.
Can I touch it?
Yeah, well, I just rolled a sling attack
because I accidentally just shot a tube out of my sling.
OK, hit the ball.
Oh, my God. OK, that does hit the bomb.
Uh, okay, the bomb goes off.
I mean...
Uh, okay, and uh, uh,
Wankoff is like, "Oh no, what the fuck, no! Everyone hold your nose!"
Um, I mean, there's no way, you're not prepared for this.
Okay, uh, "I-I think I am a nose!"
"Still not sure!"
fucking shit. So this sleepy pink fog sort of starts to billow out of the bomb and you
all sort of drift off into sleep. You hear chimes playing, you know the ones. And you're
in the candy dream zone. All each of you. Are you for real? Yeah, each of you. Oh my
My God, did I just go to heaven?
Yes, in a way.
Each of you right now are in your own.
Well, they got dead.
Don't worry.
Okay.
Each of you.
Well, but.
This doesn't look anything like the heaven I've seen.
Each of you are in your own sort of separate personal
candy dream zones.
You're not aware of one another.
You're probably not even aware of it.
you're in the candy dream sound to be honest. You're each experiencing
something specific to your character which I want to talk through with you.
What is let's start with Mr. Mr. Dibby Mr. Dibby baby over here baby baby baby
baby just baby what would be your dream zone? I'm I'm dancing in a circle
holding hands with like cars and trains and bicycles and planes and we're all
friends and we're all really happy. Holding them by the wheel. Yeah. We'll come back to that.
Just going down the the zoom call here. Mr. Redwood Fox, what's your dream zone?
what do you want I'm on stage doing the this during my stand-up routine and the
seven dirty woods you can't say on TV
can I hear a bit of that? Oak! Bruce! That's it. Pine! They won't let you say pine no more!
yeah the audience is fucking loving it. yeah it's true I can't say pine yeah
Mr. Waylon Aruwa. What is ideal for men? A really clean courtroom, there's like willows
outside and like Spanish moss, the little the ceiling fan is moving slowly. Yes. As
I say, and for that I turn I get my closing argument and say, "and then for that
reason he should be tortured to death." Yeah. And the judge hits the gavel and
says, "I agree!" and everyone applauds. Yes, of course, yeah, and you see the defendants are all just
people you've met just anybody it's not yeah it's just anyone you've met before
I'm seven I've met like ten people yeah yeah yeah and you John Candy what's your
dream zone pal I'm uh it's literally just me at a gas station just buying one
one
you
Oh my god.
Do you want to-
No!
Okay.
So.
No!
Uh, now, and uh, Wankoff's is somewhere having his.
But you guys don't have any view into that.
What?
Well you don't.
Everyone else got to see mine.
Well, yeah but Wankoff is, is, you know, that's you guys telling the audience.
Okay, you all take-
I'm sick of you.
You're not the first.
You all take 2 damage.
Okay.
Well I have 30, I'm at full health.
So I don't care.
Okay.
Now, Bibby.
You're dancing with the cars, you take this bit of damage.
Roll a wisdom saving throw.
Okay.
That is a 15.
Wow, holy shit.
Okay, that's exactly it.
As you're dancing with the cars, you're holding onto their wheels, dancing.
What are the trains, what are all the vehicles doing?
What's the plane doing? Is the plane doing like a left shark kind of dance?
Yeah, the train is doing like a chugga chugga choo choo kind of dance like a little boogie.
Yeah, the car is doing the whip and the nay nay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No cars.
Doing that. The boat is doing the hula.
Because it's kind of like a wave. Yeah, another vehicle, a bike, the bike is pedaling. That's
all it can do. Yeah, pathetic. Can't really dance. Well, it's been the handlebars.
It's doing the handlebars too. That's a good point. It is actually doing that.
But the skateboard is just covered in shit and not moving anywhere.
That's right. Even Bibi doesn't want to be friends with a skateboard. It's filthy.
Yeah. True.
Seems messed up for you to say that.
Not me, it's Bibby, so you can't get mad at me.
It seems stupid too.
I'm doing a Congo line with all of them now.
While you're in the middle of this Congo line with all these different vehicles,
cool, you're holding on to the "hips" of a car or the shoulders area. Either way,
You're touching near the door of a car and with that,
we take a bit of damage.
You don't know what that damage is.
You just feel a certain amount of pain and confusion.
If you're so slipping more into this dream zone.
But then when you have that, you have that wisdom saving
there with that score, you start to realize that this isn't real.
And as you're slowly starting to realize it, the car door starts to open up
and slam on your hands just over and over and over.
Yippee!
And so we're going to go back to you.
You Red Foxwood, Roll Wisdom Saving Throw.
Eight.
Yeah.
You are still crushing it in your routine.
You are still nailing this.
You're doing so well.
You can see in the back it's spud apatow.
Is spud a kind of thing?
It's not.
It's shrub apatow.
What was I trying to shrub apatow?
Thank you.
That's pretty good.
I think either one of those are probably fine.
Right?
Yeah.
I'm with him.
It's just a bush and he's just a he's sort of like.
Birch!
Cherry!
This guy's good I'm telling you.
What do you think Seth?
And Seth is smoking the.
Douglas fir!
And Waylon roll wisdom saving throw.
Oh yeah.
What do we got?
This is annoying that there we go.
It's going to be a six.
Yeah, you're none the wiser.
You're just enjoying this, this case.
You have another case coming up.
see that the defendant in this case is your father who would not let you sit in the front
seat because you're too small.
And you have such a great case against him.
That's what you get for trying to protect me.
Son, I didn't want to let you sit up front.
You're such a smart young man.
I wanted you to be a terrific lawyer.
I don't want you to get hurt.
Well, you should have thought about that before you put my car seat in the back
Where so I can see all the comings and goings of our journey, where did I go wrong and
John Candy
Roll wisdom saving throw
Okay, that's not enough so you're arguing now the guy is one the nine or three is over not enough
So yeah, you're the guy is now
He's saying like he's like look man. I'm gonna call the cops on you in a second call the cops. I don't care
I'm gonna do it you read uncle's a cop and my dad and my cousin and my brother
And basically everyone in my family by me
Okay, great. So I guess we'll have a family reunion then fuck you. Yeah, we will I wasn't allowed at the last one
So now I'm gonna have one here
It's all the males in my family. So there's gonna be no arguing. He's calling
I from my dream go facts.
Okay, you all except for cam you all take three damage.
Oh my god dude what the fuck is there no end to this.
You just have to roll a 15 like me.
Also my my role or my d&d beyond damage thing is not working.
It won't let me add damage for some reason.
I guess you're stuck at full HP.
Uh oh.
That sucks.
Wow.
Would you just take 6 total, right?
5 total.
I think it was 2 the first time.
Oh, okay.
So I'm at 15.
Or no.
16, I got you.
What is my HP?
21.
So, Bibby, you now know this isn't a dream.
This is the candy dream zone.
All the vehicles are now gunning to attack you.
You can try to fight them for sure.
But you also now get the sense that all your friends are also in this dream zone.
Yeah.
You can try to find them as well.
I'm going to try and like, I don't know if they're your friends.
This is a first. This is something I would never attempt in real life, but I am going
to in in in real in the in Bibby's real life.
Okay, okay.
This is something Bibby would never attempt.
Everything else I've been doing.
Bibby would never do this. He's going to try to get into the car, into the driver's seat
of the car.
Holy shit.
Wow.
Huge, yeah. Big step.
Does not have a license, no.
Definitely not.
Oh, okay.
Um, yeah, do it.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
I'm, yeah, I'm, I'm trying to get behind the wheel.
Actually fuck it a train, not a car.
Hell yes.
Okay.
You go inside the train.
Uh, yeah, you can, you can power this train.
This is your dream.
Wait, what does, what does Bibi think the inside of it?
Yes.
*laughter*
Okay, yeah, you're steering the train.
I'm gonna try to ram it through the wall of the dream into the next person's dream.
Okay, uh, yeah, do it.
Roll a...
Hmm.
You know what, I guess you could just kinda do--
No, fuck that.
Roll animal handling.
*laughter* Okay.
Nine.
Nine? Okay.
You're not really able to control the train that well,
but you are able to, like, crash it through one of the walls a little bit.
Red Foxwood.
Redwood Fox.
Redwood is not my brand. I can't do it.
Roll wisdom saving throw again.
Six.
Okay. You see a crash
coming in from the outside of the comedy theater.
It's the woke mob. They're here to cancel you.
They have axes.
Yeah. And they're like,
"Get out of here Red Foxwood!"
"Redwood Fox!"
hero so I keep going. Yeah. One of the and one of them Jerry
one of them keeps just saying. Choo Choo. Mahogany. Okay.
Waylon. I'll roll wisdom saving throw.
17. Oh beautiful. Yeah. So you already with some more
lucidity because you hear a crash from somewhere outside the
courthouse and then you hear someone go. Mahogany and so
you're like, how is and then we probably Redwood Fox is doing
on television.
And you see your father is about to go on the guillotine. And you
realize this, this is not real. And you see the judge now and
suddenly you are now in the in the guillotine spot. And the
judge says I declare you Waylon our of our guilty for being a
naughty naughty boy and he's about to bang the gavel he's banging it down I'll
die as I live Frenchly yeah but yeah you now know this isn't a dream so or this
is a dream and this is not real so you can do with what you with that what you
want we'll return to you we're gonna go to mr. mr. candy mr. candy roll wisdom
saving throw. A three, god damn dude. Yeah, the cops are here. What's up dad? What's up
Uncle Kenny? Aw, god damn it John. What's up bro, what's up? Brother Steve? Yeah, we brought
Free
Thomas we oh my god. Yeah, what's your ale?
Name the nickname ginger ale. What's up?
He drinks so much ginger ale
Piece of head yeah, I'm fuller but then there was a legal dispute with the God
Are you trying to fight very funny John? Are you trying to fight the convenience store guy again?
Yeah, you got the whole force down here good. Oh my god. Look we got your brother here brother Steve
We're hoping he could forgive you. Okay. Oh, oh my god. Yeah, you see the convenience for guys
like see this is what I was talking about this guy so you shut up your dad's now
yelling at the computer shut up shut up shut up
All right, and you and Redwood Fox take another three damage.
Oh my god.
I take another three damage?
Yeah.
So I'm at 13 now.
I'm at 24.
I'm doing fine.
All right, Bibby, it's your time.
Okay, I mean I'm just going to keep trying to crash through.
Animal handling.
Okay.
13 yeah, you crash through
There is now you what you think is the woke mob redwood fox as it crashes through and they're holding their
signs and their
fucking pink hair
They sort of morph into a train suddenly and when you see the crowd
They're all staring daggers at you now and it's sort of like scanners and you realize you're not in a dream now
Uh, this is not your stand-up routine. You don't look you look like a tree again
You thought you were actually Red Fox for a second.
Folks get in.
Get in the train.
Wow, not.
Cheek.
OK, all right, it's probably more than seven.
Yeah, I feel like it's way more than seven.
I'm dreaming.
I jump on and I'm so large that I have to be kind of
I jump on a like a like a like a freight train platform.
Yes.
Stick into this the smokestack on the train.
Yeah, you plug it.
Yeah, and the smoke is all just like filling up the inside of
it now.
Yeah, I'm just breathing this the train runs perfectly with
though either way.
Yeah, the idea of George Carlin's heaven is there's more than
seven dirty words and he just keeps going.
So Waylon Au Revoir, the guillotine's about to come down on your head.
You now know that this is a dream.
Is there anything you want to do here?
Yeah, I say, "Aha!
This is... you have engaged in the fallacy of ad hominem!"
As it comes down and it chops my head off, and my head curls, and little arms and legs
grow out of my head, and I just have a little head running around.
as a finally of liberation myself from my body
the what the devil
yeah and you're running away
a baby you're trained now which is careening through crashes through the
courthouse
and you see the the little head version of our of water
I'm if you wanna snatch him up yeah I
I'm gonna I'm gonna try and grab him I hold out my crush for him to grab onto
Yeah, grab on.
Mm-hmm. Hell yeah.
And now we're back to you.
Alright, so
I want you to roll another wisdom saving throw.
Jod Candy.
Just to see what happens.
17. No!
Okay, cool. Not bad.
So you at this point, you and your cop family
are just roasting the convenience store guy on a spit.
Little head, little head ass.
You got a tiny head. Yeah, your head look like peanut your head like you look like peanut from Jeff Dunham big-ass ears little head
Little head green like you like a hand up your ass. Yeah
What my dad said and and you look like peanut -?
Yeah, wait, do I look like peanut? No, he no
He looks like peanut. I said he does all thinks you said that they look like peanut
And they're all sort of I didn't say you guys look like peanut again John Candy
You're starting to realize this is not a dream
I mean this is like the family region again, but worse cuz I'm in a dream what and they're all harmed
And now you baby you crash through this this field of cops, I'm just sprawling them out on the ground
And John Candy you're you watch your your cop family just sort of just get just get fucking run over by this train
But you know, it's not real or maybe you don't
See them by the train, I'm like, all right here come on guys
Okay, you hop on yeah you guys speed off through this dream zone
And eventually you reach where Waylon Waylon fuck my ass
where a wake off is and you see him and he's at Best Buy.
He's working at Best Buy and he's 17 years old and you see a sort of a older mom starts to talk to him from behind the counter and she's like, oh Douglas, what do you want to do this year?
year? What's the plan sort of?" He's like, "Yeah, well, I didn't do too hot in school, but I think
if I get enough money here, maybe save up. And then I think I'm going to probably try to go to
community college next year and then maybe do something with computers. I don't know. Maybe
go to a four-year school after that. I think it'd be cool. But yeah, no, just trying to get myself
sort of together. You know how it is." And she's like, "Well, I wish you best of luck on that. And
And it was nice to see you and it was great customer service, by the way.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
And you see a manager coming from behind the Best Buy counter.
He says, "You're doing great, Mr. Tolberone.
Really good job there."
He says, "Oh, thanks."
And you see, you hear from sort of like outside of all of this, you hear, "Douglas."
And then we fast forward almost in time.
And we see Wankoff and he's in the middle of an argument with his dad.
His dad who doesn't look like Wankoff.
And you see Wankoff is yelling at his father.
Why did you tell me we were Wankoffs?
He's like, I didn't.
My brother is a psycho.
It's why I changed our name to Tolvarone.
I didn't want to have anything to do with them.
OK, just just please, like, don't listen to him.
I know he's offering you the factory.
You're on a good path here, okay?
Slow and steady, work hard, do something in computers.
You'll be good for you.
He's like, "No, Dad, fuck this.
Fuck you.
I can't believe you hid this from me.
I'm going with Uncle Wankoff."
And you see him and he sort of shakes himself out of his stupor and you see the Best Buy
backdrop and the family backdrop sort of fade away.
And he just sees you guys as a train.
He's like, "Oh.
What's up?
you you set the fucking grenade off where'd that mom go and as as you say
that the dream world fades away and you guys wake up on the floor of the bombs
the train came into the real world yeah and you wake up back in the real in the
real world and you see Wankoff and he's like I forgot my name was Douglas I'm
Douglas okay oh god uh okay let's let's get to the control room let's try to
unclog the toilet one of you will be my heir when this is over okay uh come on
Yeah, I'm following him and I have a bomb stuck to the back of my shoe like toilet paper.
I'm stepping right...
Oh my god.
It's dragging behind me.
So, yeah, you guys are now walking towards the control room and out of the bomb's room
where you were suffering under that strange stupor.
And you get to sort of a, as you leave the bombs room,
there's just sort of like one more like a walkway
that you're kind of, you're kind of above.
And there's a little, like a walkway that's above
to a larger room where there looks like
sort of a large gathering of the robots.
And you see Wankoff and he sort of looks at that
of peculiar peculiarly peculiarly peculiar and I can't say that word at all. And he says,
"That's weird. I didn't know there was a meeting today. I guess I maybe I should attend." And
you see the robots start to talk. There's one robot who's like sort of like on like a like on a like
stage and sort of all these fold out chairs out with the other robots.
And the robot that's on the stage, Wankoff sort of gestures to him,
"That's the CEO bot. He's the head of the company, I guess.
I'm the president. He's the CEO. It's all just, you know, it doesn't mean anything."
And you see the robot. He goes, "First off, give yourselves a round of applause.
You have earned it."
You hear all the robots clapping like metal clanking against metal.
It doesn't sound very good.
I mean it, you guys have all been putting in 110% and it shows.
When I go back to my cubby to power down for the evening, I see a number of you still up, still computing.
Some of you have even hardwired yourselves to some of our operating systems, self-soldered to motherboards.
I saw one of you bleed in the crypto division after hours of mining.
I didn't even know we could bleed and they all kind of laugh as robots laugh.
But seriously, we've seen a huge increase in earnings, despite some of the, and I don't want to bullshit you guys, you know, my title is just a title. I'm always going to be real with y'all. So, despite some of the unfortunate state we've seen the place in under the nephews leadership, we've still managed to crush every quarter of the last five years. You see Wankoff kind of bristle at this.
We began the fiscal year projecting a market cap of 6.7 trillion. This was supposed to be our reach
and can I say that? Maybe I shouldn't say that. Anyway, instead we made our shareholders very,
very happy with a 10 trillion market capitalization, completely unheard of,
with a generous buy courtesy of the Brown Sticker Campaign. So thank you especially to Maria in
in
should be off the chain as well. We still have one thing left for us to do and all
the robots turn to the five of you. Kill the nephew and the robots start to...
Which one? The robots start to... I'm a nephew too! Yeah, my father has a brother.
There's like five nephews here I think. I don't know about that one with the crutches or
whatever the hell he's got.
I'm the furthest thing from a nephew you can possibly be!
I'm the furthest family member!
I think I might be the furthest thing from a nephew!
We're gonna do a d20 contest to see who is further from a nephew.
Bro I'm like a week old and if you fucking hit it, it's me.
Somebody made you, I have nobody.
I have no family members in the universe.
You exist.
I don't exist.
I got an 11.
are you rolling? I don't know why I'm rolling. I just rolled because I thought we were all
supposed to. With an 18 he's definitely closer to not to being further from a nephew so far.
Oh yeah it looks like the tree man is closer to being farther from a nephew
based on this scientific analysis. That's right. That's how we resolve conflicts.
Go ahead, Patches.
Did we get to rest or anything?
Because I'm at 6 HP.
No, you didn't.
Alright. Damn.
These robots are coming after you.
You see-
It's like an army, right?
Yeah, it's a lot of them. You see Wankoff goes,
"Okay, we gotta run to the control room!"
And he starts to waddle-dash
as fast as he can.
And you see, like, the robots
are-
to
do
of robots in it and then there's other floors up that have robots in them
including some on your walkway some of them you might be able to brush brush
past some of them you might have to fight yes initiative rolling is what we
want to do right now oh that was an ah damn I thought it was a roll to see if I
could dodge past all of them you know all the d20 you didn't even roll anything
you roll a skill you roll the d20 yeah but you didn't do anything it wasn't a
role
but uh... just the sound here is jealous
the one
you gotta one your initiative role
okay
how do i roll art can we just do you i don't know how to roll and indian d_b_i_
on and not you just click
to click initiative
yes the same
boom goes the dyno.
Oh, okay.
Does it still?
Okay.
Yeah.
I just don't roll 20 up.
Yeah, it seems like we just keep roll 20 up for whatever reason, but I think Branson,
you may not have to because of how we, uh, how this went down.
Wait, where's your, oh, that's why the download bar's in the way.
There we are.
Okay.
And Pat got that 20.
And Wankoff did not do that well, of course.
He's a fucking loser.
Whoa, come on.
Yeah, I made him.
He can do it.
I'm not going to role play that.
It's going to scare me.
I was like, "Oh, that'd be a fuck bit for a second."
I was like, "No, you'll get scared."
I'm not gonna roleplay that, it's gonna scare me.
Um...
[laughter]
I was like, "Oh, that'd be a fun bit for a second."
I was like, "No, you'll get scared."
[Music]