[Music]
Last time on Wally Wankoff and the Candy Bombs and Toilets Factory,
we met the five winners of the Wally Wankoff Brown Sticker Competition.
Wankoff is, of course, the world's most famous businessman,
and specifically, candy bomb and toilet mogul on the planet.
The Wankoff Corporation instituted a brown sticker competition wherein hidden
within five of Wankoff's yummy-yums, the company's most famous candy bar, resides a
brown sticker that gives one child, adult man, or puppet access to Wankoff's famous
factory as well as a chance to be heir to his business empire. Our winners were
Bibi the Orphan, an orphan from Illinois, Waylon Aurobois, a child lawyer arguably from hell,
John Candy, a boisterous and moronic uncle/layabout, and Pinocchio, a wooden boy from
Pensacola, Florida. Also Chucky Fuckett, a nice young man. Upon arriving at the factory, they were
greeted by the strange and grim visage of Wankoff, followed by a repeated greeting of a less grim,
less strange visage of a pudgy stout Gen X loser who it seems was also Wankoff.
The supposed mogul quickly crumbled under the remote scrutiny of anyone or thing at all and
confessed to the winners that he doesn't know how the factory runs, it never lets him
leave, and that his name was changed to Wankoff, and that he's desperate for one of his potential
heirs to help him fix the factory and everything about it.
After some vague acquiescence, the winners barreled ahead with Wankoff to his factory's
front door within the titanic iron dome that comprises his estate in Duluth, Brooklyn.
Chucky Fuckett died along the way.
Once they arrived at the factory, Wankoff's door had an embossed, not embalmed, figure
on it that fought the remaining winners in order to enter the factory.
Once they slayed the door, they walked through it.
What they saw would have to be seen to be believed.
Meaning the next hour or so will, by virtue of the medium, convince you of nothing.
And yet I continue to speak and you continue to listen.
Okay, just, and you guys like see in the atrium of this factory, it's like a, ornate, it's
vast, it's like kaleidoscopic, all these colors everywhere, there's robots buzzing about,
tinkering this and that a thing, there's conveyor belts that swerve around, like carrying one
bot to another place. Caring is also these frog men that seem to be everywhere to one place and
another place. There are dashboards and holograms and massive screens with all these like data,
detailed data about consumer behavior and KPIs, civilians killed, like civilians killed,
and then parentheses toilets. One dashboard just says the pit bull problem and has like a detailed
plan on how to feed pit bulls the most chocolate. There's screens are sifted through and organized
that seemingly random cadence, monitors are flipped around and shown to manager bots,
you show it to VP bots who've been abstracted data, do nothing with it.
And there's like a water cooler, a kitchen, a gym, their cliff bars,
yoga, racial sensitivity training seminars attended by older bot models in the back.
And above you, you see like a second, third and fourth floor where there's a similar,
just sort of like this chaotic, like sort of like massive corporate operation
with all these robots and frogs.
And some of them are wearing suits,
some of them are wearing lab coats, some are janitors,
some are interns.
It's crazy. And while this is all happening,
you also see arms popping out of the walls
of the factory, tweaking the bots
as well, changing things on the
dashboards, moving things along,
reprimanding one of the frogs.
You see the factory operating on its own
accord, making everything run.
And you see Wankoff, he's like, "Pretty cool, right?
This is my factory.
pretty chill huh yeah it pretty much runs itself at this point got this bad boy
running for a while unbelievable I'm seeing cliff bars I'm seeing arms
coming out of the wall yeah frogs or robots nothing is as it seems you know
what that's I couldn't set it better myself
yeah we get to eat the candy oh right well we're gonna get to do that the
first room we're gonna go to is my my chocolate swamp there's candy in there
there's a lot of chocolate in there yeah is that count as some people don't
count that as candy I think chocolate is different from candy I also think
chocolate swamp is a slang term I roll deception I'm lying unless you do think
it is. Does your character think it is? I'm lying. Yeah, you're lying. 26. Yeah, he's like,
Oh, should I change the name of the room? I went to the racial sensitivity thing. It was for robots
though. So I didn't really know how to understand what that was. But should I change the name of
the room then? It's a term for a human butthole on a hot August day. Oh, are you serious? Oh God.
That's me right now. Yeah. Figured you would like that.
I can't stop laughing.
That kind of makes sense because so one of the issues I've been having with the factory is that
well it seemed like I have not been in the chocolate swamp room in a while.
Last time I was in there all the frogs in there were getting really mad at me.
I didn't really I didn't know what was going on.
It's hard to smell different too.
So I think some of the toilet stuff is getting in the chocolate stuff.
Yeah, it's a kind of a mess.
I got these three businesses.
Let's go there.
We'll check it out.
You guys can help me deal with that or just if it's fine, it's fine.
If it's not fine, I can use your help.
And again, if you do well, you could be my heir.
So that's pretty cool.
You get a lot of money.
You got all these robots here and these frog guys.
Does that sound good?
I've been laughing the whole time and I just started to throw up from it.
If I was to become your heir, would I inherit a candy bar?
Uh yeah you get like uh well I'm pretty much as many as I have been eating all the candy
in here so yeah you could get like a lot.
I have five faints on the spot thinking of that many candy bars.
You see a robot go up to you as they're fanning you.
Yeah it's slapping me in the face.
Yeah you are taking damage.
Don't give me any damage.
Are you sure?
I'm at 10 HP.
Okay I'll leave you alone.
And yeah, and he says like, I mean, unless you guys if you guys want to go, we can go
or you can you can chill in the atrium.
It's is there any candy or within arm's reach?
Yeah, there's tons of candy around.
There's like it's like there's Cliff bars because it's a big, silly corporation.
But there's also tons of Wankoff yummy yums around Wankoff Twizzlies.
I grab I'm going to grab a yummy yum and say,
oh, man, I love candy and then put it in my mouth and try to eat it.
But it just falls out like Cookie Monster.
Yeah, right.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And you see a one of the robots or come in, start sweeping it,
sweeping up the little crumbs of candy that comes out and put into a waste
waste, a waste bin, and it's like tummy, which like you see lights on fire
as it gets disposed of.
the
to
Yeah, you guys can get on the conveyor belt,
ride your way to the chocolate room,
chocolate swamp room.
You see a-
- Careful everyone, last time one of us
got onto the conveyor belt, we died.
(laughing)
Head exploded and we did not mourn him.
- I don't remember that at all.
- What?
- He must have not mattered much.
- Yeah, no.
- Even now he fades from my memory.
- You hear the faint buzzing of flies.
(laughing)
You guys got the conveyor belt.
This one does not whip you fast enough that it just kills a normal person.
You guys take it easily get there.
As you get to the chocolate door, you see on the robots opens the door for you.
There's no scary door man there is Wankoff's face on the door again.
And you're in the chocolate swamp and is this sea of just doo doo chocolate looking shit.
The smells are conflicting.
It is hard to tell.
It's also dotted with tons of vegetation.
He's like big trees with like fruit on them.
You also see far far in the back of this massive room.
That is, you know, impossibly large like everything else here
a sort of Tower of Babel that looks to be made of chocolate
and metal and all these other things but mostly chocolate
metal and probably a little bit of poop.
Um, and Wankoff looks at any of the okay. I don't remember the tower
so
That's a little weird
Okay, that's fine so yeah, uh
Okay, that would explain why so things have not been
all the bars that have been out have been
Kind of old bars that we have in storage and I've been trying to figure out what so I hasn't been producing any
Usually the factory does it itself?
I don't know that tower might actually be why it might be stopping the churn that I need
Maybe we
You guys want to go over there? I can get to get the boat
I got a boat we can take over there. It's pretty cool. It's a speed boat
whoa
Okay, yeah sure
And he claps twice and you see a
a little frog man sort of come around with the boat and
wait I'm on land and the boat still hits me somehow.
Yeah.
Yeah, you guys can see it's a speed boat.
It's got like flame decals on it.
It looks just like the sweetest boat ever in the flame decals somehow
somehow burn Cameron's character.
Yeah, you see, as you get close to them, they like start to like wiggle a little bit like fire.
Like, yeah.
Well, the propellers spinning mighty fast.
Yeah, I'm going to have you try to sit up in the front, if that's OK with the frog here.
And yeah, you sit with the frog and he the frog turns you guys as I.
Oh, I don't like this thing.
Oh, sorry. This is one of the they're called Sullivan's.
I don't know what they are.
My uncle got them a long time ago.
Why is he's gross?
Your uncle got them.
Yeah. Elaborate.
Oh, well, it feels like maybe these are slaves.
OK, well, let me actually you know what?
Hold on, because they're going to you said the magic word.
And you see
one year so steps ahead every one year so frogs sort of come out and they're doing a little like
a little like a uh dance like going up down one's going up one's going down one's going up one's
going down and they start to sing uh um sullivan sullivan sullivan frog we are slaves we don't
like it here sullivan sullivan sullivan frog please free us we are frog slaves what do you get when
you are a slave nothing good. Wank off came to where we lived promised us subscriptions
to Harper's Bazaar now we are slaves. Doop a hee doo a oop a solo vid solo vid the frog.
Solo vid frog. And they uh just sort of uh shuffle off like yeah see they tell you that
I've tried to get them to leave here. Well the whole thing seems like a misunderstanding.
But I didn't like him before but now I like that song. Yeah. Well, do you have an mp3 of that song?
Yeah, can I get that song on cd? Well, i've been told that I i'll that that it could be a big hit
But I i've been afraid to release it. I mean, I know that the one of the frogs is very into mastering
I mean, he's into this wall of sound thing like I oh, yeah, he's been basically trying to master it for solvin specter
Yeah, he's uh
He's a pain in the ass
Watch out for what he does to his wife.
Oh yeah, I'm sure it'll be fine.
Better make sure he doesn't have a wife.
Yeah, I mean, I don't know if the frogs marry.
And as like, almost on cue, as you like are getting closer to this tower,
you start to see that there are all these frogs who are poking their heads out of the tower.
And they're looking down and they're like looking to see you guys as you're approaching the speedboat.
And one of them is sort of swimming in the chocolate sludge river.
And he goes, halt, do not come any further.
And this people just goes over him
and another one comes out and he has like a little raft of his own.
He's like, OK, all right.
All right. Please stop. Please stop.
The other frog sort of slows it down
and he says, hey, what are you doing here?
and the wall is like a
hi I run the factory my name is
Wally Wankoff these are four children or three children and a very loud guy
we're here to that
yeah awesome we're here to just sort of figure out you know I've not been making
any chocolate so we're kind of running out of the back supply of the chocolate
bars
The Chocolate Bars
and
I'm
like a bridges and things going up in these frogs here living here and he says
we've been here trying to protect ourselves from the sludge monster and
you see that every all the frogs in the tower like sludge monster sludge monster
false it's not no no it's not here it's not here he says there's a massive beast
in the swamp it's big sort of sludge guy and he he keeps trying to he keeps eating
this
Why'd you guys is there any weapons or we just thought that we told maybe we'd be oh god. We didn't really think this through
Can you guys help us fight the sludge monster like y'all were looking for a reason to build a tower
I
Thought we were just gonna I was kind of excited by it personally
but uh, and we really put our minds to it and that was exciting but uh
Yeah, it's stopping the sludge monster. I don't think it's gonna help at all the more
In fact if I spent almost more than seven and a half seconds on it. I'm like, oh no
What's the plan to just go up kind of hide up in the tower?
Remark, maybe we would throw rocks at it. But you're
That's a good one. You thought I'd all put yourself in one central location and piss it off
Get on more a lot of us were getting drowned so you know if you go to the top of the tower
Yeah, but you're down here. Yeah
Okay
Look, we don't know why it's attacking us
But probably if the chocolates are being made it has to do with that because we always trying to make the chocolate
That's all we do we work all the time on the robots
We spin the chocolate around in the chocolate swamp work in the fudge part of the factory
We make it into fudge.
We like our job.
You know, those frogs that sing, they're crazy.
OK, all right.
Two worlds here.
No, we're not crazy about it.
Can you guys please help us with the monster?
And while he sort of looks to you guys.
So this is this is what I meant when I said I had.
I say, I say, I say, "Oh, do it!"
And I take a valiant step forward and I stomp my crutch down and I fall through like ten
floors of tower.
Okay, so they're all kind of like Looney Tunes if that's gonna be a problem.
It's a chocolate tower, right?
Chocolate and nondescript sludge.
I punch like a hole through the wall and then like grab a bunch of chocolate and start eating
the wall. Roll a constitution saving throw. You grabbed an area that was entirely sludge.
Yeah. 15. Yeah, you've eaten sludge before. Is that a fucking problem for you? It ain't
my first time. Yeah. You aimed for the sludge. A little discoloration. A green part of the
wall. This is my favorite chocolate. I love the green chocolate. It was a Halo collab that
while
to
I don't know. We'll see.
Alright. Well, you know what? I'm pretty much positive.
It seems like I'm in charge of this Pinocchio situation.
So, yeah. It does.
And now my nose is only 53 inches long.
That's not very good.
Yeah, and as your nose shrinks, which makes a sound that's like...
You hear a...
A respondent sound of a rumbling.
and like the sound of waves shaking and you see the frogs and they're like
"THERE'S A SLUDGE MONSTER EVERYWHERE IN BATTLE STATION!"
They're like running around bumping into each other.
I'm gonna grab one of them as they run by.
"WAIT NO!"
"No yeah, you stay here, you talk to me. Now look I'm only a seven year old prosecutor, but...
So I don't know how everything works but seems like we should just talk to this sludge monster, reason with him.
He seems like a good guy to me."
the
I'm 21. He's like, okay.
And he goes up because hey.
So then you know, he'll stop.
Why should we try to talk to it?
All right.
Okay, okay, you can talk to it.
And as the rumbling grows louder and it stops in front of it,
and you see this big chocolate swamp monster,
it looks like the Candyland chocolate swamp monster.
And he sort of rolls up and he's like,
"Bleah, I wanna eat more frogs."
What?
And he looks down and sees just like this posse here.
And he sees you.
- I looked down, look, all right.
Let he who doesn't wanna eat a few frogs
cast the first stone.
I've been where you're at.
I've eaten a frog or two in my day.
These frogs, they don't seem, they built a tower.
They don't seem to wanna get eaten.
(laughing)
There's nothing else you could eat?
What they want is about what I want.
I want to eat the frogs.
Yeah, if this doesn't work out, you can eat this one right here.
His name's Sullivan.
The one you kept by?
Yeah.
I want to eat him.
And his hand starts to go out to eat him.
Start pushing the frog.
Wait, but what other kind of crap do you like to eat?
It's gotta be a few, I mean, nobody likes just one food, right?
Hmm...
I never really thought about it, I just always only ate the frog since I've been alive.
Well, while you got this one, chow down, but just think about what other food you like to eat.
*Muffled*
Hmm...
I like...
I like fruit.
Like, uh...
You guys ever have a good, um, like a good, um,
what's those things called? The, uh, honeydew.
Oh yeah. Great one with the worms in it.
I'll eat worms, but, uh, I'm not thinking of that. Uh, honeydew.
Honeydew. Really? Honeydew. That's your favorite fruit.
The first fruit.
Honeydew.
You got kiwis and strawberries and...
Oh, those are all too tart for me.
You like honeydew?
Yeah, it's kinda mellow, kinda mild.
For a sludge monster!
Can't handle anything too tart?
It's just a matter of...
what you want, you know?
I don't believe that you have a tongue!
Show me your tongue!
He opens his mouth, and he doesn't have a tongue.
Okay! Alright, so this isn't even about the frog's taste.
There's some other kind of feet. It's got to be a textural thing. I roll inside
for I don't have a brain
Entirely would
So I'm not very insightful, but if anyone else maybe though, maybe there's a lawyer in our
Pull something out of this sludge monster
Hmm, and I put my my finger to my chin and I yeah the DM and ask if I can roll an insight
Yeah, I think that's fine. I think we have one more
After that, I'll get kind of okay 13 is pretty good
Um, so yeah with 13 you can tell that like he's definitely not eating the frogs for taste
You don't know if he's like eating them out of habit or something, but he's a sex freak
He's not you don't know if he's a sex freak either
But yeah, you can you're not sure
All right. Now look look see me. Obviously you don't have a tongue
There's no you're not eating the frogs for taste right? No, I'm not eating the frogs because you want to kill the frogs. Oh
yeah, I mean I
Yeah, I do hear all the frogs
Hey, who doesn't want to kill these frogs as soon as they meet him, yeah
I'll meet you halfway on that one. So I hate him. I'll help you kill him. I just like whip
Okay
All right, fine
But I don't see what that has to do with with me stopping eating them then if you let me eat them
Oh, there's only so many frogs and if I unless I misheard something earlier, they're also robots. So this is only so
Yeah, there's frogs and robots. Okay. Oh, they're not the same. No, no, no, no, there's frogs and robots
Yeah, I'm seven. So I got
And you know what the DM did kind of a confusing job outlining the space
Well, I'm seven and I've been separated from my mommy and daddy so
I've lost I hate it. So if you look, you know, there's only eventually you're gonna rat out frogs
You need to develop other eating habits
okay, all right, let me think and
he
he sort of like looks around and he sort of slits a
look at some of the trees here that have these like different like candy fruits on them and
And Wall-E's like, "Hold on, hold on, hold on, before you eat that.
Some of these are bombs, again, defense contractor, fun.
Some of these are candy.
So just, you know, don't just grab like a handful.
Let's try to like...
I don't remember which.
A lightbulb appears over my head.
Sorry, Cameron, what's your character's name?
Bibby.
Bibby!
Which of the fruits would you choose?
Well, probably this black fruit with the fuse and the skull on it.
Well I was gonna eat that.
Alright there's a big X on that one, don't eat that fruit.
Which of the fruits looked disgusting?
Someone couldn't pay you to eat those fruits.
This disgusting, red, beautiful, shiny fruit with a green leaf that you give to teachers
looks revolting to me.
What?
I wouldn't touch this with a 10 foot crutch.
I'm going to grab that and hang it against my chest and throw it to him.
Okay, the shiny one?
Yeah.
Okay, cool.
He throws it and he's like, "Whoa."
This is so much better than honeydew, which is frankly mid-tier in fruit world.
Mid-tier at best, honestly.
Yeah.
What, what, can I have more?
More?
And you see Wally's like, yeah, yeah, yeah, there's tons, there's tons.
Grab it, grab those fruits, grab those fruits.
And you see the frogs all like, like, you know, spiral out of the tower, grab the fruits,
are throwing it to the guy.
And he's like, oh, wow, this is great.
And you see as he's eating the fruits
and he's like getting happier and happier,
you see actually everyone roll perception.
I want to see what you guys notice here.
It's a few things can happen.
Oh, 19.
Oh, OK, 19.
Yes.
A Pinocchio and John Candy, which is not really a great sentence
to say start with.
Yeah, Pinocchio and John Candy.
Yes, yeah, I know you guys notice that as he's eating it he's.
He seems to be getting more mellow but you also see that there is some sort of tube as pumping into him that begins to like pump kind of cartoonishly more sludge into him and as more sludge is getting in you can see that there's kind of this like shift in his temperament.
He eats the candy he gets kind of happy the sludge gets pumped in he gets kind of angry again
He eats the candy he gets kind of happy
So you see that starting to go on oh
That guy should be eating that guy should be giving me candy, right
Hey
Monster hey, what a sludge monster? What's up with that?
that tuba sludge
Yeah, is that the tube that makes you want to give me candy? Please say yes, please say yes, please
At the tube and he's like, oh I never I never noticed this and the tube then whips out of him
Waps around the sludge monster
Squeezes it tight until he explodes everywhere. I
Just I I turn around before the next thing happens. Just kind of like hitting my hands like
(laughter)
Well boys, job well done!
I think we're done here.
We saved the frogs.
And this giant metal tube now that was extending all the way out from somewhere else in the
factory hisses at you.
And roll for initiative.
Oh god.
Woah.
15.
21.
Oh my god.
You guys are basically loco.
I'm essentially loco.
Alright.
Alright, what do we got?
We got 15.
Wow, this is much better initiative rolls than last time.
23.
You guys sucked last time.
Yeah, we know we don't have to make us feel so
fucking bad about it all the time.
I do that a lot.
Oh, wow.
Alright, and the snake.
Cool.
Okay.
I mean, you're up first, baby.
Yep.
So there's this like coiling snake monster that's spewing
sludge out of its hole.
Yeah, and I'm walking right up to it.
center. Of course you are. What are you doing? Wait, I say, wait,
hold on a second and I paint a big red target on the front of
it. Yeah, I'm marching up and I'm I'm I'm swinging my crutch
like a baseball bat. Go for it. That's a nine. Yeah, I ain't
gonna do **** Yeah, I'm going to spend a key point. What? To
use flurry of blows. Can't make out. Two unarmed strikes which
are two kicks from my legs. That's right. There's a fourteen.
Okay. Oh, yeah. Sorry that hits five damage. Nice. Awesome. A
crit. Oh **** which is the crit is the is the foot where I have
wooden toes. Of course. Yeah, which is nine damage. Nice.
OK, yeah, so you just like swipe and miss with the crutch and then you do some like howl
rang from a way.
Say his name from Tekken.
The tech window guy.
I don't know what to say his name.
He does.
I don't know.
I'll look it up tomorrow.
Yeah, you just kick the shit out of him.
I just naked.
It's like, yeah, I'm standing on my crutches and like doing a bicycle.
Yeah, you're doing more chunley type shit or the what's his name?
Liu Kang does that?
Yes, there we go.
I found the fighting game guy.
Uh, okay. We're at 21 initiative. We have, uh, Caleb, uh, Mr. Pinocchio, sir. You're
up. I'm going to use, um, so, so you said it's a metal tube. Yes, it is metal. So, so
how, how large is the, the opening of the metal tube? Uh, it's about like, I'd say like,
five feet diameter. Does it have ears and eyes? No, do you?
Uh, should I add? No, no, it doesn't. It doesn't. I have to be stronger as a DM. No.
Does it have a perfect weak, weak spot where maybe a wooden nose could
lodge in perfectly and kill it in one single hit? Look, man, well, I don't know if I'll allow that,
but tell me what you want to do and let's play in the space. Okay, and one more question. Is there
Something between a lie and the truth that Pinocchio could tell that would make his nose just grow in width
Yeah, I mean I don't what I don't know what
Yeah, this will get this gets to Pinocchio's on politic politica. Maybe a joke or what a fact right? Hmm. Yeah joke. Yeah
Tell a joke. Okay. Okay. I'll Hicks me man
and
If you do any stand up routine, that is in between a lie and a truth.
You can grow it with.
Okay, go for it.
Plus these, uh, uh, plus you ever notice there's a difference between marionettes and puppets?
Right?
Because marionettes, we be walking like this.
Okay, you gotta roll.
Puppets don't even, no, they don't even have legs.
You know what I'm saying?
Rescue me and everyone else and roll.
What should I roll?
Roll a d20.
many inches it grows. 12 inches. It's a foot wide now. Your nose. It is non-sensical. It's
so big. This is a pillar I have on my nose. Yeah. Oh god. Okay. So you have a pillar on
your face. What are you going to do? I feel like eventually too you can figure out different
types of things to make it curve too. Definitely. Yeah, we've got a few more episodes. I'm gonna,
I just have a free action left? No, you have a regular action. That was your free action.
Oh, okay. Perfect. Do that. Alright, I'm gonna use Eldritch Blast. Okay, cool. Yeah, go for
it. 21. Yeah, roll for damage. Nice. 11. Wow, awesome. So you do 11 damage. Where does that
shoot out of? Does it shoot out of the pillar on your face? Uh, yeah, yeah. No, it's like
a um... It doesn't have to. Yeah, it does. It's kinda got like an Eye of Sauron type
like in yeah yeah building at the top of it
um yeah i'm not even recognizable as Pinocchio anymore
it's a terrible i'm mostly the nose yeah i'm becoming this kind of evil
horrific your eyes and mouth like
it looks like you took like a stretch tool on photoshop
and just everything is kind of orbiting like the uh
like the event horizon of a black hole around around this nose and i'm becoming i don't know
what's happening shooting a giant pink beam out directly this is what happens when you do comedy
i'm becoming something different something different
Okay, yeah, you do some sizable damage to this snake thing.
You're also, your nose is like, yeah, you have a few more jokes you can tell and you
can be big enough to plug it up.
So we're at, it's 15, we have a couple 15s here.
I think Aurovar, yeah, Aurovar, your dex is higher, so you're up.
Sure, alright, I'm gonna cast, I'm gonna see that and I'm gonna look at it and go, "Oh!"
And I'm gonna cast Dissonant Whispers.
Oh, yes.
At second level.
So I think you've got to beat a wisdom saving throw of 14.
Yeah, let's see how I do.
Alright.
Wow, this thing is not very wise.
Let's find out how wise.
Nope, did not win.
Alright.
Lost.
So I'm going to do 46 damage to you.
Yeah, it's not gonna be pretty
What did you do yeah
19 19 damage good god, man. Okay. Yeah, what do you?
Just be just picturing
He's just he's picturing he man and he's just getting very upset
The snake takes 19 damage. Oh, man, that is he's not looking good
Yeah
And okay cool. It is now your turn John candy
So what kind of metal tube is this?
It's like one of those like, you know, like when you see like a like an AC tube
It's like the metal tube that like sometimes people use is like a robot arm and a cosplay. It's one of those. Okay
How far away am I? I mean, I'd say you're about like 30 ish feet away
Okay, I'm gonna try and run over to it and take my belt and and tie it up
Okay, so we'll do is that's a grapple check for sure. Okay, so roll a strength check. Yeah
Okay, and he will just he will try to combat that he is pretty strong
He better not be he's strong on
Yeah, he got yeah, he is you were trying to tie the belt around it and it just like thrashes about
I mean also, especially if like unless your waist is five feet around
It is
He's able to thrash about and get it get out of the way. Yeah, okay that pisses me off so much because it didn't work. Mm-hmm
So then go to a rage as a bonus action, yeah, I'm gonna go into a rage
Hell, yeah, dude. What do I roll for that? You don't roll shit. You're just gonna rage
That would have been good to do before because you'd have advantage on strength checks that's kind of funny
Yeah, now you're mad
Now I've been I've been
that
the
didn't thank you and it got it yeah we got a 20 so you're all going to take
eight damage from this thing and you're all yeah all of you yeah I'm a -
you're a - I'm at four I'm a zero you're a zero yeah yeah you're a seven year old
kid come on and you are also all you know now you all move at half speed but it
doesn't really matter for you are as I'm knocked out I'm gonna shout like I
believe in Santa Claus and I recently stopped liking Barney yeah and it is now
your turn baby okay I'm like also every time every time I get hit like a
band-aid just appears on me that's just that's just a thing so I'm covered I'm
covered in band-aids you can just see my eyes you can see my eyes at this point
I'm like a band-aid mummy okay that would have been no that would have been I
should have known that earlier cuz there's a lot of stuff that could have
happened hold on let me just write down it's fine
What? And I'm gonna attack with my crutch again. That's a 15.
Oh yeah, that hits.
Okay, that's 7 damage.
Oh yeah, he's not looking too good.
As a bonus action, I will headbutt it in whatever is close to its face.
Whatever face-like thing it has. That's a 9.
That's not gonna hit.
Yeah, I just dunk my head in sludge.
Hell yeah. Pinocchio, you're up.
Okay, um, I am again gonna try to get my nose to grow.
Okay. In width.
Um, but, uh, uh, is it, do we decide that it's just Bill Hicks style standup?
No, it's any standup bit.
Any standup bit?
Yeah, comedy is a secret between lies and truth.
Okay.
Damn, you should put that in your book.
That's some real shit.
Wow, dude.
That's some knowledge.
Okay, well first, I think I'm panicking because my nose has gotten so big and I'm becoming
a kind of monster.
I can kind of see the forest through the trees a little bit.
I realize that this thing's going to die before my nose gets big enough.
And if it gets five feet wide, I may die and lose myself completely.
I'm actually gonna go I'm gonna start at first by being yeah I start like y'all
y'all ever notice and then I read it's so much pain just already from the that I
just decided to shoot lightning at him yeah and it's a 24 yeah it's yeah y'all
yeah you'll ever notice and then I do kind of a Jim Gaffigan like lightning
a little bit more about two feet wide now describe your kill okay well I am
I don't see it actually because my nose is so heavy that I'm just looking directly down.
But I hear it kind of sputter and squirm and eventually kind of shrink up as it coils back
like a slinky.
Yes, it does and it whips back all the way somewhere else far off in the factory.
And you see the frogs and they're like, "We're saved!"
they're all like so happy.
They're doing little dances.
There's they're going to sing another song
and then before they do, while he's like, OK, get get back to work, please.
Like we have so much more chocolate to make.
And they start going back to churning the chocolate, putting it in the bars.
And while he's like, OK, thank you, this is exactly what is someone
going to help the lawyer?
The lawyer has passed out, he's seven.
What's the lawyer?
is somebody okay?
Oh my god!
It's not my job to do that, Chris!
He's a- I thought he owned the candy factory!
[laughter]
Based on how he dressed!
Yeah, I'm taking band-aids off myself and putting them on him.
Okay, yeah, just roll medicine check.
Okay.
Just to stabilize him.
19.
Yeah, he's stabilized, and then, um, uh, yeah, I mean, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
Wally's gonna just sort of like start putting like,
take finding the bits of this chocolate sludge that are is chocolate and sort of dribbling it into your mouth uh
au revoir it's like okay come on i don't need a lawsuit come on come on kid and uh yeah you're
gonna get like three kids already die what no nothing never mind okay you have a wheelbarrow
for my nose yeah yeah but that kid can't
sue you that's why you're my lawyer I shake
your hand so you guys beat this big sludge
monster slash the tube coming out of it
Uh, Pat, you did rage.
I realize now.
Uh, so I want you to roll on your wild surge table.
Um, so you'll see in the actions area on D and D beyond, uh, if you
scroll all the way down, uh, basically there's just something that
will happen if you roll that D eight.
Okay.
So you got a two that two from the D eight.
Let's see what that does.
you teleport up to 30 feet to an unoccupied space you can see
uh... until your rage ends you can use this effect again on each of your turns
as a bonus action
so
you're just i guess you just teleport you just win the fight and then just teleport
somewhere
(laughter)
yeah anywhere you can see
uh...
alright can you describe the area for me
sure you're on sort of like a mound of shit in a chocolate swamp
so
and
Thank you.
That's good.
Alright.
Yay.
And...
Yeah.
Wankoff is sort of like a little bit befuddled now, now that things are sort of settled down.
He's, uh, he's kind of like, "Okay, uh..."
So...
That wasn't good.
That was, uh, that tube that we just, you guys destroyed, which was good.
That was good.
Glad you did that.
I was making a shit monster.
the
it's it's uh okay you could i i didn't know you could teleport but i just knew you were 47 but
you could certainly that's what i do as a 47 year old i do a lot of teleporting it just happens how
do you think i got here you can't so you can't you could certainly try to teleport to the toilet room
but it's okay it's well over should i okay it's so much further away than 30 feet should i roll
to see if I get stuck in the tube.
[Laughter]
>> Uh, I mean, you, you, there's not even a tube to get stuck in.
>> Oh, right, right, 'cause we destroyed it.
>> Yeah.
I mean, the toilet room is like, also like, like a mile and a half away.
>> Okay.
>> Like, this place is huge.
Do you wanna teleport into the swamp in the direction of the toilet room?
It just sort of wade in the swamp?
>> How, do I have to teleport like, immediately?
Or is it gonna go away if I don't teleport?
uh you're raging right now and rage lasts um for a minute so i would say you have like 20 more
seconds you can rage again though um i think shit i think i'll just i'll just like stop i don't know
uh what if i just roll like uh what if i roll like a d6 and then you just choose where i go
depending on how high the number is yeah i like that okay one of the six directions yeah
six cardinal directions north south east west and then there's a there's the home and work
yeah that's yes sir yeah roll that d6 to do a forward slash four okay the north south east west
i guess you go west 30 feet okay that's what we're doing otherwise you would have to go towards home
or towards work um yeah you're just like on top of one of the frogs they're just like they're just
like you're just sort of sitting on them but shut up this is my thing so anyway
Waylon is like not Waylon sorry Wankoff yeah is like so uh okay I guess I guess
we should go to the toilet room to figure out what's going on there I'll
get the speed boat and you see one of the frogs goes up to Wankoff as he's
saying this is like uh...
and this
mister waco
yeah
uh... well
heard about the toilet room you should know is uh... because of the sludge
monster and
didn't get away with tower and uh...
you know we we haven't been to the
toilet room in a long time and i'm i'm pretty sure it's called
when he because
where the toilet room can get clocked it's that's the whole
it's sort of uh...
It's just sort of a massive pipe network.
And we haven't been cleaning it.
So--
So I can't go there?
No, you can.
It's just clogged.
I'm just letting you know.
Don't you-- I didn't--
I'm not really in charge here.
There's like other frogs who are more in charge.
Well, Waylon's going to step forward.
So it will seem to me that nobody in this whole factory
has been in the toilet room in a powerful long time.
You're going to be very uncomfortable.
Many of you, I would think, need surgery at this point.
Let's go to a toilet room and fix your business.
I'm gonna stay here, but uh...
No, no. One of you is coming with me.
Do you need like a large piece of wood to unclog the toilet room?
And then, uh, Wake Off for the first time in a while really looks at you, Pinocchio.
And he's like, "Oh god, what the fuck?"
And like really takes in the fact that your eyes and your mouth are sort of...
Yeah.
like as you just as you described or a event event horizon black hole around
you the nose that is actually I talk like this now because my mouth is just so thin
it might as well be closed and what did you just say by the way make sure I heard that right
right right then I talk like this now no no no before that oh or that do you need a hard piece
to
you're gonna have to roll, um, yeah, you're gonna have to roll to see if you can get on
the speed boat without it running into you. Yeah. All right. What do I roll? Don't question
this. Okay. Yeah, sure. Don't run into them. Roll d20 and add your acrobatics. Okay. So
just roll acrobatics is the answer. That's an eight. You start to climb towards the speed
boat and it somehow turns towards you and hits you and you take.
Oh, geez, you're dead. Yeah, you're dead.
OK, yeah, wake up, runs over. He's like, OK, I'm going to carry you onto any vehicles
we're going for. He starts dripping chocolate into your your your your little mouth.
When if he when he does he pick me when he picks me up
Is he yeah, he picks me up and though the boat hits him. Yeah
Yeah
He gets knocked back. He's like, okay, how do we get this kid on these vehicles seem to hate him? Is there?
What can we do?
To get him onto the boat. Uh
Wait
Throw him
That's actually not a bad idea. Are you any points to you John candy? You're pretty strong, right?
What can you throw this crippled boy onto the boat?
What
This sucks. You guys are making me do so much crap
Here is um, I thought we were getting cake. I thought we were getting candy
Although there's candy on the trees, I can get you one after.
If you just throw it on the boat.
Alright.
Fuck!
Okay, roll an athletics check.
Eleven.
Yeah, that's enough.
It's enough.
It's barely enough.
You sort of get him where his head hits the side.
I pick him up by one leg and toss him over my shoulder like that.
Like that. Yeah, my leg is like a it's like elastic. Like there's no.
Okay, yeah. So the rest of you are able to pretty easily get on the boat, even use Pinocchio's
face as a plank if you want to. It's it's it's pretty easy to get on there.
And yeah, Wankoff is going to take the boat. So you guys are going down through the swamp.
You start to see the frogs are back to work now on everything. They're churning the chocolate.
They're trying to get as much of the shit and sifting it through to make sure there's no more
shit in the chocolate so they can start producing new chocolate again. And sort of round what looks
like a cove almost inside of this chocolate swamp. And you start to hear the sound of a rushing
waterfall as you're getting a bit closer and uh uh wankoff wankoff uh uh starts to talk to you guys
um you know he says yeah i i i didn't i didn't want to not run the factory it was just uh again
the halo 2 thing and things got kind of complicated uh i i i just uh you know it's like one of those
things where uh well it's like yeah i started working on stuff and then things went wrong and
It was just easy with the weapons, you know, the bombs, government comes in, they get the bombs.
So what do you guys do? Are you guys also entrepreneurs?
I haven't talked to anybody in like 20 years.
Yeah. Oh, you're so boring to me, dude. Oh my god.
Yeah. All right.
Is that am I just going to be unconscious?
Oh, you're no, you he dripped a little bit of chocolate in you.
You got like, oh, that makes you feel alive.
You got three.
I mean, what does that mean?
So what happened when he takes a bit of chocolate from the swap?
He dipped it in.
You got like two and a chocolate with shit water in it.
You get knocked unconscious.
Somebody gives you a little bit of chocolate.
Yeah, we've established that it works for that sort of.
That's why you're supposed to keep a little bit of chocolate with you.
Every. Yeah.
Yeah.
So you guys like you're all kids, I guess.
So, you know, you probably don't do anything. What?
I don't know. Eight days old.
OK, I know. Damn kid.
Yeah. Wait, I was going to ask you, because this was really meant to be like
a kid thing.
What? How did you end up here?
I took it.
You took it from a child.
What?
Did you take the brown stuff?
It's fine, man.
No, I took it from the candy.
You took the candy was holding the sticker.
So the candy had the sticker.
OK, yeah.
In your mind, the candy has possession of things.
OK, just making sure that's clear.
Yeah, and I took it.
Yeah. Roll deception.
15, pretty good.
I would say all of you can roll inside as well, though, on him.
OK.
14 10.
He's practiced this lie a lot.
He's looking in the mirror and saying I took it.
I took it from the candy.
I took it from candy.
I got a 3.
What's up?
I don't know if my roll showed up but I got a 3.
Oh yeah it did not show up.
which i don't know d_n_d_ beyond game logs
uh... overtrade up
uh...
okay yeah
so yes i'm out here your powers of observation here fail you will and i
will block
uh... everyone else is actually to including waco who's like uh...
uh... okay
uh... right that's
interesting idea of percent of possession but that's
Reads to me story checks out adults are capable of buying candy
Yeah, I bought it - yeah, you sure stuck on a candy thing. We're all deception again
Well, I bought it - Waylon knows all the laws did he knows it's legal for him
Okay, we'll keep those insights so I would say I mean Bibby you're the only person who's really yeah, I'm not
I'm not paying attention anymore an act on that. I'm reaching for the outboard motor because I think it's a pinwheel
You see you see yeah, you see wake up go no no no no no no no and like start to put your hand in the way
Hey, yeah
Let's take it easy there. Okay. All right, and you hear the water is rushing a bit louder
Uh, okay.
So this part's the waterfall.
Um, it's going to lead us into the toilet room or, well, I
guess what was the toilet room.
So, uh, just everyone hold on to a different part of the boat.
It'll be fine.
It's uh, it's mostly for show.
I'm holding shoulders.
I hold onto a speck of dust in the air.
Uh, there's no force on earth that could, that could pry my, my
knows at the current weight from the floor of this boat.
Yeah, no, there's not.
Um, okay.
Yeah.
And what are you holding onto?
Weilon?
I hold on to the steering wheel.
Okay.
Well, that's, that's what I'm holding on to.
So you want to hold on to something else?
Yeah.
Out of my way.
The force of your personality and any that he doesn't want to lawsuit.
You just grab the steering wheel.
We'll it holds on to a wake off, hold on to something else.
Um, and uh, yeah, so everybody just roll a just roll a strength check. This this is not meant to be
This is not meant to throw you off
You're trying to throw me off. No
Wow
In the natural 20. Yeah
If anything happens, hold on i'll just wait
God god damn it said that you got a uh 19 branson. Oh nice. Yeah
I'm gonna have that D&D Beyond but not Roll20.
Yeah, I'm gonna have that log up.
Uh, so I just have it.
Um, okay, that is...
God, alright, this was really not meant to be anything,
but you did get a critical fail, Pat, so...
Uh, I do have to...
I'm holding onto Bibby's shoulders.
[laughter]
Okay, that's maybe why.
Yeah, okay, in this instance, uh...
Uh, Bibby somehow holds in place,
but I guess his bad voodoo tracks onto you,
and you just fall towards the front of the boat
is not your head on the front of the boat
uh... uh... you're just gonna take a little bit damage from that
uh... as you guys fall fall fall how much damage
uh...
uh... website rolled
actually just rolled a d_-forty four
uh... they can take three damage
uh...
as you not your head against about the boat
when you guys land will also resolve like a short rest is this took some time
and stuff and we'll just like that
Um, yeah.
And so you guys fall down this, this waterfall into what looks
like a massive toilet bowl.
And as you sink into that and you like shoot down that and the
water comes rushing from behind you, forcing you out into.
Something that is kind of just pitch black and also Brown and also smelly.
And you see Wankoff as he sort of like recoils from the boat.
And he's like, okay, yeah,
this was supposed to be a lot cleaner.
Okay, yeah, and there's no,
and he goes over to a wall and he rubs some gunk off
and he starts flicking a light.
And he's like, yep, nope, this isn't good.
So, oh boy.
- Well, it seems to me if it's pitch black
and also brown and stuff.
That's a nighttime poop.
(laughing)
- This is everyone's poop.
Well, it's really just the robots poop.
The frogs, we don't let them poop.
So, okay.
- What do you mean you don't let them poop?
- Well, I don't not let them poop.
I think the robots have some sort of fucked up
dominating relationship with the frogs.
- So where does their poop go?
I think they poop outside somewhere, I don't know.
The robots take care of it.
What's poop?
You said they're pooping.
What?
What's poop?
Two characters who could barely talk.
Is that?
That's Caleb's problem.
Cam's has gotten worse since I started mine.
He's trying to one up me as always.
No, my character did not have teeth since 20 minutes into the first episode.
Why? My character's face is curved around a fucking...
That was your choice.
A fucking, uh, uh, yoga ball sized head!
Baby's tongue falls out. Baby's tongue falls out.
[Laughter]
I lose all my facial features.
My vocal cords have been paralyzed.
[Laughter]
I'm gonna take out a gavel.
Okay.
The, the, the...
Alright, fine.
You win.
Hitting the front of the boat has turned me completely non-verbal.
[Laughter]
Okay, good. So only the lawyer boy can talk.
That's good.
-Oh, can I? -[laughs]
So, um...
So, WinkCup says, "Okay, we just have to..."
So, these hallways are meant to be...
Well, they're supposed to be lined with new models of toilets that you can look at.
I guess we've been only selling what's in the stock supply room,
and nobody's been working in here.
So, we just gotta get through here, I guess,
and find a way out and find out how to fix this.
Maybe the control room can get us there. Let's let's uh, let's just venture forth
Onward I say
Okay, and you just say I said on word oh
Yeah, I mean you guys can walk through this area
For a little bit and I mean as best as you can Pinocchio
I guess you're just sort of dragging your pole.
Like, do you just push forward with it?
What do you how do you walk?
Can we establish that for a second?
I think at some point I got a wheelbarrow.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
We talked about you getting a wheelbarrow.
Yes.
So you did get a wheelbarrow.
Let's let's say you did because that's the only way this is going to make sense right
now.
But at some point, it's going to it's going to get bad.
Oh, yeah.
No, it's it's it's going to be interesting.
I'm walking in front of Pinocchio's wheelbarrow and it's just like running me over, over and
over just hitting the back of your you're stuck in the wheel.
Yeah. Flattened continuously. Yeah. Some kind of looney tune
nonsense. You guys walk for a bit. Everyone roll. Let's let's
let's roll perception first. Let's make sure that you guys
see what you guys recognize or notice in this place. Crit one
Awesome. Weyland, we got 19. Okay. And then, oh, and Pinocchio somehow the 17.
So yeah, two of you guys start to notice that Wacoff doesn't really know where he's going.
You start to pick up on that after about a few minutes of traveling with him. It's not even that
that much time. So he sort of turns around he's like okay I think we're almost
there okay maybe and he starts to... Well you were here earlier! Nah there's no way.
Yeah Wally Winkoff you're more lost than a nun in a different church.
There's no... I don't... wait what are you... I'm not gonna interrogate that.
Right, yeah. Well, they have a home church at a way church
Your last is a nun is the first time at the away church
Okay, I don't know where I'm going oh what the oh
Okay, uh, maybe we can maybe we can uh, um
What if we just sort of like scream for help?
Right?
[Pewds screams]
Okay, so Pat, with that scream, which was crazy loud,
you hear, you start to hear some sort of sloshing coming from in front of you,
And what comes into view is the form of a beautiful, like, Victorian-era-looking woman.
What's up?
Made of shit.
[Laughter]
Louder, yeah. What's up?
Yeah.
And she looks to you all and she says,
I'm sorry. I can I help any of you not much
I
Suppose um and she looks I'm just chillin she her eyes meet wank off. She says mr. White golf and he's like
the
Yeah, yeah, no, I get that
My name is
My name is lady dibby. I was
What's so funny now we all like won this contest
Lady tibby
I actually win contests all the time too.
Yes, I suppose it does sound quite a bit like it.
Orphan Bibby!
I won a contest at the...
I won... I...
And I...
Ah, shit.
Okay.
Almost made it there.
Um...
Yes, um...
Your name is Bibby.
Orphan Bibby?
My name's John Kennedy.
Oh!
Yeah!
My name's...
the
you Pinocchio she's looking at you she's like rotating fat as it's as it kind of
comes to the end you know like a coin it's spinning faster and faster well I've
I've been living in this area for quite some time I was used to attend to mr.
went
It's not real quick.
And I like try to do that thing where you put your fingers
together and then like jump through.
Yeah, roll roll acrobatics.
15.
All right.
You're not physically able to do this, but it doesn't look as
stupid as you would think.
And Wankoff says, Look, you've been here a while. Can you
please help us get out of here?
We I so I'm his nephew
He gave me the factory. I guess you got lost in the pot the the picture there
I was gonna say the sauce or the picture. I was had lost in the past. That's not a thing. Anyway
can you maybe lead us out of here or
Something. Yes. I I suppose I can there's only
Do it's rather clogged. You usually have those horrible little frogs here cleaning things, but they've been I suppose lazy lately
The only way out of here that I know of would be there's a weak area of the piping
Unfortunately, there are turd devils guarding it. Yeah
You're excused no, I didn't say excuse me
Turd turd devils. What are what are turd devils?
turd devils are
It's when you put like a devil inside of a turkey
*laughter*
That was pretty good man!
Sometimes you gotta hand it to the guy.
*laughter*
Yeah, I miss 100% of the shots you don't take.
Exactly.
It just takes 100% of them.
I I maybe that's what turd devils are now. Is that so funny?
Yeah, I love having devil meat on Thanksgiving
Yeah, okay, that's what it is it's a
There's no reason to I have war but it doesn't matter I'm not even kidding this is so much better
She says it's when a turkey is stuffed inside of a devil
It's when the devil is stuffed inside of a turkey
Departed well your your lawyer. You probably know something about devils, right? Oh, certainly. Mm-hmm
Okay, well, yeah valuable source of meat you stuck inside a toy
Thanksgiving
And yeah, she says well there I have to change some of their move sets
She says so
Well, I can need you there but you'd have to I I simply can't fight them
But if you can defeat them, we could perhaps make it to the weak area the pipe and break it open
Well, yeah, I'm gonna pull out a fork and a knife and tie a little bib yeah, yes
To a devil is no match for little boy like me. Yeah, I give a big toothless smile. I
Chop my gums together. I'm so hungry and excited. Yeah, when you do that, yeah
I'm just doing I'm doing the robot and trying to see the lady notices
Not saying anything
I'm doing this now like yeah, like my fingers on my eyes and I'm back at her and then doing like more robot move
With a when yeah, would you smile and you show your your toothless smile?
the
a a
My son
Me you're not you my son
Okay, we're just gonna like
You guys walk a bit further into the pipe
You could see that there were like newer models of toilets that had been designed and like like, you know
Like the wank off toilet 3000 the wank off toilet
a
the
a turkey says gobble gobble? Well I think they say gobble, you know. I think they say bobble.
I need to think about what a devil sounds like and then filter that through a turkey.
Okay right yeah. Okay hold on. Okay that's a devil. It's sort of like fake Latin and
then. Not mad? Yeah. It just sounds like. That sounds like it could be a turdevil. Right?
It's the unmistakable sound of a toad devil.
[laughter]
Do they have a lot of these where you grow up?
Sure.
Mm-hmm. Wonderful.
Let's kill them.
You guys do that. I'll be here.
So you guys have the jump. I mean, they don't notice. They're just going
[mimics jumping]
Um, it's just sort of like
just sort of waddling around in this
sort of like where this weaker area of the pipe is.
So you guys can get creative here.
here you have the job I'm gonna I have disguised self mm-hmm so I'm gonna
disguise myself as like a pretty lady turd devil good like a blonde wig and
everything mm-hmm okay they're gonna love that yeah I'm gonna like saucily
like walk up to them yes so is anybody else have any put any one to prepare any
actions while he's doing it. I'm gonna get into a rage. Preemptively, you're already upset. I'm upset
because the the lady left. I mean she's still around she's just not. Well she didn't check
out my robot and I'm fucking pissed. Oh before we get into this this fight thing did we take
a short rest on the boat like you said we were going to? Yes I'm sorry. I have three. I'm sorry
are
just
a minus on it.
Because you have negative constitution.
You have minus to a constitution.
Yeah.
Where's the hit dice?
If you click take short risk.
Alright, I'm just going for it.
Wow.
You're getting really good rolls too.
Those are like, yeah.
Yeah, it's a max roll and then two right below max.
I got nine, seven, and eight.
Those are good rolls too, Pat.
How good are they?
They're really good, buddy.
Yeah?
They're good.
Yeah, they're really good.
That's actually the best rolls in the game.
Don't tell them that.
Come on.
I'm not going to tell them that.
the
we can't baby him. We have to tell him that he didn't win the game.
What? No, I'm sorry. Well, that was how do you do private chat here?
Uh, okay, cool. And wait on you got 17 HP back. Beautiful, magical. Um, okay. So yeah,
does anybody have any sort of moves they want to try out besides, uh, you by the way? Yeah,
Sorry, Caleb, I wanted to make sure you knew.
So, you have a new attack, by the way.
- Oh my God.
- This is gonna be the first of a few things
that might be happening to you,
depending on how you play the game.
You have Pillar Face.
So it has 10 feet of reach.
It does 2D10 damage.
And basically involves you lifting up your entire body
and collapsing it on somebody or a line of people.
Due to my huge mask.
Yes, yes.
So you can do that now.
Okay.
Yeah.
Sounds good.
Yes.
Um, I, I'm just going to stand by and be ready to, to jump into action if need be.
Cool.
Um, that sounds good.
So yeah, I mean, what you can even do is, um, if you want to like, you can prepare a
like yeah I'll prepare my an attack in case if things go south that's that's
the that's what yeah you could do your slaying basically prepare a sling attack
so that you're not like near them so they don't like see you yeah all right I
will prepare a sling attack yeah I think things go south is good enough like I
mean I know people get more specific with that they can shove it um cool
Waylon Arovois, what are you gonna do?
I'm a lady turdevil and I'm walking over to them to like a brassy
rendition of like you must be a beautiful baby and I'm like really like getting my eggs into it
and I'm gonna like sort of push my hair.
[weird noises]
Yeah, they are loving it.
uh... they are uh...
gobble gobble gobbling it up
uh... they are are trying to do a little dances
the devil in their stomachs is popping out of their mouth and going
like just like
and uh... getting really excited. Well because there's stuff so there's a seam right down the middle
right? The devil head pokes out the top
yes the cooked turkey body yes as we all know
oh i have to finish changing their attacks a little bit
Go on, go on, Branson. Tell me what you're doing here.
Um, so if there's one that's like close to me...
Hmm, okay.
I would say so, yeah.
There's one that's gonna be a little bit closer to you, and then there's two...
I'd say there's one that's kind of following, and there's a third that's kind of still more interested in like playing in this shit,
but is like kind of noticing you guys.
But there is one that's like significantly closer to you compared to the other two.
Cool, I'm gonna gesture to my like lips like a big like putter there
to that one and then when he gets closer I want to stab him in the throat.
That's good. So in that case let's do persuasion with advantage.
Great. With advantage.
Oh yeah, you're disguised beautifully.
Beautifully?
Really well.
He's seven years old.
No, no, well that's the character of the third devil, not me.
We're playing into a dangerous trope here.
Yeah, likely.
Okay, that's a 12. I think you got one more.
Oh, yeah, sorry.
What do I do with the hit dice? I never...
Whatever you rolled, you can add them to your HP.
That's how much you heal.
Or a 13.
A 13? Ooh, okay.
Yeah, I'd say a 13, the devil is kind of like...
I don't think they, like, are not... don't want to kiss you.
But they're kind of, like, playing a little bit coy.
Like this one's good.
(mimics eating noises)
Like it's not, he's not convinced.
He's like, oh, like you're, you're, you're,
you're a saucy dame.
Let me see what I can get out of this.
Might have to try something else here.
- Sure, sure.
I, I think, and I think, and I'm going to pull the like leg
of the turkey skin up to reveal like a long shapely leg
with like a garter.
- Okay. Hell yes.
- Okay, wow.
This is a great disguise self.
Okay, yeah.
He's coming in for the kiss.
- Okay, great, yes. - That's enough.
He wants to start, he's gonna start at your foot,
you're gonna try to go,
(imitates kissing)
you know?
- Oh, yeah, he's doing like the--
- Yes, yeah. - Gomez Adams.
- Yes, precisely.
- Cool, so as he's doing that,
I'm gonna just like stab him in the throat.
- That's good.
Roll an attack roll.
- Oh, I'm in the rage, right?
And I can teleport?
(Link snorts)
No?
- So you have to roll on the table,
on the wild magic table because it's random
alright okay you can address that
in a second my plan was to teleport behind them
so i guess i can't do that god's got other plans for you
uh... to as always
first
let's see what waylon's got going on over here i got a twelve
a twelve
uh... yeah wow ok yep
that's enough
alright yeah alright roll for damage
five yeah so you just jab this in this turd devil as it's kissing up your leg do you like what do
you do do you just like i go fresh and i stab him and uh we're gonna roll for initiative folks
because the battle has just begun um we're gonna start with you eventually
Devil Inside, Devil Inside Every single one of us, the Devil Inside
Every single ribbons to the devil inside
[MUSIC]