Wally Wankoff, the name on everyone's mind.
There isn't a soul in the world who doesn't know him.
He's the world's most feared and respected businessman, as well as its most successful.
While Wankoff Enterprises has dipped into every vertical under the sun, and completely
crushed it too, there are three things Mr. Wankoff does better than just about anyone.
Bombs, candy, and toilets.
When a brain-dead 19-year-old too stupid to torture cats as a kid unwraps a candy bar,
he's eating a wank off.
When his grubby, candy-covered hands grips the console where he's remotely piloting
an MQ-9 Reaper over rural Pakistan, the bomb he's gonna drop is a wank off bomb.
Then when he remembers he has to shit because he has the "no-no" feeling going on, the
smartest man in the armed forces will sprint to the bathroom and just miss, planting a stinky
in a Wankoff toilet. Wankoff once said, "People will shit, eat candy, shit, and blow up the
only movie theater in the Basdarwada Valley for as long as they live." And so far, he's
been the most right man in the entire world, and justly rewarded for it.
But it must be lonely at the top, or at least, Chucky Fuckit likes to imagine it is. Because
Because he's at the very bottom, a kind child with a good heart and without a penny to his
name, humble Chucky Fuckett just wants one thing in life.
To meet his hero Wally Wankoff.
Surely an impossibility, right?
Well not quite.
Because Wally Wankoff announced today that for the next week, in five of his Wankoff
Yummy Yums, his famous candy treat, there is a brown sticker with a QR code on it.
The QR code, when scanned, takes you to a schizophrenic substack domain.
But with one of these stickers, a lucky child or adult can enter into Wally Wankoff's
factory, too, better known as the Crazy Playhouse of Indentured Servitude, where Wankoff says
he will, from among the winners, choose an heir to his fortune and company.
Wankoff is a notorious recluse, and the day he lets the winners into his factory would
be his first public appearance in over 20 years.
When he was last seen at a Panera, with a hood pulled over his head, a mask, and a cloaking
device, so no one could see him.
Wank-off mania is sweeping the planet.
All over people were wanking it.
Wanking it is the colloquial term for buying a wank-off chocolate bar.
From all walks of life, children, adults, the rich and the poor, the black and the white,
not Koreans though for some reason, but everybody else was wanking it.
Day and night people were flooding candy stores and wanking it for all to see.
Some would shop online and wank it there, others went mad, stealing wank off Yummy Yums, this
is known as jerking it, and not even bothering to wank.
Businesses shut down for a week, schools were closing, prisoners even took the week off from
being locked up.
Everyone and I mean everyone wants those brown stickers.
So what chance does poor Chuckie Fuckit have?
Well, just as much as your eye if we were all so broke.
But fate may have something else in store for little Fucken.
And while this is a story about Chucky Fucken, the poor sweet boy who works year-round as
a dog walker for the oldest, richest, weirdest guys in New York City, there are other characters
in our story who deserve the limelight all the same, for they too were lucky enough to
get a Wank Off Browns sticker.
And so we zoom in to Shantyville, Illinois, where there's a little boy who might even
be more unfortunate than Mr. Chucky Fuckit.
Who is this little boy?
Hello!
My name's Bibby!
And I'm walking, I'm walking, I'm walking, I'm not walking because both my legs are broken
permanently in casts.
I'm crushing up and down the sidewalk in this this small town and I'm yelling.
Extra, extra, read all about it.
I'm an orphan.
Extra, extra.
I got no family.
Ah, piss off you.
And some random passerby just tries to trip you on your crutches.
Roll an acrobatics check.
Okay.
That's a 19.
Hell yeah.
Yeah, he tries to trip you.
What do you do?
How do you do this?
I deftly pivot on one of my crutches and I spin into the street to avoid the tripping.
Okay.
Whoa.
So the only issue- Pretty cool, right?
Yeah.
Pretty cool, yeah.
Man's maneuver.
So while it is pretty cool, lo and behold, here comes a truck.
No avoiding this.
Let's see how much damage you take.
That is eight damage you take from this truck that is coming by.
Okay, I take eight damage. I fly. I fly down the street. I get hit by the truck. I go flying and I smash into the wall.
A brick wall. And I go, I slide down. Like it goes like, as I slide down to the ground.
Yeah, you see a proprietor of the store you just slammed into go outside and go,
"Hey, are you doing okay, kid?" And starts picking you up and starting to brush you off.
I'm so sorry I damaged your store, sir. I could work it off if you need to.
Oh, well, it's quite all right. We have a lot of children in debt who already work here.
Is there something I can get you, young man? Perhaps a hospital?
I've been to every hospital. They say they don't know what's wrong with me.
They don't know how to fix it. I've had broken legs and arms for six years. I'm 12 years old.
Oh, you look really young for your age.
That's good when you're older.
That's going to be good when you're older.
I'm shorter because I lost six vertebrae when I was seven years old.
Okay.
Well, how'd that happen when you were seven?
A frisbee, sir.
Knocked it right out of my spine.
Okay.
Well, look, I don't know if I can help you.
Um, you seem to be unfortunate.
There is one thing I I desire more than anything and he turns around he goes what?
What is it? Well besides finding out who my family is
Since I'm an orphan, right? I would really like to eat a delicious chocolate bar
Really had one in my life. Oh
well
This week Wankoff is giving away brown stickers
So you might get lucky in more than one way if you eat that white car. That sounds delightful
Yes, it is. Well, the only candy store in 5000 miles is right across the street. So you just got to walk across the road
Can you do it?
I I would like to I would like to take another I would like to try to find an alternate route
So I'm going back. I'm okay if I can get out of the street
it. I'm going through a back alley and I'm going to try and come around the back and
cross the train tracks that run through the town. Yeah, there's a back alley. As you walk
through the back alley, you see the guy who pushed you and you also see he has another
friend with him and a couple other friends. And the guy who pushed you goes, "That's him!
That's the one who didn't fall down when I tried to hurt him!" And the other guys sort
square up against you. Um, and so they start swinging at you. Um, one of them is going
to try to attack you. We're not even going to roll initiative here. Uh, let's see how
they do. Uh, that hits you. Okay. How much damage do I take? Let's find out. I'm a fiend
for damage. You take nine damage. He cool. He guts you with a knife. Uh, uh, and, uh,
truck. Yeah. Yeah. It's for trying to avoid me. Yeah. A moth flies out of the cut in my
my stomach.
Yeah, and he's and they look at you and another one tries to
kick you now in the in the shins, which are already I think
in the dire Straits if I'm correct.
Yes, that hits you too.
All right.
How much are we talking here?
Let's find out guys.
Cam has a lot of HP and no AC.
Okay, that's 10 damage for you.
He just kicks you right in the shin your shin bends inwards
and you're sort of walking like a chicken now.
You don't look too hot.
- I'm running away like a chicken.
I'm running- - Like a chicken too?
- Yeah, well, if I'm walking like a chicken,
I'm probably running like one too, right?
- Yeah, they're like, "Get back here!"
And they're trying to chase you,
but they're, for some incomprehensible reason,
a lot slower all of a sudden,
as they're running towards you
and you run out of the alley and you're safe and sound,
you're huffing and puffing.
You see across from the train tracks is the candy store.
Turns out you don't have to go across the road.
There's one across the train tracks too.
And that guy who said there's only one in 5,000 miles
is fucking crazy.
- Oh yeah.
- But you can go, the only way across
is across the train tracks.
- Okay, I take a step towards the train tracks.
- Okay, as you do, you hear,
(imitates train bell)
- A candy bell, oh boy!
(all laughing)
I better get over there fast!
And I'm going as fast as I can, which is not very fast.
Okay, yeah, the train speeds up as you go on top of the track.
Yeah.
And you see the guy who, uh...
I notice a shiny, beautiful penny on the train tracks.
Okay, yeah.
Let's have you roll... Let's just have you do a...
Are you gonna try to avoid the train, or is she...
I don't see the train.
You don't see the train, that's true.
Okay, you're gonna add one gold.
Okay. And you're going to take... I'm gonna die. Yeah, what are you at HP wise? I'm at 13.
You're gonna take 18 damage. 18? Yeah.
Okay, I'm at negative... Okay, I'm unconscious. Okay, so you are unconscious.
Um, you see, all you see is blackness. You think this is it. This is how this is the end for Bibby, Bibby the orphan.
Uh, uh, and since this is a very playful intro we're doing, uh, you, uh, hear kid, kid, kid, kid, kid, and you're getting slapped in the face.
Uh, you're also, I want to say when I'm where I'm waking up, I, I, I woke up in a completely different town because I got stuck to the front of the train and I went all the way.
You are we woke up actually in Duluth Brooklyn.
Oh, the Luth Brooklyn which is famous for their there's it's a town that only has one residence which is the giant iron dome in which wonka lives Wankoff lives.
Yeah, who's that?
Who's Wonka?
He's... I don't know who the fuck that is.
You're gonna cut that out.
You take four damage from the slap, and you go unconscious again.
And then the guy shakes you again, and he gives you water.
He's like, "I don't know why I slapped you.
I saw it in movies."
And he's like, "Kid, kid, are you okay?"
And he starts...
He's holding a chocolate bar underneath your nose as he's doing it.
"Kid, kid, kid."
"Candy?
Is that candy for me?"
Uh, yeah, I guess it can be.
I smashed the candy.
I was just trying to wake you up.
Okay.
Did you take a big bite out of it?
I take, I don't even unwrap the wrapper.
I take a huge bite and there's a, and then there's a loud sound like glass breaking and
then like a Looney Tune, one by one, all my teeth fall out because I bit onto a hard brown
sticker inside the wrapper.
That's right.
You got one of the brown stickers, baby.
You're the luckiest boy in the world
A brown sticker!
Oh this is great!
I'm so happy I get to visit the factory!
I'll probably wake up...
...at the candy factory!
What?
And we cut away...
...to a courthouse
where the world's foremost child lawyer is
He is a dapper little man
and there's nobody quite like him. Who is this little dapper boy? Yeah we're
looking at a kid he's about seven years old he's dressed in all white he looks
like he's wearing like a like a Colonel Sanders like costume mm-hmm like the
white hair and a white goatee but that's growing naturally on him. Yes. He saw
something really scary in it.
yeah so he's dressed it all white and he's in the courtroom he has a cigar and
there you know there's like ceiling fans like lazily spinning above course yeah I
guess he's in the middle of mm-hmm yeah there's okay yeah your honor Oh what you
gotta what you gotta understand in this case is the defendant he gestures to the
defendant.
So, yeah, go,
no, go.
This young man here,
he's as guilty as the day is
long.
And some of that is
I'm innocent. I'm innocent.
I swear I didn't know that there
was cookies in the cookie jar.
Even I just I I just
and then the judge goes now.
Now, settle down.
Let's let the handsome child
speak
and he looks good.
Of course, the call
to my time
Now, obviously, in cases such as this,
it's usually we're looking at a $5 fine, a slap on the wrist,
a promise to never do it again.
But in this case, I am, of course,
pushing for the death penalty.
You do firing squad, lethal injection, electric chair.
Take your pick.
Oh, well, I don't know.
This does seem like a not minor offense.
After all, it was just a cookie from a cookie jar.
and it was, after all, oatmeal raisin.
Not even a very good cookie.
- When asked initially, the defendant,
we asked the defendant who stole the cookies
from the cookie jar, was it you?
He said, "Couldn't be," which we learned was a lie.
- Well, I couldn't be me.
I was not in, I wasn't in the vicinity of the cookie jar.
- Irrelevant, you don't need to be near the cookies
to steal the cookies.
(yells)
Why don't we open up evidence?
Let's see these little cookies, see if the bite mark matches up with this kid.
Now that's a really good idea.
You're a really smart lawyer.
Thank you very much.
In addition to that, I'm seven years old.
I remember being a baby.
Yeah.
You see all the jury nodding like, "That's true.
That's true.
He does."
And so what we're going to do is, first, I want you to roll a persuasion on the jury
for your death penalty thing.
we'll resolve that after you open the evidence too.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god.
I don't know if this is going to work.
I got a 27.
Yeah, you got a 27.
So the jury is now at this point making daggers at this little boy.
But you're opening the evidence case too.
So what's in here?
You're comparing the bite marks from that oatmeal raisin cookie.
Yeah, so there's going to be, we've got like a VHS with grainy surveillance footage of
this kid.
Yeah, right.
a cookie, there's cookies with bite marks, they're all like in ziplock bags.
And then there's evidence of this kid's bites into other things.
So there's like other stuff that this kid is eating, like a broccoli and like a single
lemon that he took a bite out of.
And there's also a chocolate bar in there.
Yeah, there's all this stuff in there.
And the grainy footage, you see the boy, it looks like the boy.
It's pretty clearly though, like you wearing a wig as the boy taking the cookie from the
cookie jar.
Yeah, I've got a shirt on that says defendant.
Yeah.
You wink at the camera, the judge goes, so charming.
You're charming.
Or is the, he's getting a little confused.
Who can say?
We all know in a court of law, details are nothing.
It's the tone of the court.
E pluribus unum, I think.
Yes.
Of course.
- Nothing. - And yeah, you have also this chocolate bar
in here. And you're gonna test it out on the boy. So you can see the defendant is on the
stand. He's shivering. You see his mother's crying. She's like, "I left out the worst
kinds of cookies and he still did it!" Like, she's in tears. Yeah, you're gonna bring
him the chocolate bar or what's the meaning here?
Yeah. So I'm gonna bring him the chocolate bar and say, "You, defendant, didn't catch
- I asked you to write your name, didn't ask.
(laughing)
I'm gonna unwrap this chocolate bar
and ask you to take a single bite of the chocolate bar.
- Okay, it's Silly Michael, but okay.
- Silly Michael?
- Silly Michael, that's me.
- I'm gonna look at his mom and give a big thumbs down.
(laughing)
- She just goes like, "Ugh."
- Sure, sure.
- And yeah, so he takes, he says,
"This is gonna absolve me, I'm sure of it."
And he goes to take a bite of the chocolate bar and he goes,
"Oh, there's something else in there."
And I would say you can notice pretty quickly
that it is the brown sticker,
but I am gonna have you roll a sleight of hand
to see if you could keep it.
- Yeah, hell yeah.
I'm gonna sleight of hand.
I'm gonna try to steal it from him.
- Yeah, 13.
Okay, so with the 13,
you're able to sort of like pocket it away
and the kid's like, "What was that?"
- Shut up.
works.
Guilty mouth. Well, I think we could all agree that it's we'll
never know exactly what happened in this case by by guns. I am
still of course pushing for the death penalty. And I got 27. So
you know, we're gonna torture this kid to death.
Yeah, you could do almost anything that is, you know,
allowed to be recorded.
And I'm gonna grab the judges gavel and Michelle court is
I couldn't I wouldn't say it any other way.
Okay.
All right, everybody get the hell out of here.
No kid.
What are you doing later?
I got some we're trying to start a poker game up and you just sort of fades out from that
and we move to a Thanksgiving dinner where the I guess the candy family is sitting sitting
happily at their yummy, delicious Thanksgiving table
in some nondescript, lovely John Hughes suburb.
And there's somebody there though,
who's always trying to cause a little bit of trouble.
He's a that uncle maybe at Thanksgiving.
Who is this guy?
- I'm John Candy.
(laughing)
I think this meal sucks, I won't eat candy.
You got it pretty good.
It's not bad.
Yeah, you see your brother, your brother.
This turkey's dry.
Look, John.
Oh, very funny, John.
But look, we can't have candy for Thanksgiving.
We can have candy for Thanksgiving dessert.
Well, we're going to have a pumpkin pie.
Fuck that.
I want to wank off.
No, you know you want to wank off.
Oh, you want to wank.
Yeah, no candy not what are you talking about? I don't know what you're talking about
You're the one who comes here and brings your attitude. You see his wife goes up behind him is like honey, honey. He's like
Do you have my candy in your purse I
God, I just want candy so bad. I hate this crap and you see
The kids at the table and they're just like why don't I go back? It's it the kids table. We don't want him sitting here
He ate all our food last year.
Yeah, John, we let you sit at the kids table and you ate all their food.
When we tried to take it away from you, you said finders keepers,
which didn't really add up.
That's a law.
It's not a law.
Yeah, it is.
You sound like that lawyer I just heard about.
Look, let's just sit down.
Let's just say grace.
Okay, grace.
Nice, normal, funny.
Let's have a nice, normal Thanksgiving dinner.
Okay, and everyone closes their eyes.
and the candy bars are around and you see
uh uh uh you see them all placed in front of the children's table so everyone's
closing their eyes so you have an opportunity here
um but you could also just let them say grace no i'm going for it
fuck yeah yeah okay you absolutely do it i was gonna say stealth or sleight of
hand but yeah stealth to get up and get to the
kids table the oh oh wait oh it's um
disadvantage with armor worn oh don't worry about that okay so just because
you're wearing plate mail yeah try to try to get up from the table while
everyone say grace and you just knock it over I'm really god damn it John are you
to the bathroom. Okay, just what's this shit so boring. Okay, it's it's all right. Go go
to the bathroom. You go to the bathroom. Right? I'm 47 years old. I can go to the bathroom
if I want. So you go up you get up. I guess you walk you walk towards the bathroom or
while they they try to resume grace. They're all watching you now. They all do not have
their eyes closed.
They are worried.
How big is the kids table?
It's like like three by three kind of like, you know, square
kind of thing.
Like those little like plastic little table tables.
Yeah, you know, it's what you can do, you know for the kids.
I just pick it up and try to take it in the bathroom with
me.
No, no, John Candy, Uncle John Candy.
No, you see the kids are following you.
Your brother is like, God damn it, John.
And he starts chasing after you.
Let's do should we?
Well, the candy, the candy bars are on the table, right?
Roll initiative. Make a fight. Yeah. Yeah.
Let's roll initiative.
And armor on anyway. Yeah.
He's doing well.
So I'll roll for the kids and I'll roll for the dad.
Oh, oh, they're not dressed in armor, though.
OK, so what's your deck?
Because the kids decks are probably higher than yours.
If I had to guess.
My decks, uh, it's 11.
It's 11, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
So the kids are going to go first.
So, uh, your little nephew, um, your little nephew, Billy Bob is going to try to grab
the candy off.
That's my real nephew's name.
Please don't use that name.
Really?
Okay.
In case I murder him.
Yeah.
So your little nephew, Gumby.
I'm kidding.
I don't care.
Oh, wait, hold on.
Now actually keep it.
Yeah.
the
but
the candy bar away from him. You're just moving the table inside like it's up a bit higher.
And now you're going to go so you can just use your full movement to get to the bathroom.
Yeah, I'm going to do that. Yeah. So yeah, I mean, like you have like 30 feet of movement,
so you can just okay, the house isn't that big. You just get in the bathroom,
you get free action to lock the door. You're in there with the table.
All the candy bars. Like one of the table legs is sticking out of the toilet.
Like you couldn't quite fit it in there.
You hear your brother slamming on the door.
God damn it!
John, I'm never gonna let you in my fucking house again!
Good, I don't wanna come back here, dude.
This place sucks.
You don't even have like a Nintendo Switch or anything.
I don't even get to play games when I'm here.
We do have a Nintendo Switch!
It's for the kids, John!
Well, I can't play it!
You always want me to stay upstairs!
If you could play it, if...
Last time, you said, "It's my turn, it's my turn, it's my turn," and my kid cried for you.
It was my turn!
and
You see the lock wiggles a little bit, and you see little Gumby looks up at you, and
he sees the sticker, and his eyes go wide.
And you enter into a rage, because you're a barbarian.
Which way does the door open?
It opens out.
Like out from you.
So what did you say about Gumby?
I think you're going to enter into a...
Were you going to enter into a rage as a barbarian, or were you going to just...
I was I want to like exit the bathroom in an excited rage.
Do it.
Okay.
So just because I found the sticker and just because I'm, you know, yeah, just a big man
child.
I just like, I just kick the door open with Gumby in front of it.
And we're cutting over to another character.
We'll find out what happened there.
Maybe.
It is a little wooden boy who is in somewhere in Italy.
No, not Italy.
Where are you at, Pam?
Florida.
Florida?
Yeah.
Where are we in Miami?
Fuck no, dude.
We're in Pensacola.
Tallahassee?
Pensacola.
Pensacola, Florida.
Yeah.
and where there is a bedraggled Italian man in Florida who is working on this wooden boy,
this puppet. Who is this wooden boy? Who is he?
How about this? How about this, Pat? I'll take the lead. He comes to life out of fucking
where okay right yeah oh my god oh oh my god I'm alive I'm alive okay oh look
Pinocchio touching me what is this no no no it's not no I don't I'm not trying to
go back so no what I made you as a gift for my ex okay she loves puppets I don't
Why she was weird, but I'm gonna give for your ex and why is your little boy puppet?
Well, I don't ask her about that, but I'm hoping this will get into it. You know
Come back
But well, but I did not expect you to come alive. This is oh, this is this is very exciting stuff. Okay, okay
Pinocchio what is
So what I'm gonna guess my name's Pinocchio. I mean you don't blaming you. Okay, okay, so I'm Pinocchio
You have Pinocchio now.
Okay, it feels, feels, eh, it feels okay.
Okay, and your nose grows a little bit when you say that.
What the, what is that?
You don't like the name?
How can you tell that?
What is, why'd my nose grow?
Okay, uh, and yeah, roll, we'll have you roll a D, one D ten every time.
Uh, uh, or one D twenty, fuck it.
Roll a D twenty every time you lie.
Seventeen.
Your nose grows seventeen inches.
*laughter*
Oh fuck, this hurts! This hurts so bad! What is this?
Oh, okay, okay, so Geppetto is able to like, shave down your nose a bit.
It hurts worse!
I can't have you walking around like this!
Stop, why? I don't care!
I'm doing an anti-semitic thing again, which I'm not.
What is this? Hold on!
Why is my nose so huge?
And, um, he, he, he goes,
"Okay, look, look, just,
I- I- I- I- I didn't know this was gonna happen. I knew that I made a deal with a guy
I thought it was gonna be something magical, but I didn't know you would come to life
I was hoping you would just light up or something
Okay
Okay, let me hold on one second and he goes out and he takes out like a
Manual that says making a magical boy and he opens it up and he's looking inside of it. He's like, hey
Okay
Do you want to be a real boy?
um
Yeah, yeah, well, I know stop growing. All right. Hold on. It's just to go to page 57. So hold on
He starts peeling through the basic
Yeah, you know, it'll stop growing
You have to do good deeds
Yes, then your nose roll d20
You're not gonna do good deeds
Okay, all right, okay
Do what to do? Okay. Hold on one second and he goes and he leaves his
he leaves a
the his little hovel he lives in and
You could see on the right
On your right. He also left a chocolate bar a
a wank off yummy yum unopened.
Um, I was born 90 seconds ago and even I know that's a wank off yummy yum.
I'd like to go try to grab it and eat it.
Okay.
As you try to go, go grab it and eat it.
Uh, um, a, you see a little, uh, uh, cricket, uh, pop up on top of the, the chocolate bar.
Uh, he goes, Oh, well there.
Well there.
Hold on.
you trying to slap him as hard as I can into a wall and he just splats.
Yep, he just splats.
And I rip open the chocolate bar.
Yep, and you find a brown sticker in there.
But Jimmy Petto is coming back in there.
So, I mean, he's going to see it unless you want to hide it.
it. I'm gonna you know what I'm gonna do. He have a I'm gonna
grab his car keys. Okay. he's coming back in so to do that.
let's have you cuz it's like I'm hanging by the door where
he just walked out of let's have you do you have a 19 inch
nose. So it's hard to hide is what you're well. What I'm
saying is you can also do an acrobatics check and get the key
ring around your nose.
Oh, well, you're smarter than me.
I will do that.
I was thinking I was probably a problem solve for Pinocchio.
If hell yeah, you just like do a swan leap in the air and just the ring of the keys just
slips on your nose and ends up like like whap whapping you in the face.
He Geppetto opens doors like the fuck you doing my keys.
I put the hanging keys in my mouth so that there's and I bite really hard so there's
really no way for me to get him off.
Give me those keys he tries to go and grab you
What are you guys doing? Can I do?
Do whatever you want. Can I do a here? I
Didn't just kill a cricket. Oh
Cool. Yeah
Roll d20 10
Near three foot nose. Yeah, he tries to go grab you and you get him right in there
camera and he's like oh no you got him right in the nards uh i'll say you have a chance how's
that smell Pinocchio bad
yeah uh yeah i would say at this point you he's he's uh doing the italian spider-man face um
and you're able to escape. And so I get in his Acura and I'm driving completely sideways
because my nose has to go out of the passenger door-winding window.
Just taking out mailboxes and side-view mirrors. Yeah, and yeah.
newspaper spinning into view. Yeah, and I have a bunch of cans behind the car and a
bumper sticker that says, "I just killed a cricket."
Perfect. That's all I wanted from you guys. So now we cut to a week later,
okay, where we are outside of the Wankoff factory. Thousands and thousands of people are lined up
outside in the Wankoff factory in Duluth, Brooklyn.
They're all vying for a chance to see Wally Wankoff.
To even, you know, for however brief, breathe the same air as him.
There's a massive iron dome that sits just outside of that sits
like within Duluth.
It's about three miles high and ten miles around and inside of
there.
It's impossibly large.
Sits the factory.
The entirety of the dome can contract.
Here are my glasses and seal from any point at any moment.
So being a defense contractor and shipping toilets and candy everywhere,
the dome is constantly just like like all these like little like pockets of the of the iron dome are just retracting and detracting and planes are flying out of there and delivery trucks are flying out.
It's this giant network where nobody's allowed inside the dome, but it's somehow like magically just like
Letting things out all day
So it but in there and so the factory's never really seen and right outside the factory are just ton of burnt corpses
They're strewn about from those who tried to enter
Famously if anyone steps within five point one five feet of the dome they are immediately vaporized
Even just today. We've seen like casualties and permanent scarring
I still the event is of the brown sticker recipients is basically it's like a tailgating party. There's jumbotrons everywhere to capture the event. There's music playing. People are playing flip cup with hot cocoa and burning themselves.
There's a dunk tank that where you sit on a toilet, and you throw a like bomb at the thing and then you dump and you fall into chocolate, like all the businesses are all represented and all these different little games, and you guys are the you know the guests of honor at this
tailgating Bonnaroo party that is before Wyckoff officially comes out.
What are you guys doing at this big bonanza at this event?
Are you guys interacting with each other? Are you guys on your own?
Doing your own thing? I'm standing like in the parking lot or like in not the
parking lot but like by the front it's like at the gate just like so
Booking boring. I just want to call my guys want to go inside. I'm gonna go in and meet this guy already
I mean you're like our
Yeah, you see people outside who are like is it true that you have a brown sticker that's so cool
Yeah, you go and see him yet
Yeah, but you're gonna right? Okay. Shut up. All right. I'm sorry. I'll leave you alone. Give me some candy
If you get me some candy, will you take pictures inside?
What if you get if I get you some candy, sorry, will you take pictures inside?
Inside of what?
Inside the factory
where?
Inside
I'll just I'll just go get you a a Mars bar. Oh my
I want that. I'm already here at the factory.
Can you go in there for me?
And what are other people doing?
I'm getting I'm getting bounced around the crowd like a beach
ball.
Like yeah, they're all they think they're going like hip hip
hooray hip hip hooray, but you're just instead.
I'm just flying all over the place.
I keep getting close to like I'm like reaching out for candy
and I keep getting close to touching it and I just get like
punted somewhere else.
Yeah, and very nearby.
There's like a there's like a one second shot of me breakdancing by spinning on my nose with a large crowd going yo
But it cuts away very fast, yeah
Yeah at the tank. Yes. I've tried to throw and my throws not strong. So I'm trying to convince the guy
to dunk himself just
Roll persuasion check. Sure. We said what did you live for? What could you have to live for?
Yeah, you got nothing to live for and I've persuaded you
Your life's a joke your wife's
It's don't respect you
This guy's like I mean, I think at least a little one, you know, you know he
he just swallows off into the bag and you see the guy there is
like, here's your price and it gives you a wank off yummy.
Yum, which when you eat these you do get a plus 5 temporary HP.
So they are I'm just going to like load up on those.
Yeah, yeah, there's tons of games.
You can play here.
There's like a ski ball game.
You can you can basically try to load up on the different kinds
of candy that will give you temporary buffs if you guys want to do that.
I'm playing skeeball and every single ball is bouncing back and hitting me in the face.
You don't want to try to win?
I'm trying really hard.
Go go go go go John.
No you go ahead.
So I just realized I said okay and I was just like meant that for you but I got confused.
Although a um, let's roll a attack roll, but we'll add your dex and your proficiency as
you're doing skeeball.
Okay, unarmed strike, 14.
Okay cool.
So with a, yeah, with a 14, you're getting pretty close, you're getting in there, but
it's not quite enough points.
You could try again, but it is going to cost you your shiny penny that you got on the train
tracks.
I will definitely spend the penny.
cool. Do it. Try again. I don't understand the value of money at all. Let me roll again.
Oh, you got a crit. Okay, cool. So-
Also, yeah, can I say what the- Yes, of course you can.
Yeah. I've been missing every single one. They're all bouncing back and hitting me in the face.
And then the last one bounces back, hits me in the face, bounces off my face,
and goes into the 10,000 point tiny circle at the top.
and you see, like, the woman who works there is like, "Can he get any luckier, this kid?"
And everyone's, like, clapping, like, "Yeah, yeah, yeah."
And I go to walk to get my prize and my foot is stuck underneath the machine.
They're like, "Can we-- do you wanna-- let's just try to, like--"
I'm already trying to chew it off.
Yeah, yeah, no, no, no, you don't have to do that.
They try to like move the machine.
I'm going to have these like normal people do like a strength check.
Let's see what they can do.
Yeah, no, they're just not able to move the machine.
They're like having a lot of trouble.
So they go to get the prizes and give it to you.
You're going to get three Wankoff Twizzlies,
which give you a temporary AC buff of plus one for for ten minutes.
Delicious Twizzly, I wish I could eat this!
Well you can, you can just- oh, no teeth.
Well, uh, let's try to...
You know what, you're the winner. Do you have a blender?
A blender? A what? A blender?
A bender? No I'm not going to get a bender. I'm having a good time. What?
A bender? A bendo? A blender?
home
right here. Who's on first?
I want to blend this! I want to blend this!
You want to blend me?
I want to blend it!
I mean this could go on forever. I'll have a great time.
Cut, cut real quick for one more second.
Let's please do it.
And now, now I'm sitting on the ground and women are dancing on the pole that is my nose.
Same exact sound. People are like, "Wah wah wah wah!"
And I'm the life of the party.
Yes, you are. Yeah, you're the best ever.
Um...
Yeah, and as you guys keep doing this, suddenly...
Uh, you guys have been having fun, you've been--
Or being mad at people, or...
- Uh, I'm-- - Making people want to die.
I've-- The whole time that everything's been going on,
I'm just beating the shit out of the gate.
- Yeah. - [laughter]
Like, punching-- Punching the gate so hard.
- It's like-- - The gate is--
[screaming]
It's like, screaming.
You have--
I gave you a big half convinced that it worked because you suddenly hear the thunderous roar of screeching metal piercing the air all the music in the sound stops this mass field as the iron dome creates another opening.
Is screeching screeching screeching and as the metal like you know the side of metal riches upwards into wherever it's going all you see is a sea of blackness inside.
And everyone like these thousands of people are like, "Huh? Like what?"
I turn to all of them and I'm like, "LUIGI IS DEAD!"
And then you hear someone say, "It's Wankoff! It's Wankoff!"
And sure enough, from the darkness, you see a face emerge.
A big, goofy, expressionless Marty Feldman face.
He's got glassy, googly eyes and a shaggy 70s bob.
And he has a goatee.
And a drone camera swoops in to take a look at his visage.
His eyes flip towards the camera
and as it hovers in front of him, he gives a big toothy grin
and on all these jumbotrons, everyone's going fucking nuts.
This is happening.
And the crowd is like going crazy.
It's Wankoff, it's Wankoff.
And then you see his eyes start to go back and forth.
Like some kind of pendulum and the crowds going crazy, then they are.
getting sleepy and then they all fall asleep except for five of you.
The four of you and little Chucky Fuckett, this little sweet blonde boy.
And eventually the drone finally, as the operator slowly passes out, the drone stays hovering
somehow and Wankoff's face begins to retreat into the darkness.
and he says to you all, come in.
OK, yeah, so you guys can all come in the five of you.
And as you walk into the dome, you move into just pure darkness
and then you hear two claps and lights come on, or rather the
sun comes on because the Iron Dome, which outside is like this,
you know, metal that you can't get see anything through inside.
It's a one-way mirror in a way where you could see the sun,
you could see the sky.
It is this like translucent thing.
You see in front of you now,
'cause it's this 10 mile circumference,
you see this massive field of bombers, tanks,
all these military grade vehicles.
You see thousands of robots and little frog men
tweaking and tinkering each of these machines,
making them, fixing up one thing,
making them work on another thing,
giving them the Wank Off stamp,
which I can draw for you later,
and then sending them off into the sky,
wherever they go or the trucks are being sent out.
It's this like massive field of all this stuff happening.
You also see far into the distance,
like a few miles ahead of you,
'cause it's flat and you could see
this like dense pink sparkly fog.
And then these like spires
of like some sort of strange factory.
You can only see the silhouette of it.
Then barreling down like five miles ahead of you,
like where this thing is, you hear the like,
and it's this uncoiling steel walkway
that's like a carpet of some kind and then it like goes and like
flaps right in front of you onto my onto your foot and you go.
and you're gonna take. You got all your HP back from before
right? Yeah, we're good also at at at the it's so startling to
me when he yells the ouch that I turn to the side and just hit
him right in the in the my nose. Yeah. So in that case,
he'll take instead. I'm gonna stab him. He's getting stabbed but like in the same place
that he got stabbed earlier. I just reopening the wound over and over again. So he takes
16 damage from all of that. And out flops Wankoff who is about 5 foot 1 and is a pudgy
Neo from the Matrix, the same face you saw earlier,
and he dusts himself off, and he stands up,
and he goes, "Hey."
- Hey.
- You guys the winners?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- Awesome.
- My name's Wally Wankoff.
It's super nice to meet you guys.
Sorry, I thought I had something prepared for this.
Hold on.
And he goes into his pocket and he's pulling out like lint
and like a bunch of other crap.
And then he takes out like a crumpled up post-it.
He says, just says, hello.
I guess I didn't finish writing.
So yeah, welcome to my factory.
Pretty cool.
All these bombers all around
'cause I'm a defense contractor too.
It's a pretty neat place, I think.
Yeah, so I'm looking for an heir.
Hoping it could be one of you guys, right?
That's pretty cool.
There's air all around us.
Oh, yeah, to be your son.
Wow.
Yeah, I never my mom always said that if I just, you know,
drank a bit more milk, maybe I would, you know, sprout up.
But uh, okay.
Yeah.
So we're just gonna what we're going to do is we're going to
hop on this walkway here.
This metal walkway.
It's gonna whip us back to the factory and I'll explain what we're gonna do today. It's gonna be a lot of fun
You guys are gonna see a lot of cool stuff
Okay, all right, come on come on now look I just stop you right there I love oh what's up my own father
Does he need to become deceased if I am to become your heir? Oh, uh,
That's a really good question. I
Don't think so cuz like just say the word. Oh, oh
Okay. Yeah. No, I'll try to make that if that needs to happen like we can figure something out. I think I smelled my father's penis
So any earlier yeah, how old are you I
Don't I maybe I don't know the other this guy. Well, I'll awake. Oh, hey, I'm like 37
Oh, I'm 10 years older than you. Haha
*laughter*
I don't know how he owned you there!
He kinda got me pretty bad.
I'll be your big brother!
Yeah, no, whatever works man.
Look, uh, okay.
So, I'm gonna, alright, I guess, alright.
I should probably level with you guys.
Um...
I...
I don't really know how any of this shit in here works.
Um...
So...
20 years ago or so,
So my uncle, it was Wally Wankoff, he was very eccentric and fun and all these things.
He died and he gave me the factory and he said all I needed to do was just change my
name and then I'd have it.
So at the time, I was working at Best Buy and I was like, "Skill, whatever, who cares?"
And I was like, "I'll save enough money, maybe go to college full-time, like a two-year school
and then go to a four-year."
I didn't really have a plan, but it wasn't a big deal.
So I was like, oh my god, like so much money from my uncle like yeah, um, anyway, the factory doesn't let me leave
uh
Can we go to best buy after this?
Yeah, if you want to go like do you still have an employee discount? Yeah, I don't have no I
I haven't worked there in like 23. I haven't seen this anything. I haven't seen people in 23 years
Um, i'm a people my uncle
Us. Yeah
Okay. Well, this is exciting for me. I get four inches. Yeah
- Yeah. (laughing)
- Is that gonna keep happening?
- No!
- I get four more inches.
- Okay, all right, it's confusing.
- I'm gonna need to keep it running totally here.
(laughing)
- Is the other kid with us too?
- Yeah, Chucky's there too.
- What's his deal?
- He's just smiling pleasantly
and listening very intently.
He's very excited. - I'm gonna turn to him
and get right in his face and go, "Explain yourself!"
(laughing)
Oh, uh, hi, my name's, uh, Chucky Fuckit.
I'm, uh...
Bonjour.
No!
[laughter]
I don't- I don't understand what he's laughing at, but I think- I wanna, like, be in on it, so I'm starting to go like...
SHUT UP, YOU DON'T GET IT!
[laughter]
Yeah, I fall over.
I've tumbled backwards.
Yeah, I'm just a chucky fuck it.
[Laughter]
Yeah, I just got very lucky one day and I got one of the brown stickers.
I've always wanted to meet you, Mr. Wankoff.
I'm sorry that you don't know how the factory works.
That sounds really tough.
It's fine.
The factory kind of runs itself.
They're doing their thing. They're those frogs. They're doing their thing. Uh, it's pretty chill. Um
But I got it. So my uncle did say I can have an air
So it looks like I was able to you know, get you guys inside
Which is really exciting for me. Hey, I got some air
Okay, so yeah, that's gonna be your thing the whole
trip
So what I need you guys to do
I'm gonna show you around the factory. We're gonna you know, you'll have a nice time. I'll get you guys some free chocolate
But uh, I need you guys to help me just
Clear out some shit. I
Haven't really been running. So okay. I was doing I was like kind of
almost a professional at
Halo 2 for a few years. It was pretty close, but I was mostly doing that
so I haven't really seen the factory in some time and I
Just need to make sure that whoever I pass it to is gonna know how to handle it. So
We'll just go to a couple of the rooms there.
You can see it, get excited by it, you know, maybe help me understand it a little bit better.
And then you know, whoever is the best at that, I guess, you know, I'll make you the air.
Does that sound good?
Hey, I got some more air.
It's really gonna be the whole time.
It was silent.
Does that sound good?
Or I could I look I I
I silently just turned green.
I'm right above them.
[laughter]
[clears throat]
Okay, alright everyone, let's just get on my, uh, let's get on the walkway.
It'll just whip us back. I don't control that, but that's what it does.
Whip us!
No, well, not like, no, I don't like that.
Uh, so yeah, you guys can get on the, uh, the metal, um, walkway.
Uh, it's zooming you back.
Uh, Chucky fuckit falls off and, uh, breaks his head open and, uh, he's dead.
And I get to the factory.
Chuckie fuck is dead.
He goes, Oh, I guess that's one down.
And you guys are at the factory.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're at the factory door.
You see it's just like big.
You get through this like dense pink fog and you see the factory and it it's it's it's like
It has this big, massive, golden door and embalmed on it is that Wankoff's face.
He's got the same sort of Marty Feldman-style, Igor-looking guy.
It looks a little bit more like an older person than him.
Looks like an older version of him.
He goes up and he starts waddling up to the door and he's like, "You guys like this outfit?"
last movie I saw was the Matrix so that was pretty sweet I thought you guys
would like it you guys like it positively luxurious okay well you're
not wearing a dress I'm not wearing a dress no okay so I'm gonna have to
figure out what that is logistically in this game.
This is huge.
Getting out of hand.
Yeah, you guys are at the door for the factory.
Again, big golden has an embalmed figure of a wank off on it or a wank off looking type
of guy.
And he says, OK, so to get in here, it's got a one second and he goes to the door and he
it's a little keyboard pops out and he starts playing it and it's sort of a syncopated bleeding
of trumpets and he turns you guys like that's a ska, ska pretty cool right and he keeps
playing it and eventually the door clicks and you hear you see the face of the Wankoff
Sort of whip out and give him a big wet kiss on the cheek and go.
Wahoo, wahoo, wahoo, wahoo.
And the door starts to creak open.
And but then the face sort of looks to the four of you right Chuckie's dead and the door slams shut and then Wankoff goes.
Okay, and he opens the piano again.
he plays the same ska tune.
So I had a ska phase.
It's awesome.
It's pretty cool.
I think and I know about ska.
Yeah,
hell is that?
All right.
Your nose is now 60 70 inches about 8 inches.
Okay.
So what we're going to do is I'm going to be honest here.
We've been playing it pretty fast and loose, but I think there
There is something to be said about what are we going to do about your 70 inch nose.
I'm not the dungeon master.
That's your job.
I'm supposed to have fun and get the biggest nose award at the end of this like it's Mario
Party.
What we're going to do is that is going to have its own attack at this point.
I think it does 1d12.
I think it's a strength attack, strength based attack when it's this length.
I think also everyone is going to have advantage on grappling you
because you have a big nose there.
Trying to discourage me from doing this.
No, no, no, not at all.
It's not going to work, but I would know I would never discourage you ever, ever, ever.
At some point, too, is it's going to be top heavy.
He's going to use his head is going to be against the ground.
If you can.
For I just think by now.
What? Oh, yeah, it's definitely.
It's been I'm two feet tall.
Yeah, yeah.
A fucking five and a half foot nose, dude.
Yeah, which is a normal height for a nose.
Yeah, I agree.
Guy. And so you're.
Yeah. So he plays the tune again.
The same thing happens.
The door goes, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Gives him a kiss, starts to open and looks at the four of you
and the door closes.
He's like, OK,
hmm, one more time.
And he plays the same thing.
and the thing does not go, does not give him a big wet kiss and go wahoo wahoo wahoo.
Instead the embalmed figure starts to pop itself out of the door and looks to all of you
and attacks. We're gonna roll for initiative. What the fuck? Oh my god, I hate this game.
What? I forgot you had to fight. It's always so uncomfortable because it's like they really
hate playing D&D. That's all I do with them. Oh my god I hate it. I brought
somebody here who does D&D. I'm no fan. He doesn't like either. Nobody likes D&D. I also do the dishes man.
I don't. Fun though. I have nightmares. I also suck the sludge out of a gutter.
I don't know what to tell you, man.
Yeah, because I have to.
I paid for the honor. I don't like it.
[Laughter]
Okay, cool.
Cam, you are going to go first.
You lucky duck.
So yeah, there's this big guy in front of you.
It's like a weird
embalmed figure that popped out.
So he's sort of two-dimensional and made of some kind
of gold or copper.
Some sort of metal.
And it is right now approaching you guys
is
crutch right up to it. I'll swing myself over there and I will I'll swing myself around
and and and and or no, you know, I'll hit him with my crutch. Okay, cool. Yeah. Do your
crutch attack? Alright. Oh, it's a crit. Holy **** Okay. You gotta crit right away. Okay,
roll for damage. Alright. Oh my god. Okay. Damn. Alright. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Yeah. So,
what do you how do you attack him? How do you do a critical attack with your crutches?
I like pirouette on one crutch and I'm holding out the other one.
I smack it.
I assume it's pretty tall probably so I smack it in the shin.
Yeah yeah and it goes like
Yeah yeah and you can yeah you can it my arm bends the wrong way too when I do it and I
go
Yeah you go there
And you see Wally, by the way, who is just like cowering away.
He's like, I swear it's never done this to me whenever I come in here.
I promise this was not.
Oh God, like he's just like totally afraid of this.
He seems completely confused by what's going on.
It is now the door things turn.
So after doing that to you, it's going to try to kick you with its like leg.
It's like weird, like, like copper leg.
So let's see how it does it that.
It does not do well.
swings and misses. I go flying anyway. Yeah, of course you do. And then it's going to like
sort of like a a a a womp in Mario. Try to like go flat and and you're all gonna roll
Constitution saving throws. Oh no. As it goes to flop on the ground. Eleven. Okay. Alright.
and
this check. As this thing whomps on the ground, you're all gonna take from the shockwave,
you're gonna take like not too much damage, probably. You're gonna take 5 damage, so it's
not too much. But you're all also stunned for the round. So the stunned condition means,
well, unfortunately for you guys, means you can't really do much. You're not really able
to
falteringly I'm pissed off that I'm stunned oh we can talk falteringly yeah
that's that's the technical rules yeah hmm I'm pissed off that I'm stunned I'm
just staying there I'm just like it's just fucking shit this I I want to move
my arms so bad and hit this guy then do it or are you faltering I'm faltering
right now. I can tell. So you guys can't take actions or reactions. So I mean, you're you
could just we could just like loop right around. Go back to the top of the round. Unless there's
things you want to do on your turn that are like free actions or something like that.
Can I can I position myself in a way that if he tries to to swamp on me again, he'll
just immediately run into my nose. You can't move. You can't move. Okay. Well, can I think
that I might do that next time? Yeah, you can think about it. Okay, I sit there and
think about it. You're thinking about it. So we go back to the top of the round and
the flop is just going to go again and this time he's going to try to kick you cam and
now he's going to have advantage against that on. Oh, so let's see how he does there. Okay.
Yeah, he hits you. Oh, which makes sense and he does. He only does six damage to you as
He kicks you in the gut.
And then he's going to try to kick.
He's going to try to kick all of our again or this time which
he's going to have advantage on that against you which by the
way, that's me.
I don't think I said my name.
Oh, yeah, just realize that yeah, I'm Waylon all of our
all right.
We'll have to add that in the beginning.
Okay, cool.
All right, you definitely get hit and you're going to take.
Seven damage from that. So you're you're you're doing okay though.
and now we're back to who is next. We got over here who got the
the eight was you Pinocchio. So you're up. Okay. I'm going to
try to use because I am I am a warlock. That's true. So
Your patron is Japano.
Pinocchio, the famous character, is going to use his witch bolt.
[laughter]
So...
Yeah, do it.
I'm gonna cast my witch bolt.
[laughter]
[deep breath]
20.
Oh shit, yeah, that hits.
Nice.
Roll for damage. Good god!
Cast that at a second level, okay.
So you just did 19 damage to this kid.
Good God, you guys are really fucking chunking away at him.
It's a Pinocchio.
All he's done is is be used for his nose to this point.
You take kind of Palpatine esque force lightning out of his hands
and nose and into a door.
I got the bombs and bombs figure that popped out of a door magic.
I'm like, yeah, I'm so I'm so happy because I finally I'm like,
Oh my God, I knew magic was real all along.
Yeah, I mean so with which bolt that just remain that can just remain and you can just like continually do damage every turn without having to roll another attack roll cool.
Waylon.
Au revoir, you're up so he just he's got hit me. I'm pissed. I'm going to throw a dagger at him.
Fuck yeah.
Go for it.
And uh...
Fuck yeah, that's a 20, that hits.
Oh, nice.
Okay, for uh...
Oh, all your rolls except for that one constitution one.
Everyone's doing good.
Two.
Nice.
Yeah, you just like get a dagger like, you know, just like stuck in its forehead.
Oh, yeah.
He's like, "Aaah!
Uuugh!"
Then I want to use a bonus action.
Hell yeah.
To uh, I want to cast something called Unsettling Words.
So I'm gonna like look him dead in the eyes and I'm just gonna say like your mother has a crush on you.
*laughter*
What do you think?
I don't actually, I don't know what it does.
So, unsettling words means I think on the next, and I'll double check this, because on the next
uh, a check he does, ability check he does, he takes like a B, where you would do like
bardic inspiration, it's like bardic desperation, so he would just roll like a D6 and subtract
it.
Oh, okay.
But I'm gonna-
So he'll be thinking about what I said?
Oh, uh, first he's-
He's gonna be stuck in his craw for quite a while, I think.
Let me make, let me double, triple check that, but I'm almost positive that's what that is.
Uh, where are you beautiful?
Unsettling words.
Yes, yeah.
Oh, you can see roll the bargain.
Spirits 91 D6 and creature must subtract the number rolled from
the next saving throw.
It makes before the start of your next turn.
Okay, so he'll take the four.
Yeah, so he'll take the four and he'll have to subtract that
from any saving throw.
It has to make before the start of your next turn.
So yeah, and he's a when you say that he's like, oh, like
he's just like very upset and is upset by the idea that he
has a mom because he's a some kind of like door figure.
and then also upset that this new blessing would also want to fuck him.
And now you're up John Candy.
I'm sitting here still pissed off that he stunned me.
Just like, "Ugh, this is bullshit!"
That's all I do.
Oh no, you're not stunned anymore.
No, I know.
I'm just so pissed off.
I don't even know, I'm not stunned anymore.
I'm like moving around.
I'm not acknowledging that I have to be involved in the fight at all.
Amazing.
Okay, we're back to top of the order and you're up, Bibby.
Alright, I'm going after the door with my crutches again.
I also realized I forgot last turn, I can make an unarmed attack as a bonus action when
I
dent into this thing. Uh, uh, dent into my leg as well. Yeah, of course. Everything that you do
also hurts you. Um, and he's not looking that good. I am going to spend a, a, a key point
because I have key. Bibby has a reservoir of key. He does use flurry of blows to make two
or wait, that is, that's another bonus action. Is that, am I able to do that? So you can't
really do it again because it's accused your bonus action. Okay, then I don't do that. Okay,
it makes sense. Um, uh, when you use your tag, actually, yeah, it's a bonus action so you can't
really do two. All right. Yeah, no, I won't do it then. Okay, cool. So now we're next, we're back
to the door. So the door is getting pretty pissed at this point. Um, and it's going to open its
mouth. Um, and you're going to hear dang, dang, dang, dang, dang, dang, dang, dang, dang, and
And everyone roll wisdom saving throw.
I got a 313.
I'm not good.
I got a three.
Yeah, it's not good.
I'm so unwise.
Now you guys are not mad and wise.
What's going on?
Cam? Oh, there's yours.
Sorry, I didn't see it.
Okay.
All right, uh, baby.
Okay, didn't do too bad.
Vivi and John Candy, you guys are going to take three damage Pinocchio and are of why you taking six?
He's taking the full damage from this attack.
And then he's going to also try to try to
headbutt you, John Candy, as you're like wandering around.
He like thinks of you as like someone obnoxious gnat.
And what's your AC, John?
That is 14.
All right, it's going to hit you, buddy.
I hate to say it. Yeah.
It does nine damage to you as he headbutts into your your luxurious tummy.
the
So I don't have to recast my laser bolt.
Yeah, your laser bolt.
My witch bolt.
Which is what you call it.
So I'm gonna hit again.
You can just roll for damage again.
Yeah.
Okay.
Wait, no, that's unarmed strike.
Hee hee.
13.
Good god.
Okay, yeah, you just like shock it again.
Oh, that's not damage.
Oh, you know what, I should have probably had you.
That was an attack roll.
Okay, there it is.
16 then.
You're welcome.
You happy now?
Yeah, I'm gonna I'm gonna let it slide.
I should have had you roll to see if you can still concentrate on the spell, but I didn't
catch it.
So I'm gonna let it slide.
He takes another 16 damage.
He is basically looking like he's not around anymore.
You're up wayland.
Au revoir.
I'm also using my nose like iron sights.
Yeah, okay.
Right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's like, yeah, making sure you can aim appropriately.
Yeah, the bolt that's coming out of your nose is just like a little like trickling little
spark.
Very, very tiny, but he's keeping it like located on it.
Yeah.
Uh, Waylon.
I got um, what do I got?
I have a rapier that I keep on me for like always like in the courtroom in case of course
like a duel.
Yes.
Uh, so I'm going to pull that out and I'm going to say, think about the mom thing again.
And I'm going to say, 11.
11 is not going to cut it.
So he's a, he's a shaking his head.
is
I point to the next person in the initiative and say "He's all yours!"
And it is all John Candies.
John.
Um, um, now that I got hit, I'm like "What the- Oh my god, what the fuck, dude!"
And I just whip- I pull my belt off of my- my pants like I'm Hootie Tang.
That's where I start- I start swinging it around.
and
this door.
I'm just hitting it.
I don't know.
Yeah.
You just like whap this like embalmed man.
I have, I have, um, it's a Chicago Bears belt buckle.
Yes.
Very big, very big Chicago Bears logo.
I fucking swing it at the door, hit it on the handle.
handle just fucking I guess it's like it's like a I don't know like a door
handle and I just break the door handle up yeah it's like really curious about
what was gonna happen did the big like yeah as a door handle it fucking falls
off he's dead this door is dead kill I break the door it just falls apart and
and the door is now open to this massive factory.
- Dude, say here's Johnny, say it.
Say here's John Candy, say it right now.
- Boo?
(laughing)
- Who are you talking about?
- You see Wally Wankoff who was cowering
and he's like, "Okay, all right."
See, this is exactly why I wanted strong children.
And you--
- I'm older than you, dude.
- Yeah, what?
So that was really, it was meant for kids
just because I get an air.
That's fine.
You know, it's OK.
It's better to have an adult in here to help out.
What?
I was just confused because like usually weird.
No, I'm not.
You're the I know you just beat a door with a belt.
I guess that's my factory, I guess.
So, you know, you're being weird.
Let's just be chill.
Come on. Let's let's come in.
Come in.
This place is already incredible.
I can't wait to see what other excitements are in store for us today.
This is the best day of my life!
Okay, yeah, uh...
Hey, Toothless.
Oh, wait, hold on. Wait till I say it.
Loser says what?
Is he trying to say "blender"?
And you step through
their defeated door into Wally Wankoff's incredible vacuum.
'Cause I've got a golden ticket
It's ours, Charles!
I've got a golden sun up in the sky
Slippers, Charles!
I never thought I'd see the day
When I would face the world and say
Good morning!
Look at the sun!
I never thought that I would be
Slapping the lap of luxury