[Music]
Last time on Wally Wankoff and the Candy Bombs and Toilets Factory.
The gang beat the shit out of some turdevils in the run-down toilet/indoor plumbing pipe section room of the factory.
After beating them up, Pinocchio completed his eldritch puberty to become Redwood Fox,
A tree man similar to the Kirby tree boss that's in every Kirby game.
That's how I pictured him.
Um...
Except it's, you know, sort of like Red, um...
Sort of like Red Fox.
Afterwards, Lady Dibby, the benevolent poop lady, led them to the loose bit of pipe that, when they break through it,
leads them ever closer to the control room so that they can fix the factory.
Um, where it leads them specifically is the bombs room,
Where Wankoff excitedly shows them the one part of the factory that does exceedingly well and has at least, you know, some of his attention.
Wankoff also shows them an experimental weapon meant to bypass Geneva Convention laws around gas attacks,
which I don't really get to explain, um, because Bibby shoots his tooth at the bomb with his slingshot by accident,
and it goes off, dispelling this, uh, pink sparkly mist, and the gang ends up in the Candy Dream Zone.
where they are in their most special, wonderful fantasy realm.
Until they're not, because if they don't awaken, they will slowly die
in the bliss that they've created for themselves.
One by one, each of our heroes awaken to the reality that they are in a dream,
at which point the dream turns on them and becomes a nightmare.
Bibby is the first to realize this, and helps the others escape
until they see Wankoff's dream world, one that is filled with the pathos
of a guy who should have just worked in computers, but was swept up
by the allure of a rich uncle.
When they awaken, they brush themselves off and head off to the control room at last.
Unfortunately, there's a company all hands with the robots going on between them and the control room.
And they all seem to agree that they want to kill nephew Wankoff.
Something is happening in this factory and the gang will finally know the truth in this part.
And they will not care very much about it. And that's okay.
I'm used to it. It's kind of how I write these at this point
Like you noticed the pink sparkle that was coming out of the bomb similar to the pink sparkle in front of the factory in the beginning
And I was trying to create some parallels there and I had some ideas about how to thread that and I abandoned it because it's not
Worth it a lot of things you realize as a DM are just not worth
You're up first
I yield my turn.
[Laughter]
An incredible man.
Okay.
Alright, so what do I have to run down a hallway or some crap?
So yeah, there's like bots in the way
that you can run past and try to brush past.
Basically,
think of it like this.
You have 60 feet of movement.
The door is probably like
120, 100-ish feet away.
The bots
are kind of
you know, scattered throughout that hallway.
So they will try to stop you if you run past them.
But we can play that out with just basically they're taking
opportunity attacks as long as you keep moving though.
You should be able to outpace the ones that are on the lower
level that are going to be coming up to get you.
What is the door say that I'm supposed to be going into control
room?
Okay, I read that as Tootsie Roll room.
But you are 100 feet away, so that makes sense.
Yeah.
I read that as Tootsie Roll Room, and I'm so mad
that these robots are in the way of the Tootsie Roll Room
Yeah.
that I go into a rage.
That's good.
OK.
You go into a rage, so then we got that table for you to roll on.
Because you have Wild Magic Rage.
I got a 2.
Oh, I can teleport up to 30 feet.
Perfect.
That's probably the best one to get in this case.
Yes.
And let's see, is that as a...
Where is that table?
Oh, I'm on the wrong character.
Is the teleporting like in Jumper and you can bring someone with you if you touch them?
Oh shit, I didn't mean to roll again, I just needed to pull the table up.
I don't think it's the Jumper teleport.
Fuck.
There's specific teleports for that, but I want to see if it's...
They do have the Jumper teleport.
Yes, it is.
If I rolled a little higher, they added it into the game.
Yeah, it's a big deal.
Um, jumper fever was sweeping the nation.
No choice.
When they were developing 5e, you know, at Wizards of the Coast,
they were, they just had that on repeat.
It was the only DVD they had.
Yeah, it's just you.
I want to make sure.
And it says you could teleport.
You can use this as a bonus action.
So, I mean, you can do your full movement and teleport.
Alright, so I'm gonna do that. I'm gonna I read Tootsie Roll room. I just start fucking
Screeching I'm just like I see that I just go like
and then just like
kind of like try to like
You know football like what's a linebacker linebacker my way through?
Mm-hmm
Fucking it's me not knowing what?
like
go
now. Oh, well, technically, I guess you used your rage as a bonus action.
What do you mean by that? So you can't teleport right now.
Oh, so I okay. Whatever you move 60 feet right now and you have teleport later.
Oh, I moved 60 feet. Oh, wait, shit. No, because you teleport and then after that,
you can use it. Got it. Okay, you're fine. You move 90 feet. You move 90 feet. Yeah.
use your full movement, use your full movement and your teleport.
You move 90 feet down that hallway.
So you just like fucking just blast it through them.
And now it is the robots turn.
So the other two guys that missed are going to try to square up in front of you all.
Um, and you're going to shoot, uh, what looks like some sort of like what would be,
uh, a, uh, sort of like repair or like, uh, uh, you know, uh, the tool laser,
but they're reapplying it to hurt you.
So they're going to shoot it at you,
Red Redwood Fox, because you are a big tree.
And they see that as like that seems like the biggest threat.
Am I going to catch you on fire?
No, unless you want to.
No, I don't. No, I don't want to. OK.
Your AC is pretty low, so it's going to end you.
Yeah. Yeah. That hits to you.
that does three damage
and the other one's gonna shoot at you
it hits you. Oh I still can't add or subtract damage
I'll fix that for you. Thank you. And it does
another three damage. Damn, they're rolling pretty low. Lucky for you
but yeah, so you take six damage from that. The other robots are moving closer now
so you're up
though, uh, based on my roles here, uh, Bibby. All right. So the, how far away is the door?
You said a hundred feet. Oh yeah. And how, how many of those feet are like,
will provoke attacks of opportunity? Like how, how far do I need to get?
Uh, if you have to, for sure there's there, like I'd say the 60 feet full is like how you're going
to get past them. If you go 30, you'll go past one. If you go like 45, you'll go past the other.
But like once you're past that 45 mark, you're pretty much past that right now.
Because I can, I want to, I'm going to use a key point to use step of the wind. Okay. But there's a,
there's a, like a smart thing I could do here or a fun thing I could do here.
Because the step of the wind, I can either take disengage, which I don't provoke attacks
of opportunity. That's the smart one. Or dash will double my movement and my jump distance doubles.
And I'm thinking maybe I can try to jump over all the robots and that might be really fun.
I'll of course allow that if you want to try.
Okay, I'm going to try to jump over all the robots with my step of the wind.
How much? Outline the increases here.
Let's see, so, well, so if I take dash I can move 80 feet this turn.
What the fuck?
Because my speed's 40.
God damn it, what the fuck?
Why is Bibi's speed 40?
Because I didn't-
He has no bones slowing him down.
He has no bones or blood or anything really.
I should have-
A jump is my strength score, I think, which is 14, but it's doubled, so that's 28 foot jump.
long jump, which I think also counts as part of my movement. So I don't think I can like
go 108 feet. Oh my God. But it'd be cool if I could. I, I, I, Oh God. All right. I'll let
you try. Um, yeah, so I'm going to run and my, the way my jump is going to work is that
I take off sprinting and I trip and I bounce into the air and I fly 28 feet past the robots.
Okay, first I want to make sure, so jump distance, is that really just your straight strength?
Yes, so when you make a long jump, as long as you move at least 10 feet first.
That's nuts. Okay, cool.
Cool D&D.
Yeah, you could just jump 14 feet. You're amazing. You're a hero.
28, no, I can jump 28 feet.
Well for you it's 28 feet.
Yeah.
So I guess they're gonna try to attack you while you're in the air.
Um, so they're gonna roll attack rolls on you while you're jumping.
Uh, because they're both gonna try to shoot at you, the ones over there.
Okay, I can deflect missiles with my reaction.
All right, I mean, how, how...
How many missiles can you deflect?
You have one reaction though, right?
I think I can just deflect one.
Okay, so we'll see how that goes.
All right, let's do this.
Okay, so you're flying through the air, this becrutched child.
I'm spinning really fast.
I like to do it when I bounce in the air and I'm like, yeah, I'm like whirling.
Yeah, it's the Matrix.
He's got the pipe and he's spinning around over all the agents.
Yeah, exactly.
And reloaded.
Yeah.
Okay, that's actually very funny to imagine.
The band-aids are flying off of me because I'm spinning so fast.
Okay, and they're going to try to attack you.
And let's see how that goes.
Um, accidentally, that's too much.
Oh, it's not too much.
One of them misses.
Okay.
The other one's going to try to hit you.
That's on the bridge right now.
It misses also.
You didn't even have to deflect.
Let's go.
And so then now what do you want to do?
Now you've landed from this crazy jump.
just
said you're going to 100 even. I got it now. Okay. Now, Waylon Au Revoir. Do you have any
of the same movement craziness that these two have?
No, I didn't know you could do- I would have given it to myself if I knew you could do
that. I should learn how this game works. The- So I'm gonna say, I'm gonna say, I'm gonna
like look around and I'm gonna say "letter of the law" and I'm gonna touch my nose and
say spirit of the law and disappear I'm gonna cast invisibility. Fuck yeah. Yes you cast
invisibility and it works you're invisible you have another 30 feet of
movement. Yeah just at my own speed I'm gonna sort of do like a keep on trucking
down just like taking my time walking right around those guys. Yeah yeah yeah I
I would say they're they they I guess can try to attack you
Just because they saw where you were before that but I don't know how successful using condoms. Yeah, they have disadvantage though, obviously
So, yep, one of them got a crit one so I guess his gun jams and he cries and the other one
Got a
What is your AC is 12, okay
I
Want to make sure I'm doing this right
Invisibility in is it technically disadvantage or
Or oh
It's yeah, it's not really I guess it's kind of DMS discretion
They don't have like heat site. Do they know they don't they're just worker bots
Yeah, no, no, so he has no reason for you to know that
Yeah, okay this one does is able to like get you but you're you're only gonna get get let's see how much you can get hit for
You take we you take six damage
And you sort of just stop in the middle of your sort of jaunt here, but you made it
I would say probably like 25 ish feet.
Like this was towards the end of it.
This is the second guy.
And then just roll a constitution saving throw.
You got it.
And one thing can I request the guy who's gun jammed?
Can I put my like Bugs Bunny style, put my finger in the barrel?
You did that. That's what you did.
Constitution saving three, you said.
Mm hmm.
So 15. OK, you're fine.
That's just to make sure you maintain the concentration
on being invisible which you can so you're still invisible um so he hits me and i'm gonna like
bleed a little and just look down and go like oh dear and yeah yeah okay awesome we are up to
uh wankoff's turn wankoff is uh not very fast or very strong he's just gonna try to run and he will
probably get shot.
Yeah, he got shot there.
He didn't get shot there.
And he's going to take some damage.
OK, all right.
So Wankoff just gets like shot in the gut by one of these like bots.
They go, Oh God, oh, somebody, somebody's got to help me.
He looks already looks blood.
That's kind of like how weak he is.
It's an escort mission, folks. I'm sorry.
is an escort mission to everyone but me is already at the fucking door pretty much.
Mm-hmm.
Mr. Tree Man, it's your turn.
Great.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Um, can I?
I have Misty Step.
Oh, why did you have Misty Step?
You're a tree.
That's all.
That rocks.
Yeah, I have Misty Step.
I can believe it.
Yeah.
Me too.
I don't know why I gave you that.
Okay, yeah.
So can I?
really have control over my branches, but can I bend over and kind of like catch the neck
of Wankoff's t-shirt and then do Misty Step?
So Misty Step you can't tech- well actually, here's the thing. Misty Step you technically
are- it's not, again, the jumper spell.
Yeah.
Sorry, I have a-
It's really hard for me to get my brain out of jumper mode.
It's not Misty Jump.
Oh, my bad.
that
is
the
this
a
the
one day and say thank you. You have a good berry. Like you have like a good berry you
can cast at will. So you just have like berries on your branches that he can eat and heal
HP. You know where my berries are? Yeah. Oh hell no. Oh god. He's like where where. Stay
away from those Wankoff. Where are the berries? Between my damn legs brother! You have. I
I just dip them they don't even hit your mouth. They hit your eyes. Oh, oh god. Yeah. I feel better though
That's right. Why are they a little boy two hours ago?
Yeah, cool
So we're back to the top of the order Pat
John candy Jonathan candy. Mm-hmm. Am I still in rage?
Yeah
Okay, there any enemies close to me like I'm like near the door now right like I'm like 10 feet away
Yeah, you're pretty close to the door. I would say like after this turn. There's gonna be you could see that there are
Enemies that are coming down from the rafters above they're gonna start jumping down as well
Jump down right now. They can't jump down now. I have to wait till their turn. It's a stupid part of this stupid game
Mm-hmm. I was just gonna say I'm like so mad. Well, how about this? I'm so mad
and
my
you're in rage you get a uh you get advantage on strength checks uh-huh um and you get additional
pluses on the strength checks as well um or you just get an advantage and then well i accidentally
rolled four times okay this will count the first two yeah we will count the first two um and lucky
you yeah one of them's a a dirty 20 yeah you bang it down and two of the robots fall they're going
going to take some fall damage. I almost wrote the role in the zoom chat. Okay, should have.
I know it would have been sick. They're gonna take some fall damage. All right, not ideal
for them. So now we want to do they're like, what happened? I thought I was up there. I
thought you were up there and then they see you and they go uh-oh I just go pig
okay I take my I take my whip out mm-hmm I just fucking slap one of them your
belt yeah for nine you miss with that nine so you squeal like a freaky pig and
then you whip the air they think it might be an intimidation tactic so so you
you don't look like a total jackass.
It is their turn now.
And they're gonna, you know, go like, "Kill, nephew!"
And they're gonna come at you and, like, you see that their hand that has, like, a laser
on it, and it turns into, like, a saw, and it's like, "Zzzzzzzz!"
And they're gonna try to come at you with the saw.
Damn.
Mm-hmm.
I have no more moves?
No, it's their turn, especially.
Oh!
Yeah, dude.
I, damn, I whiff that.
the
other one whiffs. The other two laser guys are gonna try to shoot at Wankoff
who's on the tree right now. Though he did gain some health back from the
good berries that you threw into his mouth or his eyes rather. So they're
gonna try to shoot at him because they're now like killed a nephew they
kind of identified who it is. And one of them misses and one of them does connect
I
Well now there's robots between me and the door.
Yes, that's correct.
Thanks Pat.
I guess I just have to try and go, I'm going to try and go to the door.
Can I take, how does the disengage work?
Can I take that without, can I just take that?
What kind of action is that?
So disengage is an action action, so it's like instead of moving or instead of attacking
you would disengage.
That said, Step of the Wind does allow you to disengage as a bonus action.
Yeah, but I don't want to spend any key points.
But I can take it just normally, right?
Yes, you can just normally take it.
Yeah, I'm going to use my attack to action to disengage and then I'm just going to go to the door and try to go through the door.
For sure, yeah. Yeah, that makes sense.
So, yeah, and you get to the door.
get to the door I mean in that case if the way that I'm picturing this which is
that the bots fell between you and John Candy and if they're within range of you
then you're able to disengage and then I limbo and then use a move yeah and then
use a movement action and it's very noodley when I guess nice and yeah and so
you get to the door you're there you can get to the control room if you want to
to
to be functioning normally. You could see CCTV cameras watching different areas of the factory.
You could see like that entrance way that we saw before with the tech corporate HQ kind
of thing. The chocolate room, the toilet room, the bombs room, see the front yard outside,
several angles from outside the dome, just watching those the dome go like opening up
and letting trucks out and different planes out and stuff. And you also see Wankoff nephew,
Wankoff nephew bedroom. He's got posters of the sci-fi original series of Dune starring James
McAvoy. The IT has an IT crowd box set, a Master Chief statue and a Cortana pin up on his wall.
I just roll over him and kill him immediately. Mercy kill.
He's a specific kind of older millennial and I don't think that's nice.
And yeah, and so that's what you see in the room.
Sure.
Yeah.
And you also have one screen that just shows blackness.
You don't know what that is.
Yeah, I'm watching it like TV.
Yeah.
Probably better than anything Bibi's ever seen.
Cool.
It is your turn, Waylon Au Revoir.
So I'm still way back and I'm invisible
Can that guy who shot me does he have like a sort of a sense of where I am?
The guy who shot you did yeah, he does but I'm not I'm not gonna give him like I'm not gonna say he has like regular
Advantage on regular hitting you you're so invisible
Well, I'm gonna try to appeal to him and I'm gonna like throw my voice
Who doesn't quite know where I'm coming from cool and I'm gonna say brother brother you're fighting the wrong you're fighting the symptom
not the disease. If you want to get the nephews, you need to kill my uncle.
If you kill my uncle, then I'm no longer a nephew and he can't keep-
because if you kill me he's just gonna keep making nephews. This is true, this is a
good point. Roll persuasion. Yeah. It's crazy. This is genius. Yeah, it's a good point
that uncles do just spawn nephews. Yeah. Yeah, they asexually reproduce.
So that's a dirty 20.
Good god.
I hate that about your character.
It's completely broken, I shouldn't have that.
Yeah, the robot is sort of like, thinking about it, says, "Perhaps recalibrate strategy.
Kill uncles.
Kill uncles."
And it turns to where Pat is.
It starts barreling down that way towards John Campion.
What?
But yeah, you can definitely like more easily sort of, uh, you can just like walk through
this at this point, I think.
Oh, yeah, I dust my hands off and I can.
Yeah, great.
Oh, not me.
Yeah.
So you're a lot closer now.
You're like walking alongside that robot invisible at this point, like, like you're both going
in the same direction.
Yeah, I'm just shooting the breeze.
Yeah.
So what are you like six?
Seven.
I'm seven.
And three quarters?
And one quarter.
Oh, that's pretty... I'm a robot.
What, are you like Paw Patrol?
Can't say I've seen it.
Oh, you haven't lived.
And yeah, it's Wankoff's turn. Wankoff is scurrying up the branch. That is you, Redwood Fox.
I'm giggling because it tickles me.
Please stop giggling.
like
that
mass group at the company town hall.
What is spider climb?
Spider climb allows you to walk on walls.
Okay.
I'm an 8 foot tree that can walk on walls.
Yeah.
I feel like I could kind of just scare them away by doing that.
Can I, alright, let me, I'm going to attack somebody.
Okay.
me. So there's a guy, there's, there's a guy in front of you, or rather, there's a guy behind you,
who's been a who's been shooting at Wankoff. And there's another guy who is sort of making his way
towards the the entrance. And then there's the two other guys over there already. So there's three
bots closer towards the control room. There's one bot that's behind you that's going after Wankoff.
And then there's the army that's kind of slowly filing up the stairs
Okay, um
I guess i'll attack one of the three that are between me in the control room
And I'll I will use uh eldritch blast
Hell, yeah
I'm, sorry
warlock staple
Um, look at their ac
That's not quite enough to hit them
the
a
that
and then you know the rest of the scene I already painted.
Mm-hmm.
Um...
Shit, what else can I do?
You can go to the door and just... you're 10 feet away.
Yeah, I guess I'll just go to the door.
Yeah, you'll have to...
I double birds flip them off and walk to the door.
Yeah, you could take a disengage action, just get away from them, walk to the door.
Canonically in this campaign, the disengage action is just flipping people off.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm done. Yeah. It's saying I'm done and flipping them off. And then they're like,
"Oh, all right. Shit. He's done. What am I going to do?" He said, "He's done." Yeah. You just flip
them off and walk to the door. It's now the robot's turn. The robot's group is now very much on that
platform. And so they are coming towards you guys towards the
control room. The other two, you know, john candy and and Bibi
are sort of in this doorway. They're going to come after I
guess like they can, they're gonna try to come after you guys
while you're in the doorway. Because if you haven't shut it
yet. Let's see how they do, those two guys. Let's just make this nice and easy. Yeah,
one of them misses you and one of them does hit you, John Candy, for 7 damage. Another
7 damage. If John Candy holds me out in front of him like a human shield, I can deflect the
this
hit mr. Wankoff he does four damage but Wankoff will eat good berries on his
turn he'll be okay you know I just given him the berries every fucking every turn
he's eating them off your leaves he's just trying to bet he is yeah and your
branches rather you don't need berries don't grow on I'll grow on the leaf
that's all I will and you're up baby okay I mean yeah I'm gonna jump into
John Candy's arms and just like like go like star shape like arms and legs
straight out to try and block any incoming perfect projectiles. Awesome
cool and so now you're up Waylon. Okay so I'm going to I'm like I think I've made
it like 50 feet so far so I'm still like I got a ways to go so I'm just walking
towards. Yeah, if you use your full movement, you can get there, but then you can't disengage
from the bots. So you could do that. You would just risk getting attacked by the two that
are up there. Well, I gotta get close. I'm gonna walk all the way and I'm just gonna
and I'm gonna like tug at my collar like, "Yeah, hope they don't..." Wait, does he still provoke?
Oh, wait, shit, you're invisible. Yeah, I forgot you're invisible. Yeah, you just walk past them.
I'm sorry. Oh, great. I should have thought about that. Thank you, Cam. Yeah, you just walk past
You're there, and now you're up, Redwood Fox.
Okay, um, there's still two in front of me? Or is there still three?
There's one behind you, trailing behind, shooting at Wankoff. There's two in front of you.
Okay. And then there's the crowd that's coming.
the
definitely let you try that yeah okay it's kind of crazy to think like you're
just going up like you're crazy it's crazy pants let me tell you that um okay
so yeah one willing creature you touch which in this case is you and you're
able to cross verticals. This is so funny. It's funny because he's huge. Yeah, yeah.
So you're just like walking up, Rakov has to hold on for dear life, berries are falling
into his mouth from the treetop, and you're using the rest of your movement, the other
30 feet of your movement to get there. You're not going to provoke any opportunity attacks
yet because you're not up on those guys, but they are going to have a harder time hitting
you when it's their turn. But you're closer now. Back to top of the order, Pat. You are
in the control room. You can do stuff in the control room if you're trying to unclog the
toilet or shut something down. I'm just swinging my fists everywhere. I'm
punching monitors and stuff. I'm pissed off that this is not the Tootsie Roll room.
I'm still in your hands while you're doing it.
Okay, yeah, you're just crushed beating the shit out of monitors.
And it's it's the control room is like going like it's starting to react.
Not well to that kind of that kind of action.
You see the robots are like moving faster and then slower.
They're spinning around.
It's it's you hear some noise from another part of the factory.
it sounds maybe like an explosion. You're not really solving anything though by doing that.
You're just sort of hitting shit. Is there like a big red button in this room?
Can I do an investigation check for a big red button?
You could certainly do one while you're waiting for Wankoff who probably knows where shit is.
You could try to see if you could shut things down.
I got an eight. Yeah.
There's a lot of buttons and they're all different colors.
And that's just a rub. I'm just pressing every red one. Okay. Yeah. You just, I mean, it's, it's,
it's indescribable. Let's put it that way. There are you, you look at the camera and you see the,
the chocolate room starts to have a whirlpool. You see the frogs going down this whirlpool.
they're just like, "AHHHHHHHHH!"
Like, like, you see, uh, uh, in the, uh, uh, the bombs room,
you see some of the robots are kissing the bombs somehow,
and one of them is blowing up in their face, and they're looking at the camera and blinking twice.
It is, it is, uh, like, no--
What a woman!
Yeah!
[laughter]
Nothing good is happening.
Uh, uh, and, uh, the robots that are approaching you guys from the back,
some of them are moving a bit faster now.
Uh, because you're okay. I hit every green button now.
Okay, we're gonna move to a different turn.
That's your action. The robots are up. The robot crowd is approaching you, Caleb.
Um, uh, you're far enough ahead that they can't quite reach you,
but a few of them can try to shoot at you. And so they will.
Um, I only have seven HP.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
I will say the spider climb is going to give you some advantage here
Because you are kind of perplexing them. It's not a part of their protocol. Hmm
Let's see, what is your AC again? Is it 10 10? Yeah, I gave you very low AC pretty low for a giant evil tree
Well, the idea is that you could very easily be hit but you should have more HP, but you don't
So I have 21 HP. Yeah. So yeah, you take two damage from one of the shots
From the back
The other one's gonna try to shoot at Wank off again. Can I eat my own berries?
No bit of a crass question, but yeah, right
And oh, he got a crit on Wank off
Wankoff is knocked out. He's just knocked out on your tree. He is falling to the ground. Oh my god
And uh, he started falling right at kind of the the apex of my spider climb
That sucks and the other two are gonna try to attack you now baby that you're sitting in front of and guarding the
the thing you could deflect them though right i can deflect one of them if it hits me okay one of
them you deflect sure hope two don't hit me because uh one misses and the other one you easily deflect
okay well i roll to see how much damage i i it uh i can i can deflect 1d 10 plus 7 damage
So that's 10. That's a 10. Yeah, they're not going to be able to do all right, probably not.
It ricochets off my head with a very metal. Yeah, it's your turn now, baby. Okay.
Let me see. I think I guess at this point, I kind of just have to keep guarding the door.
How far away is Wankoff on the ground for me? He's about like probably 40 ish feet.
Alright, and are there robots in range of me that are near him?
Can I just range, can I just do a sling?
Yeah!
Robots?
I'll just attack.
Do it!
Do it at the two that are attacking you, you can do it at.
Alright.
That hits.
Okay.
8 damage.
Oh, well they took damage from that fall, so one of them just like *pshh* just like
you just get it in the cranium and it just blows up.
Sick.
Nice.
Uh, good use.
Now you're up, Waylon, au revoir.
So I've, so these robots coming up behind me,
I think we're going faster than me.
So I just sort of like go limp
and just let the momentum carry me forward.
So I'm there, I've made it.
And I'm going to cast,
I'm gonna cast crown of madness on one of them.
Oh shit.
Let me just read what that is.
Okay, so you gotta succeed on a wisdom saving throw
or I can like, one of them goes insane
and start attacking the others.
- Oh yeah, and these robots do have the capacity
to go insane.
So it's gonna be very cool.
Let's see, it's a wisdom saving throw, was it 14, right?
- Yeah, yeah.
- All right, all right, I remembered that.
Okay, they're not the most wise 'cause they're robots.
Yeah, pretty bad.
Yeah, that one goes insane.
What does it do?
Alright so what does it see it yeah okay so it goes insane and it just sees
everyone becomes Waylon everyone around it just becomes Waylon and they're all
just shouting order in the court order in the court order in the court order in
the court order in the court and then all of them combine and meld into one Waylon
who's like standing before him and says kill me.
Jesus Christ, put me out of my little boy misery.
Oh my God. OK, OK, cool.
So, yeah, the charm target must use its action before moving in each of its turns
to make a melee attack against a creature other than itself
that you mentally choose.
So it is picking, yeah, any robot near it.
And that's what it will do on its turn.
So I will kill you little lawyer boy.
Um, and you're up now.
Oh, wake off is up.
He's got a roll of death saving throw.
That'd be cool if he died.
He failed.
That's one failure.
Oh, geez.
Okay.
Now you are, you are up now, uh, Caleb.
Um, okay.
I'm going to use mirror image.
you to make, uh, let me see, to make four duplicates of myself.
Yeah. So mirror image is very cool. Your people are not going to be able to tell, um, uh, uh,
what you basically they, if they, they, when they attack, they have to roll, um, uh, you have to roll
is
how you would know that's a trick. Damn. That'd be so cool though. Okay, then it does happen.
And then can I I'm gonna pick up Wank Off with my me me and then all of the all the
other me's I don't can I make them go crazy? So duplicate move with you and mimic your
reactions. Oh, okay. Well, that's fine too. Alright, so it's
really just about dodging it. Uh hit. Okay. So I'm just going
to try to just be line to the the control room then holding.
Okay. Cool. Yeah. Uh you're getting there. They're going to
try to attack you. Uh you must roll six or higher to change
your attacks. I'm rolling eight or higher because I think I
have. Yeah. You have two duplicates. You said you have
four. So, you have three. So, you must roll six or higher.
Okay, so roll roll troll d20 and roll d20 twice more and
16. Yeah, they just attack duplicates. And let's see what
their AC is, though, or rather what their attacks are. Because
they might not even break the duplicates AC.
the
this is
and he walks around and he's like, "Oh god, I haven't been here in a while."
And he looks around at all the buttons and he turns to you, John Kennedy, and says,
"You pressed all the red buttons yet?"
"Yeah, I pressed all of them!"
"Okay, all right. Good, first step is done."
"Fucking crap."
And he starts going to all the green buttons now.
And you hear *boom* as the boss shut down.
and when you hear *fart* as the shit unclogs and *fart* spills out into the hallway and you see it like
through the the door's window like it's just like coming through like a tsunami like *fart*
you see turd devils flying out from that you see frogs sliding out robots swirling around this
shit. It's not my fault I did not do that. Uh and then... Hey quick question did I make it out of
of the hallway? Yeah, you said you got pushed forward. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Uh,
the control room starts to like the window up on top where you were seeing the **** sort
of pouring in shuts and the control room starts to rumble and you feel it going down and you
you see Wankoff, he's like, "This is, uh, okay."
And you feel it going down, down, down, until it's a bottom of some kind.
And the door you were just looking at opens.
And you see a long, dark cavern.
Like not a basement, not anything, you know, built.
so far down that you're seeing like stone and rock and a long hallway and you hear somebody
say come out my nephew and bring your your lovely children friends and the one who's
not a child and the tree which one's that this is the first moment I haven't been running
for my life in a little bit and so I just scream in pain because I'm just always in so much pain.
Yeah and uh you see Wankoff and he's like "Uncle, Uncle Wally?" and he starts to wander down this
hallway um uh into this dark you see torches are kind of lighting up as he's walking down
Um, and as you guys follow him, you see a large atrium where in you see hanging up
the Wally Wankoff, the one who was, whose figure and form was embossed on the door in the first
episode. And, but you, and so he looks similar to Douglas Tolbraron, aka the Wally Wankoff you guys
no. Except he's, you know, like a normal-sized guy, not that there's anything wrong with being 5'1",
but it's not normal. And, uh, and his, but what's not normal about this one is that his limbs are
stretched out, connecting the four inner tubes that jut out at different points of the cavern,
reaching out to parts of the factory, you presume,
and his head attached to a body that is affixed to a urinal
that has a motherboard lining it. And his head is preserved in some sort of
crystal, it's crystal and candy tesseract. And there's several tubes that jut out
of his back and made of a host of stitched together
flesh. It appears to be pumping inside him literal shit.
Um, and he says to his nephew,
you've been a grave disappointment to me.
And he's like, I didn't know you were alive.
You're what happened to you?
Oh, God, you look horrible.
You look like shit.
I'm living forever.
What can you say?
Are you going to live forever?
Anti-Disestablishmentarianism.
What?
Do you want me to say that three times fast? What was that?
I said it. You say, you say, "What can you say?" I said, "Anti-Disestablishmentarianism."
You threw down a gauntlet and he picked it right up.
Yep.
You know what? I, you got me.
Yeah, you say it!
Yeah, you say it now.
I draw my rapier, you say it.
Anti-Disestablishmentarianism, was that it?
Not think you messed it up. Yeah, I think you messed up some at some point. Oh
God
You and he looks to you baby. He says oh
I recognize your face. Oh
I sent you to Illinois and turns your beautiful mother into poop
Yes, I had the money from the Dibby family for many years. They're a rich family from Cukichu Wales
That's right your Bibi Dibi
As T should plus your mom's made of shit, that's stupid anyway
Didn't you turn her to shit and you call it it's stupid now
That was your move dude, I was trying to figure out how eternal life worked obviously I was sort of right
She doesn't live on a shit. I guess that makes sense. I'm sorry for saying anything
And
You think it looks at his nephew. I
Wanted you to find me an heir
That is what I wanted you to do. Hey, I got there I
Remember this remember hearing this from the outside I see everything in this factory this factory is an extension of my body
*fart*
yes i heard that too i hear the frogs and their obsessive stupid singing
here the robots in their quarterly business reviews
i hear your farts
uh... it is bad
this lawyer child paul
it was bad
uh... job sorry guys
missus shit shooting into his body
it's not coming into my nose
anyway
You were supposed to give me an heir.
And you see Wankoff and he goes, "Well, these are heirs.
I can just adopt them or something."
And he says, "I wanted you to fuck somebody, you idiot.
They need to be blood-related.
Why do you think I brought you into this at all?
I need a host who's blood-related."
And he says, "How was I going to fuck somebody if I couldn't leave?
I don't know, get a whore.
You know, get a whore.
You could just get a whore.
You're rich.
I'm not a whore. I don't- it's really easy. Why didn't you just do that?
I- I didn't- no, I don't- I don't know. I didn't- oh my god. Anyway.
I'm sorry, all this talk of heirs and producing heirs and fucking- I'm only seven years old! What are you talking about?
*laughter*
*sniff*
Oh, you're seven.
teach you what I actually that's a that's a mission for your dad or something I
don't know well I think I had a dream I killed my dad we've all have we've all
had dreams you tree man uh-huh
yeah what you mean I could end your suffering for you then do it what you
put just standing there was shitting your back come closer and I and you do
yeah you come closer and a centrifuge opens up from the ground and you start
spinning inside of it and wank off his soul leaves his body and enters the
centrifuge and he says this is an interim step I will possess someone of
my blood I need I'm going to need more shit in my body though to stay alive and
he spins with you in the centrifuge until you know he's putting dookie in his body
the
And you have to fight your friends.
But I love my friends. This is bullshit.
These are the third through seventh people I've ever met.
Roll for initiative everyone.
Do we get to heal at all before?
Oh no.
Let me tell you what boys, I have 5 HP.
I think you're going to have a good time killing me.
Oh, I did get a nat 20 initiative.
Oh, I got an 18.
OK, and Waylon?
Oh, sorry, I got an 18 too.
What?
Whose dex is higher? Cam's, yours, right?
Mine's plus four.
Yeah, OK, yours is higher.
OK, so you're going to go before him.
Oh, boy.
And yeah, you, your pain has stopped, though.
though. You feel whole, having a soul inside of you, a soul you did not have before, Redwood Fox.
But it is controlling you against your will. As you are, your branches continue to grow and gnarl.
As your body starts to shift and as tubes fly into your back, start pumping shit inside of you.
but you don't feel the same kind of like dark twisted pain that you were feeling constantly
as a fucked up puppet boy. Your pain, he did keep true to his word, your pain did stop.
And it is your turn. Okay, can you have you have your move set, but you also have
additional moves. Okay, do I still have five HP?
You have 10 HP now. Whoa. Whoa. Mm hmm. Gonna be pretty tough boys.
Mm hmm. This is it might be unfair. Your AC is also now
sixteen. Okay. So, it's no longer ten. Uh you have a
couple of abilities. One you have is ship beam. So, you can
shoot a line of **** out of your hollow. Um that does 1D12
damage and also poisons enemies. You also have from your branches now hanging much like
a Christmas tree candy cane men. That you can basically use an action to summon and
have them fight your friends. I'm a Christmas tree. You just happen to have candy on you.
It's part of the Wank off thing. Okay. Can my my branches be can I kind of want to have
kind of a third evolution here. Yeah. I can my branches grow kind of so far out and and
kind of wrap around each other to the point where I'm kind of like a big tumbleweed with
like a cartoon face on it. I love it. Let's do it. Yeah, you do that and then with as
a tumbleweed. Yeah, do you want to have like a Katamari Dimash style attack? It kind of
works with something else. I would probably actually have less attacks as a tumbleweed
in
Canine the Lingvall Foxworthy
I
Reckon I'm about to become a tumbleweed. That's what I say right before I become the tumbleweed
Yeah, well, I reckon I became a tumbleweed. Mm-hmm
You might be a tumbleweed you might be a tumbleweed if you're me
So you're also gonna have a tumbleweed attack
You might be a tumbleweed if
Roll him over to death
That's I was gonna say you have an attack where they have to roll a deck saving throw
against a DC of 13 or they take some damage. If you go in between two men
about to have a duel... What? What? If you roll in between two men about to have a duel...
You might be a tumbleweed. Oh, okay. Alright. Right. So that would be good if you were the tumbleweed.
If your character was a tumbleweed you might be able to say that. Yeah, but I had that in the back
pocket I was waiting all day you yeah that was at the very bottom of the back pocket
you were digging through like like inches of worms
but you're not a tumbleweed
I was so relieved when he turned into a tumbleweed
all right cool you're up though man
me yeah I'm gonna use my tumbleweed ability
hell yeah
John Candy
you can use it on all of them at once
okay I'm gonna use it on all of them
everyone roll a dexterity saving throw
this is
we'd blow over Waylon and it says split right? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Cool. You take six. Like
a low poly 3D animation. Yeah. Yeah. You take six damage from that Waylon. Woo! Probably
not looking too hot. Yeah I'm at three hit point. That's right. Uh and you can attack
one more time too. Oh shit. Yeah dude. I can I just run it back and just kinda kinda. Yes
to
going back and forth every turn.
Okay, I got a 20.
Alright, so John Candy, you take 6 damage.
Okay.
What are you at? 4.
Hell yeah.
You are now up
Bibby Dibby.
Full name.
Yeah, so I get, I do double damage
because I know my full name.
I'm gonna use my
Am I melee range I get a melee range and I swing my crushes at my former friend. I'm crying
I'm sobbing my first friend in the world
You rolled over us. I don't know what I'm doing. Yeah, he has no
Chocolate monster. Well, I don't know that he doesn't know what he's doing. So I hate him. This is dramatic irony at its finest
Yeah, go for him. All right, that's a 20 shit. My dad only 16, right?
Yeah, 11 damage. Yeah, he's dead.
[Laughter]
You might be a tumbleweed if...
[Groans]
[Sighs]
Describe how you kill him.
Can I say, okay, I swing my crutch and I connect with one of the branches of the tumbleweed.
Since they used to be branches, they're brittle and hard.
And one of them breaks away and it starts this like, this domino effect
if they all start cracking and breaking and flying off, and at the center, it's Pinocchio.
It's little baby Pinocchio without a nose at all.
No nose?
And he's lying on the ground.
Hey everybody!
Well if he's lying his nose is gonna grow.
Oh no I'm dead!
I would say you could try to bring Pinocchio back to life.
I can't, I don't have anything I can do that with.
I mean, I can use, I guess I can do a, I mean, I don't have any healing items or anything.
Can I cast Dissonant Whispers to try to bring him back to life?
You know what?
We're playing insanely fast and loose.
Let's do it.
Oh, great.
Yeah, that was a joke, but sure.
No, no, I want to do it.
I think you have to, you have to.
What is Dissonant Whispers?
So, well, okay, so Dissonant Whispers does damage.
Yeah, explain it to me.
Yes.
It's related to me, yes.
So, and it does 3d6 damage, and so what I'll do is resonant whispers, which does 3d6 healing.
Yeah.
But I'm at -1 HP.
Does that matter?
No.
Okay.
I would say, before you do that, let's, let's, okay, here's what we can do.
Because it is, I'm playing too fast and too loose now.
Let's make it a little bit tighter.
You can try to do this and it whispers.
And if you get higher than 10, you'll roll a straight d20, if you get higher than 10
it heals.
Lower than 10 it doesn't heal.
And as we all know, looking at Pinocchio's original HP, which we're going to base it
off of instead of Redwood Fox and Red Fox would Fox were here 17 yeah if he gets
negative the that HP he he's permanently dead so that can be the risk factor here
okay if you want to do that let's do I mean this seems like I could just kill
him right now in one move by accident so but I'm already doesn't exist yeah with
the
he doesn't have a mouth. I forgot. Well, can I put it up his puppet hole?
Oh, he's a wooden puppet.
If you dare, can I make a hole in him?
You want to, so you want to, maybe he's like, look, there's a puppet hole.
That's weird. So you want to create a hole. I'm going to, okay.
If I can get some candy, I'm going to put it in the hole where his nose used to
be.
if there's candy nearby, is there candy that I can...
There is chocolate, there is chocolate nearby, it is mixed with shit.
I mean I'm going for it, I can't tell the difference, I think it's the chocolate.
Yeah.
And we'll, we'll roll, we'll do the same thing, let's roll d20.
Okay.
Higher than 10 it's chocolate, lower than 10 it's shit.
But it's only gonna do so much damage.
And shit heals Caleb double because he loves eating it so much.
No, no, no.
Okay, Pinocchio, you're breathed back with whatever life you had.
Friends.
What?
Where did this guy come from?
I was here a couple hours ago. You don't remember me?
No.
it baby gives Pinocchio a big hug oh oh and breaks my arms and you see a wink
off and he says all right I did not expect to kill my uncle or for him to
say such mean things to me I'm done with this factory I think I could probably
of
Yeah!
Let's go!
I don't know why I was gonna give it to a kid.
Like the more I think about it, the crazier it seems.
Yeah!
Fuck yeah!
Woo!
Um, what, we're in the control room, right?
You're in like some sort of fucked up cryptic basement.
Yeah, alright, so I'm like running around the room.
Yeah.
And I'm like, let's fucking go!
Let's go!
and i don't realize there's like a cliff
i'm doing i'd do a cartwheel perfect off the cliff
but in the in the bottom of the pit
that i do the cartwheel it's not a it's not even a tall pit
it's like six feet deep but
spike trap from tony hawks first
uh... so instead
i guess the vengeful spirit of his nephew
possessed and what's it for all
uh...
the guy i mean do you either of you wanna
I need the three of you.
Do you guys want it?
I don't, I really don't want it.
I trust you guys.
You guys got me here this far.
- Yeah, I'll take it.
I'd love it.
- Yeah, I think you would be the most obvious.
- Do you mean it?
- Yeah, I mean, yeah.
- Oh, woo-hoo, woo-hoo!
And I'll run around the room,
and I'm gonna do a cartwheel as well.
(laughing)
Spike pit.
- Okay, that was a--
He lands on top of me
I'm like at the bottom of the spike about to say like
And like all brain function stops, I'm completely dead
Okay, so there's a wooden boy
Bibby do you want to like go to your mom? I I don't really want anyone to take over this factory anymore
It seems to be a common
Thing happening here. Maybe the robot could just brought it. This is a
Nightmare now with my with my mission being over the only reason I existed in the first place. I
Finally turned into a real boy
Just my hands pop from wood to flesh my eyes
Does it hurt?
Oh my god, I'm a real boy. I have fingers. I have thoughts.
Yay!
And I run around the room.
And I do a cartwheel. My first one ever.
And I also land on the spike.
Okay.
The same spike. We're kind of stacked. You know that children's toy that's all the
circles stacked on top of each other?
The murder toy.
Yeah, exactly. We're kind of doing that. Yeah.
Yeah. Well, I'm smarter than them. And also I physically can't do a cartwheel because
both my arms and legs are broken now. So I am, I walk over, we came down in like an
elevator type thing, right? Yeah.
The control room was like an elevator. Oh yeah.
So I walk over, I'm ready to leave. I'm ready to go. I finally discovered I have a family.
I have a last name. I'm so happy. I press the elevator button, the doors open and a train
speeds out
it's a train from the dream world
you see there you see the the control panel there was an up button and a down button i accidentally
press the train button. Oh fuck. Oh god, okay. We're gonna flash forward in the future a
little bit. Everyone who went to the factory is dead. Wally Wankoff changed his name back
to Douglas Tolberone. And he's now working at Best Buy again. He's still talking about
going into computers, happily helping people. His father comes in one day and embraces him.
They have a tearful reunion. And he gets a great deal on a Vizio 65-inch television,
Believe it or not, ultra wide 4K.
That's pretty good.
We go to the factory now.
The robots are just going to run it.
That CEO bot just keeps running it, working with everyone.
The frogs have found a way to escape the factory's clutches.
Where they've gone, nobody knows.
But they have somehow gotten out of this kind of a weird indentured servitude/slavery that
the frogs were under.
And I guess you're all dead.
So there's a lot of different things I was gonna say.
And it's all gone.
Maybe all the things that you were gonna say could apply to like our identical twins that
are still alive. Yeah, sure. You just play like sad piano music as you just say what you would have said.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah. In black and white. Yeah. Bibby, you reunite with your mother,
Lady Dibby, and you inherit the wealth of the Dibby family and you move back to Wales.
I'm still hit by a train.
Waylon Au Revoir, you find a frog injured on the ground and he says,
"If only some attorney were around to take our case and make a ton of money off this obvious grounds for class action lawsuit."
And you take the case and you make more money than any lawyer ever, making you very special indeed.
[laughter]
Wow.
John Candy, you get to run the factory.
Um, I was gonna let you decide what that meant.
So what does that mean? What word of that meant?
If you didn't cannon, cannon die in the game.
Six months in, that whole operation, shut down.
Class act, like, like, like, file for bankruptcy almost immediately after.
I'm like in charge because I got so bored running it that I wanted to do something else.
I love that idea.
This is helpful for the modern world setting of the Gunsidney lore.
Pinocchio, I wrote, "Do what you want, man.
You asked a tree."
But you didn't end up being a tree.
So if Pinocchio didn't cartwheel off and fall into a spike pit, what would he have done?
If I had never, well I wasn't planning on becoming Pinocchio until Cam turned me into
Pinocchio.
My plan was to go just become a normal tree and lose all sentience and just kind of sit
there for the rest of my days.
And a young techie.
I only experience violence in my short life.
And I'd like to think that the Pinocchio that I created on this D&D campaign is a pretty
solid abortion metaphor.
You know, I'm gonna go.
Yeah.
That's right.
That's how I'm gonna go.
I gave you the warlock pack of the chain and you killed your familiar the second he appeared.
it was Jiminy Cricket. And then you never summoned it back.
I don't know how to do that crap. I'm just a simple man.
Yeah it was rocked. And yeah I guess that was, I mean unless there
was any other endings you guys would have wanted for your characters.
The rest of it, I mean. Okay fine, Pinocchio is a, Pinocchio is a celebrity,
he's at the 40/40 club fingering women with his nose.
I don't want you to say anything!
He's doing the "lie to me" joke about Pinocchio, but in real life.
We see another black and white vignette, and it's of little Chucky Fuckit who died immediately.
Yeah, it turns out he would have grown up to be the next Hitler, so it's really...
Wow!
He died when he did it!
Did you see "Check my Notes"?
How did you know that?
Yeah.
Alright.
Yeah, I feel good about this.
We're done.
Great, yeah.
Bye everybody.
Bye.
I can also, you know, um, yeah.
Great yeah. Bye everybody. Bye. I can uh, uh, also you know um, yeah.
[Music]